Chapter 1149: Qi Master versus Assassin (3)

After being blasted away by the high-level skill, Cold Seasons returned to his feet with a Quick Recover. However, when he looked across, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea showed no sign of seizing this opportunity to pursue him. He stood steadily while the airflow created by the qi attack's explosion stirred up the dust on the ground. He looked righteous and had the imposing manner of a grandmaster.

What happened? Did his playstyle also change after switching classes?

The doubt only lingered in Zhou Guangyi's mind for a second.

The Qi Master's design was radiant and righteous, but just then, Fang Rui had sneaked an attack when his view was blocked by the Qi bullet. How sneaky and deceitful was that? Playing dirty wasn't just a tactic, it involved many aspects, such as the technique and mentality. Fang Rui was someone whose dirty playing was tainted right to his bone's core.

Why didn't he seize the opportunity to launch his attacks after the high-level skill? Due to the system's judgment, it was very difficult to continue a combo after a high-level skill, but there was still a lot of opportunities for him to seize. However, Fang Rui seemed as if he were unwilling to take advantage over someone in a tough spot. Boundless Sea stood silently like a grandmaster, waiting for Cold Seasons to get up and make his move.

What was strange about it?

Zhou Guangyi had to wonder why!

When a quarter of his health was blasted from Boundless Sea's high-level skill, he thought that Fang Rui might not be scheming. Perhaps he only wanted to use reverse psychology to make Zhou Guangyi lose focus. Now that Boundless Sea had a calm and composed manner, Zhou Guangyi couldn't help but hesitate.

Boundless Sea didn't advance, but neither did Cold Seasons. There were 14 units of distance between the two. It was as if someone pressed pause.

Zhou Guangyi couldn't see through Fang Rui's intentions, so he thought about letting Fang Rui make the first move. Zhou Guangyi planned and decided to counter every change by remaining unchanged.

However, Fang Rui was patient like him, and Boundless Sea also did not move. The two confronted each other in such manner for one minute.

"Why aren't you moving!" Fang Rui spoke in the chat.

"Why aren't you moving?" Zhou Guangyi asked in return.

"I'm waiting for you to move," Fang Rui replied.

"..." Zhou Guangyi was speechless. Why was he trash talking with Fang Rui?

Then I'll move!

His Tyranny roots made his blood boil, and Zhou Guangyi decided not to overthink this. Let's charge straight on and make this an intense fight!

Cold Seasons initiated with a Shining Cut. The cool air cut through 9 units of distance out of the 14 units between them. Boundless Sea retreated the moment Cold Seasons was about to attack. Fang Rui was planning to flee!

There was a plot after all!

This thought flashed in Zhou Guangyi's mind. However, his determination was set. No matter what trap Fang Rui had prepared, he decided to fight head-on. After a Shining Cut, Cold Seasons split into two. He used Shadow Clone Technique, the Ninja's lowest level skill. The actual Cold Seasons teleported behind Boundless Sea. The dagger was about to quietly slit his throat with Cut-Throat.

However, this attack was within Fang Rui's expectations. Boundless Sea suddenly ducked down and dodged the attack. The character twisted his body around and used a Back Throw while he was ducked down half way.

Cold Seasons immediately jumped back and barely dodged the grab. His body then flickered and returned to Boundless Sea's side as he stabbed with his blade.

A normal movement wouldn't have such a quick speed. Zhou Guangyi was currently using the Assassin skill: Teleporting Stab. It was as if the three unit distance didn't exist as he flashed back to the target's side.

It seemed like Boundless Sea was still recovering from his Back Throw. However, when Cold Seasons' dagger stabbed forward, Boundless Sea's stretched out his hands from the grab immediately rubbed together.

Countercurrent!

This was the Qi Master's lowest-level skill, as well as one of the airborne skill available for every class. Although it required the Qi Master to launch it by pressing his hands together, it had its strength in staying hidden. No one had expected Fang Rui to cancel his Back Throw much earlier on, and borrowed the position where both his hands were stretched out to launch a Countercurrent. This was hard to defend from.

However, Zhou Guangyi was different! He knew Fang Rui very well. Although he resolved to attack proactively, he still reserved some power for defence.

Teleporting Stab versus Countercurrent!

In terms of the skill level, Teleporting Stab was definitely higher leveled and was faster. If this skill continued to be used, it would definitely pierce Boundless Sea first. However, this attack was unable to interrupt Boundless Sea's Countercurrent. Since the launching method of Countercurrent was unique and the air was already rising up, it couldn't be defused by such an attack.

This skill could be exchanged for damage, but he would be the one who was suspended into the air by Countercurrent.

Should he trade?

Zhou Guangyi immediately made the decision. He cut down ruthlessly without backing down. The Countercurrent then sent Cold Seasons flying in midair, as well as the beads of blood that trailed from his dagger.

Since Zhou Guangyi was willing to make the exchange, it was obvious that he had methods to counter it. Air Jump, the Assassin's unique passive skill, allowed them to face airborne effects with ease. After being suspended in midair, Cold Seasons leapt back again. He jumped even higher and activated the Assassin's new Level 75 skill in midair: Rend!

There was no need to question the damage of a Level 75 skill. There were five new Level 75 skills for the Assassin: Rend, Kill, Dodge, Flash, Exterminate.

The five skills could be used separately, but when the five were used in the order of 'Rend, Kill, Dodge, Flash, Exterminate' as a combo, it would deal additional damage. After all, the Assassin only pursued instant and efficient bursts.

Zhou Guangyi was already starting with the Rend, which showed that he believed he had the opportunity to finish using the 'Rend, Kill, Dodge, Flash, Exterminate' combo. No one would have thought that when he started with the Rend, Boundless Sea, who was previously on the ground, was tumbling away.

Zhou Guangyi suddenly had no place to use his skill and experienced the loneliness of life…

This guy!

Zhou Guangyi thought that when Fang Rui was exchanging Countercurrent with his Teleporting Stab, he had skills which would follow up after the airborne Zhou Guangyi. He used Rend, the high-level skill, so he could have a showdown with Fang Rui.

Who would have thought that, after what seemed like a wrong judgement, Fang Rui resolutely made Boundless Sea flee after the exchange.

He could only use the high-level skill by slashing at the empty air. Although Cold Seasons didn't receive any attacks after being suspended in midair, Zhou Guangyi wasn't happy at all. The moment Cold Seasons reached the ground, he followed it up with another Shining Cut. This low level skill had a short cooldown, so it was often used to launch a quick sneak attack by Assassins.

Boundless Sea suddenly turned around and fired a Qi Bullet. Zhou Guangji was hasty in his pursuit, so his lack of defence caused him to be hit straight in the face. Although the damage wasn't high, and it wouldn't stop his Shining Cut, it was satisfying to watch the Qi Bullet hit and explode in someone's face. Zhou Guangyi felt annoyed as he watched it explode on his screen, and immediately realized something: not good!

This was just like the Qi Bullet from before. Fang Rui was aiming to restrict his vision.

Zhou Guangyi mashed his keyboard, but he was too late. Boundless Sea almost came at the same pace as the Qi Bullet. When the Qi Bullet exploded, Boundless Sea's following attack had arrived. He jabbed with his finger for Pulse Break.

Break Intelligence!

No way? Zhou Guangyi yelled in his head when he saw the Pulse Break take effect. After that, the Qi exploded and Cold Seasons was blasted away. Boundless Sea was calm and stood straight like a grandmaster.

To be blasted away twice with the same method. Zhou Guangyi didn't know whether it was because Fang Rui was too shameless, or that he himself was too stupid.

Cold Seasons stood up again and Boundless Sea remained unmoving.

However, Zhou Guangyi couldn't stand idly any more. After losing some of his health twice, almost half of his health was gone. Cold Seasons immediately rushed up and launched his attack.

"Sigh, why are you so hasty this time," Fang Rui called in the chat while Boundless Sea turned and fled crazily.

An idea flashed in Zhou Guangyi's mind.

Fang Rui… was using the cooldown method!

The cooldown method was when a player attacked the opponent solely with high-level skills. However, the cooldown for the high-level skills was rather lengthy, so it couldn't be used continuously. As a result, when this tactic was used, the player would need to change positions or use any other methods to stall for time after the high-level skills was used. When the cooldown had finished for the high-level skills, they would be used again, and this process would repeat.

Fang Rui was currently using the high-level skills Pulse Break and Qi Blast. The damage inflicted on the Assassin, a class with low defense and low health, was very great. Judging from the two characters' situations so far, Cold Seasons could only receive five more of the two skills maximum before he would die.

The cooldown method was commonly seen in the online arena, especially classes with some handy high-level skills. Some players actually relied on high-level skills to attack the opponent before running and hiding for the rest of the time. This was a method of fighting that was extremely looked down upon.

However, the cooldown method was rarely seen in professional matches. One of the reasons was that the method wasn't accepted by many. The other reason was that a pro player wouldn't be helpless and struggle when dealing with high-level skills like normal players would.

However, Fang Rui still managed to use the cooldown method.

As the master of playing dirty, he had no qualms about using such an unaccepted and disdained method.

When he was using this method, it was obvious that he wouldn't purely rely on the damage of the high-level skills. He only managed to succeed twice by launching the sneak attack at the most surprising time when the Qi Bullet blocked the opponent's view. He wasn't greedy at all despite succeeding with the Pulse Break. After the Qi Blast exploded, he didn't think about how he could connect it as a combo.

This guy…

All in all, Zhou Guangyi was pretty familiar with Fang Rui, so he could predict his intentions. Since Fang Rui had changed his class, he couldn't immediately play with ease and habit like he did with the Thief for many years. Fang Rui used the cooldown method because repeating a few skills was a lot easier than having to deal with full sets of skills and combos for a different class. In addition, his unexpected dirty playing was able to make Zhou Guangyi suffer twice.

I won't let it happen a third time!

Zhou Guangyi felt that he had already paid enough for this painful lesson, so he wouldn't be tricked again.

After that, Fang Rui made the effort to avoid fighting, while Zhou Guangyi was also helping him calculate the skill's cooldown. He estimated when the two skills would finish its cooldown, then he would immediately be on guard with caution.

After he had failed twice, Fang Rui was helpless. "You've seen through me."

"It's a cheap trick," Zhou Guangyi said.

"Hey, where did half of your health go?" Fang Rui asked.

"Here's my attack!" Cold Seasons sprinted ahead.

"You only have half of your health left, you think I can't handle that?" Fang Rui yelled and faced him.

This time, it was a real showdown.

In the end, Fang Rui won.

Chapter 1150: As Blossoms Fade and Fly Across the Sky

Fang Rui understood Zhou Guangyi better than Zhou Guangyi did of him. After succeeding twice, Fang Rui doubted that his trick would work a third time. He had decided that he would face Zhou Guangyi in a direct confrontation to determine victory.

But did that mean that he would put his dirtiness aside? Of course not! In this situation, Fang Rui suddenly facing Zhou Guangyi righteously in a direct confrontation was a dirty move.

With those two previous moves, the cooldown method had deeply taken root in Zhou Guangyi's mind. When Fang Rui started playing like a great hero, Zhou Guangyi couldn't help but feel apprehensive. He was unable to fully commit to a direct fight without any second thoughts. Under these circumstances, Cold Season's health had started with about half of Boundless Sea's health. In the end, Zhou Guangyi lost. It was an inevitable outcome. Even so, when Fang Rui clashed directly with Zhou Guangyi, it hadn't been an easy victory. When Cold Seasons died, Boundless Sea had less than half of his health left. As for Zhou Guangyi, it was only when Cold Seasons fell did he realize that in that last half, Fang Rui hadn't set up any traps. However, not setting up any traps became the greatest trap. He had once again fallen for Fang Rui's trickery.

Yes...

Whether it was in an official match or a private conversation, Zhou Guangyi hadn't lost to Fang Rui just once or twice. It was just like this match every single time: he would always be constantly reminding himself to be careful and be wary of Fang Rui's dirtiness, but in the end, he would always fall into Fang Rui's trap and lose miserably.

It wasn't that he wasn't trying. His opponent was just too crafty!

Zhou Guangyi noticed that after every loss to this guy, he would always have the same thought. He didn't know whether to laugh or cry.

When Zhou Guangyi came down from the stage, he was quite calm. He simply had too much experience losing to Fang Rui, so another loss was something he could cope with. If a rookie had been in his place and lost in this way, who knew how hard the rookie would take the loss.

When Zhou Guangyi returned to his team's player area, his teammates consoled him. He could only smile and express that he was fine. Now, it was time for Team Hundred Blossom's second player to come out: their team captain Yu Feng.

Yu Feng had joined the league in Season 6. In terms of career length, he was a junior to Zhou Guangyi, but his current fame far surpassed Zhou Guangyi's. He was also Team Hundred Blossom's captain and core player. Zhou Guangyi hesitated for a moment, but in the end, he still warned Yu Feng: "Keep a steady heart!"

"I understand." Yu Feng chuckled and nodded his head. He recognized Fang Rui's fame as the master of playing dirty. As a player who joined in Season 6, he had only joined a year later than Fang Rui and Zhou Guangyi, so his competitive experience didn't lose out to those two.

When Yu Feng walked onto the stage, the crowd became even more fervent. This match would be a confrontation between two All-Stars.

The map was the same as before: Life-Seeking Path. Yu Feng was currently using what was once the former Number One Berserker, Blossoming Chaos. After receiving Blossoming Chaos, Yu Feng took back the title of Number One Berserker for his character. In recent times, Team Blue Rain had wanted to sell Brilliant Edge, the Berserker formerly used by Yu Feng, in the winter. After Yu Feng transferred, no one succeeded him, so Brilliant Edge had just been sitting there idly for half a season. However, the winter season transfer window happened to coincide with Glory's massive update, resulting in a drastic drop for the value of Level 70 characters. But because of this drop in value, quite a few teams fought for it. In the end, Brilliant Edge had been sold to Team Heavenly Swords.

However, Team Heavenly Sword was a unique team. Their team roster was untouchable and their characters couldn't be moved either. After Team Heavenly Swords took away Brilliant Edge, they immediately dismantled Brilliant Edge and gave the equipment to Loulan Slash. A rising Berserker character was thrown away just like that. Quite a few people cried at the loss. Sometimes, compared to players, the fate of these characters made people feel even more sorrowful and helpless than the players.

The Berserker that Yu Feng had used for many years had been thrown in the trash, but Yu Feng wasn't affected much by it. He had fully adapted to his new Berserker.

Blossoming Chaos soon reached the center of the map. To no one's surprise, Boundless Sea wasn't there

So you want to try the same trick?

Yu Feng thought to himself, but he didn't hesitate. Blossoming Chaos advanced forward and entered the complicated intertwining maze.

Not long afterwards, Boundless Sea appeared, shooting out a Qi Bullet to provoke and probe Blossoming Chaos.

Yu Feng had Blossoming Chaos avoid it. He didn't panic. He simply used his normal running speed to dodge and move towards Boundless Sea.

The tangled and complex map was filled with twists and turns, but Blossoming Chaos's thought process was very clear. He calmly followed behind Boundless Sea. Whenever a fork appeared, he never seemed to hesitate.

It was evident that Yu Feng wasn't a stranger to this map. He even had a decent tactical understanding of it.

The two characters played hide and seek just like this. On the stadium's large screen, a bird's eye view of the map was displayed, showing the two characters moving around.

"He's trying to trap him." Ye Xiu lifted his head and said, when he saw how the two were moving.

"This punk seems to be quite familiar with this map." Wei Chen said.

"Mm, his understanding and decisions are on point. Fang Rui has been forced into a corner." Ye Xiu said.

"He's trapped."

On the map, Boundless Sea's movements stopped. At this moment, he had reached the end of the map and could not continue moving forward. As for the other exits, Yu Feng had sealed them. Yu Feng had finally forced Fang Ruin into a dead end.

"Who would have thought that someone like you would have researched this map." Fang Rui spoke in the chat as his character turned around. Blossoming Chaos already had his greatsword out, dragging behind him.

Greatswords had the highest attack out of all swords, but greatswords were also the heaviest weapons, yet many Berserkers loved using them. Even though Blossoming Chaos had been remodeled when Yu Feng came, this greatsword had been preserved and had been upgraded to Level 75.

Burial Blossoms.

This was the greatsword's name. It didn't sound like a name befitting that of a greatsword, especially since this name gave quite an unsettling feeling towards Team Hundred Blossoms.

However, the community was brimming with youths. No one really thought too much about it. What's more, didn't the former owner, Sun Zheping, have to give up on this weapon because of what it forbade?

Burial Blossoms? Very good. Very cruel. When this weapon was created, the name automatically generated for it had once cast quite a gloomy shadow on quite a few people in Team Hundred Blossoms. However, the owner of the weapon took it up and then shattered this shadow into pieces. That year, just how tyrannical had Blossoming Chaos been, brandishing that greatsword Burial Blossoms?

Nowadays, the forgotten Burial Blossoms once again saw the light of day last season. In the second half of the season, it had been upgraded to Level 75. It was now helping Team Hundred Blossoms rise to glory again.

Burial Blossoms was lifted above Blossoming Chaos's head. Yu Feng clearly didn't plan on chatting with Fang Rui. He completely ignored Fang Rui's words. Yu Feng felt like his resistance towards trash talk was quite high. Don't forget, he had come from Team Blue Rain. The Alliance's most terrifying trash talker had been his teammate!

Collapsing Mountain!

It was the most common move used by Berserkers to initiate a fight. It was evident just how calm he was right now.

As for Fang Rui, he didn't appear to be panicked after being forced into a dead end by a Berserker. He observed the momentum of Collapsing Mountain and leaped backwards. Then, he pushed his palms and a Qi Bullet shot towards Blossoming Chaos's face.

Anyone who watched Fang Rui's fight with Zhou Guangyi would know that the purpose of this Qi Bullet wasn't to injure the opponent, but to block the opponent's line of sight. The theory was no different from the Knight's Shield Blind strategy. The Shield Blind strategy was more precise and more difficult to figure out the timing though.

This sort of trick wasn't going to work on Yu Feng though. Blossoming Chaos stepped to the side and the Qi Bullet flew past him. He pulled on his greatsword and with a Backwards Slash, the enormous sword frame hacked towards Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui immediately activated Qi Flowing Cloud. Boundless Sea's movement speed increased and he dodged the sword, utilizing this opportunity to move past Blossoming Chaos.

Blossoming Chaos immediately switched attacks. His other hand grasped towards the nearing Boundless Sea. It was the Berserker's Soul Devouring Crimson Grip.

This grab skill was quite tyrannical. The blood from the hand would form a domain. The hand didn't need to directly grab the body. As long as the target was within a certain rainge, the target would immediately be sucked in.

Sure enough, Fang Rui didn't dare let Boundless Sea keep moving forward. The greatsword Burial Blossoms swung to the side, forcing Boundless Sea to roll to the side. The greatsword Burial Blossoms chased after him. The Soul Devouring Crimson Grip left hand gripped back onto the greatsword hilt and struck out with a Wild Blood Strike.

This chain of skills was practically instinctive to Yu Feng. As for Fang Rui? Facing these fast-paced and precise mix-ups, his unfamiliarity with Qi Masters was forced out. For every variation, Fang Rui would always be slightly slow. After several blows, his rhythm lagged a beat behind. Finally, Blossoming Chaos's attack was unable to be dodged.

"A scene too appalling to look at!" Ye Xiu shut his eyes.

"He's still in the middle of changing classes. Facing a top-tier place is simply too difficult for him," Wei Chen remarked.

This Wild Blood Strike was a solid strike. And it just so happened that this attack triggered Burial Blossoms's 6% chance effect. Sword light transformed into innumerable flower petals that danced in the air. Boundless Sea should have originally been sent flying by the Wild Blood Strike, but he had unexpectedly been stopped and swept up along with these flower petals in the air.

It was a forced knock-up, which had a 6% chance of trigggering when Burial Blossoms hit a target: Blossoms Fade and Fly.

And when the enemy was in the air, any pro player would have numerous combos in mind to execute. Launching an enemy into the air was never a disadvantage for them. The only ones with a headache would be the ones knocked into the air.

Chapter 1151: Give Me A Buff

Gore Cross!

The flowery lights from Burial Blossoms had yet to fade away before Yu Feng made his move. The greatsword's range of movement wasn't great when Blossoming Chaos flicked his wrist, but it was enough to let out a horizontal and vertical slash. The airborne Boundless Sea was hit directly, the blood that flew out formed the perfect shape of a cross.

He swung out a Destruction Slash, which damaged the opponent as well as lowered his defense. The Qi Master was a class with cloth armour, so they already had low defense against physical damage. After it was lowered by Destruction Slash even further, the following chains of attacks caused his health to fall rapidly.

Was victory going to be decided so easily with just one attack?

Yu Feng was completely focused as he attacked. His opponent was an All-Star, so he couldn't leave any openings. Combos didn't work just by releasing skills in a certain order, it required him to adapt depending on the situation. . The terrain, distance, opponent's class, and opponent's reaction were all factors that would influence what skill to choose and the timing. Glory was able to continue for many years without losing popularity because of its complexity and infinite variations.

Yu Feng was currently making extremely precise judgements for every attack, and all of them were on point. The Berserker's flawless combo made Boundless Sea tumble and struggle in midair.

Yu Feng's Berserker wasn't as wild and bold as Sun Zheping's, but he was more precise and meticulous. Both of them had their own strengths, so debates on who was better was only because everyone saw them in their own lights.

The combo was able to cut down a majority of the half of the life he had remaining. What he had left was only a bit over 10%, so he was only a step away from entering red blood mode.

Bosses would release high level skills when they their health dropped to red blood, but this was only a signal of danger for players. Fortunately, Yu Feng's combo was at the point where it couldn't be broken.

With some health remaining, Fang Rui could still make some sort of counterattack, right?

The crowd in the stadium felt nervous for Fang Rui. If he was defeated by Yu Feng in such manner, then the advantage of winning with half of his health left against Zhou Guangyi would have gone to waste.

On the other hand, the spirits of the Team Hundred Blossom's players rose.

This was what it meant to be captain. This was the moment when the core raised their team's spirits.

"Go captain!" Although Yu Feng couldn't hear it, a few rookies still yelled out nonetheless. Even though the noise from the home crowd drowned them out, the rookies weren't discouraged. Yu Feng's performance was able to stir up everyone in Hundred Blossoms.

"Fang Rui isn't going to lose like this, right?" Ye Xiu said regretfully.

As one rose, another would fall.

While Hundred Blossoms' morale was boosted by Yu Feng, Happy's morale was shaken because they had lost the advantage gained at the start.

"It won't happen. It definitely won't happen.." Chen Guo shook her head. Even though she wasn't familiar with Fang Rui and barely knew much about him, she chose to firmly believe in him on the basis of her hope.

"The combo's been broken." Chen Guo spoke.

Ye Xiu smiled bitterly.

The combo indeed stopped, but that didn't mean that his attacks would rest. This was only the system's call, but judging from when the combos stopped, the distance between the characters, and that Yu Feng could still go up and make two or three attacks if he wanted to increase the number of combos, Ye Xiu knew that the combo had stopped because Yu Feng had wanted to. It was obvious that Yu Feng wasn't aiming for a higher combo count, but rather to win the match.

Yu Feng didn't continue his combo because he obviously believed that he had the chance to finish off Boundless Sea. As a qualified captain and ace, what Yu Feng thought about was no longer his personal victory, but how he could increase his team's chance of winning through his fight. This was why during the time he played, he needed to boost the whole team's morale to the maximum.

Blossoming Chaos lifted his sword with both his hands.

How was he planning to attack? Frankly speaking, even Ye Xiu couldn't tell. Boundless Sea was already falling down to the ground, so everyone was paying attention to how Fang Rui would respond. However, Ye Xiu was watching Blossoming Chaos instead because he knew Yu Feng wasn't finished with his attacks. Although raising his sword into the air would save some time if he used Crimson Storm, but using such a high level skill straight away wasn't guaranteed to connect.

Boundless Sea naturally used Quick Recover when he reached the ground, but when he made contact with the ground and rolled, he advanced forward instead of retreating, moving closer to Blossoming Chaos's location.

Everyone was stupefied…

He had finally broken out of the combo but wouldn't rolling towards Yu Feng be the same as crashing himself into the blade of his opponent?

However, just before he finished his roll, Boundless Sea lifted his hands and attacked.

Qi Bullet!

This was aimed straight at Blossoming Chaos's face.

"Oh..."

Everyone made a sound of understanding in sync. One could see how engraved Fang Rui's two performances against Zhou Guangyi last round was in people's minds. Now that they saw Boundless Sea send out a Qi Bullet by surprise, they immediately thought of…...

Pulse: Break Intelligence, Qigong Blast, right?

Everyone in the stadium became excited.

Too naive...

Yu Feng was very calm, but he couldn't help but to ridicule. After using the same trick twice on Zhou Guangyi, you still think it'll work on me? Fang Rui, you're underestimating me! Too bad for you, I've already predicted that you would do this because you don't have any other choice. With a Qi Master, you aren't familiar enough with the class to fight at such a high-level.

"Go back and practice!"

Yu Feng still managed to type up something at such a critical moment. People had to wonder if players who originated from Blue Rain all shared a certain trait.

Qi Bullet?

Blossoming Chaos was about to use his high-level skill, his body leaned forward so he could summon up power. By lowering himself, he completely dodged the Qi Bullet, and his sight wasn't blocked.

He clearly saw Boundless Sea's action.

He braced up his arms, this was…...Reinforced Iron Bones, the Strikers' low-level pre-advancement skill.

A good plan!

Yu Feng couldn't help but praise in his mind. It seemed that Fang Rui didn't expect for the same trick to work thrice, so he added another small trick this time. He already knew that he couldn't win, so Fang Rui only wanted to take away some of Blossoming Chaos's health. This was why right when the Qi Bullet was sent out to block Yu Feng's sight, he activated Reinforced Iron Bones.

Reinforced Iron Bones increased the user's defense and gave the user Super Armor.

Fang Rui knew that Boundless Sea didn't have much health left, so he charged forward boldly. If he fought Blossoming Chaos straight on, then he would be taken down. So this was why Reinforced Iron Bones became the core of his surprise attack. This skill allowed him to take a surprising amount of damage from his opponent, which naturally gave him the opportunity to deal a satisfying amount of damage..

Unfortunately, I've seen it. How could I give you this opportunity?

If he activated Reinforced Iron Bones, Crimson Storm by itself couldn't create an instant kill, but…

Blossoming Chaos let out a roar as he leaned forward. His eyes and the skin immediately turned blood red. The Berserk's cooldown was finished, so Yu Feng chose to activate it at this time. With this buff, instant killing Boundless Sea with Crimson Storm wouldn't be a problem.

Fang Rui obviously realized that his trick was seen through, but he had already reached the point of no return. Crimson Storm's attack range was pretty big, and since Boundless Sea was already this close, it was impossible for him escape from the attack. He could only charge ahead. However, facing an instant kill attack, would he still have the chance to deal any damage?

Not many people could understand the current situation. The crowd became excited and believed that Fang Rui was about to succeed again with a Pulse Break and Qigong Blast combo, which will send the opponent flying away!

Pulse Break? How much damage would it make?

Yu Feng thought to himself as the bloody Burial Blossoms struck down, filling the sky with a bloody aura. Boundless Sea, who was situated in it, started to lose health, but the height of the attack had yet to come.

The stadium became quiet,. Everyone could see that Boundless Sea was truly on the defensive now.

However, Boundless Sea continued to sprint ahead at nearly zero health.

Would he make it in time?

Everyone in the stadium felt nervous for Fang Rui. Even a pro player with the most accurate calculations couldn't predict whether Boundless Sea could damage Blossoming Chaos.

Within the boiling, bloody air, Boundless Sea's right hand managed to touch Blossoming Chaos.

He ran out of time!

Everyone sighed, Boundless Sea's health had fallen to zero.

However, at this moment, it was as if a strong blast of qi poured into Blossoming Chaos's vest as it rustled in the air.

Qigong Blast!

Boundless Sea's health hit zero, but the damage was dealt. Qigong Blast, he went straight for the Qigong Blast. Fang Rui didn't use Pulse Break to increase its damage.

Yu Feng's face turned uglier.

However, it was only damage from a high-level skill... even though it wasn't perfect, it was still acceptable.

Soon after that, Blossoming Chao's health slid down, but it was greater than he had expected.

One fifth!

The Qigong Blast actually took out a fifth of his health! It was even stronger than his Crimson Storm, a Berserk-buffed one too.

Wait... Berserk?

Yu Feng suddenly realized something.

At this moment, he saw that Fang Rui had replied to his message: "You too."

Go back and practice!

What Yu Feng meant was that Fang Rui's Qi Master wasn't up to his level.

However, Fang Rui said you too...

Yu Feng realised that he had still fallen for his trap.

Berserk buffed all of his offensive capabilities, but it also drastically weakened his defensive capabilities.

Fang Rui used Reinforced Iron Bones to trick him into using Berserk. He didn't use Pulse Break, because Berserk had given him enough of a boost to Qigong Blast.

This was why when Qigong Blast was used. Along with the weakening of Blossoming Chao's defence from being in Berserk mode, he was able to take away a fifth of his health.

Although Yu Feng won this match, he suffered a crushing defeat in the last moment. A skill he activated himself had helped his opponent.

"He's truly dirty..." Yu Feng sighed.

Chapter 1152: Rules

Fang Rui left the stage, and as he walked back to Happy's player area he waved and greeted the crowd. The last bit against Yu Feng was the most interesting part of Fang Rui's performance, but it was high-level in terms of technical content. Without the commentary, the live crowd had trouble understanding it, so they would need to go back to fully appreciate it.

But no matter what, to defeat one of the Hundred Blossom's players and then take down a fifth of the health of the captain and core player, Fang Rui had performed admirably. As the home crowd, of course they had to show their support with their applause.

In Happy's player area, Mo Fan silently stood up, and without saying anything to his teammates, he headed down toward the stage. Fang Rui was still interacting with the crowd, and all of their attention was on him, so not many noticed Mo Fan. It seemed that Fang Rui didn't notice him either, but when they passed each other, he simply said to him, rather abruptly, "Play well."

Mo Fan paused in his step and turned his head back to look, but Fang Rui didn't stop, nor did he look at him. He was striking poses for the crowd to take pictures of him!

Mo Fan continued to quietly walk onstage and entered the player booth.

The third battle of the group round: Happy's Mo Fan, playing Deception, versus Hundred Blossoms's Yu Feng, playing Blossoming Chaos.

One was a rookie, one was an All-Star level God. On paper, there was an extremely clear disparity in this match-up.

This battle was like the first battle of the individual competition, but now the situation was reversed. This time, it was Happy's player stepping onstage for the first time, against a first-string God in the professional circle. Mo Fan hadn't appeared in the opening round.

Learning from what had happened in the individual competition, the judge was somewhat anxious and made a special visit to check on the status of this Happy rookie. But all he found was that this player's face was as still as water.

Poor thing, he was so nervous that his facial expression was frozen stiff. The judge sighed in his heart.

"No need to be nervous, just treat this as a normal game," the judge said to him warmly. He sympathized greatly with rookies.

But the rookie only glanced at him. Without saying anything, he entered the player booth with that frozen expression.

He didn't hear me speak? But that's not right, he looked at me. He did hear me speak? Then what kind of reaction was that? The judge was at a loss. But this wasn't his responsibility, it was just his own good intentions. Doing this was enough, so he didn't pay any more attention, and went back to the judging area to check the confirmation status of both competitors. That rookie wouldn't be like the last one, would he? Entering the player booth and then not doing anything?

But the judge saw that both competitors had confirmed they were ready. The rookie's actions were decisive!

The judge checked the time and it was about time, so he allowed the new battle to begin.

The map was the same as before.

But Mo Fan was new to the professional scene. Even if he often played in the in-game Arena, he hadn't professionally analyzed these maps like most pro players did. And Yu Feng, on the other hand, had already demonstrated in the previous battle that he was no stranger to this map. No matter which way you looked at it, the victory in this round seemed like it was already determined.

Even the applause from the crowd was rather subdued, as though not wanting to give the rookie too much pressure. There were no shouts of "you must win" or anything like that.

The two characters entered the map. Yu Feng's Blossoming Chaos directly charged toward the center, while Mo Fan's Deception began moving along a roundabout path.

The four Nightwalker subclasses very rarely battled head-on, so Yu Feng was unsurprised when he arrived at the center of the map without seeing Deception.

He really was quite familiar with this map. He didn't even have to look around to determine the positions from which the opponent might launch a sneak attack.

Yu Feng stared at these positions. At this time, Mo Fan's Deception had already arrived, and was hiding at one of these positions, staring at Yu Feng's Blossoming Chaos.

Neither side moved. The battle was at a standstill.

For Glory competitions, whether or not to introduce a time limit had always been a source of controversy.

With a time limit, playstyles would become more utilitarian, and the battles would become more uninteresting and ugly to watch. But without a time limit, there would be patient stalemates that made the battle suffocatingly dreary, especially for the broadcast. These tactics wasted time with nothing happening, and it drove them crazy.

Right now, for example...

Neither Yu Feng nor Mo Fan took the initiative to attack. They were both waiting for the other to expose an opening they could exploit.

This sort of tense, anticipatory atmosphere sounded like it carried a lot of feeling, but when watching, it looked like a frozen image.

The players were testing each other's patience, but they were also testing the patience of the crowd. If everyone had enough patience, would this scene just drag on forever?

Part of the reason why this situation could come about was because of how Glory maps were designed. The maps they used for battles were extremely vast, increasing the number of options available in battle and increasing this sort of hiding and testing patience.

How to solve this? People had pondered this for several seasons now, but no satisfactory solution had been reached. But they had to solve this problem, otherwise it could really happen that neither side attacked and instead just stared at each other for an hour.

In the end, the Alliance gave the power to the judge. If such a situation came up in battle, they could make a ruling.

Yu Feng was of course familiar with all of the rules of competition. He didn't move.

Mo Fan was now a pro player, and of course he understood the rules, but he had never experienced the rules. He didn't move either.

Thus, soon there was an announcement in the battle system.

It was from the judge. After this long standoff, the judge declared that Mo Fan would be given a yellow card for wasting time in battle.

Even though Yu Feng hadn't moved either, he had directly approached and was out in the open, while Mo Fan's intent while hiding was obvious. In these conditions, the one who would be given a warning was Mo Fan; he was the one expected to take the initiative. Yu Feng was clear on this point, so he wasn't worried. He patiently waited until Mo Fan was forced by the judge to make a move.

One yellow card was considered a warning. Two yellow cards would become a red card. In football, a red card meant that the player was dismissed from the game. In Glory matches, in an individual match, if a player got a red card and was expelled, victory was given by the judge to the opponent.

Mo Fan had read the competition rules, and now, he finally experienced the rules.

After the yellow card, if he continued to maintain this situation, the second yellow card would come much sooner, and he would quickly get a red card.

So Yu Feng knew, after this Mo Fan must move. He focused all of his attention on his surroundings.

As expected, Mo Fan moved.

Deception left the place he was hiding, and quietly walked, switching to another position. And then, he hid himself again.

He continued not to move.

The judge was instantly furious!

At first, he had cared about this rookie, but this rookie was trying to play this sort of clever trickery with him. Switching to a different position to hide, you think that that's enough to consider yourself as taking the initiative?

Seeing that Deception appeared to have no intent of attacking, the judge sent another announcement in the system.

Second yellow card, changed to red card, Deception is disqualified!

The crowd was in an uproar.

Mo Fan was shocked.

What? Was this not allowed?

The system declared Yu Feng's victory. Even Yu Feng himself was surprised.

What was this rookie from Happy doing? He got a yellow card and still didn't move, was he looking for that red card? Yu Feng had no way of knowing that Mo Fan did move, but his movement made the judge feel that this player was mocking him. The rules were not made so you could find loopholes in them like this!

With the red card, Mo Fan was declared the loser, and players that earned a red card were banned from the next round of matches. Depending on the situation, there could be even more severe suspension penalties.

The live crowd was speechless. They had no idea how to express their current feelings toward all of this. After all, this was a rookie playing onstage for the first time, booing him seemed a little harsh! But being red carded like this was equivalent to giving the opponent a perfect victory, this this this… it really made people upset.

Under the conflicted eyes of the crowd, Mo Fan left the stage and headed back to the player area.

Happy's players wanted to cry. This was all an issue of miscommunication! But the problem was, it was truly too difficult to communicate with this kid. They let him figure things out on his own, and it resulted in this sour outcome.

Mo Fan returned to the player bench and returned to his seat. The others shot conflicted looks at each other, but no one went up to say anything.

And Mo Fan? His face was finally no longer so expressionless and now revealed some hesitation. After some internal struggle, he finally opened his mouth with uncertainty. "What… should I have done?"

He only said this one sentence. Even the point of his speaking wasn't clear.

"I'll teach you," Su Mucheng said, smiling. She stood from where she was sitting in the front row and went back to the corner next to where Mo Fan was.

Everyone breathed a sigh of relief.

But Chen Guo was still in low spirits. They'd gotten off to a good start in the group competition, but now with Mo Fan's red card, they were suddenly in a bad situation.

Happy's third competitor in the group round was Tang Rou. Facing this difficult situation, she was actually quite excited. But she was also now very clear about her own skill level.

"I'll give it a shot!" These were the words Tang Rou left as she headed to the stage.

It was unlike her normal confidence, but for a rookie facing the All-Star God Yu Feng at four-fifths health and then another player at full health, being able to say "I'll give it a shot" already demonstrated remarkable courage.

Tang Rou went onstage to the sound of enthusiastic applause. She was currently extremely popular, and not just among Happy fans. Throughout the entire Glory circle, many people were paying attention to this pretty female competitor. Of course, it was wrong to judge a book by its cover, but one had to admit that physical appearance was often the basis of first impressions. Being attractive was always advantageous.

Another rookie, but after being played by Mo Fan, the judge was feeling much less sympathetic toward rookies. He didn't say much to Tang Rou, and after confirming that she entered the battle, he quickly declared the battle to begin.

In the previous round, one scene of silence was swapped for another, and then victory was decided by a red card.

This round, 23 seconds after it began, the two opponents met in the center and began to fight.

Chapter 1153: Can’t Back Down Even A Single Step

No set up. No probing. The two characters met in the center, made a move, and started fighting. The battle instantly reached a high point.

Everyone in the crowd was caught off guard. No one had expected the fight to be so intense as soon as the two clashed. For a moment, they even forgot to cheer and applaud.

Berserker, Battle Mage. Two extremely offense-oriented classes.　　

Greatsword. Spear. These two heavy weapons had sky-high physical attack.

But at this moment, under the two players' high-paced playing, Blossoming Chaos's Burial Blossoms and Soft Mist's Dancing Fire Flowing Flame had turned into two gleams of light. The fast flashing collisions between the two weapons made it difficult for many to completely identify what skill each of them were using.

Yu Feng was an All-Star and a top player. He ought to be performing at a high-level. However, Tang Rou was able to defend against this high-level playing. To the crowd, she was a bigger highlight.

She's worthy of being a Battle Mage coached by Ye Xiu!

The countless viewers watching this match all thought this. Even though there was no official statement that Tang Rou was Ye Xiu's student, she had been discovered by Ye Xiu and a Battle Mage that had grown beside him. Whatever the case, it was impossible to say that Ye Xiu was not involved.

In fact, this was exactly the case.

As long as Tang Rou needed it, Ye Xiu had passed on everything he knew about Battle Mages to Tang Rou. After that, he helped Tang Rou establish her own style.

Tang Rou was a rookie. A rookie who had no fear. In the end, her playing was so fierce and violent that many people had trouble believing that such a beautiful girl could have such a ferocious Battle Mage.

Ye Xiu's Battle Mage had also been very fierce. If not, he wouldn't have been called the Battle God. However, his fierceness differed from Tang Rou's. His fierceness couldn't be replicated by Tang Rou because for Ye Xiu, apart from being a Battle Mage, he was a master proficient with all classes. His fierceness had been built upon this solid foundation. His techniques might seem very ordinary, but in real combat, these same techniques were difficult to defend against because the opponent would discover that no matter how he or she responded to it, everything would be within Ye Xiu's grasp. One attack until the end, bringing about the title Battle God.

It could be said that it was because Ye Xiu had chosen a Battle Mage to be his main, so One Autumn Leaf became the Battle God. But if he had chosen a different class, the title Battle God might have belonged to a different character.

Through her own style, Tang Rou attracted everyone's attention because her opponent was Yu Feng, an All-Star level top player. A rookie could fight on par with a top player. How could there be anything else but praise for her?

But were the two really evenly-matched?

The fast pace made it difficult for the viewers to clearly see the situation, but right now, Yu Feng was feeling fearful. He realized that he was being suppressed.

Countless playstyles had emerged from this Berserker class. From the Number One Berserker player, Sun Zheping, to the many players now. Even among these playstyles, Yu Feng was an anomaly. His Berserker was also very aggressive, but it wasn't as simple or crude as the traditional Berserker. Within his wildness lay exceptional precision. It could be said that Yu Feng's Berserker had founded a new style. Although it had yet to become mainstream, he was most definitely the Number One Berserker right now.

At the moment, Tang Rou and he were clashing with brute force to determine victory. In reality, this wasn't what Yu Feng excelled at. However, Tang Rou was a rookie. And he was Team Hundred Blossom's captain and core, an All-Star level top player. Yu Feng could not accept cowering against a rookie in a direct confrontation. After all, he was not someone who played dirty.

As a result, he decided to confront this rookie directly. However, after clashing with her, he discovered that this rookie's fierceness surpassed his expectations. If he truly continued to fight like this, he really might just lose out of carelessness.

I need to find back my rhythm.

Yu Feng instantly grasped the crux of the problem.

In order to protect his image and Team Hundred Blossom's morale, he had decided to fight at Tang Rou's pace and beat her. But after fighting her, he realized that beating her in this way wasn't so easy. He needed to drag the match back into his pace to win. No matter what, if he truly lost, it would be the biggest blow to his image and the team's morale.

Once he made his decision, Yu Feng immediately went from fighting for the initiative to going on the defense.　　

When Dragon Tooth came at him, Yu Feng didn't have Blossoming Chaos dodge and counterattack. Instead, he attacked the Dragon Tooth to parry it.

To his surprise, Dragon Tooth abruptly stopped and then stabbed twice into a Double Stab. The change had been too rapid, and the spear had been too close. Yu Feng wasn't able to parry it with an attack and hastily switched to using the skill, Guard.

Clang! Clang!

Two clangs rang in quick succession. The Double Stab had been blocked. Blossoming Chaos slid backwards. Yu Feng also jumped back too. He wanted to pull apart the distance and slow down the pace.　　

He had retreated quite fast, but Soft Mist pressed forward even faster. It was almost as if she had been charging forward before even confirming that Dragon Tooth and Double Stab had connected.

Phantom Dragon Teeth!

Another skill followed. Soft Mist flicked her wrist, and her spear transformed into numerous Dragon Teeth.

How many?

Yu Feng's eyes widened...

One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!

Eight after-images?

Phantom Dragon Teeth was similar to the Blade Master's Shadow Steps. It relied on player input to create and maintain these after-images. The higher the number, the faster the hand speed and precision required.

Eight Phantom Dragon Teeth?

A rookie could actually reach such a level?

Let alone trying to parry Phantom Dragon Teeth, using Guard wouldn't work either. Yu Feng didn't want to trade his health away to attack because right now, he was trying to get back his rhythm. Therefore, his only choice was to continue retreating.

These eight after-images let out eight distinct streams of air, making it even more difficult to distinguish between the real and fake ones. Yu Feng could only dodge these eight after-images as if all of them were real. He even couldn't use his normal movements to evade them. He raised Burial Blossoms in the air and Blossoming Chaos dashed back, utilizing the Blade Master's Triple Slash.

Triple Slash wasn't a common low-level skill that could be learned by all Swordsmen. The only reason Blossoming Chaos could use it was because his Burial Blossoms had a bonus skill up for Triple Slash. From this, it could be seen that Yu Feng truly was different from an ordinary Berserker. In his skill choices, he favored this Blade Master movement skill to give his attacks more life.

Through this skill, Blossoming Chaos instantly completed his movement and all eight Dragon Teeth after-images missed. Yu Feng was wondering whether he should complete this Triple Slash and attack back, but he hadn't expected Tang Rou to immediately raise her spear after Phantom Dragon Teeth and unleash a Dragon Breaks the Ranks to chase after Blossoming Chaos.

　

Yu Feng turned pale with fright. He hastily slashed again to turn away, but this time, the distance was too close. With Dragon Breaks the Rank's speed and power, even if it didn't fully connect, it still sent Blossoming Chaos into a tumble.

Yu Feng immediately Quick Recovered. Blossoming Chaos rolled and stood up. Then, he heard a crash from above the air. He looked up and saw Soft Mist. This time, she had used a skill while airborne. The bloom of magic from Dragon Rises from the Sea locked onto Blossoming Chaos.

Hit!

This time, Yu Feng wasn't able to dodge it. The Dragon Rises from the Sea landed on Blossoming Chaos's head. Tang Rou didn't wait for Soft Mist to land and followed with a Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. To the naked eye, that magic force pierced straight through. Blossoming Chaos was sent flying back. Soft Mist chased after him. The chasers produced from Dragon Tooth and Sky Strike battered against Blossoming Chaos. The entire stadium was dumbfounded.

The spectators saw Tang Rou heroically clash with a top player levels higher than her and were already very satisfied. People would always be more lenient towards rookies. How the match played out was more important than the outcome. Even if Tang Rou lost to Yu Feng, no one would say anything about it. It was just like how Mo Fan left the stage with two yellow cards turning into a red. That wasn't how someone should lose, but the crowd stopped themselves from throwing out ridicule.

But right now, even someone who didn't understand Glory could tell which side had the upper hand.

Tang Rou was going to beat Yu Feng?

After a moment of shock, the venue erupted into astonished roars. Even if Happy won in the end, there wouldn't be such a commotion. It wasn't only to drive the team's morale. The crowd had been infected by Happy's battle strength. They wouldn't look down on their determination and future.

On the other hand, Team Hundred Blossom's players stared stupidly at this scene. Their captain was being suppressed by a rookie?

Yes, it was true.

Yu Feng was both stunned and furious. He hadn't expected this rookie to be so explosive. He had retreated to try get back the pace of the match. He hadn't thought that this would be like a dam breaking. The opponent's offensive crashed towards him. Yu Feng was a mess, a complete mess.

The pace had originally been one that he didn't like. He could still play with it thought. Even if he was being slightly suppressed, who won or who lost wasn't certain. But as soon as he stepped back, the opposing side stepped forward a hundred steps. Establish his own rhythm? Yu Feng didn't get the chance before his opponent overwhelmed him to the point that he couldn't even breathe.

I'm going to lose!

In this instant, this thought leaped into Yu Feng's mind. How could a pro player not have a clear recognition of how the match was playing out?

But even if he knew, what could he do? Yu Feng did his best to defend. He was no longer looking for the rhythm that he preferred. Right now, he needed to keep up with his opponent's tempo and stabilize the situation!

But… I can't keep up!

Yu Feng discovered that Tang Rou was even faster and fiercer than the start of the battle. And this had been brought about because he had stepped back…

In front of this opponent, you can't back down even a single step!

In the end, along with this understanding, Blossoming Chaos fell.

Chapter 1154: Group Arena Decider

Applause! The instant Blossoming Chaos fell, there was no hesitation or shock. The crowd had been waiting for this moment. A rookie beating an All-Star? The crowd shouldn't be never expecting this sort of outcome, but this match was different. When Yu Feng retreated, Tang Rou pressed hard, beating up Blossoming Chaos into a sorry state. At that moment, the confidence in their hearts blazed. They started looking forward to what should have been impossible and readied themselves to cheer and applaud when it happened.

It truly did happen. Tang Rou beat Yu Feng. Soft Mist's spear pierced through Blossoming Chaos, taking away the last shred of his life.

Glory!

The symbol of victory flashed onto across the screen. The crowd erupted into thunderous cheers and applause. The rather unfortunate part was that this was the group arena. The winner needed to stay in the player booth and get ready for her next opponent. She couldn't come out and receive their her applause. The crowd didn't care about that though. Even if the main character wasn't there, the rest of Team Happy were there, no? Victory belonged to the individual and the team. This was Tang Rou's victory, but it was also a victory for Team Happy's.

When Yu Feng came out from the stageplayer booth, he looked calm, but his heart wasn't calm at all.　　

An All-Star beaten by a rookie? This might become the headlines of the news. And he served as the contrast to the news, the target to be ridiculed.　　

Yu Feng was unwilling!

If they played again, he was confident that he could beat Tang Rou. Unfortunately, there were no ifs in competition.　　

Yu Feng walked down from the stage dimly and returned to his side's player bench. His teammates didn't know how to console him. Yu Feng was the spiritual pillar of the team. It was always him who comforteding everyone else. However, he had now encountered such a defeat. What should they say?

Yu Feng didn't wait for everyone to console him. After sitting down for a bit, he regained his calm. He knew that he could not panic right now. If he did, the entire team would slack because of the loss of their backbone.

He had lost, but his loss didn't represent Team Hundred Blossom's loss. There was still another player left for Team Hundred Blossoms.

"Xiaoping." Yu Feng called out.

　

Zhu Xiaoping was Team Hundred Blossom's third player for the group arena. He had joined the league in Season 6. After a year on the bench, he was promoted to the main roster in Season 7. He played a Summoner, a class that had never appeared before in All-Stars before.

With the captain calling for him, Zhu Xiaoping immediately went over. In terms of seniority in the team, Zhu Xiaoping had been ion the team longer than Yu Feng. However, he respected the newly transferred captain, and he had the quite the opinion ofn their former captain, Zhang Jiale.

Zhu Xiaoping had officially appeared on the competitive stage in Season 7, the year Team Hundred Blossoms made it to the finals. Even though they ended up losing to Team Tiny Herb, second place was still a great achievement. The team's morale rose, and many of them clenched their fists, ready to work even harder next year.

Zhu Xiaoping was among them. However, in the next season, Zhang Jiale suddenly announced his retirement, turning Team Hundred Blossoms into a complete mess. Their successor to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Zou Yuan, paced back and forth helplessly. Their astonishing new talent, Tang Hao, was unable to carry to the team because he was not the core. In the end, Team Hundred Blossoms failed to make it to even the playoffs. Everything had started with Zhang Jiale's sudden retirement. Zhu Xiaoping had originally been a youth filled with hope that season. Of course he would hold a grudge against Zhang Jiale.

It could be said that Zhu Xiaoping was a firm Zhang Jiale opposer. When Zhang Jiale announced his return, he had been hoping that Zhang Jiale would not return. Tyranny? Zhu Xiaoping sneered. In his eyes, he saw Zhang Jiale as a selfish person. The new Yu Feng seemed to be very responsible though. He took his duties very seriously. Even if their record wasn't that good when he had first arrived, he never felt disheartened or pushed the blame onto anyone else. Zhu Xiaoping appreciated this very much, so he had always firmly supported Yu Feng.　　

"Captain." Zhu Xiaoping walked over.

"Be careful. This Tang Rou is better than we had expected. She's a model competitive player." Yu Feng said.

'But she only has half her health left." Zhu Xiapoing said.　

"She used her ½ health to take out my ⅘ health." Yu Feng said. He was implying that if she could take out ⅘ of his health with ½ her health, she could take out all of yours with what she had left. Of course, there was no need to say that out loud. Zhu Xiaoping understood what he meant.

"Got it. I'll be careful." Zhu Xiaoping wasn't displeased. Whether it was Yu Feng's professionalism or his skill, he held a high opinion of Yu Feng.

"Good luck." Yu Feng said.

"Thanks." Zhu Xiaoping nodded his head. Under the hopeful gazes of his teammates, he walked onto towards the stage.

Team Hundred Blossoms versus Team Happy, the group arena deciding match began. A half-health Soft Mist versus Zhu Xiaoping's full-health Summoner, Wind Carving.

　

Both were Mages. Neither of them hesitated when the match started.. They headed straight for the center and came across each other not long afterwards. At By this time, Zhu Xiaoping had already summoned several beasts.

Because of the limited number of skill points, Summoners could not level all of their summons to max. Which skills to level depended on each player's preferences. As a result, there were countless combinations with almost a new school of thought being created every so often. However, despite the numerous variations, they could not depart from the core design. Every new school of thought weren't solely based on a player's preferences, but also for logical reasons.　

Usually, there were one or two summons that as acted as the core and the other choices were constructed around this core. From this, it could be seen that summons were usually chosen to construct a team, so it was very complicated. A part of why there were no top Summoners in the league was because of the class. Whether it was tactics or play, this class was difficult to use. But for a new player, this class had its easy parts. When killing mobs, they just had to summon a bunch of monsters and then just sit there safely behind their summons while sipping tea. It sounded very simple.

A class that was easy to pick up, but difficult to master was quite popular. Zhu Xiaoping was had been one of these people. He liked this class and had studied this class hard. He hoped that one day he could lead his own summoned army to take the throne in Glory. He had worked hard for that day to come, every practice, every match….

Seeing Soft Mist charge at him, Zhu Xiaoping immediately had Wind Carving arrange his summons into a formation.

Zhu Xiaoping's Summoner style had been popular for a long time. It was the undying Undead Knight style. As the name implied, this style had an Undead Knight as the core. Undead Knights had high defense, high physical attack, and high health. Its huge body gave the user a sense of safety. Zhu Xiaoping's Undead Knight Style had built upon the foundations of the style along with his own individual addition to it. This addition was the usage of an Spirit Cat. Zhu Xiaoping was a pro player. His playstyle would naturally be imitated by others. As a result, the Undead Knight and Spirit Cat style was considered as the most optimal way of using the Undead Knight. All sorts of guides had appeared on the web.

　　

However, pro players weren't pro players because they were always imitated, but because they were incapable of being surpassed.

The Spirit Cat Knight style wasn't just dependent on the Spirit Cat and Undead Knight. It also depended on the player's skill in controlling his or her summons.

At this moment, in front of Zhu Xiaoping were a large, dark armored Undead Knight and a slender snow-white cat as protection for the Summoner.

Come!

Zhu Xiaoping watched Soft Mist's movements carefully and had his Undead Knight fight her. His Undead Knight held a shield in one hand an extremely long spear in the other. He raised the spear and stabbed towards Soft Mist.

The staff in his hands waved again and again. Summon after summon appeared before him. The Spirit Cat Knight style was centered around the usage of these two summons. That didn't mean the Summoner diwouldn't have summon anything else. There were many summons that supported and attacked.

For example, Demon World Flowers!

This plant came from another world and practically no Summoners would want to give up on this summon. Even though it could not move, it was extremely powerful within its attack range. It could release poisonous pollen, use its roots to attack from underground, bind the target with its vines, and its flower petals could devour the target.

Demon World Flowers were never the core of a Summoner playstyle, but if there was a poll, the vast majority of people would consider the Demon World Flowers as the most annoying summon to deal with. As long as it was summoned brought out and the Summoner stood nearby, it would bring about a whole lot of trouble. Trying to wait out the Demon World Flowers' duration was impossible. All summons could stay on the field forever as long as they did not receive damage. The only saving grace was that only one flower could be summoned at a time.

Whenever Demon World Flowers were summoned, anyone would have to carefully consider whether to step into that area, especially when there were other summons rampaging there.　　

However, Soft Mist didn't seem to notice this formation. Her footsteps didn't stop or slow down as she charged straight towards him.

"Sure enough, compared to our research on her, she's even more…" Zhu Xiaoping had trouble finding the right words to describe Tang Rou's actions. He was in the middle of his summoned legion, safely ordering his summons to surround Soft Mist.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!!

Soft Mist released her skill.

"How impatient!" Zhu Xiaoping sighed. His Undead Knight went forward with his shield to block it.

No class dared to clash with Dragon Breaks the Ranks directly, but the Undead Knight had no fear. Perhaps because it was only a summoned creature that could be born again in a new world and could be replaced with a new Undead Knight soon afterwards...

Chapter 1155: Breaking Through the Legion of Summons

The Undead Knight faced Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

In this situation, many would feel their hearts hurt seeing their high-level skill landing on a summon. A summoned creature could be re-summoned after dying. Often times, it wasn't a fatal loss for the Summoner.

But Tang Rou refused to retreat. The Undead Knight reached her, but Soft Mist didn't pause. Charge!　

As for the Undead Knight? After receiving orders from its master, even if it wasn't willing, it could only carry them out. Soft Mist's spear and the Undead Knight's shield collided against each other.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks was a high-level Battle Mage skill. A single summoned creature didn't have the ability to completely negate its momentum. The Undead Knight wasn't sent flying, but it was pushed back, plowing two ditches in the ground. The spear in its hands stabbed towards Soft Mist.

　　

Soft Mist's posture was lowered and leaned to the side. The Undead Knight's spear missed, hitting the ground instead. Soft Mist took one step diagonally to circle around the Undead Knight.

Whoosh!

A flash of white flew out.　

The snow-white spirit cat had hidden behind the Undead Knight and suddenly launched a sneak attack.

A summon's AI wasn't that intelligent. Zhu Xiaoping had controlled the Spirit Cat to make this sneak attack.

This attack was silent and sudden. But to his surprise, Soft Mist's spear was actually able to parry the Spirit Cat's attack in time.

Circle Swing threw the Spirit Cat to the side as Soft Mist continued to press forward. Neither the Undead Knight nor the Spirit Cat were her targets. She only had one target, the Summoner Wind Carving.

The Spirit Cat's sneak attack failing had clearly been outside of Zhu Xiaoping's expectations. Even with Yu Feng's warning, he still hadn't expected Tang Rou to be so quick and precise.

Devil World Flowers attacked at this moment. A vine suddenly shot out from beneath Soft Mist. However, there was always a sign before a vine attacked. Tang Rou was no longer a Glory noob. She had a solid understanding of all 24 classes now. As soon as she entered the summoned legion's formation, the first thing she did was be on the lookout for the Devil World Flowers. Just before, the Devil World Flowers' roots had suddenly rustled. Tang Rou immediately knew that a vine attack was coming, so she had Tang Rou jump.　　

Sure enough, a vine attack came. However, Soft Mist had already jumped in the air, so the vine missed.　　

Shattering Heaven and Earth!

The Level 75 Battle Mage skill crashed down at the center of the summons. The blazing Dancing Fire Flowing Flame pierced through the crust of the earth and was pulled out. Soft Mist flew backwards and magic waves erupted outwards from her at the center. Anything with health inside its range would receive damage. Even though Zhu Xiaoping ordered these summons to avoid this attack, the summons failed to dodge it cleanly. The spirit-type summons with low-defense were instantly killed by this powerful attack.

"Not good!" Off stage at Hundred Blossom's player bench, Yu Feng slapped his leg and stood up.

"What's wrong?" His teammates also stood up.

Yu Feng didn't say anything. He fixed his gaze on the battle. In that instant, neither side had made many mistakes. Even though a few of Zhu Xiaoping's spirit summons had died, the cooldown and mana consumption for summons were low, so a few deaths wasn't anything to worry about. Yu Feng didn't care about such losses. In that instant, what he saw was Zhu Xiaoping retreating.

Facing a powerful level 75 Battle Mage's Shattering Heaven and Earth, retreating was a very reasonable thing to do. However, Yu Feng, who had just fought with Tang Rou, felt a bad premonition arise in his heart.

In front of her, you can't back down a single step!

Yu Feng had understood this after losing to Tang Rou. However, it had just been a realization. He hadn't treated it like a lesson, so he didn't tell Zhu Xiaoping.

But this scene suddenly reminded Yu Feng of his previous match. That inadvertent thought floated into his mind. He suddenly felt like things weren't going to be looking good for Zhu Xiaoping soon...

Zhu Xiaoping obviously wasn't thinking the same thing as Yu Feng. Of course his Wind Carving should safely retreat from Shattering the Heaven and Earth's range. He resummoned the summons that had died, moved his summons into formation, and prepared to start surrounding Soft Mist again.

Undead Knight! This defender had taken a Dragon Breaks the Ranks just before. Now, he was the vanguard once again. Before Shattering the Heaven and Earth's power fully dissipated, it stepped into its range.

However, Soft Mist was even more eager than it. Before Shattering the Heaven and Earth's effects disappeared, she dashed out towards Wind Carving.

"Damn, a pity!" Zhu Xiaoping sighed. Behind Soft Mist, the Demon World Flower's vines had missed. The Undead Knight had just been a feint. Its purpose was to hide the Demon World Flower's attack, so the Demon World Flower vines could bind her.

Zhu Xiaoping didn't know if Tang Rou had noticed it or her eagerness had rescued her. In any case, she safely dodged this attack.

From the current situation, Wind Carving seemed to be in danger. Summoners were one of the weakest classes in terms of close combat. Zhu Xiaoping didn't panic though. Wind Carving waved his magic staff and disappeared. The Undead Knight's large body appeared before Soft Mist. Its long spear thrust towards Soft Mist.　

Switch!

Using Switch, the user could switch places with a summon. Zhu Xiaoping utilized Wind Carving's teleport to get the Undead Knight to attack Soft Mist. The timing was perfect.

Tang Rou continued on bravely though.

Her target Wind Carving was nowhere to be seen, but the Undead Knight had reached it. What to do?

The same as before! Fight!　　

After dodging the Undead Knight's attack, she noticed that the other summons had surrounded her. Soft Mist swung her spear into a 270 degree arc, stopping the summons' advances. Then, she jumped backwards and thrust her spear.　　

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike!

It was a skill that required player inputs. The spear split into numerous afterimages. For a moment, it was impossible to see how many attacks were truly coming. The system helped to speed up the attack.

The spear shadows formed a circular arc. The summons that tried to advance were repeatedly hit. Her spear's Flowing Flame effects triggered three times, shooting out lines of fire that instantly killed any unlucky summons in its path.

The only one that could continue forward was the Undead Knight.

It was because of this feature that the Undead Knight became a favored summon among Summoners. But although the Undead Knight had this strength, it was also slow and sluggish. Soft Mist pushed away the other summons and jumped back to pull away from the Undead Knight. She turned around and ran, leaving the Undead Knight's spear to hit nothing but air.

As for the Spirit Cat, it had suddenly thrown itself at her from out of nowhere.

But this time, Soft Mist pushed it away with a Falling Flower Palm. Utilizing her own momentum, along with the Falling Flower Palm, the Spirit Cat was sent tumbling away.

Then, Zhu Xiaoping discovered that his encirclement failed to take form. The encirclement had been completely torn apart by Soft Mist. And now, the Summoner Wind Carving was fully exposed to Soft Mist. He seemed to be able to feel the heat from her Fire Chasers.

Zhu Xiaoping suddenly started to panic.

A Summoner without his summons was extraordinarily weak. He had already used Switch too, so it was on cooldown. Was there enough time to summon anything?

　　

But Wind Carving suddenly disappeared.

Teleport...

Wind Carving's weapon had the Elementalist skill Teleport added to it. For a Summoner, this skill increased the survivability of the class. For example, right now, the completely exposed Wind Carving instantly teleported behind his lovable summons...

Zhu Xiaoping was overjoyed, but he couldn't laugh yet. Soft Mist turned around and without any hesitation, her spear thrust out and transformed into a dragon towards his summons.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had a grab effect. The attack target wasn't limited to just one either. In that instant, the summons in pursuit of Soft Mist were devoured. That tenacious Undead Knight was no exception; it was unable to resist Rising Dragon Soars the Sky's damage.

All of the summons were pulled together. Not just that, the magic dragon was still roaring with Wind Carving within its range.

Zhu Xiaoping had focused on getting his summons to evade it, but he had unexpectedly forgotten about himself. By the time he jumped back in panic when the dragon head arrived, it was too late. Soft Mist extended her reach and this skill's attack range was pushed to its limit. Wind Carving was chomped by the dragon head and took the full brunt of the following magic explosion arising from Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

The battle magic engulfed Wind Carving and his summons and then dissipated....

After this attack, no more summons were left on the field. Even the Undead Knight couldn't take the brunt of Dragon Breaks the Ranks and Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

The originally noisy legion of summons was instantly cleared away. The not so far away Demon World Flowers were still rooted there with its petals and leaves gulping up the earth. However, this summon was never the core. With no other summons around it, its effectiveness was drastically diminished. Soft Mist didn't even look at it as she turned around and charged towards the recovering Wind Carving.

This time, he had no protection.

This time, he had no options left.

Zhu Xiaoping was in a daze. He suddenly had trouble understanding what had just transpired.

What just happened? My summons were instantly destroyed?

Summon again? His opponent was already too close to him. How could she give him any opportunities? Zhu Xiaoping lost the battle...

Chapter 1156: Team Competition, Get Ready!

She… she won again?

This time, the entire crowd was truly shocked.

It was impressive enough that Tang Rou had managed to fight on equal footing with Yu Feng, and they considered her win to be a fortunate accident. But now, with only half her health, Tang Rou was able to defeat the third player of Hundred Blossoms… Even though Yu Feng had already lost a fifth of his health to Fang Rui's Boundless Sea, he still had four-fifths left. It was by no means a stretch to call this a 1v2.

A mere rookie, in her second-ever round of competition, successfully completed a 1v2, one of whom was an All-Star level superstar.

What was this?

What was going on?

The crowd was frozen for quite a while, until suddenly, the stadium exploded with applause, shouts, and cheers. When the results of the group arena were announced, the sound level transferred to the live broadcasts spiked. The clapping echoed through every corner of the stadium. Even those Glory fans who weren't particular fans of Happy and had just come to watch the excitement realized that they might be witnessing the rise of another Glory star.

Tang Rou walked out of the player booth, and she wasn't embarrassed by the sounds of the crowd going wild for her with their cheers. She lifted her hand in the air, letting everyone see her waving her clenched fist.

The crowd grew even more enthusiastic.

This was a truly remarkable victory, for Tang Rou, and for Happy. There were already people shouting spontaneous chants from the crowd. This was a true home stadium, enough to strike guilt and terror into the hearts of the opponents.

The uproar continued for quite a while, so much so that the sound broadcasting system of the stadium had no way of announcing the next round of the competition. But no one needed the announcement to know that after the group arena came the crucial team competition. And right now, Happy had a strong lead on Hundred Blossoms, 4 to 1. If they won the team competition as well, it wouldn't be a perfect victory, but it would still very much be a satisfactory victory. Especially with that performance in the group arena, which had been so exciting that it seemed to steal the spotlight from the team competition.

Even the crowd was this thrilled, so of course Happy's young and old wouldn't hide the joy in their hearts.

"That was too beautiful!" As soon as Tang Rou arrived back in the player area, Chen Guo swept her up in a hug. From the crowd members that were closer came several wolf whistles at the sight of two pretty women hugging, some people couldn't help but make some dirty shouts.

"You played beautifully." Ye Xiu praised her as well.

But they couldn't just spend all this time basking in that victory. After the group arena's conclusion, there was a relatively long break until the team competition. During this time, teams would often make adjustments or changes based on the opponent's condition or other problems that came up. So, after a short period of celebration, the team came together to discuss and prepare for the team competition.

Team Hundred Blossoms was doing the same thing. But it was one thing to postpone a celebration, what about an atmosphere of pressure? Were they also supposed to let themselves be happy for a moment before becoming dejected again?

It was clear they could not. They had a rough start in the group arena, but Mo Fan's penalty came as a great present for them, giving them the huge advantage of 2v1. But then the opponent pulled off an incredible reversal, crushing Hundred Blossoms's spirits for good.

"What's wrong, what's wrong with you all? Pull yourselves together. The competition's not over yet, there's still the team competition, we can win back enough points!" As the captain, Yu Feng had to raise the spirits of his teammates. But his speech didn't seem to have much effect. Although everyone acted like their morale was boosted, Yu Feng could tell that it was just to cater to his words. Their fighting spirit hadn't been ignited by this.

How did this happen?

Yu Feng knew that his words weren't anything special, it was something anyone could say. But he also clearly remembered his time in Team Blue Rain, when they were faced with extremely disadvantageous situations. Even in the finals of Season 8, where they were losing 2.5 to 7 on their home field to Samsara, Captain Yu Wenzhou's few simple words were enough to lift the spirits of the entire team.

The competition isn't over yet…

This was the phrase that Yu Wenzhou said the most often. Now, Yu Feng had become captain as well, and what came out of his mouth was the phrase he had heard the most in his previous team. But why couldn't he achieve the same effect that Yu Wenzhou could?

Yu Feng was frustrated and helpless. He had never actually experienced such a pathetic defeat before. To be defeated in a 1v2 by a rookie, where he, the captain and core player, had been playing...

Was it because he himself was one of the reasons why the team's spirit was currently so low? Was that why nothing he said could make a difference?

But there was no time for Yu Feng to ponder the wisdom of captaincy. He saw his teammates depressed and dispirited, yet he could do nothing to help. He could only stabilize himself first, calmly meet the upcoming challenge of the team competition, and hope that his own emotion would spread to his teammates.

While the two teams made their preparations for the team competition, the crowd was still enthralled by the victory of the group arena. During this break, the crowd reviewed the exciting moments of that battle, and the screens and the holographic projections were using all sorts of techniques like freeze-frames, close-ups, and slow-mos to display Tang Rou's mighty performance.

The Hundred Blossoms players and fans could see all this as well, and they were upset. But this was Happy's home stadium, who would care about the feelings of the visitors? This was the home field advantage. After all, the home team fans were the long-term guarantee for the box office!

The players actively prepared for battle, the crowd enthusiastically reviewed the battle, and what about the media?

The commentator Pan Lin was currently analyzing the match between Thunderclap and Void, but when he heard the news about the twists and turns that resulted in Tang Rou winning a 1v2 against Hundred Blossoms in the group arena, he once again interrupted to switch to broadcasting this match and explaining the situation to the viewers.

The esports television broadcast station received numerous calls that night. The polite ones asked which channel they could watch the match between Happy and Hundred Blossoms and understood the broadcasting system; the more aggressive ones directly asked why they weren't showing the Happy vs Hundred Blossoms match.

The broadcasters couldn't blame Pan Lin for switching to talking about another battle, they themselves regretted their decision. But who could have predicted that Happy's match would explode with this kind of excitement?

Those watching the television broadcast could only continue to be helpless. Meanwhile, the online stream of this match was skyrocketing in view count, far surpassing the other nine matches. The online media who could release news quickly were already sending out draft news headlines about Tang Rou's performance to their respective pages. As for the newspapers and magazines that didn't release news as urgently, those reporters had already started to gracefully describe this group arena with their words.

Was the upcoming team competition even important anymore?

To them, it no longer seemed important. No matter the outcome of the team competition, Tang Rou's performance in the group arena was guaranteed to be tomorrow's headline. They only hoped that she wouldn't suddenly hit a low in the team competition, but even if she did, they could still use the poetic descriptor "sometimes angel, sometimes demon" to portray her. From this, it was clear that no matter what, there would be something to write about, and the reporters were all excited, bubbling with delight. It was only until the team competition was immediately about to begin and the players were walking onstage that the reporters finally started paying attention once again.

For the team competition, Happy's roster consisted of Ye Xiu's Unspecialized Lord Grim, Su Mucheng's Launcher Dancing Rain, Fang Rui's Qi Master Boundless Sea, Qiao Yifan's Ghostblade One Inch Ash, and An Wenyi's Cleric Little Cold Hands, with Tang Rou's Soft Mist as the sixth person.

From Hundred Blossoms, there would be Yu Feng's Berserker Blossoming Chaos, Zou Yuan's Spitfire Bright Blossoms, Zhou Guangyi's Assassin Cold Seasons, Zhu Xiaoping's Summoner Wind Carving, and Mo Chuchen's Cleric Arrogant Flowers, with Zhang Wei's Witch Endless Forest as the sixth.

Happy's roster had rotated a bit from the previous rounds. The inclusion of Cleric An Wenyi was expected, of course, but aside from that, Qiao Yifan hadn't yet appeared in this match either. Steamed Bun, who played in the individual competition, and Mo Fan, who played in the group arena, were both sitting back in the player bench.

For Hundred Blossoms, the healer Mo Chuchen joined, but everyone else had appeared in the earlier rounds. This sort of single replacement wouldn't be considered a rotation.

The two sides came onstage. After they shook hands and performed the other necessary tasks, they entered their player booths. The judge checked that both sides were ready, and confirmed the match's start. The sound of the countdown echoed through the whole stadium.

Finally, the team competition began.

The map used was Broken River.

The map was in the shape of a standard square, divided along the diagonals into four triangular regions. The top and bottom triangles were forests of stone, while the left and right triangles were forests of trees. The paths in both types of forests were complex and winding, while the northeast-southwest diagonal was a wide road, and the northwest-southeast diagonal was a river that was interrupted by the road at the intersection at the center of the map. The name "Broken River" came from this.

The water in Broken River rushed rapidly, but it flowed backwards. The intersection at the center acted as the source of the water. It flowed to the northwest and southeast corners of the map. There, the Broken River became waterfalls, and they were clearly the exits of the map. If a character fell into the waterfalls there, they would be directly announced as dead and eliminated from the battle.

The two teams appeared at the southwest and northeast corners. Aside from these two points, each of the triangular regions had a support zone.

Team Hundred Blossoms appeared on the upper half of the map, the northeast corner.

Team Happy appeared on the lower half of the map, the southwest corner.

The connecting road ran straight through the map with no obstacles. If they followed this road, the two teams would quickly appear in each others' view. Happy directly charged along the road, but Hundred Blossoms chose a roundabout path, quickly hiding in the stone forest of the northern triangle region.

Chapter 1157: From the Front or From the Rear

According to the Alliance's rules, when teams picked their home game maps, they were not allowed to use the same map twice in a season. Otherwise, if every team repeatedly used the same map, the matches would become stale. In the past two seasons, a new rule had been established. The following season, teams could repeat not more than half of the maps from last season. By the third season, maps used twice in two seasons were not allowed to be used again.

There were a total of 20 teams in the Alliance. Each team had 38 matches to play in a season with 19 home matches. In other words, each team had 19 chances to pick maps. In order to conform to the Alliance's rules, each team needed to practice over ten maps. Next season, half of their maps could be repeated, so they needed to practice 5 new maps to continue following the rules.

From this, it could be seen that rotating through 15 maps was enough to guarantee that a team followed the Alliance's rules each season. However, if a team only cycled through 15 maps, then after two seasons, their maps would be known by other teams, so most of the time, teams practiced more than the minimum of 15 maps. The maps chosen each season were quite flexible.

Happy was a new team. Their rookies were blank pieces of paper. Their chosen maps were practiced from scratch, so it was impossible to predict what maps they would choose. However, Happy wasn't totally comprised of rookies. Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui were very experienced pro players. Each of them had maps with which they were familiar and adept with.

Directly choosing familiar maps and then teaching their rookies to learn these seemed to be the simplest method. When Team Hundred Blossoms prepared for this match, they had followed this line of thought to predict which maps Happy would choose.

But then, it turned out that the map chosen was Broken River.

Let alone pro players, even most of the crowd would be familiar with this map. This was a well-known common map in Glory. In the Glory Arena, from 2v2s to 10v10s, Broken River was an extremely popular map, to the extent that many players might be unfamiliar with every map except this one.

To put it bluntly, this map could be considered as home map for anyone. This type of map generally wouldn't appear in a pro match because the home game advantage came from which maps were chosen. Choosing this type of map was equivalent to giving up on this advantage.

Too many people understood this logic. When this match officially started and the teams loaded into Broken River, all sorts of discussion was happening in the crowd. During the Thunderclap versus Void broadcast, Pan Lin didn't disappoint and interjected with this piece of news. Pan Lin even chatted about Happy's choice with Li Yibo for a bit, forcing Li Yibo to chime in with his opinions on it. On stage, Thunderclap and Void were fighting intensely...

Happy and Hundred Blossoms were also fighting.　　

Happy walked along the main road, while Hundred Blossoms walked along the longer broken-off riverside. Since Happy didn't see Hundred Blossoms on the main road, Happy knew that Hundred Blossoms had taken a roundabout path.

But which path did Hundred Blossoms take?

The crowd with the omniscient view knew, but Happy didn't know.　

At this moment, the Assassin Cold Seasons appeared from the stone forest, but after seeing Happy, he immediately went back.

The viewers had noticed that Hundred Blossoms was hiding in the stone forest for an ambush, but wasn't this type of bait too low-level?

However, Happy's five players really did just run towards where Cold Seasons appeared and then disappeared. The crowd suddenly started becoming worried. Chasing as soon as they saw someone, wasn't that something only an amateur would do? How could pros do the same?

Then, they saw Hundred Blossoms adjusting their positions.

Pros shouldn't be like this. The viewers knew, and Hundred Blossoms knew even better, so they were mainly aiming to defend against any back attacks.

Happy didn't circle around behind them, but that didn't mean Happy had beaten Hundred Blossoms at their own game. Hundred Blossoms may be protecting themselves against any back attacks, but that didn't mean they would neglect their frontside either. Their formation could instantly adapt. The viewers could see that. Everyone was too familiar with this map. Hundred Blossoms preparing an ambush at this spot was a choice that covered every option.

With both the front and back covered, Hundred Blossoms waited for Happy to arrive.

Happy reached right outside their range. Everyone in the crowd was sweating wildly in worry, but then, they stopped.

Hundred Blossoms watched speechlessly as a Goblin waddled its way over to them from the outside...

Happy did not have a Summoner right now, but a summon could still be sent in because Happy had an unspecialized, Lord Grim.　

Hundred Blossoms watched stupidly as this weak summon walked in alone. It obviously wasn't a threat, but a summon's bravery was laudable. As soon as it saw a target, the Goblin immediately waved its club and charged at its target. The Goblin even threw a rock towards its target: Assassin, Cold Seasons.

Rock Throw was the Goblin's skill, but don't underestimate this simple and crude attack; it had a 20% chance of stunning the target. Just for this 20% stun chance, a Battle Mage or an Elementalist or a Witch bringing along a Goblin wasn't surprising.

But then again, this Rock Throw's speed was very slow. Hitting a target in a chaotic battle was possible, but in this current situation, if the rock hit its target out in the open without any setup, it would be very shameful.

Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons easily dodged it. The Goblin waddled over to Cold Seasons and then was killed in a few hits. Soon afterwards, another Goblin walked over.

Two Goblins couldn't be out at one time, but after a summon died, the summoner would receive a notification. As a result, once Cold Seasons killed off the Goblin, Ye Xiu summoned another one, which came right back in.

"What is he doing?" In Hundred Blossoms's channel, the Cleric Mo Chuchen was unable to hold back.

"Focus," Yu Feng said. He felt like this sort of confusing trick was to distract them. That was what he thought, but he didn't say it with certainty in the channel. In reality, he was also very confused. What is he doing?

When the second Goblin came in, Hundred Blossoms's formation didn't change. As a result, this Goblin once again targeted Cold Seasons. It ran at him and then was killed after a few hits.

The third Goblin came in.

Hundred Blossoms was being driven mad, but they also understood. This Goblin was sending them a message: Don't be naive. We're not going to run in.

If Hundred Blossoms didn't come out and Happy didn't go in, what would the result be?

This question was rather difficult to answer. The tactics involved in a team competition were far more complex than the tactics involved in an individual competition. Mo Fan could quickly be sent out with two yellow cards into a red, but in the team competition, if a stalemate appeared, the referee would need to carefully ponder over it. Even though referees had undeniable authority in their decision, after the match, the referee's decision could be judged to see if it was reasonable, especially for a particularly difficult decision. It was a situation no referee wanted to encounter.

However, the referee for this match was clear-headed.

Because this match wasn't in a stalemate. Three Goblins might have walked in, but Happy's other players were moving. Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi were circling around to the back.

Yu Feng's initial judgement had been correct. This deliberately confusing move was to distract them and create a diversion.

However, Hundred Blossoms wouldn't be so distracted that they wouldn't notice what was happening behind them, no? They were feeling a bit restless, but their formation hadn't slackened. No matter which way they were attacked, even if it was a pincer, they would still have the advantage.

At this point, Lord Grim had summoned a total of five Goblins now. Ye Xiu was also talking with the enemy team in the public chat.

"How many has it been so far?" Ye Xiu asked.

"5…" Yu Feng replied, unable to say anything else.

"How many do you plan on going until?" Ye Xiu asked.

"..."

If they went out now, they might be the ones caught in the enemy formation. Team Hundred Blossoms pondered over what to do. Should they go out? Happy didn't seem to dare charge in, but at the same time, if they kept up this stalemate, the referee would eventually intervene sooner or later. What would the referee rule? There was clearly an ambush lying in wait. Forcing Happy to charge in was unreasonable. However, Happy was defending the entrance. Forcing Hundred Blossoms to come out wasn't reasonable either.

At this moment, Hundred Blossoms deeply felt the referee's troubles.　

"Maybe he'll reset the match?" Zou Yuan said.

With neither side being an easy decision, resetting the match to resolve a stalemate had occurred before.

"Wait for a reset?" Zhou Guangyi said as he killed off the fifth Goblin. He didn't like this type of stalemate. In fact, he didn't even like setting up this ambush even though he was an Assassin.

The final decision came down to their captain Yu Feng. As he pondered… a sixth Goblin had waddled in. Everyone was already getting numb to it.

"I think…" Zhou Guangyi was about to type out his opinion, when he suddenly saw something out of the corner of his eye. Then, he saw three Anti-Tank Missiles shooting towards him at a speed far faster than that waddling Goblin.

Zhou Guangyi didn't have time to type. He immediately rolled. The three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded at where he just escaped. It wasn't until the explosion did the other four suddenly snap back to the battle.

All of them turned to the front, looking for signs of the enemy. For a moment, they had forgotten about their responsibilities because of this sudden attack.

Opportunity was just an instant.

From behind Hundred Blossoms, four of Happy's players charged in.

Chapter 1158: Pincer

Hundred Blossoms's negligence had only been for an instant. With the continuous pointless harassment from Goblins, a sudden accurate attack made every Hundred Blossoms player instinctively take a look in that direction. It was simply human nature.

However, this human nature became an opening in this battle. Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi, who had circled around behind them, started their assault.

Qiao Yifan first laid down his ghost boundary.

Sword Boundary increased both Intelligence and Strength. It was an extremely powerful supportive buff for any class. Dancing Rain, Boundless Sea, and Little Cold Hands were already standing inside this Sword Boundary's range. Dancing Rain, who had the longest range out of them, was the first to initiate the fight. Of Hundred Blossoms's five characters, four of them were completely exposed to her. A huge opening in their rear had appeared.

Heat-Seeking Missile!

A target landed where Dancing Rain pointed her finger, and a missile flew towards this target in an arc. Right when Hundred Blossoms's players turned back around, they suddenly saw four Happy players pop up out of nowhere. As they turned pale with fright, the Heat-Seeking Missile descended from the sky and crashed into the target. A mini-mushroom cloud erupted in the middle of three of Hundred Blossoms's players. It didn't directly hit any of them, but the shockwaves from the explosion was enough to make them suffer. The three affected players dodged, disrupting the carefully arranged ambush formation set up by Team Hundred Blossoms.

Bang! Bang!

Two consecutive gunshots rang. As Team Hundred Blossoms's ranged attacker, Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms counterattacked. On Happy's side, Boundless Sea's two hands formed a circle and then pushed out. A net of light instantly enveloped the four Happy players in the rear. It was the Qi Master's defensive skill, Qi Guard, which absorbed all damage for its duration.

Qi Guard lasted 30 seconds, but with enough damage, the QI Guard could be broken ahead of time. It was similar to a summon. Qi Guard had its own health too.　

But at the moment, only Bright Blossoms's attacks could reach them. A single character's DPS wouldn't be able to break through Qi Guard so easily.

The others in Hundred Blossoms started counterattacking too. Several summoning circles flashed, and Zhu Xiaoping summoned several creatures, which rushed out as their shields. But on Happy's side, One Inch Ash flicked his blade and laid down an Ice Boundary, which restricted the movements and lowered the defense of any enemies within it. Launcher and Qi Master came out and started throwing out AoE attacks, instantly decimating the summons and rampaging onwards towards Hundred Blossoms.

Ghostblade, Launcher, Qi Master.

These three classes had powerful AoE abilities. In this narrow stone forest, their attacks covered the entire area. Happy's ambush from behind had come with ample preparation, methodically utilizing the terrain. It was absolutely the result of professional practice.

Hundred Blossoms was caught off guard and hastily made adjustments. Trying to break through Happy's firepower directly would cost them too much. Zhou Guangyi's gaze finally landed on the sides of the stone forest. There were no lack of footholds on these stones. With the Assassin's Air Leap, he could hop over and open up the situation with an ambush.

As soon as he thought of this, Zhou Guangyi immediately had Cold Seasons jump over. Teammates had their own tacit understanding with each other. They didn't need to communicate every single of their actions. The others noticed Cold Seasons's movements and understood Zhou Guangyi's intentions. They started a full-front assault to break through in coordination with Zhou Guangyi.　

Right when Cold Seasons jumped towards the first foothold, Zhou Guangyi saw Blossoming Chaos type in chat: "Careful!!"

Who are you talking to?

A thread of doubt flashed through Zhou Guangyi's mind. He looked downwards. It didn't like any of the others had encountered any dangers! Just at this moment, a cold light silently slit across Cold Season's throat. Blood splattered into the air and rained down.　

Cut Throat!

How could Zhou Guangyi not recognize this Assassin skill? It wasn't until now did he realize that Yu Feng had been warning him. The only one who could have executed this move was Lord Grim. He was able to silently approach me from behind and complete a Cut Throat?

In this instant, Zhou Guangyi really felt like his throat had been slit. After being hit by this attack, Cold Seasons had been stopped mid-jump. However, the attacks weren't over yet. Lord Grim didn't wait for him to turn around. Lord Grim used Eagle Stamp, stepping on Cold Seasons as the two fell towards the ground.

Yu Feng's Berserker Blossoming Chaos was on the ground waiting. Observing how the two would land, he flew out with a Collapsing Mountain.

Lord Grim wasn't greedy. As soon as he saw Blossoming Chaos leaping towards him, he utilized Eagle Stamp's momentum to shoot backwards, allowing him to just narrowly dodge Blossoming Chaos's blade.

The others in Hundred Blossoms provided ample support. Bright Blossoms fired several shots in the air. Wind Carving summoned several more creatures and commanded them to surround where Lord Grim would land. Their Cleric Arrogant Flowers casted a Sacred Fire in the air for Lord Grim to run into.

Then, they saw Lord Grim pull out his sword and release a Falling Light Blade. He switched directions in mid-air, evading Bright Blossoms's gunshots and Arrogant Flowers's Sacred Fire. His sword returned to the sheath, and his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up. It didn't turn into a spear or a shield. The front umbrella ribs bunched together and formed an arc, transforming into an Exorcist's sickle. This sickle swung in a circle, and a blue light floated into the air, surrounding Wind Carving's summons.

Rising Emblem!

Lord Grim safely landed on the ground, while the summons were sent into the air. Hundred Blossoms's players were dumbstruck. This string of different skills had been performed with such freedom and ease. When had they ever seen such a thing before? Even if they had seen an unspecialized before, without the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, it was impossible to complete such a fluid chain of skills.

The crowd exploded with excitement at this combo. All sorts of cheers and shrieks clamored in the venue. But for Hundred Blossoms, failing to block Lord Grim was secondary. In order to intercept Lord Grim, their formation had been messed up again. On the other end, the other four Happy players broke through an opening and their AoE attacks swallowed up Zou Yuan's and Mo Chuchen's two characters.

Being pincered like this was no good, but which way should they break out?

As the captain, Yu Feng realized that he wasn't able to come to a firm decision. To their rear, the four from Happy had heavy firepower. Breaking through the rear would result in heavy losses. But to their front, Ye Xiu's unspecialized was all sorts of weird. Even if they had the numbers advantage, he felt like they would be unable to break free from him. That would allow the four from the rear to approach them and provide support for Lord Grim, leaving Hundred Blossoms with even less room to maneuver.

Yu Feng was hesitating. On the other hand, after Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons landed back on the ground and rolled, he directly sliced towards Lord Grim with a Shining Cut.

As a player from Tyranny, his enmity towards Ye Xiu was especially natural. What's more, he was the successor to Cold Seasons, which had once instant killed Ye Xiu with one strike. He had also been Cut Throat by Ye Xiu as an Assassin.

New enmity and old enmity formed a never ending circle. His side had four people and the other side had one, it was simple math. As a result, Zhou Guangyi didn't hesitate to charge at Lord Grim.

I guess that's what we're doing...

Yu Feng saw Zhou Guangyi make his move already, so he stopped hesitating. Blossoming Chaos immediately opened the way with a Triple Slash and slashed towards Lord Grim. The two characters arrived at the same time, instantly forming a pincer onto Lord Grim. Lord Grim didn't seem to be in a fluster though. He fished out something from his umbrella and threw it down towards the ground.

Boom!

Purple smoke spread through the air. Lord Grim had thrown a Ninja tool, Smoke Bomb.

Under the cover of the purple smoke, Yu Feng and Zhou Guangyi weren't able to find Lord Grim's whereabouts. The two could only have their characters wave their weapons and hope to hit him. Then, a dark shadow flew out from the purple smoke. The two didn't notice it due to the purple smoke. Blossoming Chaos and Cold Seasons were suddenly wrapped around by the dark shadow. The dark shadow retracted and the two characters were bound together.

Witch skill: Night Cloak.

Afterwards, a hand extended out from the purple smoke and slammed into the two of them. With a bang, Falling Flower Palm sent the two flying away back to the AoE bombardment from the other four Happy players.

At the rear, Zou Yuan and Mo Chuchen were finally able to escape from the bombardment with the help of Zhu Xiaoping's summons, but then they saw Lord Grim slap their two teammates back to them. They couldn't break through from this side, and they couldn't break through from that side either. Hundred Blossoms was suddenly in chaos. Everyone was thinking of what they should do.

Flash Bullet, Smoke Bullet!

Zou Yuan stood out. His Bright Blossoms threw two grenades and then let out a flurry of skills. Light layered on top of each other, producing Zhang Jiale's famous Hundred Blossoms style. He planned on using this light cover to let the team escape.　

This sort of strategy was no stranger to Hundred Blossoms. Even if Yu Feng and Zhou Guangyi hadn't come from Hundred Blossoms and had only been with the team for a year, when they first arrived, they had started by adapting to the core playstyle. It was only after they started gradually adjusting to their personal styles and strengths did they stop copying these former strategies.

And now, Zou Yuan had come out with Hundred Blossom's signature style. The team disappeared within the light. Seizing the opportunity provided by Flash Bullet and Smoke Bullet, they pounced towards the entrance guarded by the lone Lord Grim and got out smoothly.

This scene gave all sorts of mixed feelings towards the Hundred Blossoms viewers.

What did this Hundred Blossoms Style mean to Team Hundred Blossoms? The fans had originally thought that the team had turned a new page, but in this crucial moment, this disdained Hundred Blossoms style left behind by Zhang Jiale had helped them win a chance to turn this battle around.

The fans of Hundred Blossoms felt a mix of emotions well up in their hearts. However, the players on stage didn't have time to think about all that. They had broken out, but Happy was chasing after them. Su Mucheng's Launcher and Ye Xiu's unspecialized had extremely long-ranged attacks. The Qi Master's Cloud Grasping Fist and the Ghostblade's ghost boundaries could force them to stay if they weren't careful.

The battle wasn't over yet. It was just a new situation laid out in front of them now.

Chapter 1159: What Shouldn't Be Here

By getting out of Happy's pincer attack, Hundred Blossoms had escaped from their biggest crisis. Even though they were running away, they weren't rushed or muddled, and their speed wasn't that fast either. They had no intentions of completely shrugging off Happy.

Team Hundred Blossoms clearly had a plan in mind.

In their team's class composition, Yu Feng's Berserker and Zhou Guangyi's Assassin were close-ranged combatants. As for Happy? Their unspecialized, Launcher, and Qi Master had mid-ranged and long-ranged capabilities. Ghostblades had a slightly shorter range, but Ghostblades still had superior range compared to Berserkers and Assassins. Ghost boundaries could be placed up to 13 units away.

If Hundred Blossoms insisted on breaking away from Happy, they would suffer quite a few losses even if they succeeded. After breaking away, if Yu Feng and Zhou Guangyi wanted to go on the offensive, breaking through the enemy side's long-ranged blockade would be an issue.

However, since they had just gotten out of the pincer, the distance between the two sides wasn't too far, so their Berserker and Assassin could quickly become threats if needed.

Team Hundred Blossoms looked to be running away, but in actuality, they were waiting.

They were adjusting their formation and waiting for an opportunity to counterattack.

Everyone was focused, waiting for that moment to appear.

It's here!

With a glance at their surroundings, everyone in Hundred Blossoms immediately became understood that their opportunity had arrived.

"Turn!" Yu Feng didn't miss this timing and gave out an order in the chat. Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms was the first to turn. His gunfire poured down onto Happy. Mo Chuchen's Cleric, Arrogant Flowers, rolled behind an enormous rock to the side and readied himself to provide healing and support to his team. Zhu Xiaoping's Wind Carving stood behind Bright Blossoms. He summoned an Undead Knight as a shield for them and followed with a Demon World Flower.

Yu Feng and Zhou Guangyi, the two close-combat classes, needed to utilize the cover from their allies to enter the enemy ranks.

Blossoming Chaos and Cold Seasons, one on the left, the other on the right, a Triple Slash, a Shining Cut, to rapidly dash forward. However, they were met with two rays of light. One from a Launcher's Laser Beam, the other from a Qi Master's Sky-Piercing Strike, one on the left, the other on the right, to welcome these two.

The two were startled. Triple Slash could at least switch directions. Blossoming Chaos immediately slashed again to the side, letting him just narrowly dodge the Laser Beam. Cold Seasons, on the other hand, was out of luck. Shining Cut could not turn midway through. Forcefully cancelling it and then moving wasn't as fast as Triple Slash, which let the user turn as a built-in ability. Sky-Piercing Strike connected squarely with Cold Seasons, creating a huge qi wave. Shining Cut didn't need to be forcefully cancelled as it was interrupted. Cold Seasons was thrown into the Broken River. There was no way to Quick Recover on the water, so Cold Seasons dropped in with a splash.

Bright Blossom's attacks failed to make enough of a disturbance?

Lord Grim's huge umbrella, which was far larger than a normal shield, gave them their answer. It didn't need to be open for long. It just needed to shield at the crucial moment to allow Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea to get their skills off in time.　

Everyone in Hundred Blossoms was depressed.

Using a shield to provide cover? It was such an ordinary tactic, but unfortunately, they neglected it because the other team didn't have a Knight. Even though they had studied Lord Grim's unspecialized, without practical experience fighting against him, it was hard to fully bring what was in their mind into reality. In that quick change of pace, they had overlooked this point. But by the time they realized it, the error had been made. Bright Blossom's attacks were ineffective, thus, the assault by Yu Feng and Zhou Guangyi was completely countered.

Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons was thrown into the river, and so there was no need to talk about the completeness of Hundred Blossom's offensive right now. Zhu Xiaoping immediately had his Undead Knight push forward to be a shield for them, when everyone suddenly noticed something from the corner of their eyes. They took a glance and saw a Satellite Beam descending from the sky, directly towards Arrogant Flower, who was hiding behind a rock. Arrogant Flower staggered out; half of his body had been burnt black.

A mess! It's a complete mess!　

They hadn't noticed Dancing Rain's attack at all. Lord Grim's umbrella was just that big. It had completely blocked their line of sight towards Dancing Rain.　　

Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash also leaped out at this moment. A ghostly light dropped from the tip of his sword, and an Ice Boundary formed. The edge of it just happened to sweep past the Demon World Flower. The Demon World Flower was incapable of moving, so it could only take on the persistent damage from Ice Boundary. Not long afterwards, it was frozen into an ice cube. Suddenly, Lord Grim charged out! In the previous second, he had been holding his shield up. In the next second, he became a close-combat attacker that Happy didn't originally have.

Dragon Tooth, Falling Flower Palm!

The Battle Mage two-hit combo landed on the Undead Knight. The Undead Knight was naturally hardy though. A Dragon Breaks the Ranks only made it slide back. The stun and knockback effect from these two low-level skills were simply unable to move it. However, Lord Grim closed in another step and wrapped his arms around it, lifting the heavy Undead Knight into the air.

There were situations where a Grappler's grab failed, but the Undead Knight was not one of them. With a Back Throw, the Undead Knight slammed into the ground. The instant that heavy body hit the ground, a loud sound boomed. The resulting shockwave was twice as large as a normal target, and it just happened to reach the frozen Demon World Flower, instantly shattering it.

Lord Grim charged forward again. Yu Feng's Blossoming Chaos moved forward to block him, but Dancing Rain's support immediately arrived. After Ye Xiu changed classes, the synergy between the Best Partners hadn't lessened. Yu Feng also had teammates, but the level of coordination between them couldn't compared to that between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. When they tried to help, it felt like they couldn't keep up with the pace.

I can't rely on other people helping. I'm the core of the team!

Yu Feng was unwilling to back down. Blossoming Chaos's two eyes suddenly turned scarlet-red. Despite being under the enemy's suppression, he activated Berserk to forcefully make a counterattack!

Soul-Devouring Crimson Grip!

After activating Berserk, Blossoming Chaos's speed increased dramatically. His left hand grabbed towards Lord Grim. But as soon as his hand touched, Lord Grim was unable to endure this grab and poofed into smoke.　

Shadow Clone Technique?!

Even though Shadow Clone Technique was a low-level skill and had a quick hand seal, a hand seal still had to be formed. When did Ye Xiu form it? Yu Feng discovered that he didn't know.　　

Where did Lord Grim go?

Yu Feng immediately had Blossoming Chaos turn around. He saw Lord Grim's true body run towards Wind Carving and use his close-combat capabilities to bully the weak Summoner.　　

Blossoming Chaos immediately raised his sword and was about to rush over, when a force suddenly pulled at him from behind. His body involuntarily flew backwards.　

Fuck!

Yu Feng cursed inwardly. At the same time, he saw Ye Xiu's Lord Grim turn around decisively, leaving Bright Blossoms's explosive attacks behind him.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

Yu Feng didn't need to turn around to know that this was Fang Rui's doing.

What just happened?

In the previous second, he was struggling to break the suppression from Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. But by the time he acted, Ye Xiu suddenly switched targets to their Summoner. As a result, Yu Feng reacted instantly by chasing after him, but then, Fang Rui sneakily made his move, pulling Hundred Blossoms's core into their ranks.

After being pulled into the enemy ranks, what would the result be? Every pro player knew all too well. They would become the target of their attacks. That was the only possibility.

In front of Boundless Sea, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had stacked up several ghost boundaries, ones that lowered enemy defenses, ones that dealt damage, one that buffed allies. The instant Blossoming Chaos landed, before he could even turn around, Boundless Sea jabbed at him with his finger and then with another finger. It was the Qi Master's Level 75 skill, Pulse Break: Break Intelligence, Break Strength. At the same time, Little Cold Hand's Holy Commandment landed, immersing him inside its light...

That wasn't all. Blossoming Chaos was still inside his Berserk mode. His defenses were already drastically weakened.

The rest of Hundred Blossoms obviously wasn't going to just sit there and watch. Cold Seasons had just gotten out of he water and went to rescue Blossoming Chaos, disregarding everything else. A boom sounded. Zhou Guangyi, who had been solely focused on rescuing, didn't notice Dancing Rain's cannon pointing at him. She predicted his movements and shot a missile towards him. Splash! Cold Seasons fell into the water again.

As for Bright Blossoms's gunfire and Wind Carving's summons, Happy completely ignored them.

Kill!

The debuffs and buffs from the ghost boundaries, the Qi Master's Pulse Break, the Cleric's Holy Commandment, and Blossoming Chaos's own Berserk piled on top of each other. Finally, Happy's frenzy of attacks arrived.　　

Blossoming Chaos, Team Hundred Blossom's core, the former number one Berserker that had become number one again after Yu Feng inherited it, was instantly killed.

Nothing could be worse for Hundred Blossoms than their core character meeting its end and in such a short instant too.

Blossoming Chaos was already gone from the shores of Broken River. For that instant kill, Happy had attacked with everything they had, leaving the ground full of scars.

"Attack!!!" Yu Feng was no longer there. Thus, as the vice-captain, Zou Yuan immediately took lead. He could see that even though Happy's wave of attacks had killed Blossoming Chaos, they had messed up their rhythm to achieve it. Nearly all of them had used high-level skills and were in the middle of their ending animation. It was an opportunity for Hundred Blossoms to stage a counterattack.

After giving out the order, Bright Blossoms stepped forward.

Bang bang bang bang bang....

The noise wasn't from gunfire, but the crisp sounds of ice colliding. Bright Blossoms, WInd Carving, and Arrogant Flower had frozen into ice, immovable blocks of ice.

There was only one skill that had 100% chance of instantly freezing the targets hit.

The Elementalist's Ice Line!

A skill, which wasn't in accordance with the present class compositions, had appeared. It had been cast without any of them knowing either. As a result, as soon as the three moved, they immediately went into contact with Ice Line and instantly became frozen.

Chapter 1160: The Rushing Broken River

The Elementalist's skill Ice Line suddenly appeared at this moment.

Should this come as a surprise? The situation was too complicated to say for sure.

This was a situation with no Elementalist, yet an Elementalist's skill had appeared, so of course it was a surprise. But this situation included the unspecialized Lord Grim, so perhaps it shouldn't be surprising. But the unspecialized was only supposed to have access to low-level skills available before choosing a class, and Ice Line was not such a skill, so this was surprising. But Lord Grim had used Cloud Grasping Fist with his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella before, so everyone was aware that the unspecialized could access higher-level skills through his weapon.

Especially after the Cloud Grasping Fist, the unspecialized Lord Grim had already displayed countless high-level skills with the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and now, he used an Elementalist's Ice Line. This caused everyone to realize a frightening reality.

Ordinary weapons could only have one skill applied to them. But because the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could change between a variety of different forms, each form could have a different skill applied to it according to the class. It was known that applying a skill to a weapon was not a complicated process. The materials and skillbooks required, compared to rare materials, weren't too difficult to obtain. So the skills applied to the weapons held by professional accounts were changed regularly. Depending on the opponent, they would often choose a skill that they felt was the most useful to apply to their weapon and use it for the next battle.

One weapon, one type of change.

But the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella...

No one wanted to think about it anymore. It was a headache.

Hundred Blossoms couldn't think about such long-term headaches right now, because they were the victims of this change right now. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had the Ice Line skill? It hadn't been mentioned in the match data they had studied beforehand. Even though this general possibility had been proposed, and in theory Hundred Blossoms had been prepared for it, it had really just been an idea tossed around. The idea meant that Lord Grim could use every single ability in Glory. 24 classes, hundreds of skills. Even if just talking about aerial skills, they all had their own characteristics and uses. Now that they were talking about every single skill in existence, there was absolutely no way to defend against that.

Even more devastating was the fact that Ye Xiu used his skills so stealthily. Hundred Blossoms had no idea when he had laid down this Ice Line. They discovered it when they triggered it, and by then there was no escape for them.

Lord Grim had access to higher level skills through his weapon. Because he could only add one level, the power wouldn't be that strong. His Ice Line couldn't last for long, but it was enough. Happy only needed to withdraw their attacks and adjust, how long would that take?

The fact that he would lay down this Ice Line meant that they were already prepared for the next stage of attack.

Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons once again scrambled onto the shore from the rapidly flowing river, and all he saw was wave after wave of devastating attack, flashing so much that he almost couldn't look directly at his screen. His teammates had already been swallowed by these countless flashes, and he couldn't even find their positions. All he could see were the health bars of his three teammates rapidly plummeting.

Under the overwhelming barrage of attacks, a Cleric simply had no way of casting. Healing skills that had no cast time could be used in emergencies to save the situation, but in an emergency like this where there was no way of escaping from the situation, a few instant casts wouldn't help much.

Zhou Guangyi was their last hope, and he himself was clear on this point. He didn't shrink back, nor did he recklessly charge ahead. He controlled Cold Seasons to quickly follow the shoreline so he could get a better view of the situation. Finally, he saw the Happy trio that was blasting attacks at the Hundred Blossoms players.

Dancing Rain, Boundless Sea, One Inch Ash.

No time to hesitate, charge!

Cold Seasons flashed ahead, and Dancing Rain suddenly turned her cannon.

Boom!

The cannon blast flew toward him.

Zhou Guangyi, who had already been blasted into the river twice now, was now fiercely on the defensive. In the same instant that the cannon moved, he was already twisting aside to nimbly avoid it. Since he didn't have the support of any teammates right now, he didn't use Shining Cut, which was a skill that once used was hard to retract. It would be impossible to use this skill to directly break through the defense of so many enemies.

Dancing Rain's cannon shot missed, but she swung out a Gatling Gun, and bullets began flying everywhere.

Zhou Guangyi activated Swift Movements, then used Swift Run, and Cold Seasons' movement speed reached its peak. His dodging amidst the rain of bullets could truly be called elegant, a beautiful solo maneuver, and he finally arrived near the three players.

Cold Flash!

At this distance, Zhou Guangyi finally acted without hesitation. He was confident that no other skill was faster than him. One Inch Ash lifted his blade, the power of ghosts coalescing, as though to meet him with a Ghost Slash.

But, was he fast enough?

The cold light fell, and as expected, One Inch Ash's Ghost Slash wasn't fast enough. A string of blood droplets flew out in front of his chest, and he staggered backwards. Zhou Guangyi didn't rush to kill him, since Boundless Sea was still blasting his teammates. His priority was to rescue his teammates, because by himself, he couldn't take on all of these opponents. His use was to interrupt their rhythm.

Cold Seasons swiftly turned and came at Boundless Sea with a Heart-Piercing Stab. But his own body suddenly flew up. Zhou Guangyi turned his camera frantically only to see Lord Grim lifting high his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in spear form, sending him flying with a Circle Swing.

Where in the world did this guy come from?

Zhou Guangyi's depression was incomparable.

He really wasn't unfamiliar with Ye Xiu at all. Even though he wasn't a player of that era, he had come from Tyranny. Which team could beat Tyranny at understanding Ye Xiu?

But Zhou Guangyi discovered that he truly had no way of predicting the Ye Xiu before him now, the Ye Xiu using Lord Grim.

Cold Seasons was sent rolling on the ground, but the effects of his sudden appearance and interruption were clear to see. From Su Mucheng to Qiao Yifan then to Ye Xiu, Happy needed three players to take action to control him. Any attacks toward Cold Seasons were attacks that didn't go toward the trio from Hundred Blossoms, and Zou Yuan seized this opportunity to use one of the Spitfire's high-level skills, Chaotic Thunder.

Aside from this official name, this skill had a nickname, Goddess Scattering Flowers. Bright Blossoms reached into the pockets at his hips, withdrawing countless grenades between his fingertips as though they were flower petals, and sent them flying with a shake of his wrists.

These grenades were varied and complicated. Some were ordinary ones that exploded upon impact, some were powerful bursts, some exploded after a set countdown, some released poisonous gas, and so on and so forth. In essence, it was all of the different types of Spitfire grenades combined into one attack, and now, they were all hurled toward Happy's players.

Too many grenades were released at once to determine which type each of them were. Happy didn't dare to just take the damage, since many Spitfire grenades had effects aside from just pure damage. Take the Burst Grenade, for example: although its damage wasn't high, the impact was so powerful that even Super Armor couldn't stop it. No matter what status someone was in, if hit by the Burst Grenade, their position would be instantly scattered.

The best defense was a good attack. Happy's players all dodged in different directions, and the place where they had been standing was blasted apart. Fire, smoke, poison gas, powerful blasts, they were scattered all around.

Happy hadn't dodged enough. Because Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had been standing at the core, he was hit by the poison gas and became Poisoned, and his health began to drop by the second.

And Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain, while using Aerial Gun to escape, was hit by the blast of a Burst Grenade, sending her even farther away.

Hundred Blossoms instantly seized this opportunity. Mo Chuchen's Cleric found cover and hurriedly began casting Heals, Zhu Xiaoping's Summoner quickly called several summons as support. Bright Blossoms, who had orchestrated this stunning reversal for Hundred Blossoms, was already reaching for more grenades, and he dominated the scene with all the atmosphere of a core player. But after quickly scanning his surroundings, he suddenly realized: Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, and also Cold Seasons, where did they go?

"Underwater!" Zhou Guangyi realized that his teammates might have lost him, and rushed to send this message in the team chat.

In the midst of the chaos, he hadn't expected that Fang Rui, while dodging, had still remembered him. Boundless Sea, with Qi Flowing Cloud activated, had brushed by, specially coming by to pat him. Zhou Guangyi had tried to dodge, but he hadn't dodged enough, his shoulder was hit, and that one pat had turned out to be a powerful Qigong Blast. In an instant, Cold Seasons was sent into the air.

He had no tears left as he looked at the Broken River below him. Zhou Guangyi prepared to use Air Jump to return to shore, but Lord Grim suddenly appeared above him. With an Eagle Stamp and then a Falling Light Blade, Cold Seasons was directly shoved into the water again. And then Fang Rui, that guy, he had controlled Boundless Sea to enter the water as well! In that 2v1, Cold Seasons was miserably beaten up underwater.

When the Hundred Blossoms players saw the message, they all rushed to the riverside. But the river was rushing fiercely. The three were fighting underwater, but from the surface, nothing unusual could be seen.

"Where!" Zou Yuan sent to the chat, worried.

It was clear that Zhou Guangyi wouldn't have reported his position if he weren't in need of immediate support.

"Washed away" What a short message! There wasn't even any punctuation.

Zou Yuan and the others grew worried. If you were washed away by the Broken River all the way until the end, you'd be washed out of the map and directly eliminated. Zhou Guangyi's desperate message showed that he was currently in a bad situation right now. Right now, they could see that Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, and An Wenyi's characters were all here, but Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were still missing. Were they in the water fighting Zhou Guangyi?

Zou Yuan and the others were in a dilemma! If they went to save Zhou Guangyi, it would be hard to get rid of the three in front of them. If they didn't save him, there was nothing but disaster waiting for Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons. But as they struggled with their options, a silhouette flashed out of the stone forest, riding a broom. He directly flew to the surface of the river, and went under with a splash.

Zhang Wei!

Hundred Blossoms' sixth person, entered the battle from the stone forest. After seeing the message in the chat, he directly rushed to the riverside and entered the water. Finally, Zou Yuan and the others saw that they had support. Now, they could relax and deal with Happy's three in front of them, and at the same time think about how they could regroup with the others.

With Zhang Wei, it would now be a 2v2… But Happy's side had Ye Xiu and Fang Rui. Even though they didn't want the opponent's mere presence to smother their own spirits, they couldn't help but feel uneasy. Better to quickly confirm their status to reassure themselves...

Chapter 1161: River’s End

The water in Broken River rushed rapidly. If a character stopped moving in the middle of the water, they would certainly be swept away. Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons was forced into the water by Lord Grim's slash. His first priority at this moment was figuring out how to escape Ye Xiu and Fang Rui. Fighting against the water's flow could come later.

Once they entered the water, Lord Grim and Boundless Sea hadn't stopped attacking, and the two characters had taken control of all the advantageous positions.

What were the advantageous positions? In the midst of the rushing water, upstream positions were advantageous. Attacks that followed the flow wouldn't be as impeded by the water, and these attacks would in fact travel faster than normal. With how swiftly the Broken River flowed, the effect of the additional speed was quite significant.

At first, Zhou Guangyi was worried about these two forcing him to the end of the river and out of the map, but a few moments later he realized he was overthinking. If the current situation continued, he would be a dead body long before he reached the river's end.

Knowing that he was in a difficult situation, Zhou Guangyi finally sought help. Not long afterwards, he heard the splash of someone entering the water. His heart sped up, and he thought, this must be the backup arriving to help. And this splash had come from upstream, meaning that this person had seized a position advantageous to those of both Lord Grim and Boundless Sea. He could use the flow of the water as a buff to increase speed.

As expected of an experienced veteran like Zhang Wei, when he arrived at the riverside, he didn't enter the water immediately. He had followed alongside it for a while, carefully studying until he confirmed everyone's position. Only then did he choose the most favorable position to enter the water.

Once he came down, Zhang Wei's Witch Endless Forest began attacking. With a Broom Tornado he twisted downstream, arriving right in front of the two and battering them. Ye Xiu and Fang Rui would have wanted to dodge to the side and let him sweep past, but if they dodged, they would be letting Cold Seasons go free.

But would Ye Xiu and Fang Rui be beaten up that easily?

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim flashed to the side, making way for Endless Forest, but then he swept his sleeve, sending a Night Cloak toward Endless Forest and Cold Seasons.

Zhang Wei himself was a Witch. If he were taken down by his own class's skill, that would just be too embarrassing. He watched the attack coming, and Endless Forest waved his broom in a knocking motion.

In the air, a Witch could use their broom to jump six times. Now in the water, Broom Mastery also helped movement. With this knock, Endless Forest suddenly sank toward the bottom of the river, and the Night Cloak swept through empty water. Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons now had more space than Endless Forest. Borrowing the flow of the water to help his movements, he was also able to sink down and dodge this attack.

Endless Forest, who had sunk lower, now waved his broom again to propel himself upward toward Lord Grim. And Lord Grim waved his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, turning it into a spear and casually parrying his attack. To the side, Boundless Sea's hands were moving, water rippling between them, and he suddenly thrust downward. The qi swirled in the water, its trajectory clear, and Endless Forest immediately swept his broom again to dodge.

Happy's two players were toying with Endless Forest. It was now as though they had completely forgotten about Cold Seasons.

Zhou Guangyi was once again depressed.

When he had dodged downward earlier, he had also had some plan in mind. He thought that by sinking down, Happy's two would follow him. Zhang Wei's Endless Forest would only need to wait for a moment in the lower position before immediately being able to seize the upstream position.

But who would have thought? As soon as he swam aside, those two didn't even look at him, instead starting to fight Endless Forest.

Cold Seasons had escaped. But Zhou Guangyi couldn't just stand by and watch Zhang Wei be beaten down! His earlier little plan was too straightforward, in front of these two it was far from enough!

Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons obediently came back to attack. But Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, in this short moment of 2v1, had managed to once again seize the upstream position. When Cold Seasons returned, he was downstream with Zhang Wei's Endless Forest.

Their position was downstream, their situation was also downstream...

On the riverbank, Zou Yuan and the others were worried about Zhang Wei and Zhou Guangyi as they fought Happy. Wind Carving's summons legion had taken up the task of blocking the opponents, but in the face of the long-range firepower of the Launcher, the typical summon was already essentially dead by the time it reached close-range. The Undead Knight was a little stronger, but because it was so slow and couldn't coordinate with anything else to block the opponent, it could easily be avoided and wasn't much use.

Watching his summons being summoned and then blasted to death, Zhu Xiaoping felt his heart hurt. The death of a summon didn't hurt Wind Carving's health, but every summon used up mana. So in every battle, every summon had to be carefully calculated so that it served a useful purpose. It was like how other classes had to use their mana-consuming skills carefully, to cause damage, or disrupt rhythm, or thwart a target. No matter what it was, it had to serve a purpose.

And now, although Wind Carving's summons served the purpose of protecting them, they were used up rather too quickly. Zhu Xiaoping, judging from past battle experience, could tell that his usage pacing this match was a little too fast.

They couldn't continue like this, or else he would run out of mana, and Wind Carving would become a useless person on the battlefield.

"You guys go first, I'll cover you!" Thus, Zhu Xiaoping resolutely sent this to the team chat.

He had decided. He needed to spread out their formation and thoroughly tend to these three from Happy. He was a Summoner, so he could call forth many dear helpers; he should have this ability. To just avoid them and let his summons act as cannon fodder didn't seem wise. Zhu Xiaoping even felt that, judging from Dancing Rain's attack rhythm, the opponent was purposefully trying to waste all his summons.

"Alright!" Zou Yuan and Mo Chuchen didn't doubt him. A Summoner had the ability to take on two or even three people at once, because he was never fighting by himself.

Directly facing against his opponents, Zhu Xiaoping could carefully control all of his summons, and they wouldn't be defeated so easily by his opponents. He summoned an Undead Knight, who lifted his shield, and Wind Carving himself closely followed along behind. This time, he wouldn't summon from afar. He wanted to directly control his summons, so under the protection of Undead Knight, he would approach closer to his opponents before calling forth a summons legion.

Of course, the Undead Knight moved rather slowly, and it would be easy enough for the opponent to maintain distance. But even if that happened, Zhu Xiaoping would complete his mission of obstruction. At most he would be sacrificing one Undead Knight, a far cheaper price than all the summons he had lost earlier one after the other.

Boom boom!

Cannon fire exploded relentlessly upon the Undead Knight's shield. Although the Undead Knight wobbled, his steps were still resolute. As Zhu Xiaoping predicted, the opponent wouldn't split apart just to kite Undead Knight. They didn't slow down as they ran forward. But this time, now that he himself was here, there was no way he was letting them go around him.

One Inch Ash waved his sword, and a ghostly aura flickered along the length of his blade.

Was he about to lay down a Ghost Boundary?

Zhu Xiaoping saw clearly and summoned a Phantom Cat not far from where One Inch Ash was. Under the protection of the Undead Knight, Zhu Xiaoping wasn't afraid of being interrupted.

The summoned Phantom Cat immediately rushed toward One Inch Ash. Whether he was hit by an attack or tried to dodge, the casting of the Ghost Boundary would be interrupted. Dancing Rain went to attack the Phantom Cat, meaning that the attacks on this side lightened, and they could rush forward with their momentum.

Controlling the summons truly made a difference!

Zhu Xiaoping was extremely satisfied with his condition. He really felt pretty good today! How was he defeated by a rookie in the group arena? He didn't understand… Or maybe, today was that pretty girl's lucky day! Even Yu Feng had lost in a direct fight against her. Now that he thought about it, that pretty girl was Happy's sixth player right now. What would happen if she came out to battle?

.

Zhu Xiaoping felt that he had good control over the situation. Things were progressing as expected, and he even had the time to ponder other things. Phantom Cat's fast harassment prevented One Inch Ash from laying down a Ghost Boundary. This sort of fast and small close-range attacker wasn't an easy opponent for the Launcher and Ghostblade classes. Zhu Xiaoping seized the chance and controlled Wind Carving to summon more creatures, quickly creating an army. He didn't bother with Demon Flowers or other summons that weren't nimble. These summons would be limited in their usefulness in front of a Launcher and Ghostblade.

Right. Launcher and Ghostblade.

…Huh? Launcher and Ghostblade?

Where'd the other person go? Where was Happy's Cleric?

Zhu Xiaoping suddenly discovered that Happy's Cleric Little Cold Hands was nowhere to be found. Wind Carving was hidden behind the Undead Knight this whole time, so even though he paid close attention to the situation at hand, his vision was limited. It wasn't until now that his army was formed that Wind Carving majestically walked forward, only to discover that one of his opponents was missing.

"The opponent's Cleric escaped!" Zhu Xiaoping immediately warned the others in the team chat.

"Escaped" was really giving himself a lot of credit. In reality, he was just trying to cause a disruption, not trap them entirely.

Attack!

As Zhu Xiaoping directed his summons forward, he studied his surroundings, trying to find Little Cold Hands. And then, he found an entrance to the stone forest nearby. Had Little Cold Hands entered there?

If he entered there… Zhu Xiaoping's mind spun. This was a map that everyone knew, and as a pro player, he could clearly visualize it in his mind.

If he entered there…

He would pass the spawn point!

The spawn point, or in other words, the support zone. In Happy's limited match data, they had used this strategy before, letting their healer exit the battle, replacing him with an attacker.

And the attacker that Happy could use as replacement was someone that no one, certainly not Hundred Blossoms, would dare underestimate anymore.

All this flashed through Zhu Xiaoping's mind, and he frantically sent another message. "Healer went to player exchange area, Soft Mist might enter battle!"

"Soft Mist entering battle? Right now? To do what?" Seeing Zhu Xiaoping's message, the Hundred Blossoms players weren't as alarmed as he was. They even sent this message to the public chat as mockery.

Zou Yuan and Mo Chuchen had finally arrived, easily helping Zhang Wei and Zhou Guangyi to escape their predicament. Now that they had turned the situation around, they were prepared to bully Happy.

"To come fight, of course," Ye Xiu replied in the chat. "What use is a healer here?"

Behind Lord Grim, the riverbanks were blocked by insurmountable walls, and the Broken River became a waterfall plunging downward. Looking through this gap, one could see a beautiful expanse of scenery. But it was no use, for right here was the end of this world…

Chapter 1162: Specious Memories

The expressions on the Hundred Blossoms players became strained at Ye Xiu's words. Their characters in the game couldn't show this though. Their four characters stood in a very standard offensive formation. Zhang Wei's Witch Endless Forest and Zhou Guangyi's Assassin Cold Seasons stood at the front. Zou Yuan's Spitfire Bright Blossoms was positioned behind them in the middle. Mo Chuchen's Cleric Arrogant Flowers was to the right of Bright Blossoms.

They seemed to just be standing where they pleased, but in reality, the distance between each team member, the view that each team member had of the field, and the vigilance towards their opponents were all strategically arranged. The possible variations and tactical thinking inside this formation couldn't be explained in just a few words.

But after hearing Ye Xiu's words, the four players couldn't help but make a few adjustments.

Their previous formation had been a practiced one that they had instinctively arranged themselves in after seeing Lord Grim's and Boundless Sea's positions. However, they suddenly realized that the end of Broken River, the edge of this map, was an instant death spot that needed careful consideration before entering.

　

There used to be all sorts of strategies on how to play around the end of Broken River. However, this map had been played on so many times, and it had been so long since this map had been chosen in competitive play. What team specifically practiced for these strategies nowadays? Perhaps they might have some memory of the strategies involved, but their teammates back then definitely weren't the same today. Different classes meant different ways of coordination. If they tried to play from what they remembered, it was possible that it would conflict with their current team structure.

Thinking of this, the Hundred Blossoms players suddenly realized how terrifying it was for Happy to choose this map.

For familiar maps, coordination and whatnot could be accomplished without much thought.　

However, unfamiliar maps required more carefulness and observation to minimize mistakes.　　

As for Broken River, this map had once been a familiar one, but was now an abandoned one. Everyone had seemingly correct but actually incorrect memories. Were these memories accurate? When victory or defeat depended on these memories, the Hundred Blossoms players were hesitant. Doubt started to wel up within them. They were afraid that those fuzzy memories might lead to a fatal mistake.　　

The Hundred Blossoms players hesitated, and at the same time, they now understood why Happy had chosen this map.

These situations depended on their resolve. And judging from the current situation, they clearly weren't resolute enough. After Ye Xiu spoke those words, Hundred Blossoms kept on adjusting their positions. They were clearly having trouble parsing through their memories.

"At that time, our team still had Sun Zheping and Zhang Jiale!" The old general Zhang Wei recalled Hundred Blossoms' golden age and the scenes of their battles at Broken River.

"At that time, battling alongside our captain was truly fun…" Zhou Guangyi recalled his time with Tyranny and his days fighting with Han Wenqing's Desert Dust. 　　

At that time… Zou Yuan didn't have an at that time. He had joined the league in Season 7. By then, this map had already fallen out of use. He really didn't have any competitive experience with Broken River.

As for Mo Chuchen? Mo Chuchen was also nervous because of Ye Xiu's words. At this spot, if the opponent pushed them off the waterfall, they would instantly die. What would be the point of healing? How was he supposed to help his team?　　

The Hundred Blossoms players each had their own thoughts. For a moment, their positioning became even more disorderly.

How could Ye Xiu or Fang Rui miss this opportunity?

Sky-Piercing Strike!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea leaped up and a powerful wave of qi shot out through his hands towards Hundred Blossoms.　　

The Hundred Blossoms players clearly reacted slowly to this sudden attack. Anyone could see that their priority was distancing themselves from the waterfall.

They only dodged. None of them thought of counterattacking. After Fang Rui's Boundless Sea shot out a Sky-Piercing Strike, he didn't receive any interference, so he swiped his two hands and slashed out a Qi Blade.

This Qi Blade was formed from the Qi Master's breath, so it was without form or light. The only trace of it was the stream of air left behind when it sliced through the air. It was a very concealed flying weapon type skill. Even if the opponent noticed the attack, because of its immaterial form, it was difficult to judge the distance, making defending and dodging more difficult to time. The only way to dodge was to dodge as soon as you noticed it. Safety first.

Zou Yuan saw Boundless Sea swipe his two hands against each other, forming a ripple in the air. He knew it was a Qi Blade, so he immediately had Bright Blossoms dodge to the side. But to his surprise, the trajectory of this ripple wasn't a straight line, but a cunning arc that deviated from Zou Yuan's prediction. In the end, the Qi Blade struck Arrogant Flowers, Team Hundred Blossoms' Cleric.　

Ye Xiu just said that healing in this battle was pointless, yet Fang Rui's attack had been aimed at Hundred Blossoms' healer.

Mo Chuchen was completely caught off guard. The Qi Blade connected squarely with Arrogant Flowers. There was no eye-catching explosion or spurt of blood, but the damage dealt was no worse than those flashy attacks. Plus, it had quite a strong knockback. After taking this hit, Arrogant Flowers immediately stumbled.

As Boundless Sea fell from the skies, he stretched out his hand towards Arrogant Flower and grabbed.

But then a flash of light swept over. Zhou Guangyi's Assassin promptly attacked from the side to cut off Boundless Sea.　　

"Lord Grim!!"　　

The old general Zhang Wei had experienced hundreds of battles. No matter how ferociously Boundless Sea attacked, he would never fail to pay attention to Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. While everyone was focusing on Boundless Sea, Zhang Wei saw Lord Grim lift his two hands and get into a certain position. Wasn't that the Qi Master's Cloud Grasping Fist?

He hastily warned everyone in his channel. Zou Yuan reacted the fastest. Before even understanding what the situation was, Bright Blossoms turned and started firing at Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu had no choice but to cancel his sneak attack and dodge.　　

"Come this way!!" The rescued Mo Chuchen directed his Arrogant Flowers to the stone forest to the side. His thought process was quite simple. Since fighting at the end of Broken River was so confusing, why not just fight further away from it.

"Go." Vice-captain Zou Yuan approved of Mo Chuchen's thinking and ordered the team to shift over there. In truth, Zou Yuan didn't like these sorts of special terrain, but he could see the hesitation from his teammates towards their current battlefield.

Hundred Blossoms had the numbers advantage, 4 to 2, yet they did not confront the other side directly and took the initiative to shift the battlefield away. Arrogant Flowers ran the fastest. The other three also moved towards this direction. Seeing the waterfall leave their sight, their hearts just started to steady when a boom suddenly came from ahead of them. Arrogant Flowers, who had just run into the stone forest excitedly, was directly thrown out.

Soft Mist burst out with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Arrogant Flowers had been sent flying by this attack already, but that didn't seem to stop the dragon's momentum.

Zou Yuan and the two others hastily dodged. Ye Xiu and Fang Rui saw this and immediately became spirited.

"Grab one over!!!" Ye Xiu yelled.

"Okay, which one?" Fang Rui replied.

Hundred Blossoms' four players were greatly alarmed. They thought Cloud Grasping Fist was about to come at them again, so they kept rolling on the ground refusing to get up. But after looking towards that side, they knew that they had been duped. Lord Grim and Boundless Sea were running rapidly towards them, and Cloud Grasping Fist was not a skill that could be used while moving.

Their target was still Team Hundred Blossoms' Cleric, Arrogant Flowers. Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, and Soft Mist had quickly formed a triangle with Arrogant Flowers in the middle.

Counting on a Cleric to break out of an encirclement alone was unfair. Hundred Blossoms' other three players immediately tried to rescue him. Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms shot a Flash Bullet. However, Happy's three players responded by rushing towards the middle. Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up with a whoosh. The Flash Bullet knocked against the umbrella and exploded. However, the three behind the umbrella were unaffected by it and continued to pummel Arrogant Flowers.

Zou Yuan wanted to cry, but no tears came out. If he had known they would do that, he would have thrown a Burst Grenade...　　

There were no ifs, but it wasn't too late now. Zou Yuan threw a Burst Grenade.　

"DON'T!!" Zhang Wei shouted, but he was too late.

The Burst Grenade exploded on the umbrella's canopy. The powerful shockwave sent Happy's three characters flying, but… where was Arrogant Flowers. Teammates were exempt from allied skills, so he should still be there!

"Thanks!" Lord Grim expressed his thanks. Zou Yuan composed himself and then took another look. He had located Arrogant Flowers; he was in Lord Grim's hands.

Zou Yuan's view had been blocked by the umbrella, so he didn't know the situation. However, Zhang Wei, who was at a different angle, could see things. When Zou Yuan threw a Burst Grenade, Lord Grim just happened to grab Arrogant Flowers.　　

Fling!

Grabs had the highest priority out of any skill. Even the shockwave from Burst Grenade failed to interrupt Lord Grim's grab, leading to Arrogant Flowers being pushed out along with Lord Grim.

And Burst Grenade did nothing but send people flying away. The airborne Lord Grim was free to move around. As a result, he continued his combo with a Fling, throwing Arrogant Flower away. Where to? Towards the waterfall of course...

"Ah!" Zou Yuan cried out, but unfortunately, no one could hear him. None of the other three Hundred Blossom players were able to intercept him in time.

"Don't panic! Figure out the direction of the flow and swim back!" At the crucial moment, it was the still the old general Zhang Wei who was the calmest. He deduced that at Lord Grim's height, it was not possible for him to directly throw Arrogant Flowers outside of the waterfall. Arrogant Flower would fall into the water, but as long as he figured out the direction of the flow fast enough, he wouldn't be pulled down the waterfall. However, he needed to be fast because it had to be done in an instant.

Calm down!

Mo Chuchen nervously reminded himself. He could see the surface of the river and the scenery outside the map, which looked quite beautiful.

I can't go there!

Mo Chuchen encouraged himself, boosting his confidence. He was ready to drop into the water.　　

Bang!

What was that? That wasn't the sound of a splash? Where am I?　

His screen violently shook. By the time Mo Chuchen finished adjusting himself, he realized that the Broken River was far away. Arrogant Flower was already heading down towards that beautiful world on the other side...

Chapter 1163: Get Out!

How could this be?

Mo Chuchen still didn't understand, but Arrogant Flowers' name was already gray in the team list.　　

"Nice snipe."

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea said in the public chat.　　

"I can't stay rusty forever :)" Ye Xiu replied with a smiley face.

Just before Arrogant Flowers would have fallen into the water, Mo Chuchen had been prepared to swim against the current. At that moment, a bullet fired from the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, sniping Arrogant Flowers and sending him off the map to his death.　

What was the point of a healer here?　　

Ye Xiu's words hadn't disappeared yet and could still be seen in the public chat! Yet in the blink of an eye, the player he killed happened to be this "useless" healer.

Perhaps a healer was useless here, but what about elsewhere? The healer's value would be very high. However, Hundred Blossoms no longer had the chance to experience the value of having a healer.

Right now, Hundred Blossoms hadn't dealt any major damage to the enemy team nor were they in an advantageous position, yet they had already lost their core player and their important healer. Hundred Blossoms' current situation was extremely bad. In a normal match, teams in this situation might just directly call GG and forfeit the match.　

However, Hundred Blossoms didn't want to forfeit.

They had already lost quite terribly in the individual competition and the group arena. Right now, they only had a single point. Typing "GG" and losing would be disastrous.

If the enemy team can use this instant kill zone, so can we!

We have no healer, but the enemy team doesn't either!

In terms of numbers, both sides each have three players. Neither side has the advantage!

Zou Yuan, Zhou Guangyi, Zhang Wei. The three Hundred Blossoms players would no longer retreat. Without a healer, playing tug of war with Happy was not wise. Right now, they needed this instant kill zone more than Happy. They needed to instantly kill these Happy characters to come back from this terrible situation.　　

"Attack!

Zou Yuan ordered in the team chat. The three Hundred Blossom players sprinted forward.　　

The Burst Grenade explosion, Lord Grim grabbing, flinging, sniping Arrogant Flowers off the map had all happened in an instant. The three Hundred Blossoms players also instantly examined the situation and made a clear decision. While the three Happy players were still steadying themselves, they immediately pounced on them and attacked. Their target was the character closest to the waterfall, Lord Grim.

Broom Tornado!

Zhang Wei liked to use this Witch skill. This time, Endless Forest flew into the air. As his broom spun, he shot towards Lord Grim like a tornado.

Below, Zhou Guangyi's Assassin was using Shining Cut to move. However, this time, he wasn't using it to attack, but to coordinate with Zhang Wei and restrict Lord Grim's movement options. Along with Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms firing non-stop, they forced Lord Grim towards the waterfall.

"You guys learn fast!"

Ye Xiu still had time to type a few words. It seemed like he wasn't worried about his current situation. And just like this, Lord Grim confidently ran towards the waterfall as if to satisfy Hundred Blossoms' desires.

If only we had a Burst Grenade right now!

Zou Yuan looked at Burst Grenade's cooldown and felt annoyed. If he had a Burst Grenade, the shockwave would be more than enough to send Lord Grim off the stage. How convenient would that be?

But right now?

What do I do now?　　

Zou Yuan quickly thought about this question and realized that it wasn't easy for the three to do something. While Lord Grim could just grab Arrogant Flowers and throw him, the three of them didn't have that type of skill.

This situation gave Zou Yuan a greater understanding of why Happy chose Broken River. It seemed like a map that everyone knew, but in reality, because of each team's class composition, it was unfavorable for Hundred Blossoms. In addition, Team Hundred Blossoms only had fuzzy memories of how to play on this map. The impact of this fuzziness could now be deeply felt.

This was a map that fully utilized Happy's home field advantage!

After seeing Lord Grim confidently retreat towards the waterfall on his own accord, Zou Yuan smelled a a scheme. Happy had come to this map prepared. They had definitely practiced tactics revolving around this special terrain.　　

What is it?

Zou Yuan watched Lord Grim's movements closely, while constantly taking note of Boundless Sea and Soft Mist.

Those two were on their way back after being blown away by Burst Grenade.

What are they going to do?

Zou Yuan truly didn't have any idea. Truthfully, he didn't have any experience with this map.　　

"Careful." Zou Yuan could only remind his two teammates.　　

Zhang Wei wasn't a particularly talented player. However, having been a pro player for so long, he was well-practiced. In this instant, he also felt like there was some deeper meaning behind Lord Grim's calm retreat. He pondering over what it could be, when he saw Zou Yuan's warning in the chat.

Zhang Wei was greatly alarmed. Had something happened already?

He looked around in a panic and swept over the three Happy characters one by one, but he didn't discover anything unusual. He woke up immediately afterwards. The warning had been because Zou Yuan felt like there was something fishy about Lord Grim.

A communication error between teammates wasn't good. Zhang Wei realized that his condition was off. However, he was powerless to fix it. Without having a clear understanding of why they were at a disadvantage, they couldn't help but hesitate.　　

In any case, we have to try!

In the end, Zhang Wei made his decision. They were already at a disadvantage. In this sort of situation, if they didn't struggle and gamble, how could they win?

"Forward!" Zhang Wei feared that the other two would fail to coordinate properly because of the hesitation in their hearts, so he let everyone know before acting.

"Forward!" Zou Yuan knew that they could not drag this on. After replying to Zhang Wei, his Bright Blossoms threw a grenade.

Seeker Grenade!

This grenade came with its own propeller like a mini-helicopter. After it flew out, it locked onto Lord Grim and flew towards him.

Boom!!

Lord Grim held up his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and shot down this Seeker Grenade in mid-air.　　

But this was just the start of Bright Blossom's assault. Another two grenades were thrown, normal ones that could also be used by an unspecialized. Lord Grim jumped backwards to dodge them, but another grenade followed closely behind. Lord Grim once again opened up his umbrella and also wanted to shoot down this grenade. To his surprise, that grenade had yet to reach him, when it suddenly exploded.

Timed Grenade!

Ye Xiu immediately recognized it as a time grenade. To put it simply, it was a time bomb. The timer could be set as long as 8 seconds, but the one Bright Blossoms threw was at most set to 2 seconds. Zou Yuan linked it together with his other grenade and had it explode before Lord Grim could respond.

But at such a distance, let alone damage, Lord Grim wasn't even affected by the shockwave from the explosion. However, the smoke produced from the explosion temporarily blocked his sight.

Ye Xiu immediately had Lord Grim roll. Sure enough, a Magic Ray pierced through the smoke, but it missed because Lord Grim had preemptively dodged it.

"This old fox…" Zhang Wei was helpless. He was already one of the oldest players in the Alliance, but his opponent was even more senior than him. There was probably nothing Ye Xiu had never seen before. It just depended on whether he could react in time.

Unfortunately, their coordinated attack wasn't effective. Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons had originally been lying in wait for an opening, but Ye Xiu wasn't their only opponent. Fang Rui and Tang Rou promptly joined the battle. Cold Seasons wasn't able to act in time before the two interfered.

Zhou Guangyi could defend against Tang Rou's Soft Mist wild frontal assault, but the problem was that the cunning Fang Rui was lying on the sidelines. It was truly unbearable.

Zou Yuan and Zhang Wei saw this situation and knew that it would be bad if they didn't help. Zhang Wei's Endless Forest threw a Lava Flask over to that side. Zou Yuan had Bright Blossoms turn around and fire a few bullets, but most of his attention was still on Lord Grim.　

He's coming!

Seeing Lord Grim stop retreating towards the waterfall and instead charge at them, Zou Yuan didn't panic and started eagerly looking forward to it. Bright Blossoms held a tiny remote control in his left hand. Previously, he had thrown not three but four grenades. A Remote Control Grenade was three units away from Lord Grim right now. One step, two steps...

Boom!

The Remote Control Grenade exploded. The shockwave sent Lord Grim flying back. Zou Yuan felt a surge of excitement in his heart. Zhang Wei also noticed it and knew that this was a rare opportunity. In this instant, he and Zou Yuan displayed a high-level of tacit understanding. Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms turned towards Soft Mist and Boundless Sea, helping Cold Seasons ward them off. Zhang Wei's Endless Forest, on the other hand, rode on his broom and chased after Lord Grim.

The Remote Control Grenade's power wasn't that high. The knockback wasn't enough to knock Lord Grim off the waterfall. What's more, Lord Grim could use skills to prevent that.

Broom Tornado!　　

Endless Forest flew into the air and immediately came down like a tornado. He aimed precisely. At this angle, he could send Lord Grim towards the very edge of the map while retreating with a jump backwards.　　

"It's been so many years and you're still doing the same trick!"

A message from Ye Xiu popped into the chat. Zhang Wei suddenly felt that the situation wasn't good. However, the Broom Tornado had already been activated. Lord Grim's umbrella was faster though...

Circle Swing!

Endless Forest was knocked into the air. His Broom Tornado had been broken, and Zhang Wei was helpless. This was the difference between them. He was just an experienced veteran, but Ye Xiu? He was one of the players who stood at the top of Glory. If Broom Tornado was done correctly, it could completely avoid this type of interrupt. Over Zhang Wei's professional career, he had always favored this skill, but in the end, it was still blocked by Ye Xiu.

The umbrella drew a circle in the air. The one thrown out of the map wasn't Lord Grim but Endless Forest. However, Endless Forest was a Witch. With the skill Broom Mastery, he had plenty of room to maneuver. This was why Zhang Wei, although feeling helpless, was not yet panicked. But who would have thought, when the Circle Swing finished, Endless Sea hadn't even had the chance to move yet before the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella retracted and shifted from spear to gun form.

Bang bang bang!

Three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded onto Endless Forest, pushing him far out. And then, the shockwaves from the explosions pushed him even farther along.

"FUCK!" Seeing the distance between the inside of the map and his position outside of the map, Zhang Wei lost all hope. Witches could somewhat fly in the air, but it was impossible at this distance!

Team Hundred Blossoms' Witch, Endless Forest, killed!

Chapter 1164: The Strongest New Team in History

They had waited with high hopes for the chance to push Lord Grim off the map, but all that happened was that their own side lost another powerful general. Zou Yuan and Zhou Guangyi were agonized. It wasn't even one defeat, it was a combo. Just after Endless Forest's icon grayed out, Zhu Xiaoping's Summoner Wind Carving fell as well.

For one person to last this long against Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan was quite a feat; Zhu Xiaoping already proved himself a worthy Summoner. But he didn't have the ability to both stall and defeat two players at once. In all of Glory's history, there had never been such a powerful Summoner before.

In the team competition, Happy's roster was still whole and perfect, while Hundred Blossoms had already lost four players.

At this moment, Zou Yuan and Zhou Guangyi stopped moving. Under these conditions, was there any point in continuing fighting? They lost this match, completely and thoroughly. 1 to 9 wasn't a total sweep, but it wasn't far off, either.

Zou Yuan and Zhou Guangyi didn't say anything to each other. They just stopped at the same time, and it was clear that they were in agreement.

"GG"

"GG"

Each player sent a "GG," and then Bright Blossoms and Cold Seasons withdrew from the battle. Happy officially won the battle. The roar of the crowd was like thunder - this was a huge victory, 9 to 1!

Happy's team competition players walked out of the player booths together to greet the audience, and the stadium reached a new high of excitement.

Hundred Blossoms' players walked out as well. As the losers, it was best for them if they left this stage quickly, but they still had to follow some customs. Hundred Blossoms politely acknowledged the applause they received from the crowd, and with the spirit of "friendship first, competition second," they spoke to their opponents.

"Congratulations, you played well." Yu Feng took the initiative to congratulate Happy's players, displaying Hundred Blossom's grace.

"Haha, continue to work hard," Ye Xiu said casually as he shook hands with Yu Feng. After hearing this, Yu Feng was a bit depressed. What do you mean, "continue to work hard"? That made it sound like Hundred Blossoms' only goal was to surpass Happy.

"Haha, you too." Yu Feng forced a chuckle, then led Hundred Blossoms offstage. They met up with the rest of their teammates, and immediately left through the player tunnel. It was the winner's stage, let the winner enjoy it!

The Alliance mandated that pro players must attend the post-match press conference of every match. To the losers of the match, this was another torture to endure. Reporters were merciless, always rubbing salt into their wounds. Hundred Blossoms knew that this conference would be particularly excruciating, so aside from their captain and vice captain, they sent out their veteran player, Zhang Wei.

"It's a shame that Hundred Blossoms lost this match. Could you talk about some of your thoughts?" The opening question was rather ordinary.

"Our team members all worked hard, but unfortunately the opponent played better." Hundred Blossoms Captain Yu Feng also gave a very standard answer.

"Did you at all predict that you would be crushed by Happy like this? Please forgive my usage of the word "crushed," but judging from the final point score, the match was incredibly one-sided." A harsh question followed, deliberately attacking the Hundred Blossoms players.

"This outcome was unexpected for everyone, and I admit that we never thought this could have happened. But I don't believe that Hundred Blossoms was crushed. We won one point in the individual round, and we had the upper-hand for part of the group arena. As for the team round, maps like Broken River that have instant-kill points will often lead to a result that seems very skewed. The points are only the result, but looking at the process, I truly cannot see where Hundred Blossoms was crushed." Yu Feng didn't reveal any anger, but he replied sharply to this question.

"Captain Yu, what do you think about Team Happy's Tang Rou?" Immediately, another reporter asked a pointed question to counterattack. Tang Rou certainly wasn't a name that Yu Feng would be happy to hear right now. It was another knife to the wound.

"She's very skilled," Yu Feng replied. "She will become an outstanding pro player."

"Could you be more specific? For example, outstanding in what way?" Someone asked.

"To win a 1v2 in the group arena and help the team earn the overall victory, isn't that enough to show her outstandingness?" Yu Feng clearly saw the reporter's purpose in asking about Tang Rou. He had lost to a rookie, which was truly shameful, but he wouldn't try to hide. He had the courage to face any challenge directly because he was the captain and core of Hundred Blossoms. He had to be able to shoulder any difficulties that Hundred Blossoms had.

"Then what about Hundred Blossoms' Zeng Xinran? This was his first time playing in this season, but both the result and the process were unsatisfactory." For comparison, another reporter brought up the rookie on Hundred Blossoms' side, Zeng Xinran. In the entire match, aside from Mo Fan, who had committed a foul and was disqualified from the game, Zeng Xinran's performance was the most abysmal. This was the incontestable truth.

"It was his first official match ever, so he was inevitably nervous. It takes a while to get used to the professional scene, but he will be able to display his ability," said Yu Feng.

After that, there were more questions targeting specific details about the match. The good thing was that Hundred Blossoms was prepared for this, and the players they sent out for this conference were all experienced in this area. Finally, they made it through the questioning.

"I'd like to ask the three Hundred Blossoms players, after this match, could you talk about your opinion of Team Happy?" At the very end of the press conference, Chang Xian from the City H branch of Esports Home had the opportunity to ask the final question.

"For this question, I don't think we each need to say our own opinions. Our view of Happy is unanimous." From Hundred Blossoms, Zhang Wei was the one to answer. "Regarding their roster, they have three All-Star players - I don't think I need to say any more about that. Regarding their characters, aside from their two All-Star characters, the Silver equipment on their other characters is enough to make an opponent hesitate. During the transition stage after the game update, level 75 Orange equipment narrowed the gap between the smaller teams and the powerhouses. We were stuck for too long at level 70, so we need to take another look at the so-called gap between all of the teams. With this situation, combined with Happy's status, I think it's safe to say that Happy is the strongest new team in the history of the Alliance!"

Zhang Wei's answer brought forth even more questions that the reporters wanted to ask, but after answering this final question, Hundred Blossoms' three players ignored the reporters' shouted questions and abruptly left the press conference. Afterwards, it was Happy's turn to come out: Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, and of course the shining star of this match, Tang Rou.

The press conference opened with the typical congratulations and question about their thoughts on this match.

"Hundred Blossoms also worked hard, but we played better." Ye Xiu's answer was essentially the exact same as Yu Feng's, just switching around the pronouns. The reporters didn't care much; no one really hoped to gain anything out of this question. In post-match press conferences, this question was essentially a "hello."

After the greetings, the reporters immediately went to Tang Rou. The team battle hadn't at all distracted from her astonishing 1v2 performance in the group arena.

"An exciting victory, a grand reversal!" The reporters gave their praises without restraint. "What are your thoughts on this thrilling performance? How would you judge your own performance?"

"I hope that I can still do better," Tang Rou said, smiling.

"Still… do better? Are you referring… to a 1v3?" The reporters were in shock.

"Of course." Tang Rou continued to smile.

The reporters' feelings were mixed. Some approved of Tang Rou's courage and confidence, while others immediately turned against her. After managing a 1v2, this rookie knew no modesty and immediately entertained delusions of a 1v3? This was just too arrogant! With these thoughts, these reporters took another look at Tang Rou onstage and felt that she was just like those typical self-righteous pretty girls that often showed up in novels and television.

This was the Glory competitive scene. Being pretty wasn't worth anything. Many of the gazes on Tang Rou were now hostile and disdainful, even those who had previously chased Tang Rou with their praise.

"God Fang Rui also performed very well today, could you talk to us about it?" a reporter asked.

"It was just so-so," said Fang Rui. "A little worse than I had expected."

"What were you expecting?" someone asked.

"To sweep the group arena?" Fang Rui said, but he didn't wait for the hostile glares before immediately adding, "Haha, I'm just kidding. I did want to take some more of Yu Feng's health in the second round of the group arena, but sadly I couldn't pull it off."

"Oh, then regarding the second player to come out in the group arena, Mo Fan, what do you think about his performance? Was he too nervous about his first time playing onstage?" a reporter asked.

"That was entirely Ye Xiu's fault!" Fang Rui's face immediately twisted in grief and indignation.

"Ah? What do you mean?" Everyone was suddenly interested, and they all looked at Ye Xiu.

"It was my fault," Ye Xiu said, also wearing a bitter expression. "I didn't clearly explain to him the competition rules."

"Clearly explain? You didn't explain at all!" Fang Rui said.

"I saw that he was looking at them himself!" Ye Xiu said.

"What use is looking at them himself! Are the rules that easy to digest? You need to properly teach him how to exploit the loopholes in the rules."

"You shut your mouth, is exploiting loopholes and whatnot something that a respectable pro player should do?"

"But there will always be a few sneaky players that do this. To defeat their sneaky tricks, you first have to understand how they'll be sneaky!" said Fang Rui.

After hearing this, the reporters instantly became excited, all turning toward Fang Rui.

"By 'sneaky players,' who are you referring to?" the reporters asked.

"That was just an example, a general reference," Fang Rui said.

The reporters were disappointed, but they still felt that Fang Rui was targeting someone specific. Quite a few people were already racking their brains for a player that Fang Rui didn't get along with. Meanwhile, others continued to seize this time to ask questions.

"In today's team competition, we saw that once again, Happy's healer didn't serve any big purpose. Is this because his skill level still isn't at the professional level, so Happy has to rely on these strategies that don't rely on a healer?" someone asked.

"That's nonsense," said Ye Xiu. "He didn't serve any purpose? How was Blossoming Chaos taken down in one wave? If we were missing a single person, we couldn't have pulled it off."

"Zhang Wei of Hundred Blossoms named you the strongest new team in history. What do you think about that?"

"He praises us too highly. Zhang Wei is truly too honest," Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1165: Damage Leaderboard

Xiaoshan Stadium.

With Excellent Era's liquidation, their lease contract was terminated early and this stadium recovered its old name. But to the workers of this stadium, it was as though nothing changed. After a year, the stadium once again was hosting Glory Pro League, and the work they had to do was the same.

"Pardon, Miss, we need to clear the stadium." A worker quickly walked up to an audience member who was standing just below the stage.

"I'm sorry, I'm just about to leave." Chen Guo immediately apologized to the worker, and prepared to leave. But after taking a few steps, she couldN'T help but turn back and look again.

The audience seating, the player prep room, the competition stage...

It had already been two hours since the end of the match, but as she looked at all of this, Chen Guo could clearly picture the scene as it was during the match, even which seats had the passionate Happy fans who stood and waved their arms in the air as they screamed and cheered Happy on. She remembered it all.

"This... is our home stadium?"

Happy's first home game was already over, but Chen Guo's heart still hadn't calmed down. Of course, she had watched matches here and felt the atmosphere of a home game before, but this time, compared to when she watched Excellent Era's matches, the feeling was completely different.

"Miss…" The worker, seeing how Chen Guo took a few steps and then suddenly stopped again, reminded her again.

"Oh, I'm sorry." Chen Guo quickly turned around again. Without looking back, she walked outside through the only exit that was still open.

We'll return to this place, and we'll earn victory after victory, all the way until the end. Chen Guo's footsteps were rapid, and her heart surged.

9 to 1!

Even though she had somewhat greedily hoped for a perfect 10-0 victory, the result they got was enough to please anyone. Chen Guo picked up her phone and dialed a number.

"Hey! Where'd you all go!" Chen Guo said loudly.

"We should be the ones asking you that question…" the person on the other end of the phone answered.

"I just stayed a bit longer at the stadium, to feel the atmosphere of the home stadium," Chen Guo said.

"Everyone else probably left already, right Boss?"

"Yes, it was empty. So we can go out without worrying! Let's go, let's celebrate!" Chen Guo said.

"Isn't it too late right now?"

"We'll make an exception this time! This was our first home match! And we won so beautifully," said Chen Guo.

"Alright…" On the other end, Ye Xiu hung up the phone.

At least here, this was a night that completely belonged to Happy.

The strongest new team in history. A huge 9 to 1 victory over Hundred Blossoms.

Happy's pretty female rookie won fame through the group arena.

The next day, as expected, news about Happy vs Hundred Blossoms filled the headlines on the front pages of every major esports publication. Chen Guo was elated. During breakfast, she clutched a cup of warm milk and sat in front of the computer, scrolling through the web. She just sat there with a silly grin, completely forgetting about her milk until it had already gone cold.

The dizzying praise felt exhilarating to her. To the occasional critical comment, she swept by with a laugh of "you people wouldn't understand." In the midst of the praise, the one who was mentioned the most often was undoubtedly Tang Rou. Her thrilling performance in the group arena was truly unforgettable, and quite a few people were already discussing the question of Best Rookie for this season. One Glory player made a poll about this, and Tang Rou was at the top of the list by a large margin.

But Chen Guo knew that selection of the Best Rookie wasn't like the All-Stars, where they were determined by fan vote. Best Rookie was awarded by the Alliance based off their performance throughout the entire season and took into account many factors. Just because a rookie was popular didn't mean that they would be chose. This poll was just for the players' amusement; it meant nothing to the officials who would actually decide.

Even though that was the case, Chen Guo was still happy to see all of the favorable comments about her friend.

After reading her fill of all this excitement, Chen Guo went to the official Glory Alliance page to investigate the various technical statistics of the season so far.

There were countless official statistical records: damage dealt, damage boosted, damage taken, heal amount, damage reduced, longest combo, final kill, and so on and so forth.

A player's strength and performance could be judged from these technical statistics. However, most viewers paid attention not to the raw numbers but to the relative rankings.

The leaderboard for damage dealt received the most attention. There were separate group arena and team competition categories. As for the individual round, that was directly compared by win-loss records. There was a separate win rate leaderboard that didn't count by damage.

Tang Rou had played a strong game, and so Chen Guo came here to see her ranking on the group arena damage leaderboard.

But two rounds of the season had already passed. Although Tang Rou's performance in this round was stunning, she had lost to Sun Xiang in the first round, and her damage dealt wasn't very high. After two rounds, Tang Rou's ranking wasn't as high as Chen Guo had anticipated. The current number one of the group arena damage leaderboard was none other than Sun Xiang.

In the first round of competition, Sun Xiang had faced a 1v2 in the group arena, and his performance in terms of damage dealt was no worse than Tang Rou's this past round. And in the second round of competition, Samsara played an away game at Seaside, once again winning in a clean 10 to 0. And this time, Sun Xiang had truly completed a full 1v2. After two rounds, his 142546 far surpassed Tang Rou's 70421.

It could even be said that comparing Tang Rou with the current number one was a mistake in and of itself.

Of the 84 players that appeared on the group arena damage leaderboard, Tang Rou was only number 31, slightly above the middle. The 30 players ahead of her, including Sun Xiang, had dealt more damage in the group arena after two rounds of competition.

And this was only for the total damage output rankings. If they looked at average per match, Tang Rou's ranking was a bit lower, number 41 out of 84, very ordinary.

Chen Guo was a bit disappointed after not seeing the results she had hoped for. She scrolled the mouse wheel, searching for the names of the other Happy players. When she scrolled to the bottom, she saw Mo Fan and Deception at number 84. That 0 was particularly glaring.

"Looking at these things now, isn't it too early?" Ye Xiu's voice sounded from next to her.

"I'm just looking for fun," Chen Guo said, turning her head to look at him.

"It's only been two rounds, the leaderboards haven't stabilized. Who's number one?" Ye Xiu was eating breakfast right now, drinking from a cup of milk as he asked this question.

"Sun Xiang," Chen Guo said, scrolling back up to show him.

"140000, that ferocious? That's pretty much a 1v2 in both rounds!" Ye Xiu said.

"I know!" Chen Guo was quite depressed. She had hoped that Tang Rou was the only one to 1v2, but looking at the leaderboards, it was clear that many players had outstanding performances.

"If he played that ferociously, doesn't that mean that some people wouldn't be able to deal their share of damage?" Ye Xiu laughed.

Chen Guo blinked, and then began scrolling down again. In the end, at number 80, she found Zhou Zekai's name. Not much farther ahead flashed the names of Huang Shaotian and Wang Jiexi.

Zhou Zekai, Huang Shaotian, Wang Jiexi.

Who would dare say that these three had poor DPS? But on the leaderboard after two rounds, each of them seemed weaker than the next. The reality of course wasn't that they were doing poorly, but that they hadn't yet had much chance to perform onstage. In their respective teams, each of these three was the powerful player anchoring the group arena. To take Zhou Zekai as an example, in the first round he had faced Lord Grim at low health, and it only took a few attacks to end the battle. In the second round, he hadn't even gone onstage, since Samsara's second player ended the group arena.

Under these conditions, of course Zhou Zekai's damage output would be low.

Thus, although the raw numbers of the Glory statistics leaderboards could reveal a few things, they had to be analyzed with context. Glory's competition system had its own characteristics, such as this situation where because a teammate was too strong in the group arena, a player didn't have the chance to deal damage.

Chen Guo casually flipped through a few other leaderboards. Because they were swept in the first round, whether in the overall standings or the average standings, Happy was fairly low, nowhere near as exciting as the news reports today.

"How are the point rankings?" Ye Xiu asked from the side.

"You haven't looked yet?" As she spoke, Chen Guo flipped to the team points leaderboard.

"Not yet." Ye Xiu leaned forward a bit. Evidently, he was more interested in this information.

"Samsara's in first," Chen Guo said, looking at the leaderboard. "They swept again, 20 points."

"Mm." Ye Xiu looked further down. Samsara was in first with 20 points after two rounds, followed by Wind Howl, Blue Rain, and Tiny Herb with 18 points each. Fifth was Tyranny with 17 points, sixth was Misty Rain with 15 points. This seemed to be the cutoff for the upper tier of the points rankings, as there was a large gap between Misty Rain and the seventh place Thunderclap, who earned 13 points over two rounds. Eighth and ninth were Royal Style and Void, each with ten points. Then after that, Happy made a dazzling entrance, placing tenth with nine points. And Happy's neighbor happened to be the team they just defeated, Hundred Blossoms.

After two rounds, Hundred Blossoms had also earned 9 points. If ordered alphabetically by the pinyin of their names, then they should be placed before Happy - Baihua (Hundred Blossoms) before Xingxin (Happy). But because the two teams had fought and Happy had won against them, Happy ranked ahead of them. After Hundred Blossoms was 301 Degrees with 7 points, and then there were the various mid-to-low-tier teams. After two rounds, none of these teams broke through to the upper tier. They all obediently stayed in the bottom.

Heavenly Swords, the team that Happy was friendliest with, had earned 3 points in two rounds. They were currently in second to last place, in danger of being relegated.

After Heavenly Swords, last place was held by Seaside. Zhao Yang retired, Boundless Sea was sold. The team that had once been solidly mid-tier had directly slid to the bottom.

However, only two rounds had passed so far. It was still too early to talk about a team's chances. After all, Heavenly Swords and Seaside, the two teams at the bottom, had faced strong opponents in the first two rounds. Heavenly Swords had faced Hundred Blossoms and Blue Rain, while Seaside faced Misty Rain and Samsara. Losing to these teams, they couldn't be accused of not trying hard enough.

But Heavenly Swords, who had lost 2 to 8 to Hundred Blossoms, saw how Happy defeated the same team in a drastic 9 to 1, and they couldn't help but have mixed feelings.

"They really are something else!" Lou Guanning sighed.

Chapter 1166: Point Evaluations

Saturday was match day. On Sunday, all sorts of discussion on Saturday's matches could be seen in the various Glory forums, although most of these discussions were focused on the players. The news reports, on the other hand, were either impartial descriptions of the how the match went, or remarks from interviews. The truly professional analysis generally required a day to fully digest the previous day's matches. The most reputable Esports Home would only start reporting any detailed analysis in their Monday issue.

On Monday, Chen Guo hurried to buy a copy of the Esports Home weekly issue. But when she took a glance at it, she was slightly disappointed. The Esports Home's praise for Happy wasn't as earth-shattering as she had imagined.

Tang Rou's outstanding performance in the group arena had received positive evaluations, but Steamed Bun's performance in the individual competition and Mo Fan's send off in the group arena had not been neglected by the respected media group. Chen Guo still felt her spirits stir when she saw the high praise for Happy's performance in the team competition though, which particularly lauded the team's coordination in killing Blossoming Chaos in one go. The Esports Home called it a classic textbook example. This description couldn't help but make people think of the Glory Textbook, Ye Xiu. Sure enough, while the popular comments on the forums didn't talk much about Ye Xiu relatively speaking, the praise for Ye Xiu by Esports Home was no less than their praise for Tang Rou. Even the class-changed Fang Rui received quite the commendation.

The news related to the match were mostly done by City H's reporter Chang Xian. However, the professional analysis had been done by several special analysts. To be a part of an organization as respected as Esports Home, these analysts weren't just people who talked big. Their analyses were very on point.

One of Chen Guo's favorite parts about the Esports Home was their point evaluations for every player in the highlight match. This section was usually done by specialists too. But the analyst was different and the style was different. The writer could write more freely as well, so this section was quite popular.

From the broadcast of the second round, the highlight match was Team Thunderclap versus Team Void. However, the good thing about print media was that they could look at things in retrospect. As a result, they picked the Team Happy versus Team Hundred Blossoms as the highlight match.

Chen Guo quickly flipped to this section in glee. Sure enough, it was in the style she liked.　

Individual competition, Ye Xiu versus Zeng Xinran.　　

Ye Xiu 5 points. Zeng Xinran -4 points.

Yes, this section was sometimes just this unconventional. Points were usually given from 0 to 10, but the writer actually gave Zeng Xinran negative four points. The writer's disgust for Zeng Xingran's performance could clearly be seen. The short commentary on it wrote: Team Hundred Blossom's Zeng Xinran played his first ever match. Through this match, he told us one thing: he was here. Apart from that, he also told God Ye Xiu one thing: it doesn't matter if your hands are rusty. Against some opponents, you could cut your hands off and still win. Zeng Xingran is a rookie though, so I'll be more lenient. Instead of -5 points, I give him a -4! As for God Ye Xiu, without a worthy opponent, there's not much for him to show off, so 5 points!

It was quite a biting remark, even referencing Ye Xiu's "rustiness." Chen Guo very rudely let out a laugh and checked the name of the writer for this point evaluation.

As expected, it was Zuo Chenrui. Chen Guo was no stranger to this name. He was famous for his sharp and unkind words. His evaluations were very subjective, not conforming with Esports Home's reputation. These point evaluations were clearly marked out as "special commentary that did not represent the newspaper's views," making it the one place where Zuo Chenrui could shine in the Esports Home. And as it turned out, his exaggerated and sharp remarks became the most popular parts of this section.

As for Chen Guo, she rather liked this person's commentary because they were often very funny.

After Ye Xiu and Zeng Xinran was Steamed Bun and Zhang Wei's battle.　

Bao Rongxin 10 to 0, Zhang Wei 5.

Chen Guo laughed again just from this evaluation of Steamed Bun.

The puzzling rookie Bao Rongxing has a mind that no one can comprehend. Perhaps he doesn't even know what he's doing himself. For the first half, he receives full marks. He utterly dominated Zhang Wei. For the second half, his incomprehensible feebleness proves my bewilderment for him. Zhang Wei 5 points, facing 10 points, can only be crushed. But facing 0 points, it becomes the other way around! Bao Rongxing receives 10 to 0 points. His loss is because his performance didn't go the reverse from 0 to 10 points.

Evil! How evil!

Zuo Chenrui was just like this. He spared no efforts in ridiculing someone. If you weren't mentioned much, then that's pretty much praise for you. The mockery towards Hundred Blossoms was rather light. Those familiar with Zuo Chenrui knew that he was a Blue Rain fan. His negative bias towards Tiny Herb was truly deep. When the Esports Home did a points evaluation for a Tiny Herb match, they definitely didn't dare have him do it.

After these two rounds was Su Mucheng's and Zou Yuan's match.　　

Zou Yuan wanted to fight with Su Mucheng in a direct confrontation, but he took the wrong turn and ended up being completely suppressed. Zou Yuan's attempt to directly eliminate Su Mucheng's suppression ended up in failure. To put it simply, Zou Yuan underestimated Su Mucheng. In terms of technique, experience, and awareness, Su Mucheng is not any worse than Zou Yuan. On the other hand, her good looks surpass Zou Yuan 10000 times. Such a dominating victory makes complete sense. Su Mucheng's performance is a beautiful 10/10, her looks 10000/10. Zou Yuan's performance is a 5/10, his looks… forget about it, I won't attach a point value to him. I'll just say it's on the poorer side!

After that was the group arena.

Fang Rui did a good job. His simple trick worked again and again. It has to be said that even though this master of playing dirty has changed classes, his ability to dig holes is still as high as ever. But his inexperience with his class can clearly be seen. His methods for digging holes isn't rich enough. In the second half of the match, he was forced into a direct confrontation with Zhou Guangyi. Fortunately, he dug a deep enough hole earlier, so he didn't fall. The round ended in this way. Fang Rui 6 points. But his Qigong Blast against Yu Feng deserves a 10. (10+6)/2 gives him a total of 8 points.

Zhou Guangyi was pretty much dancing around in Fang Rui's palms. If Fang Rui was still a Thief, Zhou Guangyi might have lost in an even uglier fashion, or perhaps he might have done better because he understands Fang Rui's Thief better. I'm inclined to think the former, so Zhou Guangyi gets 2 points.

Yu Feng should have been able to take down Fang Rui without losing much health, but that Qigong Blast proved that he miscalculated against Fang Rui, 2 points. In the next round, he stood heroically in the center of the map, a well-deserved 5 points, but he won just like that by standing there, so only 5 points. In the third round, he met Happy's rookie head-on, but was blown out. Yu Feng made the same mistake as Zou Yuan: he underestimated his opponent. But compared to Zou Yuan, as an All-Star, he had the qualifications to look down on a rookie. Thanks to Yu Feng's negligence, we were gifted a spectacular 1v2. As such, he deserves another 2 points. 2+5+2=9 points? That doesn't seem right. Oh, I forgot, Yu Feng played a total of three rounds, so we have to divide by 3, 3 points. Speaking of which, if I didn't say anything, would people have noticed that Yu Feng played three battles, also playing a 1v2?

There's not much to be said for Mo Fan. He's Happy response towards Hundred Blossom's rookie, Zeng Xinran. Zeng Xinran said he was here, so Mo Fan said he was also here. I have to give him two points though, because without him, there wouldn't have been that beautiful 1v2.

Zhu Xiaoping, as a Summoner who is said to hold back 2 or 3 people with his 1, was blown out by the enemy. Still, we can't say that's Wind Carving's fault. Zhu Xiaoping, 3 points.

Tang Rou beating Yu Feng, 10 points! Beating Zhu Xiaoping, 10 points! Looks, 10000 points. There's no need for any explanation.

For the most spectacular performance by Tang Rou, Zuo Chenrui only said a few short words, proving that he loved to mock people but was too lazy to give praise.

For the final team competition, Zuo Chenrui continued with his subjective evaluations. He started off by firing shots at Yu Feng's early send off. It looked like the Team Blue Rain fan Zuo Chenrui had quite the opinion of Yu Feng, who had abandoned Team Blue Rain.

"What's making you so happy?" Everyone had arrived at the Internet cafe and was ready to begin their new week's practice, only to see Chen Guo laughing uncontrollably.

Chen Guo gave the paper to everyone. Everyone was familiar with Esports Home. They knew that there was nothing really that funny to look at besides that section.　　

Sure enough, it was that section. And looking at the writer, everyone understood.

"Who's he going at this time?" Fang Rui took the paper and started reading it.

The player being ridiculed certainly wouldn't be laughing, but to others, reading Zuo Chenrui's remarks were quite fun.

"Hehe, hehe, hehe…" Fang Rui took the newspaper, looked over Zuo Chenrui's commentary, and soon started laughing.

"Hey, he was quite nice to me." Fang Rui was surprised when he saw the group arena evaluation of him. "Let's see what he wrote about Little Tang." He continued reading. Since this guy very rarely praised anyone, a lot of people would be curious to see his views on someone who had performed exceptionally.

"Tsk tsk, to make Zuo Chenrui not give any explanation for his evaluation, Little Tang, you've got a bright future ahead of you," Fang Rui said to Tang Rou after reading over it.

"Really?" Tang Rou would also read over the Glory analysis in the papers, but she was mainly doing it to learn. She searched for material she needed in a targeted manner. Someone like Zuo Chenrui, who was extremely subjective and wrote exaggerated remarks, wasn't inside Tang Rou's study list, so she didn't know much about him.

"He's always been quite nice to girls. Have you ever seen him go all out to tear at a female player?" Ye Xiu said.

"This…" Fang Rui thought about it. It really had never happened before. He checked today's paper again and read over Su Mucheng's evaluation. Sure enough, Zuo Chenrui's usual style wasn't there.

"This guy actually has a bottom line, huh. I never noticed," Fang Rui said.　　

"Even though he exaggerates a bit, his evaluations can sometimes be very on point. If not, did you really think the Esports Home would have him someone as irresponsible as him writing just to make jokes?" Ye Xiu said.

"True." Fang Rui nodded his head in seriousness, while reading the paper aloud: "'His Qigong Blast against Yu Feng deserves a 10.' This guy's evaluation is truly on point."

Chapter 1167: Steamed Bun’s Review

"Zuo Chenrui got a lot of things right. Perfect timing, let's use his evaluation as a starting point for our discussion!" Ye Xiu said, taking the paper from Fang Rui and lifting it in the air.

Soon afterwards, whether they came onstage the previous round or not, everyone in Happy went to the strategy room. The always quiet, cold, and lonesome Mo Fan seemed quite eager this time. He was the first to go into the room, although his expression was as apathetic as always.

In the strategy room, everyone sat down at their own seat one after the other. After Ye Xiu came in, everyone stopped chatting.

The projection screen rolled down. Ye Xiu sat in front of a computer to the side and opened up their previous match.　　

"The first round of the individual competition… Yeah, there's not much to say here. That Hundred Blossoms kid was too nervous. This issue…" Ye Xiu looked at his teammates. At Happy, there was only one person who would be nervous. Ye Xiu look around the room. In the end, his gaze landed on a laptop.　　

The new season started in September and so did school. Having a young genius mathematician push his academics aside to focus on a professional gaming career was somewhat of a waste, but in this past year, Luo Ji had come to love Glory deeply. He was also unwilling to give up on his position as a pro player. After weighing the two options, Luo Ji decided on staying at school. When he was needed for a match, he would fly over to the stadium.

Fortunately, this was esports. Even if Luo Ji wasn't personally with the team, as long as he was online, he could still practice with everyone else. However, since Luo Ji was at school, he obviously had to spend a lot of time on his academics. He couldn't completely keep up with Happy's pace. Happy tried their best to arrange for more important matters when Luo Ji was free. Everything else could only be communicated online. For example, right now although Luo Ji wasn't here in-person, a laptop was placed where he would be sitting. Though a bit strange, he could participate in the meeting through a video call.

"There's not much to say about this issue. Dealing with it is mainly dependent on you. From my experience, try to focus on the match as much as possible and don't think too much about other things. It'll help a bit." Ye Xiu said.　　

"Yes yes yes…" Luo Ji spoke through the laptop. Everyone felt weird seeing it.　　

"The second round was Steamed Bun's. Steamed Bun, you see how he evaluated you? He gave you 10 to 0. Do you know why?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Why?" Steamed Bun asked back.

"Because you played very well at the start, but then played badly at the end." Ye Xiu said.　　

"No wonder I lost!" Steamed Bun suddenly understood. He lowered his right fist to his left palm.

"Yeah… let's look at Steamed Bun's match!" Ye Xiu said as he opened the VOD of Steamed Bun versus Zhang Wei.

A huge display of Steamed Bun's match started playing on the projection screen. This wasn't a recording of the broadcast, but Glory's own specialized VOD. By using a special video player, they could change the viewpoint and the speed however they pleased.

Ye Xiu fast-forwarded until the point where Steamed Bun and Zhang Wei met.

Zhang Wei threw a Lava Flask, while Steamed Bun flew over with a Powerful Knee Strike...

For the first half, Zuo Chenrui gave Steamed Bun 10 points. What was 10 points? Perfect play was 10 points. For any other analyst, giving out 10 points was extremely rare. But for someone like Zuo Chenrui, who could give 10000 points for looks, what was 10 points? He wasn't stingy about that, just like how he wasn't stingy about jabbing at someone.　

10 points...

Ye Xiu took the newspaper and for a moment, he didn't know where to start. Steamed Bun and Tang Rou were the same. Both of them had started playing in the tenth server. Ye Xiu had personally watched over these two blank pieces of paper as the papers were drawn on. For Tang Rou, her lines were crisp and clear. Her thought process was distinct. Ye Xiu could see the logic behind every stroke. He could see her thoughts. However, for Steamed Bun, his art was the legendary abstract art. His playstyle and his logic did not coincide much, if at all, with those of a normal Glory player. However, sometimes he could produce surprising results.　　

As Steamed Bun's skill continued to grow, in his practice, there were times where even Ye Xiu was caught off guard. As for Ye Xiu, he had constantly been trying to understand Steamed Bun's thoughts. For example, he would frequently review the VOD after practice together with Steamed Bun and have him explain his logic when Ye Xiu didn't understand.

Lots of times, Steamed Bun also scratched his head in wonder. He had clearly already forgotten about his thoughts at that time. This wasn't Steamed Bun getting derailed, it was simply due to the nature of this game. Glory was fast-paced. Oftentimes, inputs could not be carefully thought about and were done instinctively. There were very few players who could remember every detail in their match perfectly. In Happy, the only one who could do this was named Luo Ji, definitely not Steamed Bun.

Even though he couldn't get an answer for everything, from the places that Steamed Bun could explain, Ye Xiu gradually started to get a feel for it.

Steamed Bun wasn't playing without any logic whatsoever. It was just that his logic was rather bold and imaginative. It was born from wild creativity and observation. In this point, he was very similar to Wang Jiexi. The difference was that Steamed Bun had only played Glory for a year, while by the time Wang Jiexi became a pro player, he had been playing Glory for far longer than Steamed Bun. His foundation in Glory had been more solid than Steamed Bun's.

As a result, Wang Jiexi's creative playing was precise, sharp, and unpredictable. It was why he was called the Magician.　　

As for Steamed Bun, he was limited by his foundation. His creative playing would sometimes crash into a dead end, leading to noobish mistakes.

Once he understood Steamed Bun's situation, Ye Xiu couldn't help but sigh. If Steamed Bun had started playing Glory sooner and had more time to grow, he would definitely be even more terrifying today. But he had only just started now and suffered for that. It was true that Steamed Bun was quite talented, but this was no longer the game. Compared to the in-game Glory, everyone in the Pro Alliance was brimming with talent. And those who became Gods were the best out of all those talents.

Every rookie found by Ye Xiu in Happy had a certain amount of potential, but in Glory, because of all sorts of reasons, all of them had been delayed. Sun Xiang and Tang Hao, these new generation Gods, were only 20 years old. They were even younger than Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, yet they were already the stars of this era.

It wasn't the first time that Ye Xiu had thought about this. If he had discovered them earlier, or if they had found Glory fun earlier and started practicing systematically, would their current selves have already joined those at the top of the pyramid?

Unfortunately, there were no ifs. He could only dream. Right now, Ye Xiu could only do his best and help these latecomers grow faster. However, towards Steamed Bun, the amount of help that Ye Xiu could provide was becoming less and less. Steamed Bun's playstyle was special, his unique talent. If Ye Xiu forced him to follow the conventional logic of Glory, it would kill his talent. Ye Xiu could not help Steamed Bun develop his unique talent. As the saying went, what came next would depend on Steamed Bun's own good luck.

As a result, Ye Xiu would generally just help Steamed Bun make as few mistakes as possible. Those obvious dead-ends would help remind him not to make the same mistake next time.　　

In Steamed Bun's match against Zhang Wei, he was bold and creative in the first half, but in the next half, he regressed back to the ordinary and confronted Zhang Wei head on. When he asked for the reason why, Steamed Bun's answer couldn't be refuted.　　

"I had more health!" Steamed Bun said.

Everyone in the room stared blankly. They wanted to laugh, but they felt like it was nothing to joke about. In the first half, gain the upper hand and get a health lead. Then, in the second half, there was no need to use any special tricks, just directly trade blows. It was a very common and logical strategy. Even the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, had the same idea in his match against Zhou Guangyi. After successfully pulling off the cooldown method twice and gaining a health lead, he immediately started fighting against Zhou Guangyi directly.

"Yeah, that…" Ye Xiu also hesitated. He fast-forwarded to the middle. "Okay, then let's take a look at how you played after you had more health than him."

Steamed Bun had more health, yet he still lost to Zhang Wei. It wasn't hard to realize that Steamed Bun had made many mistakes. The strategy meetings weren't just Ye Xiu lecturing them. During this time, everyone was free to speak up. The rookies and Qiao Yifan were rather quiet, though. Su Mucheng just listened more often than not. She would typically only raise an issue if something was missed. Today, no opportunities had appeared yet. Ye Xiu wasn't the main speaker either. So, after they started analyzing the latter half of the fight, Wei Chen and Fang Rui were the ones dominating the discussion.

"Here, here. At 2:41, you hesitated! Don't you think you could have just thrown your Brick at his forehead?" Wei Chen pointed at the projection screen. His tone of voice and attitude didn't seem like he was discussing tactics. It sounded like he was telling him how to fight like a gangster.

"You're right!" Steamed Bun again put his right fist to his left palm. He had taken a liking to his movement recently.　　

"The hesitation is okay, but you shouldn't have leaped back and retreated afterwards. Why not just use Tiger Flips the Mountain?" Fang Rui said.　　

"That's not necessarily correct. After jumping backwards, you should have followed up with a Powerful Knee Strike. It would have been very strong too," Wei Chen said.

"Powerful Knee Strike? He could just use Shadow Cloak and wrap you up," Fang Rui said.

"That's why you need to jump backwards first to dodge Shadow Cloak before counterattacking," Wei Chen said.　　

Fang Rui looked distracted for a moment, but he quickly responded, "Fuck, if there's no Powerful Knee Strike, where would the Shadow Cloak come from?"　　

"Young people these days, do you not understand the word 'predict'?" Wei Chen said.

"Predict, my ass!" Fang Rui wasn't polite at all to this shameless senior. "Steamed Bun, don't listen to his nonsense. You should have just used Tiger Flips the Mountain and flip him."

"Peh!" Wei Chen spat. "Steamed Bun, trust this senior. Jump back first and then Powerful Knee Strike. Watch the opponent carefully. You're aiming for that small time gap. It'll definitely give your opponent the biggest surprise."　

"Surprise, I like it!" Steamed Bun said happily.

"Mm, mm." Wei Chen nodded his head as if he were teaching a child. "Rhythm. What's important is the rhythm."　

"Steamed Bun," Ye Xiu called out at this moment.

"Hm?" Steamed Bun looked towards his boss.

"You hesitated here," Ye Xiu said. "Don't hesitate next time. React faster."

"Okay," Steamed Bun replied.

"Alright, good." Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Chapter 1168: The Best Choice

Steamed Bun had a lot of problems in the second half of the match, so they allocated a lot of time for review until the discussion finally quieted down. After that was the battle between Su Mucheng and Zou Yuan.

Even though it was a victory, and even though Su Mucheng was already a high-level player, they didn't skip this match. No matter how good a player was, there would always be mistakes that exposed flaws during battle. Reviewing matches wasn't just to help improve the person whose battle they were studying, it let everyone learn lessons. At the same time, they could further study the opponent. Thus, no matter whom they fought against, whether they won or lost, review was always beneficial.

Reviewing Su Mucheng's battle was much easier and much lighter than reviewing Steamed Bun's. While watching the replay, Su Mucheng herself was able to notice many things about her fighting, and she would then bring them up with everyone to discuss.

After the individual round was the group arena, and first up was the battle between Fang Rui and Zhou Guangyi. Wei Chen pushed up his sleeves, but it was unclear what he planned to do.

The battle began.

Zhou Guangyi's Cold Seasons reached the center of the map, but Fang Rui's Boundless Sea wasn't there, so he began to look for him, all the way until the two returned to the center and began to fight.

"You played around too much in the beginning," Wei Chen said coldly.

"We know each other too well, I had to make him think a bit more," Fang Rui said.

"If he hadn't had doubts in his heart, your cooldown method never would've worked," said Wei Chen.

"Right." Fang Rui nodded.

In the VOD, Fang Rui was having Boundless Sea play the cooldown method, showing the moment he qi blasted Cold Seasons.

"Not decisive enough!" Wei Chen sighed.

"Me or him?" Fang Rui asked.

"Him," Wei Chen said.

"Well, of course," said Fang Rui. "This is the value of my playing around earlier."

"It's impressive enough that it worked once, but it actually worked twice," Wei Chen said.

"You guys don't understand the depth of this match," Fang Rui said.

Wei Chen made a disdainful face, but he didn't retort, because Fang Rui spoke the truth. This battle was between two players that understood each other very well. It was more of a psychological contest than one of technical skill. Battles like this couldn't be learned, not even by the most skilled players. Without that personal relationship, you couldn't play these sorts of mental traps. And then, the technical skill was another level on top of the psychological warfare.

You couldn't follow normal logic when looking at such a match. In the end, they just found some non-psychological points to look at, and they soon moved on.

After that was another one of Fang Rui's battles, now against Yu Feng. In the eyes of the specialists, there were three highlights of the Happy vs Hundred Blossoms match. First was Fang Rui's final Qigong Blast in this battle, next was of course Tang Rou's 1v2, and finally in the team battle when they took down Yu Feng's Blossoming Chaos.

Hundred Blossoms' Captain Yu Feng was named the most tragic character of this match. In all three of the highlights, he was the victim. Boundless Sea's Qigong Blast landed on the body of his Blossoming Chaos, Tang Rou's 1v2 began by killing him, and he was the one who had been so dramatically killed in the team round…

One mischievous Glory player created a montage of these three highlights, set it to the music of "Why Am I Always The One Who Gets Hurt," and posted the video online, where it quickly went viral.

Ye Xiu of course didn't show this silly video. He selected the proper battle recording and the scene began to unfold before them.

"Too slow!" The recording had barely begun when Wei Chen suddenly let out this shout, startling everyone in the room, even Luo Ji in the laptop screen.

"Much too slow," Wei Chen continued. "Every second after a battle begins is extremely valuable. If you don't get in the right mindset as fast as you can, any small ripple can become the reason for defeat."

In the VOD, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea hesitated for about three seconds after the match began before he started moving.

Everyone stared blankly at Wei Chen. What he said about "every second after a battle begins" was inaccurate reasoning, even an idiot could tell he was nitpicking. But to everyone's surprise, Fang Rui actually nodded in agreement. "You're right. If not for that three second delay, Yu Feng and I would have met under slightly different conditions, and I might have been able to take the advantage."

Everyone continued to stare blankly. Those three seconds of hesitation really affected the entire progression of the battle? Wei Chen wasn't just nitpicking, he actually made a good point?

In the next moment, Fang Rui turned his head to look at Wei Chen. "Didn't I tell you this after the match that day?"

"Mm, I was worried you'd forget, so I'm reminding you," Wei Chen said, nodding.

The sound of one cough after another filled the room. Even just hearing this, everyone felt awkward, but Wei Chen was as calm as ever.

Only Ye Xiu was unaffected. He continued to watch the onscreen maneuvering, zooming out the camera view until both sides were visible, and then he began to zoom in again, finally pausing on one scene.

"Yeah, right here." Fang Rui pointed on the screen. "If I hadn't hesitated for those three seconds, then I could've reached that fork there at two o'clock. From there, if I could lure Blossoming Chaos in, then the situation could have been much better."

"Here?" Ye Xiu used the mouse to circle the position.

"Right," Fang Rui nodded.

"Hm, right here…" Ye Xiu directly switched to a map of Life-Seeking Path and began to study it.

"What if Yu Feng circled around in the ten o'clock direction?" Su Mucheng asked.

"With his speed, he couldn't catch up, I… Oh!" Fang Rui slapped his forehead. "I'm using Boundless Sea right now, not Demon Subduer."

"So he still could've gotten you," said Su Mucheng.

"Yeah…" Fang Rui nodded, but he was still studying the map intently, trying to think of another way.

"What about here!" Ye Xiu circled another position on the map.

"There, if Yu Feng took the path to the right, they would meet face to face. If prepared, Fang Rui could still maintain three steps of distance, but that's still in the attack range of a Berserker. Whether or not he could actually break through and attack would depend on the exact conditions." Wei Chen now began to give serious analysis.

"But even if he broke through, wouldn't the distance to the next fork be enough to escape?" said Su Mucheng.

"If Qi Flowing Cloud were activated, yeah." This time Fang Rui didn't mistake the character.

"What if Yu Feng used Triple Slash?" said Su Mucheng.

"He'd have to predict my move first," Fang Rui said.

The rookies listened quietly. For this kind of discussion, they would sometimes speak up, but most of the time their views and awareness couldn't keep up. Every time they went through this review and study, everyone would notice many things. The ones fighting were Fang Rui and Yu Feng, but they could imagine putting themselves and their own characters in one of those positions, and figure out how they would act in such a situation. Through analysis, they could reach an analogous answer. Boundless Sea could activate Qi Flowing Cloud, Berserker could use Triple Slash, and other classes would have their own ways of boosting their movement speed here.

Just looking at a three-second hesitation brought forth analysis of so many potential changes. But everyone also understood that all of these situations had to be addressed on a case-by-case basis. The important thing wasn't being early or late by three seconds, the important thing was realizing and studying these changes. This was the significance of this review.

There wasn't too much to look at in Fang Rui's battle against Yu Feng, so in the end it finished quite quickly.

And then it was Mo Fan against Yu Feng. Everyone knew the results of this match, and there shouldn't have been much to review. But Ye Xiu still played the recording of this match. Everyone couldn't help but glance at Mo Fan, but this guy was as expressionless as ever. Only Qiao Yifan, who was sitting next to him, noticed how he was clenching his fists under the table.

Qiao Yifan was a bit worried. He didn't know what Ye Xiu was thinking. Was he purposely trying to humiliate and provoke Mo Fan by replaying this match? That… didn't seem too good, Qiao Yifan thought.

No one spoke. The recording quietly played, the screen splitting in half to show each character. Soon, Yu Feng's Blossoming Chaos reached the center of the map, and Mo Fan's Deception arrived soon after, hiding to the side.

"You chose a good position." Ye Xiu finally opened his mouth.

Everyone nodded. Mo Fan, with his background of scrap-picking, was extremely skilled in choosing advantageous positions, no worse than any pro player.

"But sometimes, the best position isn't actually very good," said Ye Xiu.

Everyone startled a bit, and there was confusion in Mo Fan's eyes.

"Because, when facing the best players, you aren't the only one who knows the best position." As Ye Xiu spoke, he switched the camera view to Yu Feng. "Blossoming Chaos' position looks very random, but in reality, he's carefully positioned a distance away from all possible ambush points. No matter where the opponent tries to launch a sneak attack from, he has enough space to deal with it."

Ye Xiu snatched up the esports newspaper issue on the table and waved it around. "Zuo Chenrui said that Yu Feng stood heroically and that was worth 5 points. That wasn't entirely mockery, his positioning was indeed excellent.

"Let's look at his use of his camera view." Ye Xiu switched the recording to Yu Feng's camera view. The display followed Yu Feng's control over his view as he turned.

"Do you see it?" Ye Xiu pointed to a position on the screen, right where Deception was currently hiding.

"The best position you had chosen was also where he was the most prepared for an attack," said Ye Xiu. "If you tried to attack from here, it would be very difficult for you to get seize an opportunity."

So that was the reason… As expected of senior! Qiao Yifan was sincerely happy. Earlier, he was truly a little worried that Ye Xiu's goal had just been to shame Mo Fan. If that had been the case, he really would have been disappointed in him. But now, he saw that Ye Xiu was giving genuine feedback and advice on Mo Fan's pitifully lacking performance in this match.

It was just a choice of position, but Ye Xiu used this to emphasize to Mo Fan what was different about the professional stage.

In this domain, anyone can have the same background and knowledge as you. The best choice might actually be the worst because everyone knows it's the best choice. As a player who likes to use sneak attacks, it's crucial that you understand this point...

Chapter 1169: Third Round

They finished discussing positioning. Next was the judge giving a yellow card to the calmly waiting Mo Fan, forcing Mo Fan to make adjustments, but the judge felt his actions were unacceptable, so he gave him another yellow card, and Mo Fan was disqualified.

"Mucheng, you talked to him about the rules already, right?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I did," Su Mucheng said with a smile.

"Alright, then that's that." Ye Xiu nodded. He didn't ask Mo Fan to report anything, and simply ended the discussion of this battle. "Let's look at the next battle."

The next battle was Tang Rou's thrilling 1v2. Because it was her own battle, this time Tang Rou participated in the discussion more. She wasn't like Steamed Bun, who couldn't figure out the situation. Her clarity of thought allowed her to gain the most from reviewing her own match.

After the group arena was the team competition. Every confrontation, every player's performance, from both Happy and Hundred Blossoms, was taken apart and evaluated in detail.

They spent the entire morning in review, which was already a relatively short amount of time. In this competition, there really wasn't much they could analyze. Ye Xiu's defeat of Zeng Xinran, Fang Rui's two battles, Mo Fan's battle, there wasn't much content to look at. Furthermore, this was Happy's big victory. A victory generally meant that there were fewer problems to study. Even though the opponent's mistakes could also be analyzed, the priority was generally figuring out one's own problems so that they could be fixed. For example, Hundred Blossoms' Zeng Xinran revealed the problem of nerves, but this wasn't something that Happy needed to focus on.

On the other hand, their complete defeat in last week's match against Samsara revealed many of their problems. The review that Happy did last Monday after that match lasted from morning all the way until night.

They finished review in the morning, so the afternoon was spent training as usual. The life of a pro player was this sort of dull repetition. Every day, they basically did the same thing. The burning passion was left to Saturday night to be released.

On days without matches, ordinary gamers could only wait around, looking back on previous matches and anticipating the next ones. In the second round, Happy vs Hundred Blossoms garnered a lot of attention, but to the viewers, the live television broadcast of Thunderclap vs Void was also a very high-level match.

In this match, Thunderclap took an early lead with Dai Yanqi in the individual round, but then they cleanly lost the next two individual battles as well as the group arena.

Losing 1 to 4, with so many consecutive defeats, it seemed as though Thunderclap was on the brink of collapse and Void would earn a big victory. But to everyone's shock, Thunderclap pulled off a huge comeback in the team competition. They defeated Void and won the 5 points of the team round, and in the end won the match 6 to 4.

Such an exciting plot was definitely worth live broadcast, but in the end, the live commentator was distracted during the whole thing, occasionally turning the subject to discuss Happy vs Hundred Blossoms. There were indeed some viewers that objected to this.

There was much commentary on the Happy vs Hundred Blossoms match, but the specialized media outlets needed to present comprehensive reports. Esports Weekly, for example, didn't neglect their analysis and discussion of Thunderclap vs Void.

All of the reporters and special commentators unanimously pointed out Thunderclap's biggest change this season: they had become more confident.

They won 7 points in the first round and 6 points this round. With 13 points, they were currently in 7th place, not a bad start. If they maintained this stable performance, then it wouldn't be a problem for them to earn a spot in the playoffs.

Their performance in the team competition received particular attention. Before, Thunderclap relied on their Master Tactician Xiao Shiqin, who had more of a chance to shine in the team competition. Now that he returned this season, he joined with his former teammates who had grown on their own, as well as new arrivals, to smoothly create a solid, unified team. Team Parade and Team Void, who had fought with Thunderclap this season, both expressed how difficult it was to face Team Thunderclap in the team competition.

Of course, some people said this was because Thunderclap didn't have Xiao Shiqin last season, so their skill in the team competition had gone down. This season, with Xiao Shiqin's return, Thunderclap was merely regaining its former ability. This view compared the current Thunderclap with the Thunderclap of last season, and said that if they compared the current Thunderclap to previous years where Xiao Shiqin was present, then it'd be more difficult to say which was better.

The pro scene was filled with such endless debates. After Happy's huge victory, there were people who looked back at their earlier performance, when they were swept in the first round, to find problems.

One match they were swept, one match they won big. These sort of up and down results were the best evidence of an unstable condition!

Regarding this kind of debate, they needed the third round to give them an answer.

One week passed, and the third round of matches were upon them. With the first two rounds to pave the way, the third round seemed much more exciting. Happy had a big loss and then a big win, so how would they perform in this round? Thunderclap was doing well as a team, could they maintain their win streak in the team competition?

The attention that these two teams received was a result of their performance in the first two rounds. But in the third round, neither of them would be in the spotlight. Because in this third round, there finally appeared a match that was an unquestionable pinnacle of showdowns. As much as people discussed Happy and Thunderclap, nothing could steal away their attention from this match.

Glory Professional Alliance Season 10 Round 3, Team Samsara vs Team Tyranny.

The champion and runner-up of last season, a collision like Mars crashing into Earth appeared in the very third round of matches. What match could rival this? None, none at all!

Even the pro players themselves were paying close attention to this match. After all, they were group of people that loved Glory the most, of course they loved to see exciting matches.

Right before the third round of matches began, in the Tiny Herb prep room, Liu Xiaobie was fiddling with his phone. This caught the notice of Captain Wang Jiexi.

In an instant, Liu Xiaobie's expression became strained. He attempted to hide his phone away, carefully and stealthily.

"What are you doing?" But in the end, Wang Jiexi still asked.

The prep room instantly fell silent, and quite a few looked over at them. Everyone knew what Liu Xiaobie was trying to do. This guy just wanted to check on Samsara vs Tyranny in the breaks between their battles. Everyone was curious about how that match would play out.

But even if the captain were curious, he would certainly restabilize his mindset. He wouldn't let himself be distracted during a competition, and of course, he wouldn't want his Tiny Herb teammates to be distracted, either.

"Turn off your phone." Wang Jiexi didn't ask further, and merely spoke in an ordinary tone.

Liu Xiaobie, dejected, took out his phone and turned it off.

Wang Jiexi's gaze swept over everyone, and the players couldn't help but stand up when he looked at them. "This match, our opponent is Bright Green. Although they aren't a very strong team, we can't drop our guard."

"Right," everyone answered.

"Good, let's go!" With that, the Tiny Herb players walked out of the prep room. Liu Xiaobie felt at the phone in his pocket, but in the end, he left it in the room.

Focus on the match!

This is what he told himself. He lifted his head, straightened his shoulders, and followed the pace of his teammates.

All of the matches going on at the same time were affected by this pinnacle match. Even at the pre-match press conferences, many reporters went on a tangent to ask about players' views toward this match.

In Happy's pre-match press conference, one reporter hoped that Ye Xiu would make a prediction. After all, Ye Xiu was very familiar with the old veterans of Tyranny. And as for Samsara? The account One Autumn Leaf, did those ties even need to be discussed?

"Tell us! Just give us a prediction of points?" The reporter hounded Ye Xiu for an answer.

"10 to 0," Ye Xiu said.

"What!" All of the reporters were in shock. Such a big point difference! Which team did Ye Xiu favor so much?

"Who's 10 and who's 0?" someone immediately asked, sensing that there would be a story in this.

"Doesn't matter," Ye Xiu said with a laugh.

"Doesn't… doesn't matter?" Everyone was stunned. What did that mean?

"How… how can you just say this doesn't matter?" said the reporter who had hounded for an answer.

"You were the one who said to just give a prediction," Ye Xiu laughed.

"I…" The reporter was speechless, and could only stare blankly as the Happy players left the conference.

Happy's opponent this round was Radiant. After two rounds, they finally met an opponent that wasn't that strong. Some people were already saying that real gold was revealed under fire, this match wouldn't say much. They needed a strong team to test Happy's true colors.

"Who does he think he is!" The Friday issue of Esports Weekly had lots of predictive discussions, and this one in particular made Chen Guo rather unhappy. As she waved the newspaper around, she fiercely wrote the reporter's name into her memory: Cheng Jianbo.

"This is nothing!" Ye Xiu couldn't help but laugh at Chen Guo's indignation. "This just says that, to some people, we as a team are already stronger than Radiant, and so we shouldn't be compared to them."

"How childish!" Chen Guo said.

"Yes, it's extremely childish," Ye Xiu agreed. He looked around at everyone gathered in the prep room.

"I'm sure that everyone's already aware of this week's analyses of Radiant. They're never a team that places very highly on the Alliance leaderboard," said Ye Xiu. "However, they definitely aren't a team that can be defeated easily. Focus on the match, and don't think about anything else."

In the first round, Happy was swept, and they suffered a lot of discussion. In the second round, they won by a large margin, and once again were subject to a lot of discussion. All of this discussion tended to pile up and add pressure on players, and sometimes this would negatively impact a player's condition. This was especially true for rookies, who didn't have much experience in dealing with this.

"Understood!" But for now, everyone gave Ye Xiu a spirited reply.

In the third round, Team Happy fought against Team Radiant. And after 1 hour and 23 minutes of fierce fighting, the final score hung in Radiant's stadium: 3 to 7, Radiant's victory.

In the prep room before the press conference, Tang Rou said to her teammates, "I'm sorry…"

Chapter 1170: Promise

3 to 7. In the end, Happy lost this round's away game, despite the odds looking to be in their favor.

Their roster this round hadn't seen many big changes, aside from Mo Fan, who had been penalized last round and couldn't appear this round. Instead, they sent up the veteran Wei Chen for the group arena this time.

Happy won all three of the individual battles, entering the group arena with a 3 to 0 lead.

Like the previous round, Fang Rui was first up in the group arena, and he did even better than before. When Boundless Sea fell, he had taken down one and a half players. And then Wei Chen went up. As an extremely old veteran, his reaction time and hand speed had no way of competing with those of the younger players, but although his performance wasn't flashy, Windward Formation still took down the second player and half of the third player's health.

After that, what was left to Happy's powerful anchor Tang Rou was just one opponent at half health. He wasn't a star like Yu Feng, he wasn't even Radiant's core player, he was just a very ordinary player in this mid-low tier team.

The home audience had already given up on this match. No one thought that the 1v2 Tang Rou would miss a victory like this. Some neutral spectators thought this would be very boring. They were only interested in this match to see the pretty female player Tang Rou, but now she only had a player at half health left to face. What excitement was there in that?

Tang Rou lost.

The audience was incredibly quiet - it was clear that Tang Rou was already a very strong player in everyone's minds. It was only after this pause that the home crowd exploded in excited cheering!

They all thought that she would bring the end, but it turned out that she was the one who met her end.

That eye-catching 1v2 performance was of course interesting, but no one wanted to be the victim of such a scene. And this time, Radiant managed it. A character at half health used by a player who was ordinary even by Radiant's standards managed to defeat Tang Rou, the player who had become famous with a single battle.

Tang Rou left the stage. Of course, she was extremely upset with her loss.

In the team competition, she went onstage once again.

Tang Rou was undoubtedly a fierce fighter. But after two rounds of Alliance matches, the characteristics of her fierce style had been seen through. Radiant used tactics specifically to target her, which in turn affected Happy as a whole. Because of this, Happy's rhythm was thrown into disorder.

"No victory is ever guaranteed…" In the prep room, this is what Ye Xiu said to the apologizing Tang Rou. Happy could defeat a giant like Excellent Era, but other teams could defeat Happy in turn. If raw strength was the only thing that determined victory, then what would be the point of competing?

But the factor that determined this match's victory and defeat was very clear. Even the most ordinary viewers could tell that the problems were from Tang Rou.

"We'll have to analyze this carefully during our review session. Now, for the press conference…"

"I'll go!" Tang Rou said.

Ye Xiu nodded and didn't say anything else. Tang Rou never backed down. She would always face any challenges head-on.

For this press conference, Happy sent out Ye Xiu, Wei Chen, and Tang Rou.

As soon as the three appeared, the camera flashes from below lit up the area. The target was Tang Rou, whom the reporters were rather surprised to see. During their wait, they all guessed that Happy wouldn't send Tang Rou to this press conference. This level of pressure was frightening for a rookie to bear. The team would probably try to protect its new members, and have the veterans deal with this situation, right?

But as it turned out, Tang Rou just walked out at the very front, her expression unusually resolute.

Since she dared to come out, would the reporters hold back? Click click click, everyone took their fill of pictures before anything was said.

"Tsk tsk, how popular," Wei Chen remarked.

"Hm?"

"Whether good or bad, at least she's getting a lot of attention now, no?" Wei Chen said.

"How come I smell something sour?" Ye Xiu said.

"Tch, would I care about something as unimportant as this?" said Wei Chen, filled with righteousness. But no matter how you looked at it, the whispering of these two seemed very sneaky, so the reporters turned their cameras and took many pictures of these two as well.

The three took their seats, and the reporters all focused their gazes on Tang Rou, hoping to discover something from her expression. But they were disappointed, for there was no hiding, no flinching. If anyone looked at her, Tang Rou would look right back, and then give a polite smile.

"We can begin," Ye Xiu said.

In their eagerness, the reporters almost raised their feet along with their hands. Ye Xiu randomly picked one.

"Question for Miss Tang Rou! What are your thoughts on your performance in this match?" This reporter couldn't wait any longer. He was so eager that he didn't even bother to begin with the standard phrases like "this battle's loss was unfortunate".

"My performance dragged down the entire team," Tang Rou said. "Because of this, I'm deeply sorry."

Tang Rou's condition was clear to see. An apology now seemed like a very ordinary, standard, expected answer, and so the reporters were unsatisfied.

"I remember that after the last match, you said that you wanted to complete a 1v3. But in this match, you couldn't even take down an opponent at half health. Why do you think that happened?" one reporter asked, with an air of ridicule. Tang Rou's declaration last match about aiming for a 1v3 after her 1v2 was disliked by some people, who viewed her as too presumptuous. This reporter was evidently one such person.

"Victory or defeat is never guaranteed," Tang Rou said, borrowing from what Ye Xiu had just said in the prep room. "But I will definitely complete a 1v3."

"In-game doesn't count!" one reporter jeered, earning laughter from the crowd.

"Right here, on the pro stage," Tang Rou said.

To the reporters, this unparalleled determination and confidence seemed to be unparalleled arrogance. This rookie's skills weren't bad, and she'd managed to complete a 1v2, but just because of that one accomplishment, she thought she could do anything?

Victory or defeat was never guaranteed, the reporters could agree with this. But the person who just said this then said that she would 1v3 for sure. How brazen was that?

The reporters couldn't hold back anymore. After last round, there were already quite a few people who disliked Tang Rou's attitude. Then, even after such a sad performance this round, she still didn't correct herself. She was still overstepping with that bullheaded stubbornness of hers.

One reporter was particularly aggressive, directly shouting a challenge at her during this press conference. "If you can't do it, then what?"

"If I can't do it, I'll leave the pro scene."

The crowd was shocked into silence. As a result, a whispered conversation suddenly happened to become clear for everyone to hear.

"Look look, that reporter over there really looks like a dog." Wei Chen.

"Don't be ridiculous. Which one are you talking about?" Ye Xiu.

There was a pause, and then an uproar.

Evidently Ye Xiu and Wei Chen realized that the sound of their voices had suddenly been magnified. In the midst of the commotion, they each coughed and looked to the left and right, as though nothing had happened.

The reporters didn't even know which side to respond to first. Should they be amazed at Tang Rou ruthlessly betting her own pro career, or should they be amazed at these two Happy seniors, who, instead of protecting their rookie, were mocking a reporter for looking like a dog?

Say, which reporter was the dog anyway?

The reporters couldn't help but look around and size each other up, and those who were stared at for too long turned red in the face. What are you looking at me like that for? Are you saying that I look like a dog?

The thought process of these reporters was shattered into pieces by Happy's rookie-veteran combination, and it was quite a while before things got back on track.

Who looked like a dog? There wasn't much meaning in discussing this question, and in the end everyone's attention returned to Tang Rou's oath.

If she can't complete a 1v3, she'll quit the pro scene?

Everyone looked at Tang Rou, and then at Ye Xiu and Wei Chen. Did Happy's two veterans not hear what Tang Rou just said? They didn't even stop her from pledging such a thing. In fact, they looked as though it didn't matter at all.

"If you can't complete a 1v3, you'll quit the pro scene?" One reporter felt that these two had been distracted and really didn't know the current situation, so, to prompt them, this reporter repeated the statement loudly.

"Yes," Tang Rou nodded.

"Good determination," Ye Xiu said.

"Very daring." Wei Chen even began to clap for her.

The reporters were dumbfounded. These were supposed to be the reliable veterans of this team! How come it seemed like they were just here to stir up a ruckus?

"Do you two feel that Tang Rou can accomplish this?" One reporter took the opportunity to directly ask these two.

"With that kind of determination and daring," Ye Xiu said.

"Even metal can be cut through," Wei Chen quickly followed up.

What nonsense was this? The reporters who were taking notes found that they couldn't bring themselves to write down any more. These two were just out to make trouble, right? Right?

But in the midst of all the reporters who had been thrown off, one reporter was still very clear-headed and asked, "Miss Tang Rou, how many matches do you plan to use to reach this goal? Will you dedicate your entire pro career to this?"

The one who asked this question was gleeful, because he felt that he had found the key point. Tang Rou's oath here was just a game of words. If she can't 1v3, she'll quit. But without a time limit, didn't that just mean she would keep playing match after match trying to 1v3, and if in the end she couldn't do it, then she'd just retire anyway?

You think you're so clever! This reporter smiled coldly.

Tang Rou was about to reply, but Ye Xiu suddenly moved to speak before her.

Was he finally going to rescue her? The reporters all waited to see what kind of trick he would pull.

"Five matches should be enough, right?" Ye Xiu said.

Another uproar from the reporters. He didn't come to her rescue? He actually gave Tang Rou even more pressure?

1v3 was something that many pro players never accomplished in the entirety of their careers. And now, to have a rookie swear to complete a 1v3 within five matches or else quit the pro scene… Did Ye Xiu have a grudge against Tang Rou or something?

"Five matches?" After hearing this number, Tang Rou actually revealed a happy smile. "Then five matches it is!"

Chapter 1171: The New Season’s Tyranny

The reporters couldn't even keep count of how many times Happy managed to cause such a commotion.

1v3 within five rounds!

It seemed like Ye Xiu was making things hard for her on purpose, yet Tang Rou seemed ever so satisfied. Could it be that they had some way ensuring their victory?

The reporters hurriedly checked for Happy's scheduled matches, but after they checked, they were dumbstruck once more.

It wouldn't be an exaggeration to call Happy's match schedule a journey to death.

Round 4, Happy would play their home game against Team Tyranny.

Round 6, they'd be welcoming Blue Rain in a home game.

Round 8, still on their home turf, Tiny Herb would come knocking.

The three teams at the top of the Alliance were all congregated in the next five matches. Happy might have the home advantage all three matches, but if you wanted to complete a 1v3 at the hands of these three teams, that was a senseless dream.

Ye Xiu, you really do have a grudge against Tang Rou! Right? Right?

Several reporters had their heads raised to observe Ye Xiu's expression, while the others checked the other two teams.

Round 5, Happy would challenge Team Parade in their away game, a below average team like Radiant.

In their away game in Round 7, however, their opponent was Team Heavenly Swords.

Team Heavenly Swords?!

The quick thinkers immediately let their imaginations take flight.

From what info they had gleaned from the situation in the Heavenly Domain as well as what Ye Xiu let leak during a certain press conference, it was clear that Team Heavenly Swords and Team Happy had good personal relations.

If they had the confidence that they'd be able to achieve a 1v3 within the next five rounds… Was Heavenly Swords their ace up the sleeve?

Heavenly Swords would let them win?

The Glory Alliance had never had any match-fixing issues in the past. At most, all they had were teams whose morale had depleted with their hope for their goals lost. This sort of situation would usually appear at the end of the season, when the conclusion to the regular season had been set. No team would lose their fighting spirit at the beginning of the season.

Though there might have never been such a case in history, that didn't stop people from making these malicious guesses. Almost all the reporters believed that there must be something fishy going on what with such an absurd promise. Even Chang Xian. Although he wouldn't suspect Happy of faking a match, there must be something going on.

The press conference came to an end before the reporters could figure things out. In the end, all the questions were about if Tang Rou could achieve her 1v3 or not, and no one else cared about anything else regarding this match. Even when the victorious Team Radiant came to the stage, the reporters were still discussing Happy among themselves. After it was announced that they could start asking questions, someone stood and asked a very courteous "congratulations to Radiant for winning the match, how did you feel about it" before the reporters went silent.

The reporters were all absent minded and Team Radiant's players, having come over delighted about their victory, were dumbstruck.

Before the match began, the cheers for Happy wer ever so loud. It was clear that no one was treating them like a new team to the Alliance anymore, but a team far above Radiant.

Radiant hadn't been at all angry about this. Three All-Stars, just the player lineup seemed much grander than anything Radiant could offer. But so what? It wasn't as if Radiant had never seen team with three, or even more, All-Stars. It wasn't as if they had never fought these teams before. When had they ever given up in the face of these odds?

Compared to those powerhouse teams, Happy was nothing, no?

Radiant valiantly received Happy's challenge. Radiant had never expected to find any breakthrough point in the three All-Stars, but the others, the rookies, became Radiant's focus.

They had chosen Tang Rou. She was someone who already held an important position in the team, even being placed as the last defender in the group arena. It was clear how much the team trusted and depended upon her.

Against Tang Rou, Radiant had made ample preparations. Thus, from the group arena to the team competition, Tang Rou had been completely within their grasp, burying the 7 points Happy might've gotten.

Compared to many other teams, Radiant really wasn't very strong, but they hadn't gotten to the point where they could be bullied so easily. This time, using their home advantage, and ample pre-match preparations, they had won a match that many thought hopeless. They were excited and delighted, prepared to discuss their victory at the press conference. Yet, why did they end up ignored like this?

Why would this happen?

The three members of Radiant that attended didn't understand. They weren't that famous, and their team wasn't that powerful, but that didn't mean they should be ignored like this.

At the same time, at another, slightly later, press conference, things were heated.

The most eye catching match of the round, Samsara's away game against Tyranny, had just ended.

Countless players, moved by the persistence of Tyranny's veterans, were wishing them well, hoping that they would be able to get good results in this season, hoping that they would end their pro careers satisfactorily, hoping that they could strike a fierce blow at the Samsara that had shattered their dreams last season.

The result was disappointing.

Team Samsara, challenging Tyranny on Tyranny's home turf, ended up winning by a significant margin of 8:2. They had only lost two points in the individual competitions, and managed to successively overwhelm Tyranny in the group arena and team competition.

And to think, this was their away game. Samsara was truly terrifying this season. With three rounds over, they had won flawless victories in two rounds, and in the third round, against a strong team like Tyranny, they had managed to win with an 8:2. With a total score of 28 after a mere three rounds, Samsara was still far in the lead.

As for Tyranny, at the end of three rounds, they had a total of 19 points, sliding them right back to number eight, the last position for the playoffs.

This opening no longer had an iota of the momentum they had displayed last season. Everyone's worries for Tyranny seemed to have become reality. With another season over, how much had the state of Tyranny's veterans slipped? After last season's close call, had these veterans' morale truly been unaffected? It seemed, with the loss they suffered against Samsara on their home turf, that the things that people were unwilling to see were really occurring.

Was Tyranny truly no longer capable of recreating its past strength? Many fans had already begun crying in the audience after seeing the result of the home game against Samsara.

In the post-match press conference, the air was heavy. Tyranny was comprised mostly of veterans. Many of the reporters offstage had accompanied them for years. Even for those who hadn't, after these weeks of appearing in one another's sight, asking questions, they had manage to grind out some form of acquaintanceship.

Tyranny's upset represented the decline of the era they pursued. Each veteran reporter sympathized with this sorrow. At a time like this, it was mostly newer reporters that would tactlessly touch upon sensitive questions for Tyranny to answer.

"In the new season, Tyranny has already fallen behind Samsara's immense lead by 9 points in three rounds. When faced with them directly, Samsara managed to claim 8 points in their away game. What will Tyranny do next? Will there be any changes made?" A reporter asked.

Make changes?

What changes?

Switch out the old for a newer generation and let that era truly become buried in the past?

"Tyranny will, indeed, make some adjustments." Onstage, Vice Captain Zhang Xinjie answered this question.

"Oh? Could you give us some idea of the specifics?" The reporter asked.

"We will probably introduce some rotation, in order to make the team operate more efficiently," Zhang Xinjie replied.

Rotation! Did that mean that Tyranny was preparing to switch in newer players? Did that mean that the players of that era would be truly leaving the stage?

The reporters gazed at the stage. When Zhang Xinjie spoke, Han Wenqing's and Lin Jingyan's expressions were as calm as ever.

"Then, what is Tyranny's goal this season?" someone asked. Usually, in this sort of adjustment period, the team wouldn't set their goals too high.

"Tyranny only ever has one goal: to be the champions," Han Wenqing answered.

Was this the stubbornness of veterans? The reporters sighed.

"In the next round, Tyranny will face Happy. Is there anything you want to say?" Someone suddenly thought of such a question. Happy, Ye Xiu, this was a person from the same era as Tyranny's veterans. Though Happy had another old player, Wei Chen, his pro career was short; most people saw him to be a substitute or switch, rather than a core member of Team Happy.

"We hope to give everyone a spectacular match." A very standard answer.

"Happy's player, Tang Rou, said that she would achieve a 1v3 within the next five rounds or else leave the pro circle. As their next opponents, what are your thoughts on this?" Tyranny's match had ended late so the press conference was naturally later as well. The information regarding Happy's press conference had already travelled here, and this sort of interview style was something reporters were good at.

"Good resolve. If you want to try to accomplish that against Tyranny, then give us all you've got!" Han Wenqing said.

"Will Tyranny make any arrangements against this?" a reporter asked.

"No." Zhang Xinjie answered with one simple word, but the reporters believed him wholeheartedly. Tyranny's strategist was Zhang Xinjie. Why would this strict and careful Cleric change the rhythm of the team just because of a bet?

"I give my early wishes that Tyranny earns a good result next round." After saying that, the reporter ended his questioning. The other reporters soon followed up, most asking about the switching Tyranny would do.

After Tyranny and Samsara's match, the third round came to a close.

In this round, apart from Happy versus Radiant and Tyranny versus Samsara, two other unexpected conclusions cropped up.

Team Parade had taken down Tean Royal Style, who seemed a little stronger than them, by 7-3 in an away game.

Team Hundred Blossoms, on the other hand, was defeated on their home turf by 301 Degrees with a 3-7.

Apart from that, the strong teams all won as expected, with scores above 7-3. After three rounds, the situations of the various teams were much clearer than they'd been after two rounds.

Chapter 1172: Happy’s Problem of Coordination

The third round of Season 10 finished.

Samsara stood at the top of the point rankings with 28 points. Blue Rain and Tiny Herb were second and third respectively with 27 points. Wind Howl was fourth with 26 points. From the point rankings, these four teams made up the first tier. After them was the fifth place team Misty Rain with 22 points. Thunderclap was sixth with 21 points; their start was looking quite good. In seventh was Void. After a mediocre first and second round, they finally pulled off a dominating performance in the third round, winning against Seaside with a perfect 10 points, placing them at seventh. At eighth place was Tyranny with 19 points. Compared to last season, Tyranny had taken the largest step back.

Outside of the currently qualified playoff teams, the points dropped. Team 301 was at ninth with 14 points, Royal Style at tenth with 13 points. Parade, Happy, and Hundred Blossoms were eleventh, twelfth, and thirteenth respectively with 12 points each. Speaking of which, the ranking for these three teams was quite complicated. Usually, if two or more teams had the same number of points, the teams were temporarily arranged in alphabetical order, by pinyin. If two teams had records against each other that season, they would be ranked according to who had the better record. For these three teams, Hundred Blossoms (Baihua) was first alphabetically. However, Happy had won a match against Hundred Blossoms, so Happy should be ahead of them. But in terms of alphabetical order, Happy (Xingxin) should be behind Parade (Hewu).

It was impossible to reach a consensus just from these three conditions. In the end, Hundred Blossoms' alphabetical advantage was removed and they became the bottom of those three teams. Of course, it was just the start of the season, so it didn't matter too much. But at the end of the season, when accurate rankings mattered, this type of impossibly muddled situation would usually be decided by an additional match. Using something like alphabetical order shouldn't decide a team's final ranking.

After Hundred Blossoms were the lower tier teams, who were all grouped up together. In last place in the relegation zone was Seaside, who had eaten two zeros in two consecutive matches, and currently had a heroic 2 points. Heavenly Swords was in second to last place with 5 points, but the team ahead of them, Miracle (Shenqi), was also at 5 points, only beating out Heavenly Swords (Yizhan) through their alphabetical advantage.

The point rankings as well as the performances of each team in the third round were reported and analyzed.

Happy! Happy again!

In the third round, Samsara and Tyranny was clearly the highlight match. Happy faced a mediocre Radiant, but how come they still made it to the headlines?

The mighty Tang Rou had achieved a 1v2 in the previous round. Why did she lose so badly this round?

Right after this crushing defeat, she claimed that she would achieve a 1v3 within five rounds? And if she didn't she would leave the pro scene?

Damn, this sister's so domineering!

Damn, this sister's so arrogant!

Damn, this sister's so bold!

Damn, this sister's so egotistical!

She had a brilliant victory in the second round, but an embarrassing loss in the third round. Yet even so, Tang Rou was still the most followed player in these two rounds. It was just like Wei Chen said. Whether the attention was good or bad, the attention towards Tang Rou was sky-high right now. After the 1v2 in the second round, quite a few reporters had wanted to interview Tang Rou. After the crushing defeat in the third round, even more reporters wanted to interview Tang Rou.

Seeing how popular Tang Rou was, quite a few people started asserting: promotion. This was definitely the media promoting her.

And the Esports Time reporter Ruan Cheng, who had challenged Tang Rou in the press conference and had Tang Rou make such an arrogant claim, had written a long, flowing article in a magazine calling this all a farce. So what if Tang Rou made such a promise? No one could force her to leave the pro scene. As long as her skin was thick enough, she could endure the pressure of public opinion, and she could give herself a classic excuse like "I can't give up my passion for Glory" or "I'm willing to endure anything for my fans" and so on… As a girl with indisputably good looks, she could definitely win quite some support.

Ruan Cheng's article generated a huge response. In terms of print media influence, the Esports Time was only slightly inferior to the Esports Home's weekly issue.

Those familiar with the Esports Time immediately understood after seeing that it was Ruan Cheng's article. This guy had set his targets on Tang Rou. His article had been written with for a purpose. It was to seal off Tang Rou's retreat path. Having given predictions for her retreat path, if Tang Rou still went along it, she would undoubtedly be viewed as someone with skin so thick that it couldn't be saved. She would receive a huge amount of criticism for it. Under this kind of public pressure, it would be hard to imagine what type of person could continue to survive.

After this article, many reporters tried all sorts of ways to reach Happy, hoping that Tang Rou could say a few words about it. However, Happy blocked them all. Tang Rou seemed to have disappeared. She gave no response to the criticism or the support towards her.

These days, Tang Rou was practicing like crazy.

In Tang Rou's loss against Radiant, the problems showed by Tang Rou were actually Ye Xiu's two biggest worries for her.

The first problem was that if the match wasn't enough of a challenge, she was unable to feel enthusiastic about playing and couldn't bring out her full potential. This sort of mental problem couldn't be described with numbers. It was an issue borne from Tang Rou's personality. In the game, she could still win those non-challenging battles because of the huge disparity in skill between the two sides. But in the pro scene, that huge disparity didn't exist. Facing Radiant's half-health player, Tang Rou still had to concentrate. However, the situation was very different from when she faced Yu Feng and Zhu Xiaoping. In addition, Radiant studied Tang Rou's battle against Xiao Shiqin in the Challenger League and developed a strategy specifically to target her. In the end, the half-health Radiant player beat the full-health Tang Rou.

In the team competition, because Tang Rou felt guilty and ashamed for losing in the group arena, she really wanted to win. This sort of mentality ignited her fighting spirit, thus leading to Ye Xiu's second worry: if her fighting spirit burns too hot, she is unable to exercise restraint.

Both of these two points were issues stemming from her personality. Trying to reconstruct someone's personality was harder than climbing the heavens. These were something that she couldn't control. They came and went subconsciously.

The only way to resolve these issues was to improve her skill level.

It was just like in the game. Even if she couldn't display her full capabilities, she could still win. What she relied on was superior skill.

Understanding this point, Tang Rou focused on being aware of her mentality, while also increasing her practice.　

Morning, afternoon, night. Apart from eating, sleeping, and the appropriate amount of exercise, Tang Rou practiced crazily day and night.

"Is this okay?" Chen Guo was a bit worried and asked Ye Xiu.

"It's always good for young people to practice more. The problem is only whether you have the motivation to persevere," Ye Xiu said.

"So you intentionally gave her the goal of completing 1v3 within 5 rounds, so she has enough motivation to persist with this high-intensity practice?" Chen Guo said.

"No… I'm afraid that her eagerness to win will go over her head and she'll win next round. That would be troublesome." Ye Xiu laughed bitterly.

"Even so, why didn't you give her more room? Even ten rounds would have been better!" Chen Guo said.

"If I say more, with her personality, what do you think she would do?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"Cut it down until she felt like it was right…" Chen Guo said.

"So if I say too much, she'll say she won't need so many rounds and she'll do it in just one. What then?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Fine..." Chen Guo surrendered.

"But what if, I'm saying what if, she can't do it. What then?" Chen Guo looked towards Tang Rou, who was hard at work, and whispered the question to Ye Xiu.

"Yes…" Ye Xiu said.

"What does that 'yes' mean?" Chen Guo was puzzled. Ye Xiu didn't explain, though. He looked at Tang Rou as well. This guy was pretending like he was being profound again. Chen Guo thought to herself angrily.

While Tang Rou was solving her individual problems, Happy also had other problems to fix. Their loss against Radiant in the group arena could be considered as Tang Rou's fault, but their loss in the team competition couldn't be blamed on any one individual. The team competition was fought as a whole. If any one part wasn't working properly, the other parts needed to take on some of that responsibility. And in the team competition against Radiant, Happy had done a very poor job here, even if there was Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui playing. When Tang Rou came apart, these three All-Stars failed to properly adjust the team's rhythm. In the end, Radiant seized an opening and beat them fiercely.

These three All-Stars were unable to adapt to the situation when facing Team Radiant. It sounded hard to believe, but in reality, there was a serious issue between these three All-Stars - they were still getting used to playing and coordinating with each other.

Fang Rui obviously required time for him to grow accustomed to his new Qi Master class. Apart from that, it was his first time playing with Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. He needed time to get used to their rhythm and their habits. Even Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, these two Best Partners, needed time to synergize with each other in a high-level competition.

It wasn't because the two were suddenly unfamiliar with each other after a year of not playing together. It was because Ye Xiu had changed classes.

The unspecialized, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and the unpredictable skill combinations gave headaches to everyone in the Alliance. None of them were able to keep up with such rapid complex variations.

And "everyone in the Alliance" included his teammates Su Mucheng and Fang Rui.

They weren't all-class experts. They had never partnered with an unspecialized before. Their situation was actually the same as their opponents. The only difference was that because they couldn't grasp the unspecialized's rhythm, they couldn't properly coordinate with Ye Xiu.

In the first round, facing Samsara's powerful sweep, there wasn't enough time for this issue to come up.

In the second round, through the map Broken River, they never really had any direct confrontations facing Hundred Blossoms.　　

In the third round, facing the proactive Team Radiant and Tang Rou falling apart, the three All-Stars ran into a serious problem, where none of them were able to coordinate well with one another.

Before even killing any enemies, Lord Grim had dealt a fierce blow to Happy's teamwork.

"It looks like we need to practice harder too," Ye Xiu said after carefully reviewing their match against Radiant.　　

"Yeah!" Su Mucheng's expression was exceptionally resolute. Failing to coordinate with Ye Xiu, how could that be acceptable?

"Damn, I have to keep up with the pace of 120 short cooldown skills. I can already feel my golden right hand crying," Fang Rui said.

Chapter 1173: Intense Practice

After the three All-Star players of Happy carefully reviewed their performance, they began diligently practicing for the team competition. The other teams couldn't quickly adapt to this Myriad Manifestations Umbrella-wielding unspecialized, the likes of which had never been seen before. Those other teams could only try and gain experience through the meager bits of what was available to them: real battles, recordings, and their own imaginings. But Happy could directly practice coordinating with this umbrella-wielding unspecialized. They could come to understand him, they could grow accustomed to him, they could become familiar with this entirely new and unique class.

In this aspect, Su Mucheng and Fang Rui were at a disadvantage. Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, Qiao Yifan, and even Mo Fan had all interacted with Lord Grim for a much longer period of time than them. This was especially true for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. No one else knew this kind of unspecialized, but for these two, this was just another class, always fighting right alongside them as they learned this game. They were the fastest to integrate with this unspecialized, and for now, they were the team players that could coordinate with Ye Xiu the best.

Qiao Yifan grew up in the normal system, and by the time he arrived at Happy, he already had a very solid foundational and technical strength. Like it was for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, the unspecialized was an entirely new thing for him to learn and adapt to, but unlike them, he first had to unlearn some of his established preconceptions about Glory. So, although he had also fought for a long time alongside Lord Grim, his understanding was a little bit weaker than that of Tang Rou or Steamed Bun.

Then there was Luo Ji and An Wenyi. Luo Ji was also a blank sheet of paper that could adapt to Lord Grim, but the problem was that his skill level lagged behind, and he had no way of truly fighting side-by-side with Lord Grim. An Wenyi joined a little later, and he suffered from the same problem as Qiao Yifan. He had to unlearn some things in order to adapt to this entirely new class. Furthermore, his technical skill was also lacking.

And then there was Mo Fan. Just getting this solitary hero to coordinate with the team was already an endeavor and a half, never mind adjustment to Lord Grim in particular. The road was slow and long.

And all of these people were still better than Su Mucheng and Fang Rui, who had only officially arrived at Happy this season.

However, the skill, experience, and awareness of these two players was clear for all to see. After they began emphasizing this aspect of their training, their grasp of the unspecialized improved in leaps and bounds.

Tang Rou was training fiercely, the three All-Stars were training fiercely. The others had no reason to relax, and the entirety of Happy immersed themselves in fierce training. But Luo Ji, who wasn't with the rest of them and who still had to worry about his studies, couldn't keep up with Happy's current pace of training. Because of this, he was filled with anxiety. In comparison, An Wenyi, the other college student here, was much more decisive. This person directly chose to take a leave of absence from school, and devoted himself to professional gaming.

"How did you convince your parents?" Chen Guo had asked him. She felt that, for a student, the greatest obstacle to this kind of decision would be the family.

"I gave them the prize money from the Challenger League," An Wenyi said.

Calm, rational, accurate!

These were the special traits of An Wenyi, the person whom Ye Xiu had found in-game despite his unexceptional skill.

The entire team was busy, and they invested more time than ever into practice. This made Guan Rongfei restless. He essentially never went outside, but now he often came to the practice room to hover behind Ye Xiu and cough meaningfully. He was anxious to finish research on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and he needed Lord Grim's account card to look at the umbrella. But now that Ye Xiu increased training, the amount of time that the card was in use greatly increased, thus reducing the amount of time Guan Rongfei had to study the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. This made him rather distressed.

This is also why powerhouse teams might make two or even three copies of Silver equipment, to facilitate study in the R&D department so there wasn't any conflict between them and the players.

But with Happy's current state and the material requirements for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, making an extra one was definitely unrealistic.

On days when he couldn't get the account card to study the umbrella, Guan Rongfei could only spend his time on the other classes. Equipment for the other classes was, for him, much easier than the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Especially Dancing Rain, whose equipment he had studied and developed for many years now. It was only last season, under the club's orders, that he had stopped working to raise the equipment to level 75. But now, he once again took up this research. He was so familiar with the equipment that he hardly even needed the account card - his mental visualization was enough.

Another week quickly passed, round 4 was just about to start. Happy was about to fight their second home game, and their challenger was the team that was currently the subject of much gossip, Team Tyranny.

One week of training wasn't enough to immediately cause drastic improvement. The results of training were silent and invisible steps upward, droplets that gradually accumulated into something significant. But after this week of intense training, at least Happy's spirits were greatly changed - every player seemed to be shining.

Extra training wasn't too much of a problem for young people, Chen Guo thought as she looked around at everyone.

But… what about you?

Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu.

You're certainly no young person. But to let everyone come together faster, you joined in on the extra training. What kind of impact would such intense training have on a player of his age? Wei Chen, for one, hadn't kept up with this training pace. This let Chen Guo know that older players couldn't push themselves this fiercely.

Chen Guo was very afraid. She didn't even dare ask, because she knew that there was no point in asking. Even if this wasn't healthy, Ye Xiu had no choice but to do this. Only he could wield the unspecialized. This wasn't a class for which they could find a sparring partner.

Aside from well-wishes, Chen Guo could do nothing at all.

September 26th.

One day before the the fourth round of the Glory Alliance Season 10.

Happy, unlike other teams, was still intensely practicing. Other teams, on the day before competition, would generally go through lighter practice. The players still played the game, they wouldn't let their hands get cold entirely, but the lighter practice allowed them to get enough rest and keep their spirits up.

But Happy was still practicing as fiercely as ever. Relaxation time? To them, this had no meaning. Right now, what they needed was to improve as fast as they could. Another day of practice was another day of improvement. Without enough improvement, just taking a break before the match wouldn't change the match's outcome.

Chen Guo looked around at everyone in the practice room.

The weather lately had been alternating between heavy clouds and showers, and although the temperature wasn't high, the humidity made it seem hotter. The two high-power air conditioners in the training room worked incessantly to blow cold air through the room, but many players were still practice until their foreheads were slick with sweat.

They only had to move the mouse and keyboard, which meant that they were really only moving the parts of their body below the shoulder joint. They weren't running, they weren't fighting against some obstacle with their bodies. And yet they still managed to sweat from their exertion.

The tapping and clicking of the mouse and keyboard sounded like a curtain of beads falling to the floor. This tense and high-level atmosphere in the training room made Chen Guo feel like it was difficult to breathe. But she stayed and watched for a bit longer before quietly leaving the room.

When she went downstairs to the internet cafe on the first floor, she heard someone ask at the front desk, "Is Ye Xiu here?"

She went down a few more steps, and saw the panicked and terrified face of the young woman collecting money at the front desk. And then there was a shout in the Internet cafe, and then another, and another.

Chen Guo hurried down the staircase and saw the four people standing in front of the counter. And countless guests in the internet cafe had already left their computers and flocked over.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan… Team Tyranny, the four titans who had been named the Four Heavenly Kings, were standing right in front of the counter of Happy Internet Cafe.

The Internet cafe guests who recognized them instantly went wild.

This sort of thing absolutely never would have happened two years ago.

At that time, Chen Guo was still a diehard Excellent Era fan, and Happy Internet Cafe was still a favorite gathering place for all Excellent Era fans. If a Tyranny player appeared at the front desk then, who could predict what the impulsive fans would do?

But now, things were different. Ever since Chen Guo turned from a fan into a hater, Happy Internet Cafe was no longer filled with such passionate Excellent Era fans. Those that still came were calm and rational fans. They wouldn't necessarily do anything if they saw a Tyranny member.

And now, many of those that came to Happy Internet Cafe were fans of Happy itself. This forced Chen Guo install another door between the stairs and the second floor, and in the back of the building, there was now a direct exit from the second floor.

Fans were wonderful, but they could also be such a hassle!

After Su Mucheng officially transferred to Happy, there was even some shameless male who, carrying a large bouquet of flowers, said that he wanted to express his love to Su Mucheng. Chen Guo was so scared that she almost called the police. At these times, having the more delinquent-like Wei Chen and Steamed Bun around actually made Chen Guo feel a little safer.

In an instant, the Four Heavenly Kings of Tyranny were surrounded by energetic fans.

To openly appear in an Internet cafe, these four Gods were too careless.

Fortunately, no one did anything excessive. Most people just came to watch. Some of the braver ones went up to ask for an autograph, or even begged for a selfie, until Han Wenqing furrowed his brow and everyone scattered back to their seats.

At this moment, Chen Guo realized that there had to be a reason that these Tyranny veterans dared to show up in an Internet cafe. Han Wenqing had the Intimidate skill, with no cooldown. He could activate it whenever he wanted.

This was the first time Chen Guo had met up-close this ten-year captain of Tyranny. Two years ago, this was the painful enemy! Excellent Era's potential fourth consecutive victory was lost to this person, which had earned her hatred.

But now, Excellent Era had faded into the mists, and Chen Guo did truly respect the fighting spirit of these Tyranny veterans. When they lost to Samsara last season, she almost teared up for them.

When interacting with people in the pro scene, Chen Guo often had to remind herself to project a strong aura. She, after all, was the boss of Happy. But in front of this Han Wenqing, Chen Guo felt that she shouldn't try to act all high and mighty in front of him. This was a person who would directly kick out the boss from the training room.

"You're looking for Ye Xiu?" Chen Guo went up to greet them.

"Yes. Is he here?" Han Wenqing asked.

"Follow me!" Chen Guo led the four upstairs, and took the opportunity to study the other three Gods. Zhang Xinjie, hair and clothing immaculate, wearing his glasses. When he stared straight ahead, he would never let his gaze wander to the sides. Zhang Jiale, a spirited and energetic figure, yet revealing a hint of melancholy. Was it because of too many second-place finishes? Chen Guo couldn't help but wonder. Lin Jingyan, the former number one Brawler, didn't have that delinquent aura that Wei Chen and Steamed Bun had. He was a very refined person, and when he saw Chen Guo looking at him, he even smiled and inclined his head.

Chapter 1174: A Casual Greeting

"Ye Xiu, there are people looking for you!" Chen Guo pushed open the door of the practice room. She was a bit excited to see the expression on Ye Xiu's face when he saw these four Gods suddenly appearing here.

"Who?" But to her disappointment, Ye Xiu didn't even look up.

"Me." Han Wenqing didn't let Chen Guo introduce him, he just directly spoke.

"What are you doing here?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Match," Han Wenqing said.

"The match is across the street," Ye Xiu said.

The atmosphere instantly grew cold.

The match was tomorrow. Tyranny had clearly arrived in City H a day early to rest and adjust their condition before the match.

"Everyone, feel free to take a seat!" Chen Guo had to try and diffuse the tension, inviting the four to sit on the sofas near the wall of the practice room.

"Practicing hard?" But Lin Jingyan didn't sit down, instead coming over to watch Happy practice.

"Do you have any dignity? Trying to sneak a peek at our practice?" Ye Xiu finally lifted his head, giving Lin Jingyan a disdainful look.

"Is this sneaking?" Lin Jingyan ignored him and stubbornly continued to look.

Right at that moment, Fang Rui happened to mess up.

"Haha, feeling the pressure from behind you?" Lin Jingyan laughed.

Fang Rui turned around and gave him two middle fingers.

"You changed classes pretty well!" But now Lin Jingyan stopped with the joking tone, and spoke sincerely.

"It's alright!" said Fang Rui.

The two fell into silence.

Former teammates, the number one Brawler and the number one Thief, the famed Criminal Partners, now both abandoned by their team. No matter how honorably they left, it would never be enough to make up for their feeling of loss. And now, one went to Tyranny to persist with the little light he had left, while the other came to the newly-formed Happy, changing classes to strengthen the team. Although they were no longer teammates, the goal toward which they strove was still the same. Now, they would face off against each other onstage. They could no longer strive toward this shared goal together. It was inevitable that one of them would lose.

With Fang Rui's practice interrupted, the team coordination practice could only stop as well. Ye Xiu stood up and looked at the four of them. "Did you need something?"

"Nah, we're staying nearby. We figured we'd come walk over and take a look." As Zhang Jiale said "walk," he himself was walking around in a circle around Happy's lineup of computers, finally stopping next to Ye Xiu. He looked at Ye Xiu's character Lord Grim, who was still onscreen. Lord Grim, the character that had caused so many headaches for the Gods, big and small, of the the pro circle.

"Hey, let me try your little toy here," Zhang Jiale said, trying to squeeze into Ye Xiu's seat.

"Don't you have any dignity? You also want to peek at our equipment stats?" Ye Xiu, of course, didn't give him any room.

"Haha, what secrets do you still have to hide? The stats have long been figured out already," Zhang Jiale said.

The stats of Silver equipment weren't displayed, but for a long period of time, Lord Grim had worn one Silver and twelve Orange equipment. A character's overall stats were displayed, as were those of orange equipment. With the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella as the only variable, it really wasn't difficult to deduce its stats.

"That was before, now we've levelled up, do you need us to tell you that too?" Ye Xiu said.

"Really? 75? How sharp, let me look." Zhang Jiale was still trying to force his way in. If talking about rules, his doing this was extremely inappropriate. Silver equipment were the secrets of all of the teams, no one would ever try to insist on seeing them. Zhang Jiale was taking advantage the fact that he was familiar with them, plus Happy with its grassroots origin didn't have a very serious atmosphere, so he could struggle like this.

"Go away, go play over there." Zhang Jiale was pushed away once and for all, and he could only bitterly give up. Watching him, Ye Xiu was all sorts of speechless. "Don't tell me you're really here to spy on us! For those sort of methods, we'll have to call the police."

"Call the police? How embarrassing is that?" Steamed Bun jumped up. He grabbed a bag of drinks from under the table and swung it around in circles, instantly creating a fierce meteor hammer.

"Guys, can you stop!" Chen Guo yelled, exasperated and feeling the beginnings of a headache. Normally, these Gods were all glittering and glamorous, and she couldn't help but worship them sometimes. But now that she thought about it, not a single one of them was older than herself.

With Chen Guo's scolding, the practice room quieted down.

"So what did you come here for?" Ye Xiu asked.

"It's been a while. We thought we'd come see you," Zhang Xinjie answered. When Chen Guo had gestured toward the sofa, in the end Zhang Xinjie was the only one to neatly sit down, and now he politely gave a response. This made Chen Guo feel that he was the only good person here.

"How about it, it's not bad here, right? Anyone want to come over? Our boss is right here, if you make a good plea, then maybe in the winter transfers you can hop on this championship bus," Ye Xiu said.

"You're really aiming for another championship victory," said Zhang Jiale.

"Who isn't?" Ye Xiu said, before adding, "Oh, you're not. You'd have to get rid of that 'another.'"

"You bastard!" Zhang Jiale cursed. Just in this room, there were many people who had never won a championship - Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Lin Jingyan, none of them had. But Ye Xiu specifically attacked him, to mock his four second-place finishes, of course.

It was said that you shouldn't expose or attack someone's shortcomings, but because everyone here was friendly with each other, sometimes shortcomings were attacked like this. It was just like how Zhang Jiale insisted on looking at the equipment, which would be unacceptable in other contexts with different people. But the problem was, not only did he fail to see the equipment, he was still ridiculed by Ye Xiu. Zhang Jiale was rather depressed.

"If you're not here for anything serious then hurry up and leave, stop disrupting our practice." Ye Xiu started waving his hands to get them to leave.

"You're still practicing even now?" Zhang Xinjie furrowed his brow. To someone like him, who always maintained the strictest of practice schedules, practice the day before a competition was unthinkable.

"What do you understand!" This was what Ye Xiu said to this Glory Master Tactician, a man that really understood quite a lot of things.

Zhang Xinjie didn't retort. He stood up and said, "It looks like your team still has areas that need urgent improvement!"

Chen Guo gulped. Just from this one little clue, he was already able to make such a guess. This "only good person" was in reality quite terrifying!

"Not used to playing with unspecialized?" Zhang Xinjie looked at Su Mucheng and Fang Rui.

"Since you've guessed it, what else is there to say," Ye Xiu said, helpless.

"I hope that we'll have an exciting match," Zhang Xinjie said.

"We will," Ye Xiu said.

"See you onstage tomorrow." Han Wenqing left this final statement, and the four Tyranny players departed.

"I'm feeling dizzy. They seriously just passed by to come say hi? Don't they have anything better to do?" Seeing the four leave, Ye Xiu sighed.

"They completely guessed our current condition." Chen Guo thought about Zhang Xinjie's careful expression, and she shivered at how accurate his judgment was.

"It's not hard to guess," Ye Xiu said.

"So now what?" Chen Guo asked.

"We honestly don't have much hope of winning the team competition. We'll focus on getting the individual battles." As Ye Xiu spoke, he glanced at the time. "It's about time, let's take a look together at our opponents for tomorrow."

"Are we chasing them back here?" Steamed Bun asked.

"Huh?" Ye Xiu didn't understand.

"Aren't they our opponents tomorrow?"

Ye Xiu was speechless. Steamed Bun was being himself again…

After that, the entire team went to the strategy room. Tyranny's match recordings, especially those of the previous three rounds, had already been dug up and prepared. Every day, after doing the intense practice with the rest of the team, Ye Xiu still had to make time to organize all of these materials… Chen Guo deeply felt that they couldn't continue like this. Wei Chen could help to some extent, but he couldn't free Ye Xiu completely. Chen Guo could only be grateful that at least now they had Guan Rongfei and Wu Chen. Otherwise, if Ye Xiu had to manage things on those two ends as well, they would have to cut him into pieces.

Managing a pro team really wasn't easy! During this time, she had been trying to recruit helpers. On the guild side, things were going pretty well. A number of people had been drawn in, giving semi-professional help to run the guild. Even though these people weren't here, but work done in an online game didn't require everyone to be in the same place. As long as there was internet, things could be accomplished.

On the R&D side, Chen Guo also wanted to find more help. Her number one targets were the R&D workers of Excellent Era after the team dissolved. From Guan Rongfei, she had managed to obtain the contact information of three of his former colleagues. But when she reached out, she found that these three were still together, and were still at Excellent Era - New Excellent Era!

New Excellent Era had applied to participate in this year's Challenger League. When Chen Guo checked, they were advancing quite smoothly. Their current roster had Qiu Fei as the core player, and then some former Excellent Era trainees. This season's Challenger League didn't have any monster like last season's Excellent Era; everything was back to normal. Chen Guo casually looked over, and also discovered Team Jade Dynasty, one of the teams they had fought last season. After the entire team had been fired, it seemed like they'd gathered another group of people from who knows where to give it another shot.

At the time, Chen Guo had invited Lin Yi and the others that Jade Dynasty's boss had directly fired. They had expressed that they would consider her offer, and then there was no more news from them. Chen Guo contacted them twice more, but they were still wavering.

Not until the new season began did Lin Yi call her. He and two of the players from Jade Dynasty ultimately decided to join Happy, working for the guild in-game.

For them to reach this decision now, Chen Guo was quite able to understand Lin Yi's state of mind. In the end, he still wanted to be a pro player, and this entire summer, he was likely working very hard to try and find such an opportunity. But by the time the new season began, he had been unable to find a team, and so his dream of being a pro player was put to an end. So, he contacted Happy, and became one of their guild workers.

Relative to ordinary players, Lin Yi's skill at Glory was quite high. For him to be a team captain, he was exceptional in some areas. After he joined, he quickly became Wu Chen's most effective helper.

With the hard work of these people, Guild Happy's current development was very stable. On the high-end battlefields, because Ye Xiu and the others were no longer helping, the guild lost its overwhelming advantage. But in all of the various ordinary servers, Guild Happy was up and running smoothly. Happy finally had its own stores of basic materials filling its vaults. What had happened back in the day in the tenth server, with Ye Xiu selling his labor to obtain dungeon materials, would never have to happen again.

Chapter 1175: Tyranny Fanclub

September 27th, Glory Pro Alliance Season 10 Round 4 began, with Happy playing their home game against Tyranny.

The influence of a powerhouse team was incomparable. Although Happy now had a certain amount of popularity themselves, the crowd they could attract wasn't enough to fill the entirety of Xiaoshan Stadium. Compared to Excellent Era's glory days, when they'd sell out seats and even one ticket was hard to come by, Happy was still lacking.

But this time Tyranny had come, which drew many spectators. Plus, Tyranny itself had its fans organized everywhere. Many of Xiaoshan Stadium's seats were filled up.

For a weak team, this was an annoyance of something fortunate. When a powerhouse came, they could generate a lot of ticket revenue. But at the same time, when a powerhouse came, that meant defeat was likely.

For Happy, this was only their second home game, they didn't have any expectations regarding ticket sales. Even with so many spectators, Chen Guo wasn't particularly excited. Her focus was all on the upcoming match.

There were many highlights to watch for in this match. There was the confrontation between longtime rivals Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing, there was the former duo Fang Rui and Lin Jingyan, there was Tang Rou's promise of a 1v3 within five rounds. Unfortunately, although there were so many highlights, this match wasn't the most beautiful in this round. At the same time, City S's Samsara was playing their home game against Blue Rain.

A showdown between powerhouses, the television broadcast stations wouldn't miss any of it. For those who wanted to watch the livestream of Happy against Tyranny, they would have to stream it online.

Xiaoshan Stadium, the away team Tyranny came onstage first. During an official match, the team members all wore their team uniforms. Tyranny, as a powerhouse team, had unusual influence. Throughout the country, their fans had formed their own fanclubs. Whenever Tyranny had a match, the diehard fans that travelled with the team to watch all their matches would contact the fans in whatever city they travelled to, and they would all come to the match together to cheer Tyranny on. Right now, on the west side of the stadium were gathered many Tyranny fans all wearing Tyranny's uniform, and when their team came onstage, they began wildly cheering and yelling, waving various banners and slogans. Compared to Hundred Blossoms who had come in the second round, their spirit was much stronger.

Although Happy now had quite a few fans, they didn't have these sort of organized fanclubs. Everyone came to cheer the team individually. In the face of the other team's powerful momentum with their organization, Happy's fans suddenly seemed very fragmented. Happy's home field was about to be conquered by Tyranny.

Tyranny's players waved to acknowledge the support of their fans, igniting more waves of excitement from them. It wasn't until the home team came out that Happy's fans started cheering, temporarily suppressing Tyranny's spirit. But it was only temporary. The unorganized and scattered cheers were no long-term match for the Tyranny fanclubs, and Happy's fans had to admit defeat first.

It seemed… they needed to create their own team fanclub.

Seeing all of this, Chen Guo thought back to when she was still an Excellent Era fan and her experiences with Excellent Era's fanclub. These fanclubs, although initially formed from spontaneous friendships, after obtaining a certain amount of unity and influence, the official club would give them a certain amount of support. Happy could also follow this pattern, but for now, since Happy had only just started, they didn't have any powerful clubs. During the Challenger League, Tian Qi and the other guild brothers had grouped together quite fiercely, but now unfortunately they weren't in City H. Building a home team fanclub would progress more smoothly starting from the fans in the city.

The noise of the fans reached a peak when the players of the two teams greeted each other. At this time, the fans would become the powerful backing of their respective teams, giving them momentum from behind. The Tyranny fans, with experience and training, was able to give their team an aggressively powerful momentum at this time.

After the teams shook hands and exchanged greetings, they returned to their player areas. The match was about to begin, and the players for the first battle of the individual round were announced.

Team Tyranny. Player: Lin Jingyan. Character: Dark Thunder, Brawler.

Team Happy. Player: Su Mucheng. Character: Dancing Rain, Launcher.

A faceoff between top-level players at the very start! The crowd went wild. The two players stood from their respective areas, and after a casual greeting, they headed toward the stage.

The experienced players entered the match, and the first battle swiftly began.

A one-on-one map, a village at dusk. It seemed less like a battlefield and more like a scenic view at twilight, slowly revealed by the holographic projection. This was a map with which Su Mucheng was very familiar. She liked the scenery of this map, and because she liked it, she became familiar with it, and once she was familiar, she could use it in a competitive match.

What about Lin Jingyan?

With his former partner Fang Rui, Happy knew all of his secrets. When they were choosing maps, they considered opinions from all sides. Following Fang Rui's reports, all of the maps they had chosen for today's match were ones that Lin Jingyan hadn't studied. Of course, on the other hand, any maps that Lin Jingyan hadn't studied, Fang Rui wouldn't have any deep understanding, either. He had grown up under the same training as Lin Jingyan, the only change being that one year when Lin Jingyan had left first.

That year, Wind Howl had made some adjustments to welcome the new core Tang Hao, so they had practiced a few new maps.

"However, these maps were to welcome Tang Hao, who had grown up in Hundred Blossoms. I think that even if they don't fit Tyranny, Zhang Jiale would probably be familiar with them anyway." This was Fang Rui's analysis. It was evident that the effects of a player transfer were complex and far-reaching. Those who thought that Glory was just about hitting and killing had a far too shallow understanding of this game.

So, for the first battle of the individual round, the player Su Mucheng selected a map she liked, Rainfall Village.

When talking about how big a 1v1 map could be, they would talk about this village. It was really an entire corner of a village.

The two characters loaded on the map and the battle began. After circling around a small hut in front of the spawn point, Su Mucheng already saw Dark Thunder ducking around and borrowing the scenery as cover, looking like he wanted to do some strategic maneuvering.

But at this point Lin Jingyan clearly saw Dancing Rain over here, so Dark Thunder stopped ducking around, and boldly walked forward.

"This map really doesn't have good cover!" Lin Jingyan said in the chat.

Su Mucheng replied with a smiley face.. Of course that was the case. A long-ranged attacker needed the target to exist in their line of sight; it wasn't good for a Launcher if there was a lot of cover. Su Mucheng chose a map she liked, but of course she would first consider how advantageous the map was to her in a battle.

"Here's not bad!" Lin Jingyan suddenly sent this message. Dark Thunder, in the afterglow of the setting sun, circled behind a tile-roofed house.

Su Mucheng smiled. Dancing Rain continued to move, and then she lifted her cannon. Power accumulated at the opening, a charged Quantum Bomb.

Dark Thunder, behind the house, was currently looking around. Lin Jingyan was truly rather unfamiliar with this map, and he was currently investigating to see if he could find something he could use to his advantage. He was trying to develop a strategy, he wasn't in a hurry to directly fight Su Mucheng. As an old veteran, it wasn't suitable if he always wanted to fight head-on to determine victory. A veteran should use the experience and tactics he had accumulated through the years. Leave the direct confrontations and the hand speed competitions to the youngsters!

As Lin Jingyan studied, he suddenly heard a "biu" sound, short and sharp.

Quantum Bomb!

The sounds of the Launcher's skills were quite loud, and they all sounded different. Just from the sound, you could distinguish the skill. Not only could Lin Jingyan hear that this was a Quantum Bomb, he could also tell that this shot was charged.

The power of a charged Quantum Bomb simply couldn't be compared to a direct instant shot. Lin Jingyan hadn't even figured out where Dancing Rain had appeared and he had no idea which way he should dodge. But ducking and rolling would at least reduce the area of his body that was exposed, and it was certainly better than just standing around and waiting to be attacked.

But Dark Thunder had barely started to roll before the powerful shockwave hit. The wall of that tile-roofed house was blasted into pieces, bricks flying everywhere, a few hitting Dark Thunder. The power of the Quantum Bomb could directly break through walls, and the rolling Dark Thunder was sent tumbling.

"Damn, that's dizzying!" Lin Jingyan controlled Dark Thunder to stand up, and saw that the Quantum Bomb had directly blown a hole in that wall. Through this hole, he could see the large open doors on the other side of this building. Dancing Rain? Lin Jingyan had no time to see those shadows clearly, for a beam of light shined at that door, as though to swallow it, but in the end it only passed through the doors, and then the hole, directly toward Dark Thunder.

Laser Rifle!

Across the house, Su Mucheng's attacks were still continuous. Lin Jingyan, who had just been knocked down by that Quantum Bomb, was clearly a bit slow to react to this. He was unable to dodge this Laser Rifle either, and was hit square on, directly pushed back into a pile of hay behind him.

The hay scattered around him, swirling in the wind like snowflakes. Dark Thunder waved his claw and burrowed out of the pile, only to see that Dancing Rain had already gotten a lot closer. She lifted her hand and a brilliant lighter flew toward him in an arc.

Is this still scientific? The throw was this far and this strong, yet the flames of that lighter were as stable as ever.

Lin Jingyan cursed silently, but he also knew, the lighter wasn't the point here, the fearsome thing was the subsequent Heat-Seeking Missile.

Once he accurately studied the path of that lighter, Dark Thunder retreated back, quickly returning to that haystack.

But the path of that lighter wasn't what Lin Jingyan had predicted. It seemed to fly a bit farther.

It was affected by the wind speed?

At this time, there was no time to ponder scientific principles. Dark Thunder retreated further.

Boom!

Dark Thunder was instantly surrounded by roaring flames. When that lighter landed, the Heat-Seeking Missile hadn't even arrived yet. The hay was ignited first.

Suddenly surrounded by fire, Lin Jingyan was clearly stunned for a moment, his controls a bit slow. Dark Thunder was just a few beats slow in escaping from the field of fire, and he was hit by the Heat-Seeking Missile.

The mushroom cloud rose into the sky, and the thick smoke again enveloped Dark Thunder.

Chapter 1176: Starting to Falter

They'd only been attacking for a short while now, only three attacks had been used, but the beautiful rural scenery had already gained a broken wall with a gaping hole, and an inferno of flames, and a rising mushroom cloud.

The sunset, the quiet evening beauty, was gone in an instant. The sight of Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder pathetically crawling out of the thick smoke only added more tragedy to the setting.

But not all was lost. Dancing Rain continued to follow him with her attacks, and Dark Thunder had to jump this way and that to try and hide. Not long after, the map scenery was destroyed even further. This setting was beautiful, but the Launcher was a force of destruction upon this map. And this was a map that Su Mucheng liked…

Lin Jingyan didn't even have the strength to complain right now. He was at far too much of a disadvantageous situation right now, and as he looked around, he couldn't find a single suitable place where he could hide and catch his breath. In the face of a Launcher's firepower, everything on this map might as well be non-existent.

What a weak little village!

This was the only lament Lin Jingyan had left.

Was he going to just lose like this?

There was no way for Lin Jingyan not to think like this. If he lost, the media, the reporters, the commentators, the players, countless people, would they all once again start pointing at his old age?

Do I need your gossip? I know my own condition better than anyone else. Old age? Yeah, right! I'm not even thirty yet, okay?

Lin Jingyan had a very gentle and warm personality. In the face of all sorts of provocative questions, he generally wouldn't have any sort of aggressive response. But no response didn't mean that he didn't have any opinions. Lin Jingyan felt that he was still fine, that he could still fight.

But could he really still fight, or… or was he just unsatisfied, and motivating himself to make this sort of assertion? Sometimes Lin Jingyan himself was unclear, but he still believed in the feelings he had during a match.

This match was extremely difficult. But this was absolutely not because of his age.

On this map, Su Mucheng's offense was extremely coherent. All of the map's features could be used to help her attack. And Lin Jingyan wasn't very familiar with this map. But even if he were, it wouldn't have helped much. By now, the features had basically all been destroyed.

It was definitely because of that kid Fang Rui, Lin Jingyan could guess. But this sort of "selling out" was very logical, and while in Tyranny he had also given lots of reports about Fang Rui, possibly even more than what Fang Rui had revealed about him. After all, he had watched Fang Rui as he grew up, all the way from when he was a baby rookie switching classes and finally settling on a Thief. More could be seen when looking down as opposed to looking up.

Was there really nothing he could use to change this situation?

Lin Jingyan hadn't given up yet. He used the Glory knowledge he had accumulated over eight years.

Thick smoke, thick smoke, thick smoke…

Thick smoke covered the areas the Launcher had destroyed.

And then, the wind direction on this map…

Lin Jingyan studied his surroundings. Behind him, the Launcher's cannon shots were loud as Su Mucheng chased him closely.

Lin Jingyan hadDark Thunder duck through a cloud of smoke. It was much like the effect of a Smoke Bullet; once Dark Thunder entered, he couldn't be seen.

Su Mucheng immediately adjusted Dancing Rain's position.

Over here, a line at 2 o'clock… Lin Jingyan calculated, and continued to move Dark Thunder.

Still nothing?

Su Mucheng had Dancing Ran increase the angle,, but Dark Thunder was still nowhere to be seen.

Next, I can walk over here… this wall was half-exploded, a bit low, if I duck down… no, I'll be exposed. Too bad I don't have the Gunner's Slide Kick! Alright, I'll have to be a bit wasteful…

In a place where there was no target at all, Dark Thunder suddenly used a Tyrannical Chain Punch.

This skill was used to press an opponent onto the ground and flatten them. Naturally, there was a forward charge movement to throw the person. With this throwing animation, Dark Thunder passed over the wall as as though he were crawling.

Then over here…

Lin Jingyan continued his careful calculations.

Su Mucheng was surprised to realize she'd lost Dark Thunder's position.

He just vanished right from under her eyes? Su Mucheng didn't know where he was, so she could only look around randomly.

The audience had the greatest clue. The omniscient view of the battle showed them that Dark Thunder was currently circling around to the back. But the path he chose to get there, how come Su Mucheng couldn't discover him? Even though the screen displayed Su Mucheng's camera view, you needed to be able to visualize on your own to understand what was going on here.

Under his patient persistence, Lin Jingyan finally succeeded in circling around.

The audience let out some gasps. Even the home fans were feeling a little moved. And the Tyranny fans were shouting and cheering like crazy, as though they had just won a grand prize.

But even if he had successfully circled around, Lin Jingyan still had a ways to go! Even if he managed a beautiful sneak attack, that didn't necessarily mean he could close the gap between himself and Su Mucheng for good.

He had spent too long being attacked in the beginning! Lin Jingyan understood this clearly. This opportunity now had been difficult to come by, so he treasured it. Carefully and silently, he moved Dark Thunder forward.

Powerful Knee Attack!

Lin Jingyan finally launched his offensive. Dark Thunder, who had vanished from Su Mucheng's eyes for so long, suddenly appeared, but he was already behind Dancing Rain's body. The knee hit right at the center of Dancing Rain's back. After that attack finished, he followed with a Brick, knocking Dancing Rain dizzy.

Combo start!

One hit, two hits, three hits…

The system's combo counter jumped upward as Lin Jingyan fought meticulously. The veteran maintained the precision and accuracy of his controls. Although his hand speed had slowed, it was now more stable.

To directly take down an opponent with one system-counted combo attack was very unlikely. A pro player might be able to do it when fighting an ordinary player, but in an equal fight, there was no way to play so gorgeously.

So, false combos were created. When chaining attacks together, the usefulness of false combos couldn't be disregarded.

Lin Jingyan's ability to execute false combos was also quite significant. The true combo had already been interrupted twice, but with a precise false combo attack linked on, he was able to continue attacking.

Slap, Uppercut, Sand Toss, Tiger Flips the Mountain, then toss a Molotov Cocktail…

Lin Jingyan continuously adjusted his attack method.

.

But in the gap between the Sand Toss and the Tiger Flips the Mountain, Dancing Rain suddenly fired a shot.

The powerful recoil changed Dancing Rain's position in the air. But the Tiger Flips the Mountain also came very quickly, and the swinging arm headed toward Dancing Rain in midair.

A grenade flew from Dancing Rain's hand.

Lin Jingyan ignored it. He wouldn't give up his currently ongoing offensive just to dodge this attack.

Tiger Flips the Mountain must stop her!

Lin Jingyan grit his teeth. With a swipe of his mouse, Dark Thunder's hands advanced swiftly.

Boom!

The light of the grenade swallowed Dark Thunder whole.

He missed… In the end, the Tiger Flips the Mountain hit nothing but air. The grenade hit Dark Thunder, and Dancing Rain's next attack landed as well, beginning the counterattack.

Lin Jingyan felt a twinge of sadness in his heart.

He hadn't been able to stop it?

If this was before…

Yes, to be suppressed by Su Mucheng at the start of the match wasn't because of his age. But this time, he failed with this Tiger Flips the Mountain, precisely because his reaction time and his speed were falling…

Uppercut, Sand Toss, then Tiger Flips the Mountain… Had he already fallen to the point where he would leave an opening with this combo?

To realize one's inability during a live match was truly a heartbreaking thing. Especially this kind of inability, in an area that couldn't be improved further. If he couldn't do this now, he would never be able to do it again. This is what the passing years brought; no one could turn back time.

Dark Thunder was once again beaten down.

Lin Jingyan, discovering that his ability was slipping, found his attention divided. He was unable to take back the initiative. In the first battle of the individual round, Su Mucheng won.

The stadium was filled with applause.

The scattered fans could still come together at this time to show their enthusiasm.

Su Mucheng came offstage and waved to greet the audience.

Lin Jingyan came offstage and smiled bitterly.

This time, if he was criticized again, he truly had no rebuttal.

Was he really starting to falter? Lin Jingyan lifted his head to look at the scoreboard in the stadium. Tyranny: 0. Happy: 1.

It was just one point.

The difference wasn't so large!

It was still early! Lin Jingyan's thoughts suddenly cleared. If there was an opening in this combo, then in the future he'd just have to pay attention to it, that's all. How could he fill this opening, what effect would this opening have when fighting the various classes, would he need to warn his teammates to cover and coordinate in a team battle…

After they went back home, he would just have to study this!

As Lin Jingyan thought to himself, he returned to the player area.

"Your positioning was pretty good." Zhang Jiale praised him.

"Haha!" Lin Jingyan laughed. It was true, that bit of positioning was pretty good. He had lost some things, but gained some things as well. Perhaps he could no longer accomplish the Uppercut - Sand Toss - Tiger Flips the Mountain, but he could still accomplish this kind of clever positioning.

"Now, watch me!" Zhang Jiale gave Lin Jingyan a thumbs up, and Lin Jingyan responded in kind.

The second battle of the individual round.

Tyranny: Zhang Jiale, using the Spitfire Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Happy: Ye Xiu, using the unspecialized Lord Grim.

"Oh hey, it's you," Zhang Jiale said, as they shook hands before the battle.

"Scared? Kneel before me!" said Ye Xiu.

"We'll see who's kneeling in a bit," said Zhang Jiale.

"Such irrational confidence." Ye Xiu shook his head and sighed.

Zhang Jiale was a mighty God, what was so irrational about being confident? Ye Xiu's mockery was baseless.

"Fuck.." In the end, Zhang Jiale just cursed bitterly. Because he was clear that in a 1v1, his chances of winning were indeed not very high.

His Hundred Blossoms style relied on confusing the opponent and hiding himself. But Ye Xiu was the Glory Textbook, and his skill at playing a Spitfire himself was quite high. Compared to others, he could see through the skill composition of Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossoms style, and then find the secret door to unravel it all.

There was a reason, after all, that Ye Xiu had been able to break through Blood and Blossoms by himself all those years ago.

But the past was the past, and now was now.

Without having fought, who knew the outcome?

Zhang Jiale shrugged his shoulders and entered the player booth.

Second battle of the individual round, begin!

Chapter 1177: Scared?

"Ah!"

The instant the map loaded, quite a few people in the crowd gasped.

Because the map that Ye Xiu had chosen for this round was the Arena.

It was a map used in game when two people wanted a fast match. It was incredibly simple and bare, a square expanse of flat land.

There were no places for shelter, and the area was also very small. When the two characters appeared, their eyes already met, and it would only take a few steps forward before they were within a Gunner's attack range.

"You actually chose this map…" Zhang Jiale said in the chat. The meaning of this map couldn't be clearer. It was a straightforward confrontation, nowhere for the opponent to hide or dodge. Of course, that also meant that you yourself couldn't hide or dodge, either.

"Heh, scared?" Ye Xiu asked.

Scared? Scared? Scared?

Online and offline, it was this same phrase over and over! Scared, my ass! Zhang Jiale fumed, and in an instant he released smoke and fireworks to surround himself, as though it were a small universe suddenly bursting into existence, sometimes shrinking and sometimes expanding.

Ye Xiu didn't hold back either. Lord Grim rushed forward!

The light and shadows shrouded him, an obstruction and an attack all in one.

Lord Grim instantly turned into smoke. What the lights attacked was only a Shadow Clone.

The real body was already behind Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Cut-Throat! Light flashed from his hand.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms rolled and avoided the attack and simultaneously retaliated with a grenade.

Lord Grim didn't retreat or dodge. With a whoosh, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up, and the explosion was blocked outside of the umbrella.

The umbrella closed, flames crackled in the air, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had already become a spear, and Dragon Tooth thrust forward.

Rolling, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was still rolling, and he tossed another grenade of another unknown type.

Lord Grim still didn't give way, the spear was retracted, a slide-step, a palm thrust forward.

Falling Flower Palm!

The slide-step allowed him to avoid the newly thrown grenade, but Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was now two rolls away, a bit out of reach of the Falling Flower Palm.

But suddenly, a cold light appeared, it was Sword Draw!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was retracted, this was the ready pose of a Falling Flower Palm, but having the weapon at one's side, wasn't that also the ready pose of a Sword Draw?

Two skills. One pose. But because of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's ability to shift between spear and sword, they were completely merged together.

This Sword Draw came faster and more unexpectedly.

The normal way to prepare for a Sword Draw was to notice the sheathed ready pose, but because the Falling Flower Palm pose, it was completely overlooked.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was hit by the sword, and blood droplets flew everywhere. Lord Grim took the chance to rush to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms' side. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was broken apart into two tonfas, one in each hand, and he came at Dazzling Hundred Blossoms with punches and kicks.

Sptifires weren't good at close-combat, and Zhang Jiale fought for his life to dodge and get free. Finally, he seized an opening, and a grenade hit the ground.

Burst Grenade!

A powerful knockback came out, a force that couldn't be blocked.

But before this, Lord Grim stepped once.

One step wasn't enough to escape the blow away effect of the Burst Grenade, but one step could change one's position relative to the grenade.

One step forward, the shockwaves from the Burst Grenade would hit Lord Grim's front.

One step backward, the shockwaves from the Burst Grenade would hit Lord Grim's back.

The damage from an AoE skill sometimes varied by whether or not it hit one's back. The Burst Grenade did not follow that rule. Thus, the damage and effects were entirely the same.

What was different was that, behind Lord Grim there was no one, but right in front of him was Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Lord Grim was pushed flying by the shockwave, but since he was sticking so close to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, he immediately hit the other's body, and so Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was sent flying as well.

"You fucker…" Zhang Jiale wanted to cry. Who knew there were such shameless close-combat tactics?

The two characters were together sent flying. In midair, the Spitfire was still at a disadvantage in close-combat, and the midair Lord Grim was already making his next move.

By the time they were about to land, Lord Grim had already sent out a number of low-level attacks, and ultimately he didn't let Dazzling Hundred Blossoms land freely. Eagle Stamp, Falling Light Blade, Lord Grim was stomping on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. And this wasn't the end, there was still a Punisher, several bullets sent to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms' head.

The crowd was shocked!

This was the map with which they were most familiar, this was the method of fighting to which they were the most accustomed. But who could fight with such rapid and fierce rhythm like these two?

Zhang Jiale could hold his own in the beginning, but after Lord Grim started close-combat, he was stuck on the defensive and sent into a mess. He'd only dropped that Burst Grenade with difficulty, hoping to send Lord Grim a little farther away, but Lord Grim had managed to take advantage of it, and he was pushed even more closely to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

The following nonstop sequence of an unspecialized's low-level skills was frankly dizzying. The viewers couldn't even count the number of skills, they could only watch the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifting back and forth, a feast for their eyes.

Attack, attack, nonstop attack. Lord Grim had the advantage all the way. When the occasional attack from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms hit him, it was clearly just his sacrificing a bit of health for a better offensive.

No way, was he really going to kill off Dazzling Hundred Blossoms just like this?

Everyone held this thought in their hearts. And in the end, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was really killed off just like that.

The corpse fell at the corner of the map. Lord Grim sheathed his blade, opened his umbrella, and lifted it to the air to block the raindrops of blood that scattered down.

"These days, I've been training ferociously." Ye Xiu left this final message in the chat and cleanly exited the battle, collecting the point and leaving.

The crowd was stunned for a long time before they finally reacted.

This battle was already over. This was an entirely one-sided domination. And this opponent was by no means an ordinary person, this was the top God Zhang Jiale. In this battle, the unspecialized class revealed its heretofore unseen dominance, extraordinarily high skill speed and complex variations were used to their full potential. This time it was Zhang Jiale who met this opponent, so what if he were switched with other players? How would they fare? Would they also be ruthlessly beaten up like this?

When Zhang Jiale walked out of the competitor booth, his expression was still a little horror-struck.

Before, he had felt irritation at the difficulty of facing an unspecialized. This time, Zhang Jiale felt terror. That huge assortment of the low-level skills of 24 classes, the feeling of them endlessly striking his body with no opening to break free...

But just because he couldn't find an opening didn't mean that there was no opening. It was only because he was unfamiliar, because he lacked experience, that his reaction couldn't keep up.

This battle was pretty good for gathering intelligence, wasn't it? Zhang Jiale laughed bitterly. This was the only comfort he could take from this. He had actually suffered a perfect defeat. Zhang Jiale shook his head and sighed as he walked offstage and returned to the player area. Over there, Ye Xiu had also just returned. Seeing the other player look over here, Ye Xiu smirked. "Scared?"

Scared scared scared! Fuck off with your scared!

But this time, Zhang Jiale was truly a little scared…

For now, they couldn't fight this class. But it was alright. After this round, they wouldn't face him again for several months. The situation then wouldn't be the same!

Now was now. The future was the future.

Without having fought, who knew the outcome?

Zhang Jiale maintained this attitude. To Ye Xiu's "scared?", he shrugged his shoulders and sat back down in his seat.

The second battle of the individual competition was over. Happy: 2. Tyranny: 0, still.

The fans needed morale as well, and their morale generally came from the team's performance. When the team was low, how would the fans have the spirit to cheer you on?

Zhang Jiale's perfect defeat destroyed the fans' morale, and their lagging behind in the points had them in low spirits as well.

At least there was still the third battle, hurry and win a point!

The fans pulled themselves together to cheery Tyranny on. This was an away game, and so the fans were relatively lacking in numbers. Before, their unity and understanding was enough to knock over Happy's scattered fans. But now, their morale was cleanly killed, and meanwhile Happy was all riled up after such a perfect victory. The atmosphere of the home game was won back. After only a few cheers from the Tyranny fans, they were drowned out by the hollering of the Happy fans.

Round 3. Tyranny's player: Song Qiying, character: Striker, River Sunset.

.

A rookie from Tyranny, onstage for the first time, playing the same class as decade-long core player Han Wenqing. And the name of the character he played was from the same line of the same poem as the name of the King of Fighting, Desert Dust.

Was this the successor to the King of Fighting?

The people couldn't help but make guesses. There were two ways to find successors for core characters. One was to raise someone within the team, and the other was to recruit someone from elsewhere who played the same class.

Once upon a time, Tyranny had raised someone to inherit the character. But Han Wenqing was old and strong, refusing to retire, and the person who was supposed to replace him could wait no more.

A pro player only had so many years to shine, and no one would be willing to passively wait and let their time run out. In Season 6, the Striker player who Tyranny had raised to replace Han Wenqing, named Jia Shiming, transferred out of Tyranny.

As it turned out, this was a wise decision. Han Wenqing continued to play from Season 6 to Season 10 now, and was the ace player for all that time. If Jia Shiming had continued to wait, he would have melted on the bench by now.

But after Jia Shiming left Tyranny, he hadn't managed to earn any big fame.

He had chosen to join Royal Style, and after playing with them for two seasons, he transferred to Void. Right now, he was still on Void, but he still had not made it onto their main roster.

Now it was already Season 10, four years of Jia Shiming's professional career had gone by, and no one still expected him to make any grand breakthrough.

Many people wondered, this player had been chosen to be a core player for his team, how did he end up without even a spot on a main roster? How did Tyranny pick people?

Even when Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan joined Tyranny, people brought up this point as ammunition for ridicule. They said that after Jia Shiming, Tyranny no longer trusted their own eyes when picking people, so they could only taken in powerful Gods that had already proven their strength.

This was only a joke, of course. Tyranny's training camp was still very seriously raising young and interested players.

Song Qiying was only 17 years old right now. Whether or not he would become Han Wenqing's successor had yet to be decided for sure.

But as long as he was skilled enough, they wouldn't need to ask Tyranny for any proof.

How would this rookie's first battle play out? As they waited in anticipation, Happy's player had already stepped onstage.

Fang Rui, the master of playing dirty…

Many people were already in mourning. For a rookie, no type of player was more hated.

Chapter 1178: Normal Etiquette

The battle loaded, revealing the map: Magic World.

It was a bit difficult to pin down exactly what kind of world the world of Glory was. There were firearms and cold weapons, there was magic, the Glory world truly encompassed too many things. So, in terms of maps, there was everything from magical dreamlands to a parking lot.

The map that Fang Rui chose was a strange, shifting little world crafted from magic, one of his preferred maps. Lin Jingyan would certainly know this, but Fang Rui wasn't deterred because of that. He was skilled at many maps, so even if Lin Jingyan told Tyranny everything, they wouldn't be able to guess which map Fang Rui would use for this match, and they couldn't specially prepare for every possible map. That was why choosing the map was such an advantage for the home team. Even if the opponent had some understanding of you, it would still be difficult to make any preparations.

The match began, and both characters began to move.

Song Qiying was a rookie that had never appeared onstage before. Aside from age and class, there was no information on him. Although he was only 17 years old, Fang Rui didn't dare underestimate him. After this season finished, Han Wenqing would have played for a full decade. If he still wasn't finished within two years, then some scientists should really take him apart for research.

Needless to say, Tyranny needed a new player to step up. And Song Qiying's age fit quite well. For now, he could play a few matches, gaining real experience and steadily growing up, and in two or three years he could play a big role.

Although Tyranny had made a mistake in the past, there was really no way of underestimating someone who was being raised to be a core player. After the battle opened, Fang Rui opted to lie low as he moved, strategically weaving this way and that as he moved.

On this map were countless magic lights and shadows which were unbreakable. If you touched some of them, you would take damage. Fang Rui knew the distribution of these magic lights like the back of his hand, but if a player was unfamiliar with them, then the battle would become extremely difficult.

In the three individual battles, Happy's map choices were all very distinctive. Su Mucheng chose a scenic map where the props could all be destroyed, Ye Xiu chose a simple and bare stadium map, and Fang Rui chose a magic map where nothing could be destroyed.

The carefully-moving Fang Rui neared the center of the map. He looked outwards, but he didn't find a trace of River Sunset.

Was he also strategically moving? Fang Rui found this unexpected. This was Han Wenqing's successor. Although every player had their own style, it was generally easier to transition if the successor had a similar style to the original. If possible, the team generally hoped that the familiar style of the core player could be passed down.

"Strategically moving? What a personality!" Unable to see his opponent, Fang Rui began his trash talk attack in the chat.

The message was sent, but the opponent didn't respond. The audience members exchanged looks with each other.

Because they knew, Song Qiying was not, in fact, using any strategic movements. He was heading straight toward the center of the map. He hadn't arrived yet only because his movement speed was a bit too slow.

Even with no opponent and no obstacles, Song Qiying had River Sunset move slowly, very slowly. The display screen showed Song Qiying's viewpoint, and everyone could see his camera constantly turning this way and that. But even if you were trying to defend against the opponent, you didn't need to start this early? It wasn't like the opponent could instantaneously teleport to any position on the map. For the two characters to meet, there was a minimum amount of time that would have to elapse first. But Song Qiying acted as though he were defending against something and continued to walk this slowly. After Fang Rui launched his trash talk attack, the crowd anticipated his response, but in the end, he didn't even acknowledge this message, like a stone facing the roaring ocean.

"What's up, too embarrassed to talk? The rookie's quite shy, this isn't like Team Tyranny's style at all!" Fang Rui continued.

"If there's no need, then a reply isn't necessary, it wastes time." Song Qiying suddenly sent this reply.

"Haha, then how come you just talked? Logically, your message wasn't necessary, a waste of time!" Fang Rui replied.

"No, this was my explanation of my position to you. After this, meaningless talk will be ignored as stated above," Song Qiying said.

"Oh really? Then what's considered meaningful talk?" Fang Rui asked.

No reply.

"How is this question not meaningful? If a discussion of what has meaning doesn't have meaning itself, that's just too ironic." Fang Rui was almost talking in tongue twisters, but still, no response.

"My friend, you're really quite resolute!" Fang Rui still didn't give up.

"You really won't say anything?" Fang Rui said.

"Looks like I'll have to think of a meaningful question, then!" Fang Rui said.

"Hm… Did you eat dinner yet?"

The crowd was about to die of impatience. This Fang Rui was only focusing on the trash talk, but River Sunset was already very close to his position, approaching in a roundabout way. Fang Rui had wanted to strategically maneuver around his opponent, but he was the one about to be strategically maneuvered. And he was still trash talking. Spewing this nonsense without losing control, do you think you're Huang Shaotian or something?

Straight Punch!

River Sunset finally circled around to a position with which he was satisfied. While Fang Rui was happily trash talking, he suddenly unleashed a Straight Punch. River Sunset darted forward and was at Boundless Sea's side in an instant, a fist flashing out.

But Boundless Sea seemed as though he were long prepared for this. With a roll, he easily dodged this punch, and even typed another word in the chat: Haha.

This guy!

The crowd was speechless. So Fang Rui had detected River Sunset's movements early on, but he purposely didn't do anything. He continued to use trash talk to pretend that he was distracted, luring Sunset River to take the initiative to attack.

The Straight Punch missed. Song Qiying knew that Fang Rui had noticed him before. At this moment, when the attack was already started, even a normal player would probably continue to attack and see what they could accomplish. But Song Qiying, after this one attack missed, immediately jumped backwards twice. He didn't continue to attack, instead taking a defensive stance.

"What's this, my little friend is a bit of a scaredy-cat? I didn't scare you that much, did I?" Fang Rui continued to blab in the chat, but in his heart he was a bit alarmed. He knew that Song Qiying was about to ambush him, and so he had prepared to defend against it and launch a counterattack. Once the opponent's attack missed, he would seize that chance to attack. But in the end, this Song Qiying immediately retreated after missing that one attack, completely throwing off his plans.

Was this guy really that scared, or did he see through my intention? Fang Rui couldn't help but wonder. Their two characters couldn't just maintain this three body unit distance without moving, of course. When he saw the opponent retreating, Fang Rui finally decided to attack. Boundless Sea's fist swung forward with a low-level Qi Bullet. Attack and disrupt, and then follow through.

But River Sunset didn't dodge this Qi Bullet. He sunk his stance, lifted his chest, left hand protecting his front, right hand bracing his waist, and then after he completed this pose he didn't move, as though he were a statue. Boundless Sea had already prepared a follow up to the Qi Bullet, but he saw River Sunset just take the bullet and sink into this stance.

"Fuck!" Fang Rui suddenly realized what was about to happen and he hurriedly tried to adjust, but the right fist had already swung forward.

A seemingly very ordinary fist, but Fang Rui knew what was about to happen. The attack that Boundless Sea had been preparing was shattered by this one punch, instant proof of its power. And then the punch reached Boundless Sea's chest, and with a burst of power, Boundless Sea was sent flying.

Emperor's Fist!

A punch that looked very ordinary, but hid a vast amount of power.

"You little brat!" Fang Rui was normally the one taking advantage of people, but now he was the one made a fool of. He was rather upset, but could the opponent's attack really be considered taking advantage? It was an upfront and noble punch, was there an attack any more unembellished?

In the end, this unembellished attack became the single thing that broke through Fang Rui's complex plan of attack, with his distraction, interference, preparation, follow-through, and so on.

One strong can defeat ten clever.

Realizing this, Fang Rui calmed down. He needed to carefully deal with this opponent, study his every movement.

Striker River Sunset, Qi Master Boundless Sea, these two Fighters began to brawl.

In the end, Fang Rui's skill was a step higher and he smoothly killed River Sunset. But his Boundless Sea didn't have much health remaining either, only 14%.

When the match ended, Fang Rui let out a relieved sigh, feeling a bit stiflingly hot. This match had not been won easily.

After thinking over this match in the competitor booth for a moment, Fang Rui finally prepared to leave the stage, but then he inadvertently saw Song Qiying standing right at the center of the stage, looking at him.

What's he doing? Standing in the middle of the stage, is he posing for the cameras? Fang Rui was mystified and continued to walk offstage, but suddenly he saw Song Qiying quickly making his way over.

"He's looking for me?" Fang Rui continued to wonder, stopping his footsteps and waiting. Song Qiying came over, and extended his right hand.

Fang Rui hesitantly shook his hand, and heard him say, "Thank you Senior for your teachings."

"Mm." Fang Rui didn't say anything, feeling that Song Qiying must have something else to say.

But no, that was it. After he said this, Song Qiying turned around and headed back.

Fang Rui stared after him, dumbfounded. As it happened, the judge came by to check on the competitor booth, and so Fang Rui asked him, "What's up with this kid?"

"Hm?"

"What'd he run over here for?"

"Shaking hands and giving thanks, normal etiquette for a match," the judge said lightly.

Fang Rui blinked. Indeed, it was the traditional etiquette to shake hands before and after a match. But now everyone was much more casual. Typically, they would just shake hands before a match, and shake hands after a team match, and that was it. For the individual and group rounds, they would skip on this post-match handshake, but this kid still came over to shake hands with Fang Rui.

"Did I inspire him in this match or something?" Fang Rui pondered over whether he had done any deep, significant thing in this battle. When he returned to the player area, he immediately complained to Ye Xiu. "This kid, he's nothing at all like Han Wenqing."

"Yeah," Ye Xiu nodded. "He's more like Zhang Xinjie."

Chapter 1179: A Positioning Expert

The individual competition had finished, and Happy had unexpectedly won all three points. This was a surprising result. But after thinking about it carefully, Happy's three All-Stars had went on stage in the individual competition, so winning all three rounds wasn't too crazy. But then again, none of players Tyranny sent up for the individual competition were weak either. Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale were both top All-Star players.

But Lin Jingyan just ran around in a circle and then flashed before dying, while Zhang Jiale straight up suffered a crushing defeat. It was actually their new rookie Song Qiying who performed well facing the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui. In that match, it wouldn't have been a surprise if Song Qiying had won in the end.

Not earning a single point was a somewhat disheartening outcome for the Tyranny fans. They could already imagine how the media would talk about Tyranny, especially Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale. There would probably be a few irresponsible people that would grab at the opportunity to question if they were too old to play. Those guys would definitely ignore the fact that Ye Xiu, the person who beat Zhang Jiale, was also an old veteran.

After a short break from the individual competition, the group arena was about to begin. Because of Tang Rou's promise, the group arena was viewed with even more interest. From the ongoing discussion, this promise had attracted even more attention towards Tang Rou, but it had also damaged her image. Even just a casual remark claiming a 1v3 within five rounds was already too arrogant and egotistical, and putting her professional career on the line only made her claim even more irresponsible. Glory wasn't played alone. Tang Rou also had a team around her. Everyone could see that the team valued her quite a lot, so even many Happy fans could not agree with her reckless promise.

In any case, what's done was done. In the group arena, Tang Rou would be the first to go up. The other two would be Mo Fan and Steamed Bun.

It was an assembly of rookies. As for Team Tyranny, their first player would be the helper to the Four Heavenly Kings in the team competition, Qin Muyun, and his Sharpshooter Negative Nine Degrees. Their second player would be Bai Yanfei and his Elementalist Rota. Their final player was their one and only captain during Tyranny's ten years of history, Han Wenqing.

If Tang Rou wanted to 1v3, she would need to be beat these three opponents consecutively.

Many people didn't know what type of attitude they should be watching this match with.

If she really did complete a 1v3, it would be proof that her arrogance and ego were not unfounded. That would be truly displeasing.

If she failed to complete a 1v3 and left the pro scene, everyone would feel great, but Happy would have lost a dauntless general. Wouldn't that be bad?

This type of conflict made them feel annoyed at Tang Rou's rash act.

The match was about to begin. Even though Tyranny's failure to earn a single point in the individual competition disheartened their fans, they still cheered them on for the group arena. As for Happy? They had a huge lead, but seeing Tang Rou go on stage, the atmosphere of the crowd turned cold. The cheers for her were sparse and soft.

Chen Guo was very worried. She discovered that this event would greatly damage Tang Rou's image, even if she did succeed with a 1v3. Compared to how the crowd exploded when she completed a 1v2 in the second round, the crowd this time had become ice cold.

"Why did things have to turn out this way…" Chen Guo sighed. If she could go back to that day, she would have done everything she could to stop Tang Rou from going out to the press conference.　　

The countdown ticked. Five seconds later, the group arena began.

Despite receiving such criticism, Tang Rou's style hadn't changed. As soon as the match started, her character decisively charged towards the center.

Shouldn't we give her some applause? The crowd hesitated. They hesitated the entire time. On the other hand, Tyranny's fan group became more and more excited as the match progressed until they seized control of Happy's home stadium.

This time, the unwavering support from Tyranny's fans didn't disappoint. Tang Rou, with a 1v3 as her goal, lost in the very first round of the group arena.

The Tyranny fans were overjoyed. They obviously sent down merciless boos towards her. There were even many neutral spectators and a portion of Happy's fans that booed along with Tyranny's fans.

Tang Rou came down from the stage amidst the boos and returned to her seat in silence.　　

"This Qin Muyun needs to be studied carefully," Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?" Tang Rou looked at him.

"Keep working hard!" Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou nodded her head.　　

Next up was Mo Fan. His one round suspension had been lifted; he and his Deception could come onto the stage again.

Happy's fans suddenly started livening up. Their treatment towards him was the complete opposite of their treatment towards Tang Rou. Tang Rou had originally been Happy's most popular player outside of Happy's Gods...

Chen Guo felt uncomfortable. She glanced at Tang Rou and saw her with her head up. Tang Rou's eyes were staring at the highlight replay of her fight with Qin Muyun. It wasn't until the scene shifted to the upcoming match did Tang Rou's gaze return to the stage.

Qin Muyun, who had beat Tang Rou, didn't have that much health left. His Negative Nine Degrees only had 11% health left, nearly at red blood.　　

Despite facing such a frail opponent, Mo Fan didn't rush over. He moved strategically as always. Qin Muyun also moved strategically. As a result, at the center of the map, neither of them directly appeared. They were all hiding, carefully observing their surroundings.

On the screen, the camera views of both players could be seen, letting the audience know which direction the two were looking at.

From Mo Fan's view, he had already locked onto the location of Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees. Afterwards, he slowly started moving.

He's circling to his back...

Much of the crowd felt quite annoyed. The guy only had 11% health left, yet you still feel the need to sneak to his back? Just charge at him, bring him out, chase him, and kill him.

The opinions of the viewers clearly weren't being sent to Mo Fan's mind. Even if they were, it would be a question of whether or not he would accept their opinions.　　

Mo Fan was outstanding at sneaking behind someone. He quickly traversed in a circle towards Negative Nine Degrees' previous location. Yes, previous. While he was moving, Negative Nine Degrees had already moved, but Mo Fan didn't know.

It hadn't been easy for Deception to find his target, but by the time he got there, his target was nowhere to be found.

He had moved according to his predictions. In reality, he wasn't certain of his opponent's location either. Not finding his target either meant that his prediction had been wrong or his opponent had moved. Mo Fan didn't know which one was correct.　

Just when he was thinking about what to do next, a sneak attack came from behind Deception.

Qin Muyun had moved away, but he hadn't gone too far. An important reason for why he picked his new spot was that he could see his previous spot.

His choice wasn't wasted. While Mo Fan was thinking that he had ran around for nothing, Mo Fan didn't know that he had already fallen into Qin Muyun's trap.

Through the scope of his gun, Deception's head was magnified extremely large!

Snipe! Headshot! Double damage. The powerful impact of the snipe pushed Deception's body askew. Negative Nine Degrees rushed out and immediately started attacking fiercely. Deception was suddenly enveloped in a rain of bullets. The Sharpshooter's attacks weren't as fierce as Launcher's, and their skills weren't as handy as Spitfire skills. In reality, most of their skills were simply normal attacks with buffs.

The number of bullets produced from Rapid-Fire, Dual Shot, Scatter-Shot, and other Sharpshooter skills were definitely the champions among other Gunner classes though.

Deception was in a tough spot. This time, Mo Fan didn't employ his favored strategy of running away and then searching for another opportunity later. Instead, he had Deception directly attempt a counterattack.

However, to counterattack, the first step had to be to break through Negative Nine Degrees' bullet rain.

Shadow Clone Technique? Smoke Bomb? Substitution Technique?　　

When an opportunity arrived, Mo Fan used his escape skills. However, to his surprise, he was still unable to escape. Negative Nine Degrees' attacks were always able to instantly shift to where ever he had just escaped to in pursuit.

"He's being suppressed that hard?" Fang Rui was astonished. Tyranny's old generals hadn't performed well today, but their rookies were giving a frightening show.

"His positioning is extremely good," Su Mucheng said. She was a Launcher and proficient at a support playstyle like Screen Cannon. With just one glance, she could see the key to Qin Muyun's complete suppression towards Mo Fan.

Negative Nine Degrees' position allowed him to cover all of Deception's options, including the possibilities from Deception's various Ninja skills. He wasn't just standing there either. Whenever Deception moved, he would always adjust according to the situation, maintaining his positional advantage.

"He's a positioning expert!" Ye Xiu concluded.

Positioning experts were especially suitable for playing long-ranged classes. Long-ranged classes had attacks with wider coverage. When melee classes picked spots, what they could attack was only limited to the area immediately surrounding them. When long-ranged classes picked spots, the area that they could cover was on an entirely different level. Very few players were like Ye Xiu, who picked flat maps without any obstructions. In maps with obstructions, long-ranged players with poor positioning skill would find it difficult to bring out their class's full capabilities.

Qin Muyun was this type of expert though.

After watching Tang Rou's match and this current one, Ye Xiu could completely confirm it.　　

"Positioning… Mo Fan is quite good at that too, no?" Chen Guo said.

"Mo Fan is an expert at picking static locations. Qin Muyun is an expert at picking spots while moving. The two are completely different," Ye Xiu said.

"Then this match…"

"If you can identify the opposing player's possible movement options, you can make accurate predictions. No matter how great you are at positioning, there will always be dead angles. Thus, after making predictions, the rest is up to reacting to the opposing player. However, Qin Muyun adjusts his position extremely fast. Trying to escape one step at a time isn't likely. In order to escape, you need to complete it one go. And when you do, you have to be careful that your choice wasn't read by him or else he'll just start suppressing you again," Ye Xiu said.

"From what you're saying, this guy sounds invincible…" Chen Guo said.

"If you have Mo Fan compete against him in positioning, then yes, he's practically invincible," Ye Xiu said.

"Then what should he do?" Chen Guo said.　　

"Find a way to restrict or interfere with his positioning," Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1180: Dumb Method

All attacks began from positioning, and positioning came from choosing a position and moving there. Harassing an opponent and limiting their freedom to move was equal to interfering with the foundations of an opponent's offensive. This reasoning was very simple.

Ye Xiu had fully analyzed the problem at hand already, but Mo Fan clearly hadn't realized the key to resolving his current situation. Mo Fan, having specialized in scrap-picking, had honed the skills and awareness required for scrap-picking to an amazing degree. However, his other abilities fell short. After joining Happy, he relied on self-teaching due to his loner personality. Now, he was a registered pro player. His abilities were special in their own way, but Mo Fan was still greatly lacking a lot of theoretical knowledge.

In addition, Qin Muyun specialized in this sort of foundational skill, which was something easily dismissed by others. No reports had ever highlighted this ability of his. Ye Xiu and the others had also never noticed during their limited preparations. It was only now, at the match itself, that they noticed.

He's so hard to deal with, I can't shake him off!

Mo Fan currently had that vague idea. The reason why he was hard to deal with and impossible to shake off eluded him, and he didn't even think to try and find it.

His thought process was rather simple, just to run and shake him off. Deception kept running, but Negative Nine Degrees was like a personal satellite, always following him and suppressing him with bullets.

"This idiot!" Chen Guo watched anxiously. Mo Fan was currently just challenging Qin Muyun to a contest of movement. If Ye Xiu dared to say that Qin Muyun would be unbeatable at such a competition, then it was clear how large the gap was between the two. If they continued like this, would Deception be defeated by Qin Muyun with this amount of health?

Tang Rou had been defeated in the first round and, to her, this was a huge disappointment, because her goal was to accomplish a 1v3. However, in the group arena, leaving the opponent with 11% health left wasn't bad. However, Happy's second player didn't seem to have any way of dealing with this remaining 11%, and that was no good at all.

"Calm down. He's not as stupid as you think," Ye Xiu said, watching the match.

"What?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"He's saving his skills," Ye Xiu said.

"Hm? What does he want to do?" Chen Guo didn't bother guessing and asked directly.

Her answer came in the form of a sudden change in action from Mo Fan.

Attack! A full frontal assault!

Ninjas were designed as a rogue-style class, talented at ambushing and assassinating. Currently, he was acting more like a main DPS, using brute force.

Smoke Bomb, Substitution Technique, Shadow Clone Technique, Storm Shuriken!

One Ninja tool, one disruption skill, one disruption plus movement technique, one projectile. Finding an opportunity, Deception unleashed four consecutive skills. Negative Nine Degrees' movements were still not disrupted. Mo Fan had never noticed that it was Negative Nine Degrees' movements that were causing him trouble,, but the purpose of these four skills wasn't to disrupt his movements.

These four skills were just to create an opening.

Ninja Arts: Shadow Dance!

The four skills were just to create a chance for this powerful skill.

Deception quickly leapt to Negative Nine Degrees' side. Negative Nine Degrees moved about the encirclement. His precise choice of pathing and positioning were just starting points while on the offensive, but when on the defensive, they were sometimes everything. Negative Nine Degrees was actually able to dart out of the encirclement.

However, it had cost him. His health had fallen even further.

Deception's offensive didn't end there. Attack, attack, attack, relentlessly attack.

The health of both sides were dropping. Deception's might be depleting faster, but Negative Nine Degrees had started with less health.

"What a dumb method!" Ye Xiu exclaimed.

"Hm?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"He's copying Little Tang," Ye Xiu explained.

Chen Guo started, and then, when she looked back, she realized something.

Qin Muyun was still that Qin Muyun. When he had fought Tang Rou, he might have won, but it cost him almost 90 percent of his health. It was clear that facing Tang Rou's style was still very stressful for him.

Mo Fan couldn't find where the problem lay, but he had watched the previous match. He knew that with this way, he could lower the opponent's health. Thus, after saving up his skills, he launched a fierce offensive. He might have not be as intense as Tang Rou, but Negative Nine Degrees didn't have much health left anyways.

So this was the dumb method… As Chen Guo thought to herself, she glanced at Tang Rou who was next to them. Was Ye Xiu's analysis of how Mo Fan should deal with Qin Muyun for Tang Rou to hear?

In the end, Mo Fan won, but Deception had lost almost half of his health. Compared to Qin Muyun's 11 percent, Happy had still lost.

Tyranny's second player Bai Yanfei stepped into the arena.

As a member of Tyranny, you had to be at least a little tyrannical. Bai Yanfei's Elementalist really shouldn't be called Rota, but Cannon Tower*.

Elementalists didn't have as good of an attack range as Launchers, but when discussing AoE, magic won against technology. Out of all the light, dark, fire and ice elements, the character Rota focused on AoE skills. When he charged into the middle of the map and didn't see Deception, he just unleashed a barrage of attacks onto the map and blasted Deception out of his hiding place before blasting him to death...

Rota didn't use up much health, but Happy was already at their last player, Steamed Bun. On the field, Steamed Bun had performed admirably, but in the end, he was unable to complete a 1v2. In the Group Arena, Tyranny had won back two points.

The Tyranny fans now really had something to be excited about. They organized their cheers, once again defeating Happy's home advantage. Next, was the all important team competition. The overwhelming cheers lasted until the lineup for the team competition was announced.

Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, Tang Rou.

This lineup seemed to be Happy's best lineup. Currently, it was the fourth round and Team Happy hadn't sent out any other players.

Tyranny: Zhang Xinjie, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Qin Muyun, Song Qiying, Bai Yanfei.

No Han Wenqing!

When the lineup for Tyranny was announced, the audience was in uproar, including Tyranny's own fans.

Switching people in and out for the team competition was a common sight, but core players were very rarely switched out. They were core players because they were irreplaceable in the team. The entire team's strategy revolved around them.

But now, Team Tyranny's lineup didn't include their captain of ten years. In the post-match interview after round three, they did say that they were going to introduce some rotation, but no one would have thought it would start from their captain, Han Wenqing.

They had switched in Song Qiying, who played the same class as Han Wenqing. He might have fallen in the individual competition, but he did rather well. He was one rookie that people would be keeping an eye on.

Discussions arose. Was Tyranny already transitioning between a new and old core player?

If even Han Wenqing was beginning to back down, then what about Zhang Jiale? Or Lin Jingyan?

The entire stadium was filled with whispers as the players met center stage to shake hands.

"How come Old Han isn't playing? He afraid?" Ye Xiu asked with a smile.

"Rotation," Zhang Xinjie replied briefly. Anything he could say had to be true, had to be fact.

"Even core players are being rotated?" Ye Xiu voiced the crux of the problem. Rotation was normal, but rotating out core players was only done when it was necessary. It wasn't normal.

"It's none of your business!" Zhang Jiale retorted. Zhang Xinjie didn't say anything else, silently nodding in agreement to Zhang Jiale's words. Since it was none of their business, there was no need to explain.

"Fine, let's fight then!" Ye Xiu didn't bother to continue the conversation. The members of each team got in place. In the end, Happy, even after their week of specialized training, wasn't able to defeat Tyranny's experienced players. With Tyranny's Master Tactician's flawless planning, Happy wasn't able to cause any upsets. In the team competition, Tyranny won against Happy, gaining another five points. After losing all three points in the individual competition, Tyranny won the group arena and team competition, turning the tides and winning Happy 7 to 3.

There was no need to talk of how excited Tyranny's fans were. As for Happy, disappointment was inevitable, but their spirits weren't all that low, since after all, Happy's loss wasn't too ugly. The only awkward aspect was that Tang Rou, who had said she would complete a 1v3, had been defeated in the very first round. However… Tang Rou wasn't very well liked among Happy's fans either recently. Most people didn't mind seeing her fail. Not many people would feel sorry about this.

In the post-match interview, most of the questions were about the 1v3, as expected. Tyranny replied with the attitude they always had and showed their support to Tang Rou's promise. This answer clearly wasn't something the media wanted. Currently, very few media outlets were on Tang Rou's side. The more mockery they could get from other team, the better.

In Happy's press conference, Tang Rou didn't attend, but they couldn't escape these sorts of questions. However, the reporters really stood no chance against the few that attended. Especially that Wei Chen, who didn't even play during today's match, spewed out words at the press conference he somehow got to attend. The questions surrounding the 1v3 had been somehow swerved off topic to the Alliance of the past. He had rambled for ten minutes and the reporters were all at a loss...

Happy and Tyranny's match had its spectacular moments, but nothing that could really be written about. It was Tyranny, with their rookie replacing their core player captain in their team competition, that became the center of discussion.

The most popular match of the round, Blue Rain versus Samsara, had finished by then as well. Blue Rain, challenging Samsara in an away game, didn't manage to halt Samsara's momentum in the end. The final score was set at 3 to 7. Blue Rain had gained a point in the individual competition and two points in the group arena.

In these two consecutive rounds, one home game, one away, both against the powerhouses of the Alliance, Samsara had truly been tested and passed these tests. Who could stop Samsara's advance? This became a hot new topic. Tyranny had fallen, Blue Rain had fallen. Who was next? Tiny Herb? Or Wind Howl?

Chapter 1181: The Demonic Journey to Championship

Although Samsara's performance was as strong as ever, on the points rankings after this round, they slipped down two places. Tiny Herb, who had originally only lagged behind by one point, won 9 to 1 against Miracle and surpassed Samsara by one point. Wind Howl, who was originally behind Samsara by two points, had swept Bright Green 10 to 0 and were also now one point ahead of Samsara. Because of their alphabetical advantage, Wind Howl (Huxiao) was currently in the lead. Tiny Herb (Weicao) was in second with the same number of points, 36, and third place was Samsara with 35.

After losing in their away game to Samsara, 3 to 7, there was a bit of distance between their 30 points and the first three places. Misty Rain had 30 points as well, but lost alphabetically (Yanyu) to Blue Rain (Lanyu) and were currently in fifth.

Sixth place Tyranny was now a full ten points below the first place. Although their 7-3 win against Happy wasn't terrible, the fact that they'd gotten a big fat 0 in the individual competition was still snatched up by the reporters looking for a topic of interest.

There were two other teams also at 26 points, Thunderclap and Void. This round, Thunderclap played an away game at 301 Degrees, and in the end they tied at 5 to 5.

This result happened when one team won all of their individual battles, and the other team won 5 points in the team competition. This result was relatively rare. The individual battles were split into the individual competition and the group arena, and those 5 points were split up, so a team could normally snatch at least one or two points. Unlike the team round, there were no teammates to help save a dangerous situation, and the team's strength was scattered. There could be a situation like Tian Ji's Horse Race*, or just one large mistake that affected a battle's outcome.

Thus, even when a powerhouse faced a weak team, they wouldn't dare to guarantee a full 10 point victory. With one small mistake, the opponent could snatch that one or two points. It could be said that it was even more difficult to get all 5 points of the individual battles than the 5 of the team competition, since the team competition was determined in one battle.

And in this match, 301 Degrees won 5 points in the individual battles. As long as they won the team competition, they would win 10 to 0, a perfect victory. But in the end, even though they had the home advantage, they were still defeated by Thunderclap…

To fail to get a single point in the individual battles would definitely have an effect on a team's mindset when entering the team competition. Thunderclap, however, was exceptionally resolute. Thunderclap's change this season had been discussed all throughout the past three rounds, some people felt that they had changed, while others felt that this was just the return of the old Thunderclap. But after this team competition, famous commentator Cha Xiaoxia wrote that Thunderclap had indeed changed, even from the previous Thunderclap that had Xiao Shiqin.

"The current Thunderclap is more confident and more determined.

This change is what Xiao Shiqin brought back upon his return. He experienced a failed year with Excellent Era, but he found exactly what he needed. He brought this back and changed the face of Thunderclap. I look forward to their performance this season."

This was the commentary Cha Xiaoxia wrote after this round. And, as a self-proclaimed Happy fanboy, he of course wouldn't skip on the commentary of Happy vs Tyranny.

Regarding Tang Rou's promise of a 1v3, fanboy Cha Xiaoxia was resolute in his hope that Tang Rou would succeed, but he was still a bit worried. He worried that Tang Rou couldn't accomplish it, but he also worried that Happy, in order to facilitate the 1v3, would ruin the rhythm of their their team arrangement. In this round, Happy's order of battle for the individual battles were indeed different from before.

In comparison, the Esports Time reporter Ruan Cheng, who attacked Tang Rou the most, didn't write much after Tang Rou lost to the first opponent in this match. All he said was a simple "as expected." It seemed that Ruan Cheng wasn't someone who would get excited over the just smallest thing, and it even seemed that he had begun to lose interest in this matter. However, the people who knew Ruan Cheng understood that this was just because the time wasn't yet ripe. She had five rounds to 1v3, this was only the first.

"If she doesn't do it in four rounds, and in the eighth round, Ruan Cheng isn't at the Tiny Herb vs Happy post-match press conference, then there are only two possibilities. One, Tang Rou completed the 1v3 in that match. Two, Ruan Cheng experienced an inescapable natural disaster." This was the judgment of someone who knew Ruan Cheng well. This wasn't even a Glory match any more, it seemed to be a showdown between player and reporter.

Winning 7 points against Happy, Tyranny's current score of 26 points wasn't too bad. But Void (Xukong), who also had 26 points and was one place behind Tyranny (Batu) by alphabet, hadn't done too well this round. Although they were playing an away game, their opponent Conquering Clouds wasn't any strong team. The final score of 6 to 4 was unsatisfactory to Void supporters.

There was also Hundred Blossoms. After losing to Happy in their away game, they played a home game in the third round, but lost to 301 Degrees, 3 to 7. It seemed like Hundred Blossoms was beaten senseless. This round they fought an away game against Seaside, but the end result was still only 6-4. It had to be remembered that Seaside was the team with the worst performance in the first three rounds. Aside from winning 2 points against Misty Rain in the first round, they were swept in the second and third round. In low spirits, they fought against Hundred Blossoms who was also in bad condition, they actually managed to snatch 4 points. Even though Hundred Blossoms won and Seaside lost, but because of each of their skill levels and positions, Hundred Blossoms was the one unsatisfied, while Seaside seemed to have found the light of dawn.

After Hundred Blossoms' small victory of 6 points, they were 11th on the leaderboard with 18 points. Ahead of them was the team that had tied with Thunderclap, 301 Degrees with 19 points. Ninth was Parade, after fighting a home game against Radiant, a team around their skill level, they earned a beautiful 8 to 2, and currently had 20 points.

Royal Style was at 12th, having suffered in their away game this round against Heavenly Swords 3 to 7. Royal Style slid down two places on the leaderboard, while these 7 points allowed Heavenly Swords to finally fight out of the relegation area, to 16th place.

At 13th was Happy, at 15 points after four rounds. Aside from their big win against Hundred Blossoms in the second round, they had not tasted another victory. Disregarding the first place on the leaderboard, their distance to eighth place, the last playoff spot, was a large 11 point difference.

This ranking was a far cry from their early declaration of aiming for the championship. Quite a few people talked about this alongside Tang Rou's 1v3 in five rounds. Was this sort of arrogant attitude just Happy's style?

Crashing in two consecutive rounds, Happy couldn't help but feel a little disheartened. Even though they knew that this team still had problems here and there, their thirst for victory wouldn't be dampened at all. Sundays after match Saturdays were Alliance-regulated rest days, but when Chen Guo came to the Internet cafe early Sunday morning, she saw that the door to the second floor was already opened, everyone already lined up in the training room.

These guys…

Chen Guo couldn't help but sigh. In reality, she'd already lamented this many times. Even if Happy's people might lack in skill, their spirit was never something to worry about. Big loss, big win, ups and downs, many people might not even be able to sleep at night. But Happy's people could always adjust, and continue to sit in front of their computers, working hard.

Like this, we'll win for sure. Chen Guo carried this thought, and Happy continued to train hard.

Round 5…

Round 6…

Time passed quickly. September was over in the blink of an eye, and they were now halfway through October. Starting from the fifth round, the Pro Alliance was reaching consecutive highs, powerful matches appearing one after another.

In Round 5, Samsara played an away game at Tiny Herb. Samsara's crushing dominance seemed to shrink again, but they still managed to win, 6 to 4. On Tiny Herb's home field, Samsara obtained a small victory. In the same round, another match between powerhouses received attention, Tyranny against Blue Rain. On their home field, Blue Rain emerged victorious, 7 to 3.

And then in Round 6, there were two more important faceoffs. Tiny Herb at Tyranny, Wind Howl at Samsara.

In the end, Tyranny earned a small victory over Tiny Herb, 6 to 4. But the discussions about their capabilities didn't quiet down. Compared to their strength last season, where they had led the leaderboard the entire time, this season Tyranny was hovering just above the cutoff for playoffs, even falling down occasionally. They no longer had the boldness of last year.

Samsara had their home game this match, taking down Wind Howl 8 to 2. And in the post-match press conference, the manager of Club Samsara suddenly expressed his complaints about Samsara's match schedule this season.

"Starting from Round 3, Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Wind Howl… If I called this the most demonic match schedule in history, I don't think anyone would object? At the same time I haven't forgotten, after this round in Rounds 7 and 8, we're facing Misty Rain and Void. This is truly an unforgettable journey to the championship."

In reality, the sharper reporters discovered early on that Samsara's match schedule was so demonic, and they'd used this in some of their questions toward Samsara. Samsara didn't try to avoid the topic, but they downplayed it. Now after six rounds of opponents, four of which were powerhouses, no matter whether they were home or away, Samsara managed to defeat all of them. No one asked, but Samsara now voluntarily brought up this point.

The reporters suddenly understood. Samsara didn't want to discuss this before because they wanted to follow the style of their captain Zhou Zekai: no talk, just do!

And so they won their way here. Big or small victories, they won against every powerhouse.

And so now, they could discuss this problem with no pressure at all. This wouldn't feel like an excuse, because they had completely conquered this challenging match order.

The cameras clicked and flashed as the reporters asked each of the players onstage about their feelings after facing this demonic match schedule.

"These victories were extremely important, both in earning points for our team, and in suppressing our main competitors. I'm glad we were able to accomplish this," Vice-captain Jiang Botao said.

"Not bad, but I think that we can do even better." Bringing One Autumn Leaf from Excellent Era and swiftly becoming a crucial player for Samsara, Sun Xiang had become less haughty than before, but his confidence had increased quite a lot.

"…" Samsara's Captain Zhou Zekai, after about ten seconds of long thinking, finally nodded. "Good."

"What's good? That winning these matches was just 'good,' or 'good' thing you managed to win these matches?" one reporter asked.

"Mm…" The long thinking was inevitable, and everyone waited patiently.

"Both!" After this long thinking, Zhou Zekai replied with this one word.

"Could you talk about your views of Tang Rou of Happy, who declared she would complete a 1v3 in five rounds?" The reporters tirelessly chased after almost every player in the Alliance with this question. They were still asking, which meant that Tang Rou had yet to succeed. Right now, three of the five rounds had passed. Tang Rou only had two more chances.

Chapter 1182: Round 5, Round 6

In the fifth and sixth rounds, Team Happy's opponents were Team Parade and Team Blue Rain.

Away game against Parade, home game against Blue Rain, but their scores were 3-7 and 1-9. After their win against Hundred Blossoms in the second round, Happy had now lost four matches in a row. Even though their losses to powerhouses like Tyranny and Blue Rain were expected, teams like Radiant and Parade were only mid-tier teams in the Alliance. Disregarding the championship, even if their goal was just to make it to playoffs, they needed to earn points against teams like these.

But facing Radiant and Parade, the final score was 3 to 7 for both matches. They won all three individual battles, but in the group arena and the team competition, they couldn't defeat their opponent.

The strongest new team in history?

After the sixth round, the issue of Esports Time that released once again used this title, the same title that had been brought up after the second round. That time, Happy was the headline on the front page, but this time, they were just in a casual spot in the issue, and the title now had a large question mark after it.

After 6 rounds, Happy had 19 points at 15th place, only 9 points away from the relegation zone of ten points. Maintain their current position? Everyone felt that this goal was realistic for them. As for championship or whatnot… That was such a joke, wasn't it?

This was Ruan Cheng's mockery in the latest issue of Esports Time. It seemed like he was no longer interested in Tang Rou's promise of 1v3, and he now focused his efforts on doubting the entirety of Happy. It had to be said that Ruan Cheng was an experienced reporter. After six rounds, he accurately pinpointed all of Happy's problems.

"The various teams all worried in the face of Lord Grim's new unspecialized class, but it now seems that this worry was unnecessary. Instead of saying that Lord Grim is their threat, it should be said that Lord Grim is their helper. I think that if Ye Xiu were not using this unspecialized right now, and was instead using a Battle Mage, Team Happy's scores would be slightly better than what they are right now. Though, if that were the case, would the self-declared 1v3 pretty female rookie still have a spot on the team?"

Ruan Cheng correctly identified Lord Grim as the culprit of the problems of coordination that Happy faced, his tone all sorts of mocking, and in the end he still remembered to single out Tang Rou and her bet.

Esports Time's articles could to some extent influence public opinion. In round 7, Happy played their away game at Heavenly Swords, and in the pre-match press conference, the reporters were already coming to attack.

"Losing four matches in a row, the unspecialized has a strong problem of compatibility with the rest of the team members. Happy's performance in this season so far is far from your target of the championship. What do you think about this problem?" one reporter asked Ye Xiu.

"Our team is improving every day, and every round could see a turning point," Ye Xiu answered.

"Really? Then could you give a prediction of how many more rounds that'd take?" someone asked, biting on that "more." Ye Xiu took a look, wasn't this that reporter from Esports Time, Ruan Cheng? Unlike Esports Home, Esports Time didn't have reporters stationed everywhere and reporters following teams. As a half-monthly magazine, they didn't need news as urgently as weekly publications did. They generally didn't report extensively on specific matches, and instead published more overview-type articles. So their reporters often wouldn't appear at every live match, and would instead hunt for material as needed for what they wanted to write.

It was clear that after Tang Rou, Ruan Cheng considered Happy as his material. After his article, he once again came to Happy's home game. This was the fourth round of the five-round promise. In two rounds, the bet would be decided, and it happened to fall on a week where Esports Time was set to release an issue. Ruan Cheng was calmly absent from the previous three rounds, but this round he finally couldn't restrain himself and came to Happy.

To emphasize that "more," he was clearly referencing the fact that Tang Rou's five-round promise was nearing its end. Ruan Cheng certainly had reasons for being unable to stay away from this match. Tang Rou's five-round promise happened to fall during a demonic match order. Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, who expected a rookie to accomplish a glorious 1v3 in the face of these powerhouses? Thus, the key was in the rounds against Parade and Heavenly Swords.

Tang Rou had failed in their match against Parade, so now, their match against Heavenly Swords was critical.

Plus, there was the fact that Heavenly Swords and Happy were on such good terms with each other. What if they had some prior arrangement? Everyone could see Tang Rou's importance to Happy. If she really ended up quitting, not only would it affect herself, it would be a huge blow to Happy as a whole. Under these conditions, whether or not she could complete a 1v3, Happy was probably even more nervous than Tang Rou.

At this time, they met Heavenly Swords. Heavenly Swords and Happy had a good relationship. And this team had a special characteristic. Their captain was the boss, the main players were just a group of the boss's friends. A team that played Glory so much that they invested money into a team to enter the Pro Alliance, one could imagine how unscrupulous these people were. Ruan Cheng truly worried that these guys would throw a match. So he wanted to come to this match in person. If Heavenly Swords did do this, then Ruan Cheng would be powerless to stop it, but he could at least carefully stare at everything that happened in this match. He wouldn't let these group of people carelessly discard the spirit of competition.

So in this pre-match press conference, he asked a question like "how many more rounds" because he wanted to see if Happy dared to confidently declare that today was the day.

Ye Xiu looked at this guy, laughed a little and asked, "What do you think?"

Ruan Cheng blinked, then chuckled. "I'm the one asking the questions here, how come you're asking me now?"

"Yes, I'm asking you, how about you help give us a prediction?" Ye Xiu said.

"I hope that Happy will obtain satisfactory results today." Although Ruan Cheng hoped that Happy would fall over and die in the street forever, in public he still got by with some righteous words.

When the other reporters asked questions, they were all about Happy's difficulties and Tang Rou's 1v3.

After six rounds, the standings were becoming clearer and clearer. Right now, they were separated into three tiers.

The first seven teams all had scores above 40 points. Samsara, with 49 points, was once again in the lead. Wind Howl was second with 47. Blue Rain and Misty Rain with 46 points each were third and fourth. Because Tiny Herb lost consecutively to Samsara and Tyranny, they had 44 points and were in fifth. Thunderclap, the team regarded as changing the most this season, were in sixth also with 44 points. Void had 42 points, seventh place.

After these seven teams, the 40+ point top tier ended. Tyranny at eighth place was still in range for playoffs, but they only had 35 points right now. Although this score was a distance away from the first seven, it was about the same distance from the teams in ninth through twelfth. All five of these teams were in the 30-point mid-tier. Judging by the current point standings, they all had a chance of earning the eighth spot in the playoffs. Hundred Blossoms hadn't encountered a strong team in rounds 5 and 6, so they finally performed rather well and earned the ninth place spot with 32 points. Afterwards, Parade, 301 Degrees, and Royal Style were tenth through twelfth place.

After them were Radiant and Heavenly Swords with 22 points each, and after that were the bottom tier teams with below 20 points. Happy, at 19, was first among these teams.

There weren't too many surprises in the sixth round. The strong teams continued to be strong, the weak teams lost in all sorts of ways. The final point counts were about as expected, comparing the teams' strengths on paper. Tyranny was the biggest disappointment. Last season they had swept countless forces, challenging records, yet this season they were at the doorway to the playoffs, a distance away from the first seven.

Thunderclap was the biggest excitement. Even though they frequently made it to playoffs, it was normally by a small margin, squeezed in like Tyranny was now. But now, their point score was good, only five points away from first place. Aside from points, what was also important was their change in matches. Their current confidence and resolve was a rare sight in the past.

Last season, Hundred Blossoms had gotten off to a weak start before ending strong. Their playoff fight against the strongest team at the time, Tyranny, made them optimistic about their future. But this season, in the very second round they were powerfully defeated by Happy, then drifted along in a dreamlike state for a few rounds. These past two rounds though, they finally seemed to wake up, but on the whole, their performance was rather disappointing.

These three teams, as well as Team Happy, were currently the subjects of the most discussion. Clearly, there wasn't much good to say. People generally enjoyed seeing other people's suffering.

At this time, the round 7 matches were finally about to begin. Like the previous rounds, this round didn't lack exciting matchups. Samsara, with their demonic match order, after fighting four powerhouses would be facing Misty Rain this round. In addition, the four powerhouses were all fighting each other this round: Tyranny at Wind Howl, Blue Rain at Tiny Herb.

The television broadcast team was in a dilemma! It was too hard to reconcile all of these conflicting important matches. Happy, Hundred Blossoms, Thunderclap? No matter how much discussion they generated, they couldn't compare in such a situation. In the end, they chose to broadcast Wind Howl versus Tyranny. Tiny Herb and Blue Rain had their old rivalry, but Wind Howl versus Tyranny represented a confrontation between the new and the old. Ever since Tyranny gathered its three old veterans, this sort of conflict noticeably became much more intense.

At the same time, the players of the various teams appeared onstage.

"God, hello! Everyone, long time no see!" Lou Guanning pulled out the attitude of a host at this home game, giving Happy's members a grand and warm welcome.

"Long time no see, long time no see." Upon investigation, Happy's closest friendships were really just with these few from Heavenly Swords. Compared to the previous rounds, where the pre-match player greetings were just formalities, this time they truly expressed their feelings of having not met in a while, shaking hands, and even chatting a bit.

"How are you? Going onstage today?" Ye Xiu asked as he shook Sun Zheping's hand.

"Of course," Sun Zheping said.

"Oh really? I really want to just crush your hand right now!" Ye Xiu laughed.

"Just try it." As Sun Zheping spoke, he tightened his grip. His hand was injured, but not to the extent where he couldn't feel anything. He just couldn't endure the rapid, long-term, high-intensity controls required in playing Glory competitively, that was all.

"Haha, see you onstage." Ye Xiu shook his hand free and went to the next player. In Heavenly Swords, it was still just the same five plus Sun Zheping who had the professional attitude. The other filler members just skillfully walked by with no fighting spirit, as though they just wanted to hurry up and sit back down.

"God, have some mercy on us!" Lou Guanning cracked a joke when he shook hands with Ye Xiu.

"Not good, the judge is listening!" said Ye Xiu.

"Kidding, kidding!" Lou Guanning quickly said. Glancing to the side, he saw the judge really was aiming his ears toward them. Because of Tang Rou's promise, the relationship between these two teams had been brought up again and again, and Lou Guanning was well aware of this. But in the middle of this turmoil, Ye Xiu still said this sort of thing.

"God, you're just too good at making small talk!" Lou Guanning said, wiping away sweat.

Chapter 1183: That Familiar Feeling

After this genuinely warm-hearted greeting, Happy and Heavenly Swords began their match.

This was Heavenly Swords' home game. Although they were a very distinctive team, just from the number of seats filled, it could seen that they weren't a particularly popular team right now. Even after one year in the Alliance, they weren't any better than Happy. In the end, strength was the most important thing in competition, and Heavenly Swords' strength was only about mid- to low-tier. Additionally, Heavenly Swords wasn't the only professional team in their home city. For many years now, City B was home to Tiny Herb, which was a team that was much more famous and had long established themselves as this city's symbol of Glory. Heavenly Swords was both a weaker and a later team, so it was very difficult for them to establish themselves here.

While they were preparing for this, they had billed themselves as a grassroots team, which made a lot of noise in game. But now everyone knew the truth. The only thing "grassroots" about Heavenly Swords was their strength. The five players were all from extremely rich families. Not a single hair on their heads was "grassroots."

Heavenly Swords wasn't too successful commercially, but no matter how senior or professional a Glory commentator was, they wouldn't casually try to judge the operations of a team like Heavenly Swords, which was formed by some people who played Glory themselves and invested their own money to form a team, even acquiring a stadium. Their beginnings were different, so it wasn't suitable to apply conventional logic to them.

But no matter what kind of background or what kind of business operations, when a team stood here, victory was everything. The players of both teams returned to their respective player areas, until only the first two players in the individual competition remained onstage.

Ye Xiu.

Sun Zheping.

"Not bad." Sun Zheping was very pleased with this matchup, and a fire ignited in his eyes.

He'd retired for many years, and then returned to this stage. This was all familiar to him, and yet foreign at the same time.

What was familiar was that, no matter what updates and upgrades there were, this was still Glory's battlefield, it was still the same 24 classes to slaughter.

What was foreign was that many people he had known in the past were no longer here. With every round of battle this season, all Sun Zheping saw were unfamiliar faces, including the people currently standing by his side. None of them were the Alliance of his memory, the teammates of his memory.

Characters as strong as iron, players like flowing water.

It's all in the past…

This wasn't the first time this sigh had crossed Sun Zheping's mind. But now, in this moment, the one who stood before him on the battlefield - Ye Xiu!

Sun Zheping felt as though he were suddenly transported to those earliest seasons, with familiar people, familiar characters, familiar settings, familiar feelings.

"Let's begin!" Sun Zheping clenched his right hand into a fist, lifted it to his mouth, and blew inside.

In the past, this motion had been his habit, but many fans had now forgotten it. Even Sun Zheping himself hadn't revived this habit after his return. But now, after suddenly rediscovering this feeling of familiarity, this trademark motion naturally reappeared.

"Don't push yourself." Ye Xiu saw everything. He smiled, and entered the competitor booth.

The battle began.

Berserker Another Summer of Sleep, unspecialized Lord Grim, appeared at the two corners of the map.

When the map loaded, the audience was stunned.

This was Heavenly Swords' home game, they had the right to choose the map. For the individual battles, the maps were of course chosen by the battling player. And the map that Sun Zheping chose was the Arena, the map that was limited in size, with no obstacles or changing features. It was the same map that Ye Xiu had chosen in the match against Tyranny, when he completely defeated Zhang Jiale.

And now, Sun Zheping chose this same map to welcome Ye Xiu in a battle. Of course, he hadn't known beforehand that his opponent would be Ye Xiu, but the choice of this map still seemed like it was sending some message to Happy.

"What a…"

Once they entered the map, Ye Xiu was about to send a message, but he'd only typed out two words before Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep had already sprinted several steps forward, sending a Collapsing Mountain his way.

It was a very normal opening for a Berserker, but when Sun Zheping displayed this skill, something felt different about its momentum.

Why was that?

For someone like Ye Xiu, with many years of Glory experience, this wasn't enough to cause a doubt.

It was rhythm, Sun Zheping's rhythm, revealing this fierce and aggressive momentum. Ye Xiu had only typed two words before the light of the blade was already falling.

Ye Xiu could only switch his attention to controlling his character. Complain about the map choice? Sadly, Sun Zheping didn't give him this time.

When the Collapsing Mountain fell, Lord Grim had already rolled to the side. Without waiting, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened to become a spear, slashing up with a Sky Strike. It seemed that this skill was a bit hasty, since Sky Strike had lesser priority than Collapsing Mountain. If these two skills met, Collapsing Mountain would shatter the Sky Strike.

But experienced Glory players could quickly realize that the timing of Lord Grim's Sky Strike was impeccable. It would hit the opponent exactly when Another Summer of Sleep's Collapsing Mountain hit the ground and ended, completely avoiding the system's determination of priority.

Unfortunately, Sun Zheping was one of these experienced Glory Players. The Collapsing Mountain, about to hit the ground, was suddenly twisted to the side.

Such a small twist didn't change the time difference between these skills, but it allowed the shockwaves from Collapsing Mountain head closer toward Lord Grim…

The skill had reached its ending sounds, and Ye Xiu noticed this change, but there was no time to change his controls.

Collapsing Mountain hit the ground, and in this moment the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella lifted up in a Sky Strike.

Hit!

Another Summer of Sleep was sent to the air, but at the same time, Lord Grim was blown back.

Lord Grim was unable to dodge the shockwaves of Collapsing Mountain.

This was just two low-level skills, but they encompassed such a rich, exciting confrontation, completed in a rise and fall. Those with weaker eyes, whose skills weren't high enough, didn't even notice the precise timing of the Sky Strike or the urgent adjustment of Collapsing Mountain. Those who just treated this as a direct clash of two skills were, as the saying went, burning a piano for fuel and cooking a crane for meat.

Boom!

At this moment, there was another explosion between the two characters as they were pushed away. Lord Grim, knocked away by the shockwaves of Collapsing Mountain, shifted his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into gun form and sent an attack toward Another Summer of Sleep. But Another Summer of Sleep immediately used a Blade Master's Guard, parrying the fired bullets with his sword.

"Your reaction's not bad!" This time, Ye Xiu had time to type out a message. This was a change of skill that only an unspecialized could manage, but Sun Zheping still managed to react in time.

"Don't push yourself." Sun Zheping didn't care if the time wasn't exactly right, he just shoved Ye Xiu's exact words from before the match right back at him.

"Not at all." Ye Xiu still sent a reply. As soon as Lord Grim hit the ground after the shockwave, he lifted a cold light and swept toward Another Summer of Sleep.

Assassin skill, Shining Cut!

In an instant, the distance that seemed to be growing between the two characters was suddenly shrunk again. And in this moment, Another Summer of Sleep was still rolling on the ground, a Quick Recover after being hit by Sky Strike.

Destruction Slash!

As Another Summer of Sleep stood up, he unleashed this Destruction Slash.

The Berserker was a wild and aggressive class, and the skills of this classes often had one characteristic: high priority.

The sub-level 20 skills of an unspecialized had no way of competing with the priority of a Destruction Slash. Lord Grim's rushed approach with a Shining Cut seemed more like he was delivering himself into the jaws of a tiger.

The Destruction Slash, carrying the Berserker's intent to kill, surged toward Lord Grim.

But Lord Grim's body vibrated, and a strong aura seemed to envelop his body.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Lord Grim used this Striker skill now, meaning that he intended to take this Destruction Slash head-on.

The damage of a Destruction Slash wasn't very high, as it was more of an effect-inducing attack. Targets hit by a Destruction Slash would have a large reduction in defense, this was the so-called "destruction." So, taking a Destruction Slash wasn't just sacrificing some health, it also meant that in the next five seconds, the character's defense would be reduced by up to 70%. Classes with naturally high defenses were especially affected by this skill, which was why it was called a nightmare for high-defense classes.

Lord Grim's equipment was a chaotic mess, with no bonus effects from class armor, and the defense granted was all over the place, not following the logic of a single level. And now that he activated Reinforced Iron Bones, which raised his defense not by percent but by points. This, plus the chaotic defense of the character Lord Grim himself, and then reduced 70%, the question of what his defense would ultimately be after all of that was a complicated calculation…

The audience didn't need to calculate, because once this attack hit, they could directly see the changes of the character's stats. And the pro players? With their practiced calculation ability, they could instantly grasp the effect on Lord Grim's defense after a points increase and a percentage decrease.

The end result: 7% reduction.

7% decrease in defense, ten times less than 70%. The effect of this Destruction Slash was basically negated by this Reinforced Iron Bones. But the Reinforced Iron Bones wasn't as simple as just increasing defense. In the 20 seconds of Super Armor after activating this skill, it also guaranteed that the character could unleash unreasonably strong attacks.

The Destruction Slash slammed down.

Lord Grim's body swayed slightly, but under Super Armor, this swaying was basically the extent of the effect of Destruction Slash's priority.

Lord Grim swung his fists, which clenched the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, already shifted into two tonfas.

Straight Punch, Knee Attack, Uppercut, Qi Bullet…

The combo attack was already unleashed, landing like raindrops upon the body of Another Summer of Sleep. Lord Grim's strengthened state exuded an intense madness, hardly below that of a Berserker…

That's right… If he weren't like this, how could he have broken our Blood and Blossoms combination all by himself back then?

As he watched Another Summer of Sleep suffer this succession of attacks, Sun Zheping rediscovered another familiar feeling of days gone by.

Chapter 1184: That Terrible Feeling

Lord Grim practically only used Grappler close combat skills. In their match versus Tyranny, Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was directly blown out under this howling whirlwind of attacks. What about Zhang Jiale's former partner of Blood and Blossoms, Sun Zheping?

There weren't many in the crowd with such old memories of the past, but for these two players, this match was a battle that had continued from the past until today. Sun Zheping seemed to have never left, and Ye Xiu seemed like that past Battle God.

"It won't be so easy!"

Sun Zheping roared in the chat. Another Summer of Sleep seized an opening, an aura of blood erupted from his body.　

Berserk?

No, this was even stronger than Berserk. It was an Awakening skill learned at Level 50: Bloodthirsty Frenzy.　

Bloodthirsty Frenzy could not be stacked with Berserk. Only one status effect could exist at one time. Bloodthirsty Frenzy increased offensive stats by 25% more than Berserk, and also gave the user Super Armor and a Bloodthirsty effect, which can be split into two opposing effects. Bloodthirsty gave the user 10% Life-Steal for all attacks, but Bloodthirsty also traded health with each attack, consuming one's own life to deal more damage to the opponent.

When this skill was activated, it was very rare for Berserkers to continue being on the defensive. Just the Super Armor effect that was stronger than Reinforced Iron Bones could let the Berserker avoid the effects of most skills.

However, grabs were a special case. As soon as Ye Xiu saw Sun Zheping activate his awakening skill, he immediately dashed forward to try Fling him. However, Bloodthirsty Berserkers were even more ferocious than Berserk Berserkers. The heavy greatsword was almost like a lightsaber as it cut through the air. Lord Grim's hand had yet to extend when Another Summer of Sleep's greatsword arrived. Ye Xiu realized that if they had to compete in speed, Lord Grim would be at the disadvantage.

Guard!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a sword. Lord Grim raised the sword horizontally and blocked the attack with a clang. This Guard had been executed tightly, but the Bloodthirsty Another Summer of Sleep had extraordinary strength. Although this attack had been blocked, Lord Grim had actually been knocked back, his two feet sliding over the ground.　　

This wasn't outside of Ye Xiu's expectations though. Lord Grim borrowed the momentum and leaped back. His sword returned to its sheath, and the umbrella turned into a gun, shooting the ground with Aerial Fire to quickly pull the distance between the two of them. However, Another Summer of Sleep's greatsword had already arrived.

This guy!!

Sun Zheping's speed had exceeded Ye Xiu's imagination.

This attack wasn't a skill. It was just a normal attack, which had little starting and ending lag. The greatsword sliced through the air in an arc to try catch the Aerial-Fire retreating Lord Grim. Aerial Fire worked, but Lord Grim was still caught by the tip of Another Summer of Sleep's greatsword.

Bullets shot straight at Another Summer of Sleep's chest. Blood splattered everywhere, but Another Summer of Sleep didn't even flinch. He raised his greatsword in the air. Sword shadows from Wild Blood Strike spread through the air and hacked at Lord Grim, dragging along a bloody mist.

With just one attack, Lord Grim's health slid down. Even the crowd felt worried.　　

Knights had exceptional defense. It wasn't just because of the plate armor worn by them, but rather their Plate Armor Proficiency that took the health and defensive capabilities of plate armor to the next step. However, just the existence of Plate Armor Proficiency wouldn't make an Elementalist want to choose Plate Armor for better survivability because they couldn't give up the Intelligence and Cast Speed from Cloth Armor.

Every class obtained huge improvements in combat capabilities from Armor Proficiency, but the unspecialized didn't have these. Lord Grim could only rely on the original stats of the armor to strengthen himself. However, he effectiveness of the armor on Lord Grim was weak. It couldn't compare to his transforming Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Wild Blood Strike struck Lord Grim to the ground. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim try to roll away, but Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep was already in pursuit. With an Earth-Shattering Slash and the offensive buffs from Bloodthirsty, it was almost like he teleported. His figure flickered. He suddenly appeared in front of Lord Grim and slashed downwards with his greatsword.

Lord Grim dodged again. However, Earth-Shattering Slash dealt AoE damage, and Lord Grim was unable to completely get out of its range. Under the intense swaying from the earthquake, Lord Grim wasn't able to stand up stably. Another Summer of Sleep slashed twice, horizontally and vertically, completing a Gore Cross.

Hit, hit, consecutive hits!

Sun Zheping bravely activated Bloodthirsty Frenzy, letting him forcefully interrupt Lord Grim's continuous attacks and also giving him the initiative.

This bravery and boldness did not let down his former title as the Number One Berserker. No, even now, no one had this same confidence and this same valor to employ such a brute-force method to take back the initiative. To many people, this type of choice might be unwise. If Lord Grim's grab had been just a bit faster, he might have been able to throw Another Summer of Sleep away before his frenzy of attacks.

However, Sun Zheping had done it. This wasn't his first time either. In his professional career, who knew how many times his risky and imprudent brute-force transformed into the deciding point. This was not just luck. Behind this brute force hid precise observation and judgement. After that was his determination and resolve to put everything into one move. This was what many lacked, but Sun Zheping possessed.

To others, the always advancing Han Wenqing was more fierce, while Sun Zheping was more wild. It was a wildness that disregarded everything else!

"It won't be so easy!"

In the public chat, Sun Zheping's words from before his Bloodthirsty Frenzy activation had yet to disappear. These same words suddenly popped up again. These two seemed to like to return each other's words in today's match. However, did just saying it won't be so easy make it easy?

Lord Grim suddenly trembled. This unspecialized also turned scarlet red. A dense aura of blood seemed to be emanating from his skin.

Bloodthirsty Frenzy?

No, that wasn't possible.

Those who understood the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella knew that while a skill could be added to each transformation, awakening skills such as Bloodthirsty Frenzy were exceptions. Level 50 awakening skills as well as Level 20 class advancement skills were every class's most distinct skills. They were skills that could not be used by any other class. An unspecialized was no exception.

Lord Grim wasn't using Bloodthirsty Frenzy, which meant the only other possibility was Berserk.

Berserk was very different from Bloodthirsty Frenzy, but it was generally viewed as a lower-leveled Bloodthirsty Frenzy. In fact, according to Glory's narrative, Berserkers learned Bloodthirsty Frenzy through their understanding and control over Berserk. Bloodthirsty Frenzy could be considered an upgraded version of Berserk.　

At this moment, Lord Grim activated Berserk. Did he want to want to use the budget "Bloodthirsty Frenzy" to fight with the real Bloodthirsty Frenzy? And because it was a skill placed on his weapon, it would only have one skill point in it. This Berserk was far from the Berserk that Berserkers always maxed out. It was like trying to break a stone with an egg!

Everyone was thinking this, but Another Summer of Sleep's next attack unexpectedly missed.　　

No way?

Everyone was shocked.

It was just a level one Berserk. The buffs given to Lord Grim couldn't be that much, yet just this slight boost made it so that Sun Zheping was unable to react in time?

Yes, he couldn't react in time...

Another attack whiffed. Sun Zheping couldn't help but laugh bitterly.

It had been so many years from his injury to retirement to his return, yet his habits hadn't changed. And Ye Xiu still remembered. As a result, in this match, Sun Zheping searched for the feel from that year and burst forth. Ye Xiu's choice to fight measure for measure suddenly suppressed Sun Zheping's momentum.

The change was because of that Berserk.

Although it was only at level one and the buffs were minimal… Sun Zheping was unable to keep up with this tiny change. This had nothing to do with speed, but rather rhythm. Sun Zheping always pushed his rhythm to the highest. Switch the beat, switch the speed? No. There was no such concept in Sun Zheping's mind. He got to his rhythm in one step and that one step reached the limit. As a result, when Ye Xiu's Lord Grim activated Berserk and his offensive stats increased, Sun Zheping's attack rhythm seemed to have reached a bottleneck, unable to reach the next step. This was because he had already been at his limits. Sun Zheping had always competed at his limits.

Sun Zheping needed to adjust his rhythm, but he wasn't good at it and he felt disgusted doing it. Moreover, he also knew very well that Ye Xiu wanted to stop him there. The instant he changed up his rhythm, Ye Xiu would take back the initiative once again. At their skill level, just this change up in tempo could be the deciding factor of this match.

The difficulties of subtleties within this fight was not able to be understood by even pro players, let alone the average viewer, if they did not understand these two well enough. They would be astonished just like the viewers: it was just a level one Berserk, why can't Sun Zheping keep up?

"How disgusting!" Having his surging offense get cut off like this by Ye Xiu made Sun Zheping feel as sick as if he had eaten a fly. It hadn't been easy for him to find back that familiar feeling from the past. Why did this terrible feeling have to come back too? This opponent is just as annoying as before!

A sense of rhythm… what was that? I'll probably never understand in this lifetime… Against this guy, I'm probably not even doing as well as Zhang Jiale.

In the end, Another Summer of Sleep fell.

The sense of rhythm was an extremely fatal flaw for this first-generation God. Compared to what a pro-level player should possess, his sense of rhythm could be described as a complete mess.

As a result, facing an opponent who knew him well, his weakness was quickly drawn out and he met a crushing defeat.　　

"Not bad. To think you could still get out that type of offense. You scared me." After the match, Ye Xiu specifically went to call out to him.

"Stop with the nonsense. I still lost." Sun Zheping was annoyed.

"How could you beat me alone?" Ye Xiu laughed.

Chapter 1185: An Opponent Thoroughly Understood

In Happy's away game, with Ye Xiu's victory, Happy led 1 to 0. However, for those who supported Happy, this sort of opening was unable to excite them. Recently, Happy had this kind of tempo; their openings were good, but then they started dropping points, especially in the team competition. Up until now, their only team competition victory was against Team Hundred Blossoms.

What about today?

In the current climate, it was still rather rare for Happy's fans to come to their away games. However, Happy had fought in City B in the Challenger League finals. It was the place where they beat Excellent Era. Seven Fields and his group of guild buddies were all residents of this city. In the Challenger League finals, they had formed a small group and came to cheer them on. Guild Happy was flourishing at the moment, and Seven Fields and his guild buddies were core guild members. Team Happy was coming to their city to play a match, so how could they not organize guild members ahead of time to cheer for Happy?

The Pro League's seating arrangements weren't as casual as the Challenger League's. Away team fans would usually be grouped together in one area to avoid being mixed in with home team fans, so if any disagreements arose, there wouldn't be any conflicts. Seven Field's group sat at Happy's away team seats. Quite a few people had come. After Happy won the first round of the individual competition, all of them were cheering loudly. In a stadium usually filled with home team fans, it was quite a spectacle to see.

The second round of the individual competition took place under this type of atmosphere.　

Team Happy, Qiao Yifan. Ghostblade, One Inch Ash.　

Team Heavenly Swords, Zou Yunhai. Elementalist, Ocean Ahead.

Heavenly Swords' characters had been created when these friends first started playing the game. Now that they were in the pro circle, they switched out their equipment for new ones. After much effort from Lou Guanning and them, they replaced their old equipment for better ones. From this point, Heavenly Swords had pretty good equipment because their efforts were focused! The good things were all piled on their five core characters. Even if the other characters were butt-naked, they wouldn't care. With such a concentration of resources, their characters naturally became a lot stronger, albeit at the cost of their non-core characters.

Happy and Heavenly Swords used to play with each other constantly in the game, so they were all familiar with each other. After Qiao Yifan and Zou Yunhai entered the stage, they even chatted a bit in the chat. After the countdown started and the two began fighting, Qiao Yifan won in the end. His performance was always consistent. Even though he never had any overwhelming advantage over Zhou Yunhai, he always had control over the situation. When Zou Yunhai came down, his expression looked a bit ugly. He was clearly unhappy with being stuffed out in this fight.

Friendship first, competition second?

These were oftentimes just words. As long as one was on stage, who wouldn't want to win? Bad blood appearing because of a bad match wouldn't be anything new. Quarrels occasionally arose even when teammates practiced against each other, let alone an official match where victory or defeat mattered.

Of course, Zou Yunhai was just gloomy. He wasn't at the point where he would quarrel with Happy. It was just that after two consecutive losses, Heavenly Swords wasn't nearly as relaxed as before. Just because the two teams were good friends with each other, hoping for a peaceful ending was too sweet.

For Happy, their third player was Su Mucheng.

For Heavenly Swords, Lou Guanning had originally planned on saying a few words to their third player, but when he saw that their opponent was an All-Star, he ended up not saying anything. He simply patted their player's shoulder and sent him up.

Lou Guanning admitted that he was still a distance away from an All-Star. If he had to face an All-Star, whether he won depended on luck and how he performed that day, so he wasn't able to point out any crucial win conditions.

Heavenly Sword's player was called Li Weiyi. He was the one that Heavenly Swords had signed to meet the minimum requirements. The individual competition and group arena required six players to compete in, but Lou Guanning and his friends were five people. Among them, Zhong Yeli was a Cleric and could only come out in the team competition. Thus, there were only four remaining; two others were needed.

They didn't try to recruit any famed generals to meet this quota. The positions of the five friends were untouchable. What famed general would be willing to just be someone to meet the quota?

In the end, Lou Guanning found two people from who knew where. They had some skill, but there would be some objection to call them truly skilled. In the third round, Su Mucheng easily won. Happy had a 3 to 0 lead, sweeping the individual competition. Lou Guanning didn't say anything to the returning Li Weiyi. Asking a stopgap cheerleader to win over an All-Star was asking too much.

Team Heavenly Swords' roster was extremely abnormal. It wasn't like they didn't have the resources to change that, but rather they weren't willing to. Their original aspiration was to give the five of them an opportunity to fight on the pro stage. They weren't done yet, so they didn't plan on giving up on this opportunity to other pro players.

A short break followed after the individual competition. The two teams could talk and do some preparation for the group arena during this break. With the individual competition over, it was obvious who would be playing in the group arena.

However, the roster for the group arena was set before the match began and could not be changed at this time. The Alliance had considered letting teams make adjustments mid-match, but in the end, they hoped that the players would focus their attention on the match itself and not waste too much of their efforts on benefiting from making adjustments.

Because of their good relationship with each other, it was hard to avoid the two teams mingling together during this break time. The Alliance didn't forbid two teams from talking to each other during this break, but whenever there was any contact between two teams, the referee would always be watching over very strictly in case the players were violating the integrity of the competition. There was someone in Happy who had made a bet. With Happy's opponents being their friends, all sorts of rumors had flown around long ago. The staff members of the Alliance were watching the communication between the two teams very tightly.

But it wasn't Happy taking the initiative to go over and talk, but rather Heavenly Swords who had just gotten swept in the individual competition. Lou Guanning looked like he was at a funeral. He walked around Happy in a circle before finally saying to Ye Xiu: "God, you're too fierce. What you guys are doing is saving up your strength and then taking out the knife to start the operation!"

"Haha," Ye Xiu laughed, "It's undeniable, our understanding of you guys is the most comprehensive."

Lou Guanning was speechless. He was most scared of God Ye Xiu's calm and righteousness that was completely reasonable and irrefutable.

"But then again, you guys can't keep doing this long-term!" Ye Xiu said. "Even if you guys are constantly improving, if your team is always just you five, you lack variance. You'll quickly be completely grasped by others."

"I feel like… it's fine…" Lou Guanning said.

"That's because there aren't any teams who feel threatened by you guys, right?" Ye Xiu said.

"God…" Lou Guanning cried. Could you not be so honest? For their matches this season, Lou Guanning had felt quite satisfied with Heavenly Swords' performance. No matter who their opponents were, they always won a few points. In their fourth round, they even beat Royal Style 7 to 3.

That was Royal Style! Even though they were no longer frequent visitors of the playoffs, for good or bad, they had an All-Star and were a very experienced team. Taking them down gave Heavenly Swords a huge boost in confidence. All of them felt like they had grown and improved after a year in the Alliance. But to God Ye Xiu, they were just opponents "who weren't worthy of being studied."

This couldn't be considered as others looking down on them though. A team had 19 opponents in the Alliance. Everyone's time was limited, so teams needed to choose who to focus and who not to focus on. If a team tried to grab them all, it was very possible that the team would end up not grabbing any. And among these teams, Heavenly Swords belonged to the category of who not to focus on. Lou Guanning had no choice to concede on this point, which was why God Ye Xiu's words made him tearful.

"You'll be going up in the Group Arena, right? Hurry up and get ready. We'll let you guys see just how disastrous it is to be completely understood by your opponents," Ye Xiu said.

How disastrous it is to be completely understood by your opponents?　　

Lou Guanning and the others knew very well by the end of this match.

Facing Hundred Blossoms, they had won 2 points. Facing Blue Rain, they had won 1 point. Facing Royal Style, they had won 7 points. And facing Royal Style, who had beaten Happy, they had won 6 points. This season, they had utilized their home game advantage well. Both of their victories were their home games.

But this time, in their home game versus Happy, Heavenly Swords ended up with 0 points.

10 to 0!

Team Heavenly Swords was swept clean by a team that had only won one match so far.

Happy didn't give them any mercy. Of course, Heavenly Swords also maintained proper sportsmanship. In the group arena, after Tang Rou beat one of their players, she lost to their second player, Wen Kebei's Battle Mage.

1v3? Four rounds had passed, and Tang Rou had yet to achieve even a 1v2.

Her chance with Heavenly Swords ended with failure. Her only chance left was against Tiny Herb. A 1v3 against Tiny Herb?

What a joke.

In the post-match press conference, Ruan Cheng had snatched a good spot. He trusted that even though Happy had a perfect win today, their mood probably wasn't too good. From a long-term perspective, Tang Rou failing a 1v3 and leaving the team was an enormous loss to them, whether that was in strength or in popularity. This beautiful girl really did have some fans right now. Ruan Cheng had received no small amount of hate for his attacks on her.

"Did Tang Rou not come? What a pity. There's probably a lot of pressure on her, right?" Seeing that Tang Rou was missing from Happy's seats in the press conference, Ruan Cheng didn't even say any polite congratulatory words for their win today. He directly brought out the bet that he had been banking on this entire time.

"Everyone in the team from top to bottom is confident in Tang Rou," Ye Xiu said calmly.

"There's still one round left. We can't be too hasty with our words, so we'll just have to wait and see!" Ruan Cheng's words weren't said too early, but his confident look as if he had planned this in advance was truly loathsome. He might as well have just displayed the schadenfreude at the bottom of his heart out in the open. It would have looked more sincere and natural!

"Little Tang is too pure! I say, she only said what she would do if she didn't keep her promise. But if she succeeds? Don't you think you should do something?" Fang Rui said to Ruan Cheng.

"I'll send her my heartfelt blessings, really." Ruan Cheng put on an honest face. He wasn't about to be provoked!

"Grab me a bucket!" Fang Rui shouted. "I'm going to puke!"

Chapter 1186: Never Happened Before

After finishing their post-match interviews, Happy's group ran into Heavenly Swords' players.

Being swept 10 to 0 was truly embarrassing, and Heavenly Swords was clearly unhappy with tonight's match. However, they fulfilled the words "enemies on stage, friends off stage." They put their emotions in order and showed their hospitality as hosts to Happy.

Around this time, the other matches this round were also finishing up. The highlight matches this round coincidentally ended with the home teams losing as well.

Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain, 4 to 6.

Wind Howl versus Tyranny, 4 to 6.

The powerful young Team Wind Howl tripped up against the experienced old Team Tyranny. The controversy over Tyranny finally eased after this match.

Apart from these two matches, there was also Samsara versus Misty Rain, ending 9 to 1. Samsara continued onwards with their unstoppable march. During the pre-season, people had been worried about compatibility issues between Sun Xiang and Samsara, but from the looks of it, Sun Xiang's addition to the team was an exceptional move. Whether it was in the individual competitions or the team competition, Samsara's strength had improved remarkably. If their momentum stayed, Sun Xiang's and One Autumn Leaf's transfer could definitely become a classic example of an amazing transfer in the history of Glory.

Apart from these powerhouses, the other powerhouse met with misfortune. Team Void had unexpectedly lost against visiting Team Miracle in their home game.

The other new team this season was not as weak as the other new teams in past seasons. The former Team Excellent Era players that made up Team Miracle showed why they had once been in a powerhouse team. After being swept by Team Blue Rain 10 to 0, Team Miracle was able to win a few points every round. This round was even more of an upset.

Although their 17 points at the moment was able to get them to 17th place, fourth from last, because they were a new team and because the other new team was very popular, the amount of attention towards Team Miracle was limited.

When Samsara complained about their demonic match schedule this season, if anyone had taken a look at Miracle's schedule, they would have noticed that within these seven matches, Miracle had already run into Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, Wind Howl, Misty Rain, and Void.

Demonic schedule? Team Miracle's was even worse. Despite their schedule, for their team to not even be in the relegations zone was already incredible. After this upset, Team Miracle finally received some attention. This team consisting of former Team Excellent Era players as the core had some substance to them.

Apart from these matches, the rest were practically all home team victories. Only Team Parade lost as the home team 4 to 6 against Team 301.

After these seven matches, Samsara remained at the top of the rankings with 58 points with Blue Rain in second. Thunderclap once again showed astonishing improvement. Thunderclap used to be a team pacing back and forth at the edge of the playoff zone. Right now, they had pushed their way to third place with 52 points, the same as Blue Rain. Fourth place, Wind Howl. Fifth place, Tiny Herb. Sixth place, Misty Rain. Seventh place, Void. Eighth place, Tyranny. Not much had changed between these eight playoff teams.

Happy crushed Heavenly Swords 10 to 0. With these 10 points, they were ranked 14th with a total of 29 points, one place up from last round. The bottom two relegation teams were Seaside and Bright Green. The gap between them and the other two teams had grown even wider. The distinction between top, middle, and bottom tier teams were becoming more and more clear.

That night, Happy accepted the hospitality of Heavenly Swords, who had suffered a crushing defeat by their hands. Heavenly Swords, of course, wasn't in too great of a mood. Happy didn't lose themselves just because of this long-awaited win though. At this moment, they were all concerned about one problem: Tang Rou. There was only one round remaining for her five round bet, and their opponents for this final round was Team Tiny Herb.

Complete a 1v3 against Tiny Herb?　

Unfortunately, looking at past data, the situation was looking extremely unfavorable. Ever since Wang Jiexi joined Team Tiny Herb, Tiny Herb had never been 1v3ed in the group arena, whether this was against the Battle God, Sword Saint, King of Fighting, or the Great Gunner. The teams with those Gods may have won the group arena in the end, but a 1v3 had never been done before by anyone.

Of course, just because it had never been done before didn't mean it couldn't happen in the future. These statistics were also reported to let people know just how much of a challenge Tang Rou faced.

There were obviously people who were rejoicing at her misfortune and quite a lot of them too. At Happy, the most worried was Chen Guo, of course. She was too afraid to talk to Tang Rou, fearing that her uncontrollable nervousness would infect and disturb her. Right now, she really wanted to hear a concise solution from Ye Xiu.

"What do we do?" she asked Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu only shook his head. "She can only rely on herself."

"There's nothing you can do?" Chen Guo said.

"It's not possible to have a surefire method for something like a 1v3," Ye Xiu said.　

"What if… she fails? What do we do?" Chen Guo was worried!

"Then it'll be her choice," Ye Xiu said.

"Didn't you help her choose 5 rounds? Why didn't you say 50!" Chen Guo didn't care about Ye Xiu's previous explanation.

"Be more serious!" Ye Xiu looked at her and said.

Chen Guo was speechless. She wasn't joking though. If Ye Xiu had said 50, perhaps this matter would have just been left as banter. But then again, even if a reporter like Ruan Cheng didn't deny Happy that opportunity to regard it as a joke, Tang Rou herself might not accept it. When she really put her mind to it, she was quite scary. Chen Guo remembered when Tang Rou helped her complete the Heavenly Domain challenge. Once she had decided on doing it, she kept trying again and again, unable to be pulled away.

Chen Guo let out a long sigh. She had thought of too many ifs. In the end, what had to come would come.

October 25th, the eighth round of the Glory Pro League sounded. There were several powerhouse confrontations: Blue Rain vs Wind Howl, Tyranny vs Misty Rain, Samsara vs Void. However, the match chosen to be broadcast was Happy vs Tiny Herb.　

1v3 in 5 rounds was the biggest topic of this match. Even though practically no one thought Tang Rou could do it, they still hoped to personally witness this moment. The broadcast team had chosen this match to comply with the popular opinion.

When it was almost 8 PM, the players on both sides entered the stadium. After greeting each other, the first players in the individual competition went onto the stage. But in the commentary, they still hadn't started introducing these two players. They were still discussing Tang Rou's 1v3.

"A poll on whether Tang Rou could complete this 1v3 just closed right before this match started. We can see that among the 65525 voters, 64388 voters thought that Tang Rou will not be able to achieve a 1v3. In other words, only 1137 people believed in Tang Rou, which comes out to about 1.7%, not even 2%. Coach Li, what are your thoughts?" Pan Lin said.

"Uh… even though Happy is a new team, they're quite popular. We can see this from the number of seats filled in their home stadium. 1.7% means that many Happy supporters don't think that Tang Rou can complete it. In addition, fans don't always vote based on a logical analysis. Most of the times, they vote based on their feelings, a show of their well-wishes. However, from looking at how Happy's supporters are voting, we can see that even among their fans, Tang Rou's bold 1v3 promise is unpopular," Li Yibo started speaking.

"Oh, then what are your thoughts, Coach Li?" Pan Lin asked.

"Haha, the courage and confidence of young players is laudable, but they can't be too ignorant!" Li Yibo said.　　

"It looks like Coach Li doesn't think highly of Tang Rou's 1v3! Okay, then I'll stand opposite to you. I'll support Tang Rou." Pan Lin laughed. His attitude was clearly just to liven up the atmosphere. It didn't mean he was a true fan.

"If she can really do it, it'll be a historical moment! If I remember correctly, according to past data, Team Tiny Herb has never been 1v3ed before, right?" Li Yibo said.

"Yes! I hope we can see this historical moment! Okay, the first round of the individual competition is about to begin. Happy will be sending out their team captain, the former owner of the Battle God One Autumn Leaf. Nicknamed the Glory Textbook, Ye Xiu is using the unspecialized Lord Grim, a character that has received much attention this season. As for Tiny Herb, they sent out their new generation Witch, the genius Gao Yingjie. This could be considered a confrontation between two generations. The map chosen is Red Plum Pavilion. Coach Li, who do you think will win?" When the match went underway, Pan Lin immediately stopped discussing the topic of Tang Rou's 1v3 and started talking about this confrontation. Asking about predictions of the outcome was a common topic for commentators. In reality, the question wasn't simply for predictions on who would win. In order to make a prediction, an introduction and analysis of the two opposing players had to be done, so it always worked as a conversation topic.

"Ye Xiu is experienced, he's familiar with every class, and he uses an unspecialized. These are where his advantages lay. However, Gao Yingjie has grown into a youth that can take charge. He's young. He has energy. And to Ye Xiu, Gao Yingjie is perhaps an unfamiliar player. They have never fought before." Li Yibo was familiar with how to reply to this type of question. He lay bare the advantages that both sides possessed and didn't talk about his actual prediction. When the outcome of the match became clear, he could just follow up: See, I told you guys XX is very XXXX!

As for this fight? Who would be Li Yibo's justification this time? At this moment, the two sides finally started clashing.

Chapter 1187: Carefully Honed Talent

Magic Missile!

Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree started out simple, testing the waters with a not-so-powerful Magic Missile.

Lord Grim dodged easily. Obviously, he didn't lack in ranged methods of attack. Myriad Manifestations Umbrella raised, three Anti-Tank Missiles seemed to have been swung out, roaring with a fiery tail as they flew at their target.

Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree immediately waved a hand, and a star shaped symbol was tossed out, transforming into a Magic Ray as it darted forth.

Star Ray?

No!

This Magic Ray accurately struck one of the Anti-Tank Missiles, then immediately rebounded towards another, then another, and then sped right for Lord Grim.

This was a variant of Star Ray: Star Refraction. Compared to Star Ray, it wasn't as powerful, but one could utilize the distinguishing feature of this refraction to create unexpected attacks. Currently, after refracting thrice, the three Anti-Tank Missiles had already exploded in midair, light flashing and smoke billowing. As for Lord Grim? He had no choice but to dodge the attack that came refracted at him.

With his sidestep, Kind Tree was already charging out of the smoke and fire, directly at Lord Grim. With a wave of his hand, a Lava Flask was thrown down, and soon after, he was swinging his broom at Lord Grim. Gao Yingjie's flurry of attacks quickly followed swiftly after his Star Refraction, barely giving Ye Xiu any chance to react.

Sword Draw!

The broom was about to hit Lord Grim's head when a blade of light flashed out. Because of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's transformative abilities, it often hid a lot of very easily-distinguishable skills in strange movements. This Sword Draw was exactly this. However, the prodigious Gao Yingjie reacted swiftly. Kind Tree's advance immediately stopped and turned into a backwards jump.

The ground had already melted under the Lava Flask, but Ye Xiu refused to give up such a good opening. Lord Grim used a Knight's Charge and pursued Kind Tree against the damage from the lava.

The two figures moved, immediately changing positions. Lord Grim came over with his Charge while Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree avoided the attack by getting on his broom mid-jump.

Gao Yingjie's reaction speed was truly amazing. Even Ye Xiu was a little surprised at his miss. However, a counterattack immediately followed.

Broom Tornado!

Just barely dodging this attack by riding his broom, Kind Tree immediately turned his broom and quickly swung it down at Lord Grim. The entire process looked as if Kind Tree had simply switched directions twice in midair, smoothly and clearly.

This time, Lord Grim didn't have the time to dodge. With the rapid spinning of the broom that Broom Tornado created, it was hard to parry as well. Ye Xiu could only go onto the defensive, raising his sword horizontally with a Blade Master's Guard. What followed was the continuous sound of the broom clashing with the edge of the sword. Broom Tornado battered at Lord Grim at high speed, sweeping him back.

Star Ray!

Gao Yingjie wasn't greedy. Just as the Broom Tornado was going strong, he suddenly canceled the skill and threw out a Star Ray. At such a close distance, there was no way Lord Grim could dodge. The Magic Ray hit, causing Lord Grim to stumble. Kind Tree's broom was already enchanted with Frost Powder. As it was whipped through the air, it left a trail of shattered ice crystals in the air as it slapped down at Lord Grim.

For melee combat, Witches mostly just used normal attacks, but with specialized magic tools, they could enhance their weapon's damage and enchant their weapon with special effects. For example, Frost Powder had the chance of freezing the target directly. Even if you were unlucky, it would still inflict a slow. Everything depended on the target's resistance.

Now, the number of pieces of Silver equipment on Lord Grim's body was slowly increasing, but he still mostly had Orange equipment. This meant his stats were easy to figure out. Gao Yingjie currently used Frost Powder naturally because he had realized that Lord Grim didn't have much of a resistance to ice.

Slap, slap, slap…

That was how Witches attacked. Even with Frost Powder, normal attacks wouldn't do any significant damage, but if he was hit and frozen, that would be dreadful.

Kind Tree started off with three consecutive attacks which Lord Grim barely dodged. The fourth attack, Gao Yingjie knew the other wouldn't be able to dodge, but that was when Lord Grim threw a handful of powder over as well...

This was...

Gao Yingjie recognized it immediately, but Kind Tree's attack was already sweeping forth, he didn't have time to retract it.

A hit!

As expected, Ye Xiu couldn't dodge this attack, but it was just a hit. What could a normal attack do?

Freezing effect?

It was gone… What Lord Grim had thrown just now was something Gao Yingjie was more than familiar with, the Witch's Disperse Powder. The effect of Frost Powder on his weapon also counted as a buff. When met with Disperse Powder, it was immediately neutralized.

However, only the Frost Powder was neutralized, not Kind Tree's attack. This hit was just a normal attack, without the wanted freeze effect, but with the following attack, Gao Yingjie was already attempting to inflict his own effects.

Sweep!

The broom swept up diagonally with the Witch's knock-up skill. Lord Grim was immediately suspended in the air. Gao Yingjie quickly followed after with Kind Tree to take this chance to unleash a combo, but instead saw the suspended Lord Grim facing him, looking straight at him.

A trap!!!

Gao Yingjie instantly realized.

When struck with a knock-up skill, it was impossible to adjust your position so well, so there was only one explanation: Lord Grim hadn't actually been struck; he had merely jumped up. Ye Xiu had predicted his next move and cooperated to create the illusion that he had been struck, and then he would launch an unexpected counterattack...

The light of a blade flashed and Lord Grim plummeted with a Falling Light Blade. Gao Yingjie was already having Kind Tree hurriedly avoid it, but Falling Light Blade...

With this attack, it was clear that Ye Xiu had once again predicted Gao Yingjie's next move. Falling Light Blade's small shockwave was just enough to capture Kind Tree.

Kind Tree, hit by the shockwave, was knocked to the side. Gao Yingjie rushed to Quick Recover, but Lord Grim had already pursued him over, swing down from overhead with a Collapsing Mountain.

Was Collapsing Mountain a hard to dodge attack? No, but the problem was the timing Ye Xiu chose. He attacked right as Kind Tree was in the middle of his Quick Recover. He couldn't really cancel, but continuing wouldn't do him any good, and it was too late to change directions.

Another trap!

What a troublesome opponent….

In the Season 8, Gao Yingjie rarely had chances to play, so he hadn't fought Ye Xiu before. Afterwards, they had come to a few exchanges in the online game. In the new server, at the beginning, they had been crushed by the unspecialized with their low leveled classes. There was no helping that. For the unspecialized, if it wasn't for the lack of skill points, the class would be mature at level 20. But what about other classes? When they were level twenty, they only had five skills for their class. Even if they learned more from other classes of the same type, that couldn't compare to the unspecialized. Fewer skills meant fewer variations, then, considering how they were against God Ye Xiu with his comprehensive knowledge, their attacks would be easily seen through and dealt with. Training with Ye Xiu in the new server was a painful memory.

Back then, Tiny Herb's members all had the same thought. They all believed that their immature characters had crippled their ability, and would naturally be at a disadvantage against the unspecialized. If it wasn't so, then the result would be very different.

Now, fighting Ye Xiu one on one, Gao Yingjie really wanted to tell those teammates the truth. With a mature character, it really was different from using a low leveled character, but if you were to say the result would be different when fighting Ye Xiu, that wasn't necessarily true. Even with Kind Tree, Gao Yingjie still felt that he was using the low leveled character he had once used against Ye Xiu.

All of his intentions had been seen through, his every move predicted. The attacks God Ye Xiu executed weren't magnificent, but they were inescapable, always timed when you were incapable of dodging. How did he manage to hone his awareness and experience to such a degree? Gao Yingjie was suddenly a little envious. He had hand speed; he was quick at reacting; he could switch between playstyles and combinations whenever he wished. He was a prodigy; he was far faster at learning, at mastering anything thrown his way than other people. However, it was impossible for him to gain the carefully honed talent God Ye Xiu had sharpened from who knew how many battles.

It seemed as if everything that he was doing was being discerned and analyzed.

This feeling was so intense. Even against his captain, Wang Jiexi, Gao Yingjie had never felt such an imposing pressure. Shouldn't his captain understand him better than God Ye Xiu?

His usual combinations wouldn't be of any use. He had to do something that the other wouldn't be able to predict!

Gao Yingjie, after losing the initiative, fell into a helpless situation. No matter how he switched up his tactics, he wasn't able to escape Lord Grim's control.

From the outside, it seemed that he wasn't at such a disadvantage. Occasionally, he would still find chances to counterattack. In the beginning, that's what Gao Yingjie thought as well, but soon enough, he realized that while he had accurately grasped these seemingly valuable chances, he never managed to achieve what he had been intending. He could send out a few counterattacks every now and then, but in the blink of an eye, Ye Xiu would have taken back the advantage.

Thus, he came to a realization. These so-called chances were all under Ye Xiu's control as well. No one would dare say that their fighting was flawless, but Ye Xiu was able to keep the openings he revealed under his control. Thus, Gao Yingjie might've grasped chance after chance, but was never able to make anything out of it.

So this was the Glory Textbook? The strongest player in the history of Glory?

Gao Yingjie gazed at the weird character, swinging a strange weapon, and wearing an uncomfortably mismatched set of equipment, with fearful reverence.

He really is strong, but, I can't give up just like this!

Gao Yingjie grit his teeth. Kind Tree didn't have much health left, and he still wasn't able to find an opening to turn the tides. His only choice was to go all out!

Glory!

When the word flashed on the screen, the match came to an end.

So in the end, he still lost?

Gao Yingjie stared at the fallen Kind Tree, stunned.

Chapter 1188: Grinding Out a Win

Happy welcomed the visiting Tiny Herb. After Ye Xiu won the first round of the individual competition, the two competitors walked down from the stage.

"What do you think?" Wang Jiexi looked at Gao Yingjie, who had just been beaten by Ye Xiu and was looking a bit downcast.

"Amazing…" Gao Yingjie said. "He's even stronger than I imagined."

"But you're still young. Keep working hard, and one day you will surpass everyone," Wang Jiexi said.

"Yes!"

The Gao Yingjie of two years ago may have been named a genius and carried the hopes of countless people, but he had never dared to be so ambitious. He had always felt like having a seat in this team and playing on the competitive stage was already very, very good.

However, everyone in the club from top to bottom, his team captain, his teammates, they all had extremely high expectations of him. Just a member on the team? No, not nearly enough. Tiny Herb was expecting him to be the team's pillar, the one who would hold up Tiny Herb's banner after their captain Wang Jiexi retired.

Could he do it?

His goals were forced onto him. When he looked towards the figure of the Magician, Gao Yingjie had doubted himself more than just once. He felt like his captain was so strong. How could he ever hope to reach his level?

Everyone seemed to be more confident in Gao Yingjie than Gao Yingjie himself. While wallowing in uncertainty, Gao Yingjie grew, following what he was told blindly. Up until that day, the Season 8 All Stars Rookie Challenge, where he beat his captain under the gazes of millions of people.

At that time, Gao Yingjie had been astonished. He couldn't believe it. It was then that a seed had finally started to sprout in his heart.

So I really can do it.

Gao Yingjie began to think to himself. After that, practicing and growing, Gao Yingjie changed beyond recognition. He had found confidence in himself. He had recognized his potential. He could firmly advance towards that goal, which he had once thought as inconceivable.

That season, because he hadn't appeared in enough matches, he didn't have the qualifications for the title of Best Rookie. However, this wasn't important. In Season 9, Gao Yingjie became part of the starting lineup, directly learning, growing, battling alongside the person he would surpass and succeed. He was chosen as an All-Star and became one of the top 24 players in the competitive scene.

He had yet to reach the level of his captain, but Wang Jiexi had already given him a new target.

Surpass everyone!　　

And this time, Gao Yingjie didn't panic. He would work hard towards this goal. The road to Glory had no limit.

In the broadcast, commentator Pan Lin and guest Li Yibo hurried to give a recap of the brilliant plays that happened in this match. Pan Lin looked at the data in his hands and suddenly said, "Coach Li, I just discovered something. Happy has been the center of attention with so much to talk about, but there's a reality that everyone seems to have missed."　　

"Oh? What is it?" asked Li Yibo.

"After Samsara clean swept them in the Round 1, Ye Xiu began coming out as Happy's first player in their individual competitions. So far, he has a perfect record in these seven rounds, in seven individual matches. This is something that somehow no one noticed," Pan Lin said.　　

"Oh? Really?" Li Yibo immediately grabbed the data in his hands. Data from too far in the past might not be there, but the win records for the two teams this season should all be there.

"You're right…" Li Yibo looked at the data and confirmed it twice before continuing, "With this match, he's won seven consecutive individual matches. To think no one's reported on this yet."　　

"Even if Team Happy's win record at this point isn't too ideal, this point shouldn't be covered up!" Pan Lin said.　

"Yes… seven consecutive wins. If I remember correctly, he's tied for the most consecutive individual wins in Glory history, no?" Li Yibo said.

The two of them didn't have this information on hand, but Pan Lin quickly found someone to search and confirm it. "Correct, the current best record for consecutive individual wins is seven, which had been set by Team Blue Rain's Yu Feng in Season 8."

"It looks like Ye Xiu's name is going to have to be added to it," Li Yibo said.　　

"Or perhaps he'll be the only one?" Pan Lin said.

"Who's Happy's opponents next round?" Li Yibo asked.

"Let's see… Miracle…" After Pan Lin found it, he became silent.

Li Yibo was suddenly speechless too. Miracle. Ignoring everything else, if this was just a 1v1, it was practically giving away this point to Ye Xiu. This team's foundation consisted of former Excellent Era players, who had grown under Ye Xiu's hands. As for the others, they were new rookies that had joined along with Miracle; their skill levels were subpar. It would be embarrassing to compare them with a God.

"Uh, let's go back to the match!" Li Yibo dragged the topic back to the match. Even though he had already given Ye Xiu eight wins in his heart, since the match hadn't been played yet, it wouldn't be good to talk about it.

The second players for the individual competition walked onto the stage.

Happy. Su Mucheng. Launcher, Dancing Rain.

Tiny Herb. Xu Bin. Knight, Angelica.

Xu Bin. During his time in Team 301, he had earned the nickname "Grind King".

This nickname wasn't a pretty one, but it was quite a mighty one. It really was the best title for Xu Bin's playstyle though. After joining the championship team Tiny Herb, Xu Bin didn't lose his defining feature. Instead, because of the support from better teammates, his speciality improved a step further. Last season, he had been voted into All-Stars at 14th place.

Against Su Mucheng, Xu Bin obviously wouldn't abandon his style. After encountering his opponent and being suppressed by heavy gunfire from Dancing Rain, he didn't panic. For someone to be named "Grind King," he possessed unimaginable toughness. Xu Bin contended patiently with Su Mucheng. It was as if he was also a long-ranged class, but in reality, he had absolutely no attacks that could pose any threat to her. He fought with Su Mucheng in a situation where he couldn't fight back, dodging and defending to skillfully dissolve Dancing Rain's attacks. At the same time, Angelica tried hard to decrease the distance between the two of them.

Grind King didn't mean Xu Bin was slow and that his playing wasn't clean. It was pointing to his style, where he wore down his opponent's spirit and skills, grinding at the opponent's patience and pushing the opponent's mentality off balance, or perhaps grinding until the opponent was tired. In any case, his playstyle led to openings. And whenever an opening appeared, Xu Bin's offensive would be like a thunderstorm.

Knight's Spirit!

The instant he saw the opportunity, Xu Bin immediately had Angelica activate his awakening skill. Along with a Heroic Charge and a Justice Leap, he instantly closed the distance between himself and Dancing Rain. Su Mucheng wanted to Dancing Rain to retreat, but Angelica had used Sacrificial Roar, forcing Dancing Rain to continue attacking him. Before this, Angelica had activated an Honest Maelstrom Counterattack. Launcher attacks could also be returned by this skill...　

In the end, Xu Bin won. The margin of victory wasn't large, and he wasn't particularly dominant, but all the matches he won seemed to be like this...

"Good job," Wang Jiexi said to Xu Bin. He appreciated Xu Bin's consistency very much.

Tiny Herb's third player for the individual competition started getting ready.　

Zhou Yebai. Ghostblade, Rangoon Creeper.

Of the eight rounds this season, this was Zhou Yebai's third time appearing in the individual competition. To be sent out so many times was worthy of being excited about for a substitute player like Zhou Yebai. However, the individual competition? Zhou Yebai didn't really understand. He was a Ghostblade. It wasn't that he had no individual combat capabilities, but of the players in the team, Zhou Yebai really didn't think that he was better than any of the others in 1v1s, but their team captain didn't pick the others and picked him again and again in the individual competition. On the other hand, for the team competition, of the eight rounds, he had only appeared once, which truly confused him.

He had lost the last two times he went up. What about this time?　　

He didn't understand this arrangement, but he respected his team captain's wishes, so he upped his spirits and went onto the stage. On the way there, he lifted his head and looked up at the screen to see who his opponent would be.

Team Happy. Qiao Yifan. Ghostblade, One Inch Ash.

Qiao Yifan!

Zhou Yebai turned his head in astonishment and saw Qiao Yifan almost at Happy's player booth.　

Zhou Yebai subconsciously glanced at his teammates. He saw that everyone was looking at Qiao Yifan too.

In the pro scene, players came and went. Teammates today, opponents tomorrow. It was very common. Those who had played for a few years all experienced this, but Qiao Yifan… Zhou Yebai had never really thought of him as a teammate. Qiao Yifan had been more like a busboy?

But right now, this busboy had found his home, and he had even changed classes to be a Ghostblade just like him. Qiao Yifan's position in Team Happy was more firm than his, and he had appeared on stage this season more times than Zhou Yebai had.

Zhou Yebai hadn't been interested in this individual competition at first, but now a sliver of fighting spirit rose.

Yes, just a sliver.

Qiao Yifan was just a lowly busboy. He even changed classes. How good could he be? He's probably the same as when he had been playing with a… a what? Zhou Yebai suddenly realized that he couldn't even remember what class Qiao Yifan played before in Tiny Herb.

He was probably so bad that he didn't leave an impression on me? Zhou Yebai thought to himself.　　

Do you think that just because of you've switched classes, you're an ugly duckling that turned into a swan? Today I'll definitely teach you a good lesson!

The characters loaded into the map and the match began...

"Yifan, long time no see!" Zhou Yebai had his Rangoon Creeper advance as he greeted Qiao Yifan in the public chat. In his heart, he was wondering how he should teach this Qiao Yifan how a Phantom Demon was played.

"Senior, long time no see," Qiao Yifan replied. Apart from Gao Yingjie, everyone else in Team Tiny Herb were his seniors.

"So you've switched to a Phantom Demon. Nice job!" Zhou Yebai said.　　

"Thank you senior for your praise," Qiao Yifan said.

"Is there anything that you don't understand, that you'd like me to show you in this match?" Zhou Yebai wasn't modest at all.

"Sure… I'm behind you," Qiao Yifan said.

Chapter 1189: Ghost Chaining

Behind?!

Zhou Yebai went pale with shock upon seeing this message, hurriedly having Rangoon Creeper turn around.

Unfortunately, Qiao Yifan was focused on the match, and not here to joke around. He had tactically managed to swerve around and get behind Rangoon Creeper. When he sent the message, One Inch Ash's sword was already on its way down.

Moonlight Slash!

Phantom Demons usually wouldn't put too many skill points into slash attacks, and Qiao Yifan didn't intend for damage to be the purpose of this strike. It was just a simple opening attack. Unless the other was under a Super Armor status, any attack would be enough to disrupt the target a little. Combos were built upon such a foundation.

It was definitely far too late for Zhou Yebai to dodge after seeing Qiao Yifan's message. Considering Qiao Yifan's caution, he naturally wouldn't expose himself without having an absolute grasp on the situation. Zhou Yebai's Rangoon Creeper had happily and brainlessly charged forward, while speaking with Qiao Yifan like a senior to his junior in the chat. Meanwhile, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had successfully and precisely gotten behind the other. The audience could see all of this with clarity. Zhou Yebai had become a joke at the very start of the match, one that didn't seem to understand his own place at all.

Now, moonlight arced downwards, not doing much damage, but still stunning Rangoon Creeper for a split second. One Inch Ash followed up with a Ghost Claw. A sliver of the Phantom Ghost's power drifted through the air, throwing Rangoon Creeper up. This was the Ghostblade's knockup skill.

Knockups were usually a good time to follow up with a combo, but for a Phantom Demon, they shouldn't hurry and deal as much damage with slashes as possible, but quickly set down as many Ghost Boundaries as possible.

Ice Boundary!

Plague Boundary!

Ghost Boundaries had cast times, so you couldn't instantly set a boundary. It was a struggle to finish casting these two Ghost Boundaries during Rangoon Creeper's knockup. However, Qiao Yifan very smoothly transitioned between the two Ghost Boundaries. After setting down an Ice Boundary first, he began chanting a Plague Boundary, carefully keeping an eye on Rangoon Creeper. Upon seeing the other land, Qiao Yifan was prepared to cancel the chant already, but the effects of Ice Boundary activated!

Rangoon Creeper, slowed by the Ice Boundary, definitely wouldn't be able to get to One Inch Ash's side in time. His blade trembled, and instead he sent forward a Spellblade skill: Earthquake Sword.

He could make it!

Qiao Yifan made an accurate judgement. Even as the Earthquake Sword came over, he continued his cast. The Plague Boundary was set before the Earthquake Sword swept at him, as expected. He wasn't interrupted. After that, he had One Inch Ash roll to the side and Earthquake Sword was dodged cleanly. Qiao Yifan was very familiar with the characteristics of these skills.

Plague Boundary lowered the defense of the characters inside the boundary. If he didn't attack, then there was no point to the Plague Boundary. Zhou Yebai was a Phantom Demon player, so how would he not understand this? Now, in two overlapping boundaries, he didn't ignore everything and try to run out of the two boundaries, but instead carefully observed One Inch Ash's movements. He couldn't predict what Qiao Yifan would do next. That was when he realized, despite living together for a year, seeing each other everyday for a year, he didn't understand Qiao Yifan at all. Perhaps, as a team member that he often had to train with, he knew a little of Qiao Yifan's style in Glory, but now, Qiao Yifan had switched classes to the class he was most familiar with: Phantom Demon.

What was Qiao Yifan's Phantom Demon like? Zhou Yebai didn't have a clue. However, he believed that he had more experience as a Phantom Demon than Qiao Yifan. He might've been caught off guard in the beginning, but, so long as he didn't panic, and kept a clear view of the situation, dealing with each action as it came, there was nothing to fear.

Ice Boundary, Plague Boundary, one focused on control, another focused on weakening. These two boundaries wouldn't deal any significant damage, he could slow down his pace and observe slowly. Bring it, Qiao Yifan!

Wait!

What was this?

On the screen, the blade in One Inch Ash's hand was spinning. It was less like an attack and more like some sort of spell being cast. As a Phantom Demon player, how could Zhou Yebai not know what this was?

The Ice and Plague Boundaries under Rangoon Creeper's feet seemed to be responding to come sort of summons, the Phantom Ghost's power pulsing, resonating! Zhou Yebai wanted to get his Rangoon Creeper out of the boundaries, but it was already too late.

Ghost Feast!

With only two Ghost Boundaries on the field, Qiao Yifan already had One Inch Ash use Ghost Feast.

The two pools of the Phantom Ghost's power, representing ice and plague erupted. Compared to a Ghost Feast with multiple overlaid boundaries, the power of the explosion of two boundaries had been reduced, but was also much clearer. Everyone could even see Rangoon Creeper struggling under the corrosive power of the Phantom Ghost's power.

The match had just started and Zhou Yebai had taken an ultimate to the face, but now his nervousness after being ambushed had disappeared along with it.

A Ghost Feast with just two Ghost Boundaries?

Zhou Yebai wanted to laugh. From his point of view, this was a display of Qiao Yifan's lack of experience and his stress from facing him. He couldn't figure out what to do next, so he just hurriedly made the Ghost Boundaries erupt. Every little bit of damage counted, after all.

How pitiful!

Zhou Yebai lamented to himself. Did the other really think that he'd become something great just by switching classes? How naive!

"Grow up already!" Zhou Yebai sent into the chat, admonishingly, as Rangoon Creeper charged out of the smoke and lights made by the opposing Phantom Ghost's power.

Moonlight Slash, then Full Moonlight Slash!

The two strikes were formed as one, arcing beautifully through the air, but, if there was nothing to hit, then the two arcs of light merely looked awkward!

Where was he?

Zhou Yebai was shocked.

He had seen One Inch Ash at this very spot just now. He was fast enough, so how could this happen? How was this possible?

What on earth happened?

Zhou Yebai was shocked, the audience was shocked and Pan Lin, in the middle of his commentary, was also shocked.

"What is Zhou Yebai doing?" Pan Lin wondered aloud. The audience, with their omniscient view, clearly saw Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash standing just off to the side behind Rangoon Creeper, but Zhou Yebai had Rangoon Creeper strike the air with a beautiful two hit combo while yelling something like that. Was this some sort of… tactical trap?

"Er…" Li Yibo was very awkward. As a special guest and commentator, as Adviser Li, he had to give an answer in this sort of situation. However… what the hell was this guy doing? Li Yibo was very confused as well.

"Let's watch the match first!" Coach Li's commentary IQ was expert level. Knowing that the players on the field wouldn't give them time to analyze this one detail, he quickly suggested they watch first, analyze later.

One Inch Ash, stood behind Rangoon Creeper, had already struck. By the time Rangoon Creeper's two slashes were soaring through nothing, another Ghost Boundary had been placed. Dark Boundary! Another boundary that focused on inflicting a status effect. This time, Qiao Yifan wanted to take Zhou Yebai's sight.

The screen went dark...

Dark Boundary!

Zhou Yebai immediately realized what this meant.

Where was this guy? Where did this Ghost Boundary come from?

A chill ran through Zhou Yebai's heart as he stared at the dark screen that looked like it had shut down. He was finally feeling pressured. Qiao Yifan was no longer someone he could defeat with ease. Definitely not.

Zhou Yebai was so shocked that he forgot to move. One of the characteristics of Ghost Boundaries was that while inside, you'd definitely feel the effects, but as soon as you stepped out, then it'd all disappear. Characters in a Dark Boundary would be blinded, so no character would give up trying to make their character move out of it. They'd usually even use movement skills to help them move a large distance at once, just to escape this annoying effect.

However, Zhou Yebai, too lost in the shock over the trouble Qiao Yifan was giving him, forgot such a crucial thing as to move.

He was stunned, but Qiao Yifan wasn't. One Inch Ash closed in, sending out slash attacks and setting down ghost boundaries whenever given an opening.

One boundary...

Two boundaries...

Three boundaries...

The effects of Ghost Boundaries were stackable, but Qiao Yifan didn't let all the Ghost Boundaries he send out overlap completely. The boundaries overlapped, chained together across a larger area. The very center had several overlapping Ghost Boundaries, but as you got further away from the center, some areas only had one or two boundaries presiding over them. However, with this arrangement, the area under One Inch Ash's control had greatly increased. The Dark Boundary had disappeared by then and Zhou Yebai's sight returned, but he couldn't escape the control of the chained Ghost Boundaries at all.

This was...

Ghost Chaining!

Zhou Yebai recognized this playstyle and was once again filled with shock. Ghost Chaining required a player to have a very good awareness of the situation at large. Each boundary was set down individually, but needed to be placed so that it formed a whole with the other Ghost Boundaries. As a player did this, they also had to use slash attacks to fill in the gaps left by the Ghost Boundaries. The timing of these slashes, of these boundaries, what boundaries to place, where to place them, they all needed to be planned out. It wasn't something a person could achieve by mechanics alone.

This guy… can use Ghost Chaining, and so well… As for me...

Zhou Yebai didn't want to admit it, but had no choice. He was incapable of performing such a beautifully done Ghost Chaining.

How is this possible?

Zhou Yebai felt like he was going crazy. This was Qiao Yifan? That little nobody? Had he really already mastered something as high end as Ghost Chaining? Was his skill already above mine?

No! Impossible!

Zhou Yebai didn't believe it, or rather, he didn't want to believe it. How could that Qiao Yifan be so strong? How could he defeat me?

Of course he could!

Glory!

When the word flashed on the screen, Zhou Yebai's Rangoon Creeper had fallen with his denial and disbelief. When he walked out of the competition booth, his face was still set in an expression of disbelief. He returned to Tiny Herb's player stands, head down as he stood to the side.

He had lost to Qiao Yifan, that Qiao Yifan...

"Someone you never bothered to take notice of has grown to such an extent… Is it scary?" Wang Jiexi suddenly asked.

Zhou Yebai opened his mouth, but didn't know what to say. He suddenly realized, if Qiao Yifan hadn't left, if Qiao Yifan was still in Tiny Herb, both of them as Phantom Demons, would he still have a place in Tiny Herb?

Zhou Yebai suddenly felt a creeping sense of terror. He knew that Qiao Yifan was no longer in Tiny Herb and he wouldn't have to compete with the other for this place, but he still felt a formless pressure on his shoulders, trying to tell him something.

"You can't stagnate! In this Alliance, survival is swimming against the tide," Wang Jiexi said.

Chapter 1190: New Ghostblade Technique

With the three individual rounds over, Happy was in the lead 2 to 1. There would be a short break before the group arena, but the commentator and special guest still had much to do. Due to Qiao Yifan's beautiful Ghost Chaining, they still had a mystery to uncover! Li Yibo wanted to just leave this be, but Pan Lin, at a time like this, just simply refused to sync to his rhythm. After hurriedly going over the current progression and situation of the round, he immediately returned to the match that had just occurred, and immediately returned to the mystery they had left unsolved.

"Zhou Yebai's mistake really shouldn't have occurred. Isn't his judgment way off?" The broadcast cooperated with Pan Lin's commentary and was currently giving a playback of Rangoon Creeper's beautiful two strike combo. It was aimed at nothing, completely ignoring One Inch Ash behind him.

"Such a weird mistake wouldn't be without reason, right?" With Li Yibo refusing to cooperate, Pan Lin could only keep talking to himself, asking the program director to switch to Zhou Yebai's point of view at the same time.

"Wait!" The scene flashed by and Li Yibo suddenly yelled, seeming to have noticed something.

"What?" The scene paused.

"Go back, slow motion!" Li Yibo's voice had twisted a little.

Pan Lin didn't understand, but still had the broadcast director cooperate, rewinding the recording and replaying it.

"Stop!" Li Yibo suddenly cried out.

The prepared broadcast director stopped the scene. Li Yibo pointed at a point on the screen: look here!

In Zhou Yebai's point of view, there was the lighting effect of the explosion after the Ice and Plague Boundaries had been blown up by Ghost Feast, and right in front of him, there was the clear cut silhouette of a person.

"One Inch Ash!" Pan Lin yelled, "One Inch Ash really did appear there. There was nothing wrong with Zhou Yebai's judgment, but…"

"Keep this scene, switch the view," Li Yibo directly interrupted him.

Pan Lin was stunned, but still had the broadcast switch to an full view.

"Hey!" After switching, Pan Lin cried out, unable to control his surprise. In the full view, One Inch Ash wasn't there at all. He had already arrived behind Rangoon Creeper by then, about to get to the position he had launched his offense from.

"What on earth is happening?" Pan Lin was shocked, switching the shot back and seeing the silhouette of One Inch Ash once more.

"This…" Pan Lin stared, and stared some more, and suddenly gave a "ah!"

"Do you see it now?" Li Yibo asked.

"This… This…" Pan Lin grabbed the mouse, tracing the cursor over the image, over the edge of the silhouette of "One Inch Ash".

"This isn't One Inch Ash at all, but a silhouette formed by the lighting from the explosion of the two Ghost Boundaries," Li Yibo explained.

"This… Is this something created by the system?" Pan Lin suspected.

"Probably not." Li Yibo shook his head. He had never heard of anything like it.

"A coincidence?"

"We probably won't know until Qiao Yifan is interviewed," Li Yibo guessed.

The audience at the venue all saw the scene and commentary in the TV broadcast through the big screen, seeing the silhouette made in that moment by the two boundaries of Ghost Feast.

It wasn't just the crowd that was surprised. Even the pro players at their respective benches, including Gods like Ye Xiu and Wang Jiexi, were all dumbstruck.

This was something unique that they had never seen during their pro careers, such a lifelike silhouette… It was a coincidence, right?

Tiny Herb's members could only guess, but Happy's members could be more direct. They all turned their heads as one to face Qiao Yifan, using their gazes to prompt him to explain.

"Ah… This, is something I discovered by accident," Qiao Yifan said.

"You created it purposefully!" Ye Xiu's surprise didn't fade because he knew that, for something like this, noticing was one thing, but replication was something else entirely.

"Yeah… I tried to practice it, I'm just lucky that Luo Ji helped me with the calculations involved," Qiao Yifan said, pulling out Luo Ji to give him credit. Luo Ji was usually at school, but when it came to matchday Saturday, he would swiftly rush to the stadium to regroup with everyone else. It was tiring, but if he couldn't even make it to the matches, then there really was no point in being a pro player at all.

"Just a little," Luo Ji hurriedly added, having been pushed into the spotlight.

"Amazing!" Ye Xiu complimented. Setting aside the practicality of this technique for now, for such a young player to have such creativity and spirit to research a new technique was something praiseworthy. Ye Xiu dared to be certain that this was an unprecedented new technique, something that even the All-Star level Ghostblades of Void hadn't even discovered.

"Ah… It's alright! I just felt like it might be of some use." Qiao Yifan was at a loss in the face of such a compliment.

"When we get back, let's all discuss together," Ye Xiu decided with a smile.

"Yes!" Qiao Yifan was very happy too. This acknowledgement was something he'd never get tired of.

The break after the individual competition soon ended. The following group arena would be the focus of this match, of all the matches this round. The reason the TV broadcast would choose this match was also mainly because of this group arena.

The venue suddenly fell silent. The Happy fans at their home stadium felt way too conflicted about this match that would decide the the result of the 1v3 promise.

Tang Rou stood from her seat. Five rounds… She had already failed four rounds, but her gaze was as determined as ever. Even though her opponent was Tiny Herb, even though no one had ever achieved a 1v3 against this team, Tang Rou didn't feel a trace of hesitation or fear.

"I'm going."

She gave her teammates a simple goodbye and went onstage. Seeing her, the Happy fans continued to be at a loss, uncertain how to respond. Instead, it was Tiny Herb that erupted into cheering and support when their first player Liu Xiaobie stood up. Happy's home turf once again become useless. Tang Rou, who could once create an uproar, had become someone who brought a chill to the stadium atmosphere.

The match begun amidst this strange situation.

"I'm very honored to become your first opponent for your 1v3," Liu Xiaobie typed. As a Hand Speed Expert, Liu Xiaobie enjoyed warming up by typing as he moved into position. Liu Xiaobie wasn't trying to mock the other by choosing the topic of the 1v3. He truly admired this young woman for her 1v3 promise. Who didn't have this sort of ambition? However, someone who dared say it, and make such a promise, that really was powerful, fierce.

"However, can you get past me?"

Windy Pavilion was a simple map without much decor. The two characters approached one another, closing the distance between them rapidly, as they adjusted their positions to prepare to attack. Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword leaned further and further forwards, his right hand creeping to his sword hilt with the cover from his body.

The two were only fifteen steps apart.

Fourteen steps...

Thirteen steps...

Liu Xiaobie was on guard for any attacks. The female Battle Mage in front of him often used Dragon Breaks the Ranks to increase speed and charge into an offense. With a mere ten something steps, it was just a blink of an eye for a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Twelve steps...

Eleven steps...

The closer they got, the clearer of a view Liu Xiaobie had. He carefully observed Soft Mist's form. Soft Mist kept her spear held backwards. A Dragon Breaks the Ranks start didn't look like that.

Was she not going to use Dragon Breaks the Ranks?

Then, take this!

Sword Draw!

At six steps away, Sword Draw had already been sent out.

Not close enough?

No, when the attack flew forwards, the two characters were still moving. Six steps was a short distance, so this attack was timed just right!

As expected, the flash of the sword created a shining line, linking the two characters together immediately. Soft Mist suddenly bent her knees in front of him.

That wasn't enough!

There were very few Hand Speed Experts who had slow reactions. Creating variations in their attacks were their best weapon and the sword's slash was immediately adjusted. Just bending down wasn't enough.

However, Soft Mist didn't just get down.

Sky Strike! Soft Mist's spear was launched upwards. Bending down had given her a miniscule chance to maneuver, letting her parry this attack perfectly with her Sky Strike.

Clang!

Their weapons clashed. Sky Strike didn't seem to be enough to completely parry Sword Draw, but Soft Mist had fully adjusted her form by then and used the momentum from that attack to increase her movement speed and the speed of her counterattack.

Dragon Tooth!

The attack sped towards his chest.

As fierce as expected! Liu Xiaobie exclaimed. Wanting to take the initiative to strike with just this attack, she really hasn't changed a bit!

Liu Xiaobie couldn't help but think to back in the beginning, when their captain had them go to the tenth server to train with Ye Xiu. This girl had been been quite a pain to deal with. The her who couldn't even last a minute was already clearly showing her style. Never back down, attack whenever possible, from the first attack to when she fell, she was always on the offense. Though her abilities were unpolished back then and every member of Tiny Herb could defeat her, her burning spirit had left a deep impression on them.

And now, she was finally on the same stage as they were and shouldering a promise of 1v3 in five rounds.

You really have character, but we Tiny Herb aren't willing to be a background to that character!

Liu Xiaobie wasn't Huang Shaotian, and he didn't have the habit of chatting as he fought. Determined and resolute, Flying Sword darted out.

Triple Slash!

Liu Xiaobie didn't back down from Soft Mist's advance, but instead used this movement skill to meet her.

This sort of exchange was exactly what Tang Rou wanted.

Dragon Tooth stabbed forth, but hit air as Flying Sword slashed, his form swerving, and then swerving again.

Triangle Triple Slash!

With Liu Xiaobie's extremely fast hand speed, his direction changes with Triple Slash were dizzying. Flying Sword seemed to teleport, instantly dodging the Dragon Tooth and getting to Soft Mist's flank, the edge of his sword plummeting down!

Chapter 1191: Swift Hand Speed

The tip of the sword dropped down, but… it was a miss.

Afterwards, Flying Sword was already flying out.

Tyrant's Destruction!

Liu Xiaobie's triangle Triple Slash had been extremely fast, but what about Tang Rou? Her speed was no slower. Her Dragon Tooth turned into a Tyrant's Destruction, keeping up with the dizzying Triple Slash. Before the sword could strike her, her spear thrust into Flying Sword's body, throwing him to the side.

Whoa!

Liu Xiaobie was shocked. In the Happy versus Excellent Era Challenger League finals, he had a very deep impression of Tang Rou's hand speed. Xu Bin had asked how he would compare, but Liu Xiaobie hadn't replied.

And now, Tang Rou had been able to catch his triangle Triple Slash, hitting him first before he could hit her...　　

Although his triangle Triple Slash required more inputs, the difference in attack speed between Soft Mist's spear and Liu Xiaobie's sword could not be ignored.　　

Spears usually had low attack speed; most had an attack speed of 2. On the other hand, the Blade Master's lightsabers were the fastest weapons; most had an attack speed of 10.

In Glory, the attack speed on weapons were rated from 1 to 10. However, the difference between a 1 and a 10 wasn't by a magnitude of ten. In reality, the difference between a 1 and a 10 was around 20%.

Glory was an input-heavy game. What truly decided an attack's speed was the player's hand speed. But the difference between having a weapon with an attack speed of 1 versus a weapon with an attack speed of 10 indicated that if you wanted to match the speed of a 10 attack speed weapon with a 1 attack speed weapon, your hand speed would need to be 20% faster.

Thus, a faster weapon attack speed was never a bad thing. However, the game was set up such that weapons with lower attack speed had higher physical attack. Finding the right balance was an issue every player had to consider. Blade Masters tended to use lightsabers and tachis, but there was no shortage of greatsword and broadsword users.

The weapons used by Soft Mist and Flying Sword:

Soft Mist's spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame, had an attack speed of 4. Among spears, it was already a very fast one. Along with the bonus stat of attack speed +1, it's total attack speed was 5.

Flying Sword's Lightsaber, Chasing Spirit, had an attack speed of 10. It had a bonus attack speed of +2.

In total, Chasing Spirit had an attack speed of 12, 7 points higher than Dancing FIre Flowing Flame, a 14% difference.

With this difference, for Soft Mist to match Flying Sword, Tang Rou's hand speed had to be above Liu Xiaobie's. However, in a fight, the two sides wouldn't be starting their attacks at the same time and checking to see who reached the other side first. Because of the inputs required for skills, variations between skills, and differences in attack speed, it wasn't easy to make a simple comparison. Most players used their intuition to make a judgement.

Liu Xiaobie's intuition surprised him. In this match against Tang Rou, he had actually been quite mentally prepared for it. Because of the 1v3 bet, Tang Rou was always first to go in the group arena. Because of this order never changed, it was easier for opponents to prepare for. For example, Liu Xiaobie knew that he would be playing against Tang Rou, so he focused his preparations towards her.

She really is fast. She can completely keep up with me.

But if you think this is the fastest I can go, then you're very very wrong!

As Flying Sword was thrown aside by Tyrant's Destruction, Flying Sword also made his move. A sword light flew out, leaving a sword mark on Soft Mist.

What a fast sword! Tang Rou saw the attack. She wanted to dodge, but her hand speed couldn't keep up.

Wow!

Tang Rou couldn't help but be astonished. Flying Sword had been thrown aside by Tyrant's Destruction, but in that split second, Liu Xiaobie had been able to leave an attack behind.

Although… the attack was more for show? I still have the initiative!　　

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame moved, drawing afterimages one after the other in the air.

Dragon Tooth, Double Stab, attacks that couldn't be more normal, thrust fiercely towards Flying Sword.

Clang clang clang!

Clang clang clang clang!

The weapons of both players collided with each other repeatedly. The two competed speed against speed. Sword light and spear shadows collided and separated. Blood blossomed in the air.

Everyone stared in awe. The commentator and guest in charge of commentating the match were speechless too. 　　

What was there to say?

With how fast the two were fighting, by the time they finished talking about a point, victory might have already been decided. There was no chance for them to say anything.

This was where the difficulty in commentating a Glory match lay. When the two sides started fighting, there were too many small details and mix-ups involved. And if the pace was also fast, there was no room for commentators to give a detailed analysis anywhere. And with how fast Tang Rou and Liu Xiaobie were playing, the commentators couldn't even use the "list the skill names" strategy.　　

By the time he finished calling out the name of a skill, both sides had used another three skills.

"Too fast…" Pan Lin was able to squeeze in two words. It was truly somewhat embarrassing to not be able to point out anything.　　

"Overly fast." Li Yibo was an experienced person with a professional experience. There might not be time to talk about the details, but he could talk about the overall picture. He didn't look at the interactions between the two, just their skill trees.

There seemed to be a bunch of clocks on their skill trees. More and more of the icons on their skill trees were going on cooldown.

Rhythm?

There was no rhythm. These two people were constantly playing catch up. You're faster than me, I'm faster than you, you chase, I chase. It became a competition of pure speed. If they continued to use skills at this pace and this quantity, there won't be any skills to use soon. Or perhaps only low-level skills would be left...

Li Yibo wasn't wrong.

Stab stab stab!

Slash slash slash!

Liu Xiaobie was putting in inputs like crazy, but he still wasn't able to thoroughly suppress his opponent. At this moment, he put in inputs, but the attack he had wanted to get failed to come out. Flying Sword's offensive suddenly halted.　

How?

Liu Xiaobie was only astonished for a second before he immediately realized the problem.　　

The skill was on cooldown, so it couldn't be used.　　

But the skill was still on cooldown?

Not good!

Liu Xiaobie realized that his hand speed had gone out of control. His blind pursuit of speed had put him in this awkward position of being unable to connect skills because they were still on cooldown. It was because of this imbalance between hand speed and rhythm, a frequent mistake in the past, that he had been seen as a player who was wasting away his talent.

Fortunately, he noticed it and fixed it. He started learning how to effectively utilize his hand speed, going as fast as he could when he needed to, but also suppressing it when he needed to be slower. This imbalance in rhythm stopped appearing after being aware of it.

After fixing the problem, Liu Xiaobie improved immensely. Last season, he was just a bit away from making it into All-Stars. This season he hoped that he could breakthrough. But in this match, his old problem had unexpectedly returned. Without him being aware, his hand speed had sped up to such a level already.　

She really is an opponent that's hard to stay calm against!

Fortunately, Tang Rou had been chasing after his hand speed, so she had also been recklessly wasting her skills too to reach that speed. Even though this should have been a huge mistake and a huge opening, it wasn't really one in this match because both sides had committed the same mistake.

"Haha, really…" Liu Xiaobie had wanted to say something in the chat, when Dancing Fire Flowing Flame flashed before him.　

A normal attack?

Liu Xiaobie swiped his mouse and Flying Sword blocked this attack. Soft Mist wasn't done though. She attack again, this time with a Dragon Tooth. Since the vast majority of their mid-level and high-level skills were on cooldown, the two sides were mainly using low cooldown sub-Level 20 skills or normal attacks.

She's still attacking even in this situation. How stubborn! Liu Xiaobie sighed, while warding off Soft Mist's attacks. But he gradually realized that something wasn't right.

Normal attacks had no cooldown and could be used at any time.

Low-level skills had short cooldowns. After a few exchanges, they would be back up and could be used again.

Soft Mist was relying on this offense. It was just like before, dense and fast.　

As a result, Liu Xiaobie that when he noticed his excessive speed and prepared to control his rhythm, Soft Mist continued to stubbornly commit this mistake.

She was still keeping up with her previous hand speed, or it could be said that she was still burning, still trying to think of a way to go faster.　

This...

Liu Xiaobie didn't know how he should assess her. All he knew was that he was starting to have trouble warding off her attacks.　　

What is this girl thinking?

Liu Xiaobie was astonished, but he felt like he had discovered something.　

Among these were memories of the past. When he failed to meet expectations by blindly utilizing hand speed, he made adjustments had made huge improvements. Tang Rou was like the him, who hadn't realized the issue and continued to charge through wildly.

If I had continued along this path, how would things have turned out?　　

Liu Xiaobie discovered that he had never thought about this question before. After not getting the results he wanted from this playstyle, he had quickly made changes.

As for Tang Rou? Did she know? Or was she just stubborn?

Liu Xiaobie didn't know. He only knew that he was having trouble defending. A feeling rose in his heart. The two used to be speeding along neck and neck, but midway through, he suddenly realized that there was perhaps a better way to win, so he stopped speeding along and went to study. The person who kept on speeding along instantly overpassed him...

Was this limited to just this match? Or… his entire professional career?

Would the one who won in the end be the one who continued to speed along or the one to study a better way?

Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword fell with this confusion in him. He didn't fall to Soft Mist's normal attacks and low-level skills, but rather her overwhelming tempo.

Chapter 1192: Imaginary Enemy

I lost!

The instant Flying Sword fell, Liu Xiaobie collapsed against his seat in a daze.

His adjustment after slowing his rhythm had become opening for the opponent. He had figured out this "correct" method with difficulty, only for it to be broken. Was this method not actually the best choice?

Liu Xiaobie now began to doubt himself, just like he had doubted himself when he had used his explosive hand speed time and time again and yet was unable to achieve victory.

Carrying this shock, he walked out of the player booth, offstage, returning to Tiny Herb's player area.

"You played well." His teammates tried to cheer him up, and Liu Xiaobie managed a weak smile. They patted him on his shoulders, but they didn't worry about him too much. It was normal to be disappointed and melancholic after a defeat. If he had come back in high spirits, that would be more worrying.

Liu Xiaobie sat in his seat. Lowering his head, he looked at his two hands.

His hands were still very warm, fatigued after the high-speed playing in that match, and they were still trembling nonstop. Suddenly, a cold drink landed in the palm of his hand.

Liu Xiaobie lifted his head and saw Xu Bin's face.

"Still feeling the aftertaste of that match?" Xu Bin chuckled.

Liu Xiaobie shook his head. There really wasn't too much of an aftertaste. It was just two players losing control of their hand speeds, making two different choices. One didn't care and continued to go wild, while the other recognized the problem and immediately corrected himself.

No matter how you put it, the second option sounded like the correct one. But the victory had gone to the one who continued to go wild.

"It's not a big deal if you lose a match. But don't lose your conviction with it!" Xu Bin said.

Liu Xiaobie was startled.

Conviction!

What was his conviction?

Liu Xiaobie looked at this player in front of him. Xu Bin hadn't even been in Tiny Herb for a whole season, he wasn't any more senior than him here, but he had integrated into Tiny Herb extremely well. And his playstyle was distinct and unique in the professional scene, a style that grinded away at time. Even the audience would become impatient watching him, so despite his skill, he wasn't a very popular player. Before he transferred to Tiny Herb, he always lost by a large margin in the All-Star poll.

Tiny Herb's stage allowed him to shine more, but he didn't abandon his usual style. This was his choice. No matter where he was, he would perform this style unwaveringly.

"Sometimes a choice isn't right or wrong. It just depends on whether or not you have the conviction to carry it out." As Xu Bin spoke, his gaze landed upon another person.

Wang Jiexi, captain of Tiny Herb. Ever since he entered the team, he was Tiny Herb's soul, a presence that every person here respected and admired.

When Liu Xiaobie had been unable to get the results he wanted with his early methods, he made changes with a determined resolve. Because there was this successful role model in front of him, he had complete faith that he could make these changes.

Wang Jiexi, the one called the Magician. But he threw away this title, and it wasn't until he changed many of his battle methods that he led Tiny Herb to its summit.

Wang Jiexi's story was the source of Liu Xiaobie's faith. It was what gave him the determination to change his style and make a breakthrough. But after this battle, his determination was now wavering.

This just showed that he wasn't determined enough. It also showed that he was far from mature enough.

The road was still long!

Liu Xiaobie cracked open the drink and took a long gulp.

By this time, Tiny Herb's second player of the group arena had taken to the stage.

Xiao Yun, Tiny Herb's Battle Mage, Euphorbia.

Number two!

Tang Rou quietly counted in her head.

1v3. After that day, she hadn't made any speech on the matter. Even on a normal day at Happy, it was never brought up, as though it didn't exist. But in her heart, she hadn't forgotten this for even a second.

I have to complete this! Tang Rou didn't know how many times she had repeated this in her heart. And now, this was the final chance in her bet.

This was opponent number two, and Soft Mist had 57% health remaining.

To take down an opponent in the group arena and still have over half health remaining was generally an extremely pleasing result, but for Tang Rou, this was far from enough, because her goal was to take down all three opponents by herself. But now, after only defeating Liu Xiaobie, she'd already used up 43% of Soft Mist's health. This 57% remaining to her was a tired remnant.

To clash head-on with a player who relied on his hand speed, the burden on her own two hands was unimaginable. Added to the crazy intense training Tang Rou had undergone these past 35 days, it would take a toll on even the youngest and most fit people.

And now, she still had to face two opponents, one of whom was Wang Jiexi. Tang Rou had known for a very long time just how fearsome this opponent was.

But now, there was not a trace of fear in her heart.

Defeat the one before her, and then, Wang Jiexi. Her thoughts about Wang Jiexi stopped there, nothing more.

At the start of the second battle, Xiao Yun's message appeared in the chat. "Pretty girl, your show ends here."

There was a taunt in Xiao Yun's words. 1v3? In his eyes, it was just a show.

Xiao Yun had strong feelings of hostility toward Tang Rou. In the team, he had heard that Tiny Herb was interested in Tang Rou and wanted to recruit her, but she had unfortunately turned them down.

Tiny Herb already had a Battle Mage player, himself, Xiao Yun. And yet, the team was now looking at another Battle Mage player. Xiao Yun wasn't at the point where he needed a successor. The fact that Tiny Herb had their eye on her, did that mean that this girl was better than himself?

Such a conclusion wouldn't sit well with anyone. Towards the team, towards Tang Rou, Xiao Yun was rather dissatisfied. And now he had a chance to face off against her. Tang Rou had made that promise of quitting if she couldn't complete a 1v3 in five rounds or whatever, and it just so happened that he was in the fifth round, stuck right in front of Tang Rou.

Xiao Yun was rather excited. To be able to send this Tang Rou, this player who had threatened to replace him, out of the professional scene, it was his pleasure. But he didn't dare to underestimate Tang Rou. In fact, ever since hearing the news that the team had interest in recruiting Tang Rou, he had started paying a lot of attention toward her.

Tang Rou became a powerful competitor in his eyes. Any of her matches, any reports about her, Xiao Yun paid particular attention, so much so that his teammates thought that he was trying to make some advances toward this pretty girl.

"Advances, hell! She'd better hope she doesn't fall into my hands!" This is what Xiao Yun said to Zhou Yebai, one of his teammates with whom he was close. And now, Tang Rou really fell into his hands.

I won't let you have a good time!

Xiao Yun reaffirmed his determination and controlled his Euphorbia to walk out of the spawn point. Although Soft Mist only had about half health remaining, Xiao Yun still hoped to move strategically if possible, instead of meeting her charge directly. Even if he didn't like Tang Rou, he had to admit her ferocity. Direct attacks weren't his forte, he didn't want to use his weakness against her strength. But the problem was, this Windy Pavilion map had hardly any cover on it. There was no way to strategically move to launch a sneak attack. Xiao Yun was helpless and could only direct his character to charge forward. At the opposite corner, Tang Rou's Soft Mist was doing the same thing as always, rushing without any hesitation.

What advantage did he have over Tang Rou?

Imagining Tang Rou as his opponent, Xiao Yun had thought about this comparison consciously and unconsciously many times now.

Experience.

Compared to Tang Rou, he was introduced to Glory earlier, he trained as a Battle Mage earlier, he became a pro player earlier, he played pro matches earlier. Even though he wasn't a very stable core member of Tiny Herb, he was still in Tiny Herb, this powerhouse that had won two championships. Even a casually discarded rookie from this team was picked up and treated like a treasure at Happy. To have a piece of land in this kind of team, this was already something of which to be proud. And a mere rookie wanted to replace him?

Xiao Yun grew angry.

He didn't care that this was just the subjective will of Tiny Herb, or that Tang Rou's refusal had in some ways helped him. He didn't dare express any of his feelings toward Tiny Herb, but this dissatisfaction accumulated in his heart until it finally found its target, Tang Rou, as though she had been the one who actively wanted to steal his position.

The more Xiao Yun thought, the more hatred and rage he felt.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

This was an opening move that Tang Rou liked to use, but in this battle between two players of the same class, it was Xiao Yun who used it first. Not only did he want to win, he wanted to win beautifully. He wanted to show his team that he was far superior to Tang Rou. Anything she could do, he could do better.

This Dragon Breaks the Ranks came very suddenly. But a powerful attack at the beginning rarely hit the opponent because the starting animation for such powerful attacks was generally more noticeable than the ones for smaller attacks. Tang Rou was now a skilled Battle Mage player, and as soon as she saw Euphorbia's pose, she immediately controlled Soft Mist to dodge. Even though Xiao Yun also immediately made adjustments, when his spear shot out, it didn't manage to land on its target.

Soft Mist dodge to the side, and after Euphorbia's powerful attack whistled by, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame leapt out.

Sky Strike!

Soft Mist's first attack in this round was rather plain.

Euphorbia immediately leapt backward, as though still carrying some remnants of the Dragon Breaks the Ranks. After avoiding this Sky Strike, his spear was already sweeping wildly toward Soft Mist.

From top to bottom, this was a Draconic Crusher, a level 50 Battle Mage attack. If this attack landed, the target was guaranteed to fall over on the ground. And the priority of a level 50 skill was much higher than low-level skills, so even if Soft Mist was able to adjust the angle of her Sky Strike, she wouldn't be able to parry this Draconic Crusher.

So Xiao Yun was completely confident. But Soft Mist's Sky Strike continued toward him.

Ridiculous, I'll flatten you!

Xiao Yun's mouse moved faster. The Draconic Crusher pressed down on Soft Mist and her Sky Strike.

Ping!

The two spears met in the air, and the result was decided in an instant. The parrying effect of Sky Strike didn't seem to exist and was immediately smothered by Draconic Crusher.

What about Soft Mist? It seemed that this attack was too strong, so strong that she had no way of bracing herself against it, instead rolling to reduce the force.

But that movement wasn't necessary, Xiao Yun was very clear. The Sky Strike was just crushed by the Draconic Crusher, but there was suddenly a jump, and a Dragon Tooth leapt towards him like a viper.

Chapter 1193: What’s Fearsome Is Her Overwhelming Determination

She's so fast! No wonder Liu Xiaobie lost.

Xiao Yun had Euphorbia dodge. Although he had been mentally prepared for this situation, when it actually happened, he became a bit nervous.

Indeed, this was not an opponent he could take head-on! With this, Xiao Yun's prediction was confirmed. And since he knew this long before, of course he had prepared a strategy.

If she wants to be fast, then I can't let her be fast. With my understanding of the Battle Mage class, I can definitely suppress her rhythm!

In a battle between two players of the same class, each side had a greater understanding of what changes could be made in battle. If Tang Rou weren't a Battle Mage, Xiao Yun wouldn't have this confidence, but since she was a Battle Mage, he believed that he could control the flow of battle. After all, his opponent was still a rookie, with limited understanding and control of the class. In this same-class battle, he had a slight advantage, Xiao Yun believed.

He calmly controlled his character to jump backward and avoid Soft Mist's Dragon Tooth.

Another jump let him avoid Soft Mist's subsequent Double Stab.

After the Double Stab, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame suddenly flipped up to a Sky Strike, the skill's cooldown having just ended. But Euphorbia stuck his spear downward and this Sky Strike was suppressed. None of Soft Mist's consecutive attacks managed to succeed.

The corner of Xiao Yun's mouth twisted into a cold smirk. He felt like a cat toying with a mouse.

But a Magic Chaser was already flying toward him, a Light Chaser accumulated from the earlier Sky Strike.

As expected, not a second of rest!

This Light Chaser wasn't outside of Xiao Yun's expectations either, and he very calmly dodged it. Soft Mist immediately came with another attack, even faster, with the speed bonus granted after firing a Light Chaser. This, too, Xiao Yun had accounted for, and after he dodged the Chaser, he was already defending against the sudden attack that would come next.

And his responses to her attacks weren't just ordinary dodges, as that would just give Tang Rou more space to increase her speed. Xiao Yun relied more on parrying attacks, limiting her ability to chain attacks and ruining her rhythm.

He did fairly well. After all, he was a member of Tiny Herb, and he had trained with the Battle Mage class for several years now. He was very clear on where and how to attack to maximally interfere with her attack rhythm.

This again…

Tang Rou was no stranger to this current situation. In fact, it could be said that she had just experienced this.

Last round against Heavenly Swords, even though Happy had won the two points from the group arena, Tang Rou, who was the first to come out, was defeated by the second person on their team. Heavenly Swords' second player, Wen Kebei, was a Battle Mage.

Tang Rou had just experienced a same-class battle last round, and this round she once again fought against a same-class player. Xiao Yun and Wen Kebei both fought with this interference style that could only be executed by someone familiar with the class. But Xiao Yun, compared to Wen Kebei, was more practiced, and Tang Rou was suppressed harder than she was last round.

It was harder, but she knew it better.

Tyrant's Destruction! Tang Rou still refused to give up on attacking.

That smirk continue to hang on the corner of Xiao Yun's mouth. With a practiced motion of the mouse, his Euphorbia also unleashed a Tyrant's Destruction, crashing toward Soft Mist's.

An instantaneous control, an instantaneous attack, and in an instant, the spears were about to collide once again. But suddenly, Dancing Fire Flowing Flame suddenly shot upward.

In the last moment, just before the two skills were about to hit, Tang Rou adjusted the direction of her skill. No time to delay, the timing couldn't be off by a hair.

She did it!

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame and the spear that Euphorbia swung toward her slipped past each other. And Soft Mist jumped into the air, and in the same way, with hardly a second to spare, she just barely dodged his attack.

Barely, but she managed to dodge it. And Xiao Yun? After discovering this change, it was already too late to react.

Tang Rou pushed her change all the way to the end, leaving no time for Xiao Yun to make any follow-up move.

Not just him, even someone with ten or a hundred times the hand speed wouldn't have been able to keep up with Tang Rou's change at that moment.

Shit!

Xiao Yun only had time to shout in his mind. He didn't even have the chance to retract the smirk on his mouth when Euphorbia was hit by Soft Mist's Tyrant's Destruction. At the same time, flames burst forth and landed upon Euphorbia's body, as Dancing Fire Flowing Flame's special effect "Flowing Flame" was activated.

After one attack succeeded, things got easier. The next skills came one after another in a combo.

This was a combo. If this offense could be casually broken, then it wouldn't be called a combo.

Xiao Yun's Euphorbia and the Dancing Fire Flowing Flame in Soft Mist's hands met over and over again. Tang Rou was completely immersed in the controls. Of course, she hoped with this one chain of combos she could defeat her opponent, but sadly, things didn't turn out that way.

Xiao Yun, who understood Battle Mages well, quickly found a flaw in Tang Rou's combo.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

Seeing the flaw, Xiao Yun directly used a powerful attack. Tang Rou hastily responded, Soft Mist drawing back her spear, but she had no way of completely parrying such a high-level attack.

Soft Mist's offensive came to an abrupt end, and Xiao Yun used this Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart to retaliate with a new high of attacks.

Tang Rou's response to this offensive was completely different from Xiao Yun's. Xiao Yun would observe, anticipate, search for an opportunity. But when she faced each of Euphorbia's attacks, she would always try to make a move, she controlled her character nonstop, as though Euphorbia's attack sequence contained flaws everywhere.

But in reality, Euphorbia's attacks were not interrupted. Tang Rou struggled endlessly, but to no avail.

But her struggling like this gave her opponent a lot of pressure. Xiao Yun felt a strong sense of danger, as though if he made the tiniest slip, it would immediately cause him to lose this match.

This state was unexpected for Xiao Yun. He was nervous, he didn't dare become careless, but the more he felt this, the more flawed his controls became, often scaring himself into a sweat. Thus, Xiao Yun was unable to maintain his offensive for long before he, too, finally revealed an opening. The unrelenting Tang Rou instantly seized the opportunity. Even death wouldn't have stopped her as she surged forward. One attack landed, and immediately a chain of attacks followed. If Xiao Yun seized a chance and interfered again? No worries, she'd just come again!

The two sides traded the initiative back and forth, but whether or not she was attacking or being attacked, Tang Rou's Soft Mist always maintained an offensive stance. When attacking, she was always moving forward; when being attacked, she caused a constant fear of counterattack in the opponent, like a thorn in the back. The sweat on Xiao Yun's forehead accumulated, and the string in his heart was wound tighter and tighter.

The tighter he was, the more he didn't dare relax his hands or legs, and Xiao Yun's apprehension only increased. The more he didn't want to make a mistake, the more often a mistake would come find him. The battle seemed like a continuous exchange of attack and defense positions, but Xiao Yun's attack periods grew shorter and shorter, and Tang Rou was seizing opportunities and attacking for longer and longer periods of time.

Under these exchanges, Xiao Yun watched as Soft Mist slowly closed the gap between their health levels. He grew panicked, and he started making more mistakes. He once again reminded himself to stay calm, stay stable, but his two hands were so stiff, so unresponsive, it was as though they were no longer his own. Where did his normal casual and easy controls go? Xiao Yun wanted to stuff his hands in his mouth and bite down hard.

His 43% health lead was pulled to a tie, and then, he started losing.

The more Xiao Yun played, the more chaotic he became. He no longer had a fraction of the confidence he'd had at the beginning of this match. All he had was overwhelming panic.

How could it be like this?

Xiao Yun didn't understand. He had prepared thoroughly to face Tang Rou, he was confident, so how come as soon as he was onstage, he couldn't perform? How was his condition today so bad?

Xiao Yun couldn't stabilize himself or control the situation. He could only lose.

Tang Rou completed the 1v2, successfully entering the third battle of the group arena.

The crowd was silent.

1v2. This result was already valiant, but because Tang Rou promised a 1v3, she wasn't done yet. Tiny Herb's next player onstage was their captain Wang Jiexi. And Tang Rou? Soft Mist, after this battle, only had 16% health remaining.

"Coach Li, what do you think… this…" Commentator Pan Lin spoke haltingly. To challenge Wang Jiexi with 16% health, it was very difficult for anyone to have hope!

"Haha, the wonder of competition is its unpredictability! Perhaps we will witness a miracle!" Li Yibo laughed.

"That's to say, Coach Li still looks favorably on Tang Rou?" Pan Lin said.

"We've already reached this point. Tang Rou is a player full of energy, so who knows, she might achieve the inconceivable!" Li Yibo said.

"Alright, let's look forward to the result of what has been the focus of the past five rounds! Team Happy's Tang Rou versus Team Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi!" Pan Lin announced.

The television broadcaster made this announcement, and the live screens in the stadium displayed the next player from Tiny Herb who was about to play. But Wang Jiexi didn't hurry to go onstage, and instead waited for Xiao Yun to return.

Seeing the captain looking at him, Xiao Yun lowered his head, and looked for a corner in which to hide.

"What's most fearsome about Tang Rou is not her technique, nor her hand speed, but her overwhelming determination." After Wang Jiexi spoke, he stepped toward the stage.

Happy versus Tiny Herb, third match of the group arena.

The final opponent in the 1v3. Win this, and she would complete her promise. Just one last step.

However, Tang Rou was already powerless.

Vaccaria slid down from the sky, trailing behind him the glittering remnants of starlight from the dance of Star Extinction.

"A 1v3 is not so easy!" Wang Jiexi said.

In the third battle of the group arena, Wang Jiexi won. No damage taken.

The audience was once again silent.

If Tang Rou's 1v3 had succeeded, they would have been dissatisfied. But seeing her defeated so swiftly by Wang Jiexi, everyone felt a bit disappointed.

They themselves couldn't say for what sort of outcome they had hoped.

In Happy's player area, everything was even more still. Failing to complete a 1v3 was nothing. In fact, in terms of the match progression, for their first player to meet the opponent's third, they held a great advantage. But, the outcome that this 1v3 failure implied…

At this moment, no matter how hard Chen Guo tried, she couldn't squeeze out even a half-corner of a smile.

Chapter 1194: I Don’t Agree

She lost…

In the end, Tang Rou was unable to complete her promise of a 1v3 within five rounds. Chen Guo couldn't muster even the barest of smiles, but when Tang Rou returned, she was still able to smile at all of them, just like after her losses in all of the previous group arenas. That smile was to let them know that they didn't need to worry for her. But if they didn't worry now, when would they? Five rounds had already passed, there were no more chances!

Seeing how Tang Rou was still wearing such a smile, Chen Guo only felt more miserable. She wanted to go up and say something, but she didn't know what she could say. Tang Rou quietly sat back down in her seat, and her face finally revealed a trace of exhaustion. 35 days of crazy training, and a frenzied performance in every match. This time, facing the powerhouse Tiny Herb, she defeated two opponents in a row, but in the end, she fell so swiftly at the hands of Wang Jiexi.

Was everything already over?

Chen Guo felt a numbness in her nose. She looked at Tang Rou, whose head was lifted, staring at the replays on the screens, just like normal. They were all displaying shots from her match that had just ended.

Ye Xiu stood up, but he didn't say anything to Tang Rou. He still followed the progression of the match and said something to the next player who was about to go onstage. Chen Guo was right next to him, and yet she couldn't hear a thing he said.

Happy's second player in the group arena was Steamed Bun, a player that many people thought shared some traits with Wang Jiexi. This time, facing Wang Jiexi, he lost speedily.

Two opponents defeated consecutively, yet Vaccaria had barely lost any health. The audience's eyes were wide.

Everyone had been focused on whether or not Tang Rou could complete a 1v3. But now, it was actually shaping up to be a total reversal like this?

Amidst everyone's guessing, Fang Rui went onstage…

In the group arena, Tiny Herb won.

The dead silence in the crowd only belonged to Happy's reporters. The Tiny Herb fans supporting their away team were thrilled, excited, and screaming crazily. Even Pan Lin, in the middle of the broadcast, was nearly incoherent.

"This… This is truly…" Pan Lin tried to organize his words. "Just when Tang Rou defeated two Tiny Herb players and everyone was wondering whether or not she could create a miracle, Wang Jiexi, Tiny Herb's Captain Wang Jiexi, the Magician Wang Jiexi, with a crisp and clear 1v3, tells everyone: impossible! Tiny Herb maintains its record of never being 1v3'd! Wang Jiexi is truly one of the most reliable players in the Alliance! An awe-inspiring reversal!"

The excitement of the Tiny Herb fans conquered the entire stadium.

Tang Rou failed her 1v3, and the opponent pulled off a 1v3 to reverse the situation and win the match. One could only imagine how low Happy's spirits were.

How would the upcoming team competition play out? Very few people could concentrate on this question, as everyone was still worrying about Tang Rou's future. On the other hand, after Wang Jiexi's 1v3 to win back the group arena, Tiny Herb's morale reached its peak. With this shift, in the end, Happy lost the team competition to Tiny Herb as well. The match ended, 2 to 8.

To be honest, Happy losing to Tiny Herb wasn't any big news. The most attention-grabbing part of this match was Tang Rou's promise of completing a 1v3, and this too was a large reason why the live broadcast chose to show this match. And now, the dust settled. The reporters had all already gathered at the post-match press conference, discussing in a chaotic manner, some regretful, some gloating.

Esports Time's Ruan Cheng, of course, would not miss this press conference. It could even be said that he was the star of this conference. Right now, he acted like a victor, delightedly moving through the crowds of reporters, chatting with some here and some there, leaving the sound of his hearty laughter throughout.

"Are you happy?" Ruan Cheng suddenly heard someone speak up beside him. He turned his head and saw this person glaring right at him.

"Seeing such a talented player forced to leave the professional scene for a reason like this. Are you happy?" When Ruan Cheng turned toward him, Chang Xian spat out this sentence word by word, syllable by syllable.

He was the reporter closest to Happy, but among all of these people, Chang Xian was still just a junior. His identity and position couldn't compare at all to Esports Time's senior writer Ruan Cheng. But at this moment, Chang Xian mustered his courage and hurled this question at him.

"Haha," Ruan Cheng laughed. "Everyone needs to take responsibility for their choices, and I'm pleased to see a player meet such a result after their own arrogant words and actions. Of course, I prefer to see that she learns a lesson from this, corrects her shortcomings, and continues to improve. Something like this wouldn't actually force her to retire, no? Haha."

"You're exactly right, take responsibility for your choices. Everyone's very willing to accept a sincere apology!" Another reporter who disapproved of Tang Rou's actions came to support Ruan Cheng's opinion.

Seeing these seniors pretending to be innocent and sympathetic, Chang Xian truly felt disgusted. These people always put themselves on the moral high ground, casually pointing fingers at other people, as though anything that didn't fit their views was automatically wrong. They spoke as though this were all for Tang Rou's good, but Chang Xian was clear, they just wanted to see Tang Rou embarrassed, see this strong and tough player bow her head before them, thus proving the authority of their right to speak.

Chang Xian didn't want to see Tang Rou lower her head before these guys, but he was even less willing to see Tang Rou quit the pro scene like this.

"They're here, Happy's people are here." After this shout, all of the reporters took their positions. Ruan Cheng smiled and organized his appearance. With all the attitude of a victor, he prepared to thoroughly enjoy this evening.

Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, Chen Guo, and Tang Rou, these were the four people from Happy that came for this press conference. The reporters were quietly delighted, since they had worried earlier that Tang Rou simply wouldn't attend. But now, it seemed this girl was quite magnanimous! Not bad, lower your head! Apologize!

As long as you come with the right attitude, everyone will gladly accept it.

Although everyone was eager to jump right in, seeing the four Happy members take their seats, in the end they all turned toward Ruan Cheng. After all, this whole affair was his creation. At this time, they had to give him face, let him complete this topic.

"Ahem!" Ruan Cheng of course wouldn't pass up this opportunity. After the signal that he could begin, he gracefully stood up to ask a question. "It's a great shame that Happy was in such condition, only to suffer such a reversal." Ruan Cheng was in no hurry, and said these perfunctory opening words.

"Yes, it's a shame," Ye Xiu answered.

"It's a greater shame that Miss Tang Rou failed to complete her 1v3 by just one step." Ruan Cheng smiled as he hit upon the topic at hand.

Tang Rou sat on the panel. Contrary to everyone's expectations, she didn't appear to be in a rush to examine her mistakes, nor did she show any sign of disappointment or loss. Like every other time she had appeared in such a press conference, she simply sat there, upright and proper.

What was the meaning of this?

More than a few reporters were already having second thoughts.

Promise?

To be honest, not many people really took this very seriously. Tang Rou, with her looks and skill as a player, had an immeasurable value in the pro scene. There was really no way to strictly enforce this so-called promise. But for the sake of the team's most immediate interests, at this point, they had to smooth over their public relations somehow, right? Even if they used the reasons Ruan Cheng had exposed earlier, "for love,""for the team,""for the supporters," or other such arguments. Or if they really had nothing else, even a reason like "to generate interest" could very well be brazenly announced!

But, with this calm and stability in front of them, as though this whole situation didn't exist, what was she planning to do? Was she pretending to have amnesia?

Everyone looked at Ruan Cheng. Stop playing around, get to the point!

Ruan Cheng was also beginning to have doubts in his heart. At this time, this player seriously didn't have any intention of lowering her head? What an infuriating person!

Ruan Cheng's mood worsened, and so he picked up the pace.

"If I've counted correctly, this is now the fifth round since your promise of five rounds. Although Miss Tang Rou only missed it by one step, the 1v3 was not completed. It seems that, Miss Tang Rou, you said earlier, if you couldn't complete a 1v3 in five rounds, you would quit?"

Ruan Cheng had initially intended for Tang Rou to stand up of her own volition to admit her wrong and beg forgiveness, but now, she was just sitting motionless at the panel, as though she would completely ignore the topic if no one brought it up. Ruan Cheng couldn't stand it any more, and so he directly dug up the promise.

Instantly, everyone's gazes swiveled to Tang Rou.

Tang Rou smiled. "Quit? I don't agree. Go on."

I don't agree, go on?

What was that?

The reporters were instantly in an uproar. Even Ruan Cheng was stunned. Chang Xian hadn't expected Tang Rou to do this, either.

Refuse to lower your head, but refuse to quit as well, what can you do?

Chang Xian hadn't expected that even this pretty girl would have delinquent tendencies. To put it bluntly, she was admitting that she was breaking her word? This this this… She was completely destroying her reputation!

A promise, no matter in what context, held significance. The words you said, the water you spilled, you could find this or that ridiculous excuse, but in the end you needed to find an explanation to give yourself a place to stand.

But Tang Rou wasn't standing on anything, she just gave that sentence: I don't agree.

Exactly!

If the player didn't agree, there was truly no one who could force her to quit, so this reason was very strong. But to do this was to burn your image and reputation to ashes. Having a good appearance couldn't save you. Character, integrity, those were forever a person's most important traits.

"You don't agree?" This response caught Ruan Cheng completely off guard. His voice had gone strangled, he had no idea how to go on. "You… you shameless!"

He couldn't hold back, Ruan Cheng just couldn't hold back. To directly hurl such insults was of course frowned upon, and these writers often had to use very roundabout ways to insult someone. But in this moment, he truly couldn't hold back anymore. This was shameless. No word could describe this more accurately.

"You can say what you will," Tang Rou said. "I will continue as always. Thank you."

Thank you? What the fuck! The reporters were instantly enraged. Are you trying to make fun of us?

Chapter 1195: Each Crazier than the Next

The atmosphere of the press conference reached a boiling point. Even those who hadn't initially harbored any ill-will toward Tang Rou could no longer hold themselves back after seeing her current attitude.

What was this? The stubbornness of a mule? You clearly lost the bet, but you don't apologize and recognize that you were overly confident, nor do you quit the Alliance like you said. You just toss the sentence "I don't agree"?

In the ten years of the Glory Pro League, there had never been a player like this before, a player who simply refused to recognize the words they had previously said.

Pro players were public figures, so it was crucial that they had a good reputation. A player like this who didn't keep her word, no matter how good her appearance or disposition, what kind of business would dare endorse her? Without these endorsements, who would be willing to use her in advertising? Even pro teams, in order to avoid affecting the image of the team as a whole, would stay far away from a player with such a bad image, no matter how skilled the player was.

Tang Rou's action was completely self-destructive. Although the reporters were boiling, aside from Ruan Cheng's accusation of "shameless," none of them could find any other condemnation. None of them had ever experienced such a situation before, they didn't have experience!

For now, the reporters were like wasps whose nest had just been attacked, filling the air with their buzzing. In the midst of it all, it was possible that a few wanted to ask some questions, but in such a noisy and chaotic situation, no one could hear anything clearly.

"Everyone quiet down, quiet!!" the Alliance's media spokesperson shouted. Normally, a pro team had its own spokesperson, who would act as the host for any press conferences a team held. Happy didn't have one, so the Alliance's employee was a temporary fill-in. A worker from the Alliance would defend a pro team to some extent, but in the end they wouldn't be as exhaustively dedicated to the team like a worker from the team itself. This worker right now just wanted to restore order and didn't particularly care about Happy itself.

The reporters' uproar lasted for almost five whole minutes. As it slowly settled down, everyone adopted faces of indignation. This time, none of them felt that they understood Tang Rou's actions. Chang Xian had been pleased at first to see the reporters utterly flustered and anxious, but after that passed, he too started to worry about Tang Rou. He understood clearly how disadvantageous Tang Rou's attitude was, and he didn't know what sort of public relations strategy this was. With his understanding of Happy, they didn't have any dedicated public relations team. Their press conferences were all very casual, otherwise this wouldn't have attracted so much hatred.

Amidst the reporters who had regained order, Ruan Cheng acted as the voice of general opinion as he stood at the front, face filled with resentment.

"Miss Tang Rou, may I ask, what the meaning of your words was just now?" Ruan Cheng asked, exceedingly sophisticated. Although he had already carefully considered this, he still feared that Tang Rou had hidden some sort of trap in her words. After all, this whole situation was too incredible and ridiculous, and had never happened before in all ten years of Glory.

"I mean that I will not quit the Alliance, I will continue to play," Tang Rou said.

Alright, this time she made herself clear. There was no way for her meaning to be twisted, was there? Ruan Cheng was suddenly full of energy.

"Then, what do you think your earlier promise was all about? You think that your simple 'I don't agree' is enough to erase it? What do you have to say to all those Glory players that cared about you, wished you well, supported you?" Ruan Cheng said.

"Oh." Hearing this, Tang Rou stood up.

"I deeply regret being unable to complete a 1v3. I have disappointed all those who have cared about me, wished me well, and supported me." As she said this, Tang Rou made a short bow, and then straightened. "However, I will not retire because of this. Even if it hurts me, I will continue, and I will bear the burden of the disgrace that results. I only worry that my teammates will be dragged into this, and I hope that the team will not be harmed by any of this, because this is all my own decision. I hope that all of the criticism and accusations will only be aimed at myself, and not at Team Happy or the other team members."

"Your behavior tarnishes the reputation of your team," Ruan Cheng said.

"Yes, you are correct, the team is implicated because of me, they are victims," said Tang Rou. "Thank you for being so reasonable."

The atmosphere of the press conference became twisted again.

What's this? She wants to bear all the consequences of her faults? After this clear spiel of words, those who wanted to defame Happy along with her could no longer open their mouths. But to take all responsibility like this, this Tang Rou, has she not considered her future?

All of the reporters sensed how insane it was for Tang Rou to destroy her reputation and future prospects like this. But they had no way of attacking this point.

"Do you know what effect this will have on your future?"

For a question like this, a simple "none of your business" was enough of a retort. If the other party really didn't care about their future prospects, it was idiotic to make this a point. So Ruan Cheng had opened his mouth to point out to her supporters how Tang Rou harmed her team. But Tang Rou accepted all of this, in a "if you want to curse me, just bring it" attitude.

Any other possible position was unsustainable!

Were they supposed to say, so many people were looking forward to seeing you leave if you failed the 1v3, so now that you really failed, how can you make it up to those who were anticipating your departure?

An attack like that would probably only make Tang Rou more earnest in breaking her word, right?

The experienced reporters actually had no idea what to say next. They could only quietly swear in their hearts that as soon as they left they would figure out how to attack this Tang Rou. But looking at Tang Rou's stance, they couldn't help but feel a bit timid again. She already made it clear that she didn't care about her reputation and that she didn't need your support or understanding. What use would their attacks have? Would it just be a catharsis?

The reporters were at a loss because of Tang Rou's toughness. Ruan Cheng had been prepared to taste the fruits of victory, only to be faced with this unexpected scene. Tang Rou embraced the situation and took everything upon herself. Then what about Happy? What do you think of this?

"To Happy's members, what do you think of Tang Rou's performance today?" Ruan Cheng said in a low voice. He finally avoided Tang Rou, he had no way of facing her toughness, he had to find a new breakthrough.

"Tang Rou's performance today…" Happy's Captain Ye Xiu opened his mouth, "was excellent." He nodded his head, filled with certainty. And then in the face of a field of dumbstruck stares, he continued, "In the group arena, she defeated two opponents and fought all the way to the third person. A performance like that is truly powerful."

The reporters felt like crying. God, could you please stop playing dumb! You know that that's not what we're asking. But then again, disregarding the promise, for one player to fight all the way to the third was indeed very strong! Some reporters fell into a trance. But the rest were just about to accuse the God of playing dumb, when Ye Xiu continued to speak.

"The ones who should be strictly criticized are the two players who went up next. Two players, and you couldn't take down the opponent's one player? Especially the third player, the great general anchoring the group arena, Fang Rui! The team didn't spend so much money to get you over here just so you could be a useless dim sum! You couldn't even take care of a Wang Jiexi?" Ye Xiu berated him. The tone of that "couldn't even take care of a Wang Jiexi" was deafening! Ever since Wang Jiexi had entered the Alliance, the reporters had never heard this kind of sentence before.

"Yeah yeah yeah." To the side, Fang Rui confessed, ashamed, "I messed up, I couldn't focus my spirits to play well. Someone like Wang Jiexi, I should at least be able to fight ten of him."

"That's a bit much!" Ye Xiu said.

"Eight?" Fang Rui said.

"Mm." Ye Xiu nodded.

The reporters were going crazy. They had no way of reporting talk like this. Anyone could hear that it was a joke. If you actually talked about this seriously, everyone would doubt the judgment of your report. They could only record this talk while cursing this shamelessness, and when Wang Jiexi came out later, they could interview him and see if he objected to this. Only that would be reasonable.

But the main topic right now shouldn't be this!

"God Ye Xiu, as the captain of Team Happy, what are your thoughts on your teammate's retraction of her promise? I seem to remember that before, you very firmly believed Tang Rou could complete a 1v3?" One reporter, through gritted teeth, strung together a few clear keywords to spit out this question.

"Those were necessary words for the public," Ye Xiu said dismissively. "Is this your first day as a reporter or something?"

The reporters spat blood. But they had to admit that he had a point. When facing doubts about a team's player, the captain, or even any member of the team, had to defend the player, unless there was some serious conflict! Whether or not you believed in your teammate, when facing the world, the answer was always a public "yes."

But Ruan Cheng seized a flaw in Ye Xiu's words.

"That's to say, God Ye Xiu, in reality, you didn't actually believe that Tang Rou could complete a 1v3, right?" Ruan Cheng aggressively asked.

"How could that be the case? Have you forgotten, I was the one who set the five round limit?" Ye Xiu laughed.

"But now, she failed to complete it," said Ruan Cheng.

"Mm, in the end, no one can be one hundred percent certain about the outcome of competition, not even me," Ye Xiu said.

"But she made that kind of promise," said Ruan Cheng.

"And now she doesn't intend to uphold it," Ye Xiu said calmly.

"What do you think of that?" Ruan Cheng said.

"The team cannot interfere in a personal decision. I'm very glad that Tang Rou could make such a decision, allowing us to avoid losing such an outstanding player. Thank you." Ye Xiu's last two words were directed toward Tang Rou.

"You're welcome," Tang Rou replied with a smile.

Insane! Everyone on this team is insane!

The reporters were dumbstruck. Could these people not tell the severity of this situation? They were still relaxed as they responded with ridicule. If this were any other team, the public relations team probably would have already burned to ashes from this, no?

Tang Rou said that her promise was her individual decision and had nothing to do with the team. But, as a member of this team, her reputation was part of the team's reputation as a whole. Even with her statement, the team would still experience a negative effect. Regarding this, did the manager of this team, their boss, have no objection to this? She must be enraged in her heart? As it happened, Happy's boss Chen Guo was also on the panel of this press conference, and the reporters turned their fire.

Chapter 1196: The Most Challenging

At any other time, Chen Guo would have just about died laughing from seeing these reporters harassed like this. But now, she didn't feel like laughing at all, only crying. From the very first second she sat on this stage, she was trying very hard to control herself and prevent the tears from falling.

The rules of the Alliance didn't extend to a team's boss, so Chen Guo could have skipped all of the pre- and post-match press conferences. But now, she sat here, next to Tang Rou, because she wanted to be with Tang Rou, because she knew that Tang Rou was making a very difficult decision.

Chen Guo felt like she was good for nothing. She had wanted to sit up here to give Tang Rou support, only to find that she herself was the weakest. She couldn't be calm like Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, or steadfast like Tang Rou. Hold back the tears… this was all she could manage to do.

The 1v3 promise had caused an uproar in the outside world, and within Happy, it had also been a topic that everyone treated with caution. After the end of the press conference where she had made the announcement, the absolutely rational An Wenyi had said frankly that Tang Rou's actions were irresponsible to the extreme.

Tang Rou hadn't retorted, and afterwards, she spent her days and nights in intense training. Everyone saw this, and so An Wenyi temporarily refrained from expressing his opinion any further. After all, the five rounds hadn't been fought yet, perhaps Tang Rou could really pull it off. As her teammate, at a time like this, An Wenyi went along with the others and chose to encourage her and cheer her on.

35 days passed, five rounds finished, and in the end Tang Rou hadn't been able to do it. In the prep room after the match, An Wenyi didn't rush to say anything, but everyone could see from his eyes just how dissatisfied he was.

And then, Tang Rou apologized, for her earlier irresponsibility. And then, she announced her decision: revoking her promise, and continuing to play.

Everyone was stunned, especially the most dissatisfied An Wenyi. Now, this rational player viewed Tang Rou's decision as even more inconceivable.

Everyone knew the pressure she would have to bear from a decision like this.

The irresponsible Tang Rou now used this sort of method to take responsibility for her team. Why couldn't she just soften up a bit, admit some weakness?

An Wenyi couldn't understand. He just knew that if it were him, he never would have thought of this self-destructive tough method.

The prep room was quiet.

Why wasn't anyone dissuading her? An Wenyi looked at Captain Ye Xiu, at Boss Chen Guo, at his other teammates, but no one said anything. Was it because no one recognized the severity of this problem? That certainly wasn't the case. The current silence precisely demonstrated just how shocking and frightening Tang Rou's decision here was.

But no one stood up to say anything. Had everyone lost their reason? An Wenyi wanted to step forward, wanted to logically analyze the most appropriate way to address this situation. But, he couldn't open his mouth. How to address this? An Wenyi thought that she should just lower her head to the reporters, admit that her earlier words were improper, and earnestly request that everyone agree to let her withdraw her improper promise.

An Wenyi could clearly see that those reporters weren't actually very interested in forcing a player to retire, as that would generate animosity towards themselves. They were looking forward to this kind of scene, her lowering her head. With that, they could paint themselves as saviors leading a player to the correct way.

Was that what had to happen?

In his mind, An Wenyi imagined Tang Rou's voice quietly begging forgiveness, and he saw those gleeful, arrogant, puffed up faces. After that, those guys would of course generously accept Tang Rou.

"Fuck!" The rational An Wenyi actually swore, harshly kicking a locker. This was just so fucking disgusting! An Wenyi found that he couldn't find it in himself to persuade Tang Rou to act any differently than she had.

"Then… that's that!" Ye Xiu said.

"Ye Xiu, come out here for a second." Boss Chen Guo suddenly walked out of the prep room and called out to Ye Xiu.

"Hm?" Ye Xiu followed her out.

Just when Tang Rou made her decision, a terrifying thought suddenly surfaced in Chen Guo's mind.

Given Tang Rou's personality, it wasn't too hard to understand her making such a tough answer and taking greater pressure upon herself. And so, Chen Guo suddenly thought of Ye Xiu. That guy, maybe he anticipated early on that Tang Rou couldn't 1v3 within five rounds. The five round limit was his taking advantage of the situation to throw her into a trap.

Because he had very clearly expressed before that Tang Rou's dedication to Glory wasn't stable. Her interest came from the challenge, so it was possible that one day, when she reached a certain height and there were no more challenges to interest her, she would lose her interest in Glory. At that time, this added to her life attitude of a casual rich girl, what would be her resulting attitude? Would she directly quit Glory, just like she had quit music? Or would she aimlessly continue along, just because she was part of the team? Neither outcome was one that Happy wanted to see. So this time, Ye Xiu threw Tang Rou into a trap, putting her in shackles and forcing her to endlessly fight?

"You woman, you're really too scary!" Ye Xiu was shocked after hearing Chen Guo's blunt questioning.

"It's not like that?" Chen Guo said.

"Of course not."

Chen Guo sighed in relief. She didn't know where this thought had come from either, perhaps because she had watched Ye Xiu for a while now, and his normal way of doing things was often rather cold and indifferent. But Chen Guo would not tolerate his orchestrating this kind of plan to the teammates at his side. Hearing his refutation, Chen Guo was relieved.

"But now, she…"

"She'll suffer an enormous amount of pressure. This is really her personality, always choosing the most difficult and the most challenging," said Ye Xiu.

Tang Rou chose the most difficult way to face this. Then what about Chen Guo herself? She couldn't retreat. As a team, no matter what, they should always support and accept every single member of the team. Today, she stood here with Tang Rou, with whom she was the closest, but if it were any other member of Happy, she would do the same.

With these beliefs, Chen Guo calmly faced the reporters who raged around her. Even if she couldn't control her tears, she would be Tang Rou's most firm supporter, the most firm supporter of every single player on Team Happy. Just like that.

Insane! Happy's people are all insane.

This Tang Rou didn't consider her own image at all, and Happy's boss didn't consider the effect of such a player on the team's image as a whole. There were clearly problems with the thought process of this team's operations, big problems.

Don't they understand these principles? It seemed that they did, but they acted like this anyway. Tang Rou was willing to bear the public pressure, and Happy's boss? Even under these conditions, she emphasized her thanks toward Tang Rou for making such a difficult decision for the team.

How could there be a team like this, how could there be a player like this!

The reporters were completely resentful of Happy and Tang Rou, who didn't fit their expectations at all. When the winners of today's match, Tiny Herb, came out for their press conference, the reporters were still alight with an anger that couldn't immediately be extinguished.

They carelessly finished with their congratulations toward the winning party and immediately asked the Tiny Herb players for their thoughts on Happy's actions today.

"Oh?" Hearing that Tang Rou made such an announcement, the Tiny Herb players who attended this press conference, Wang Jiexi, Gao Yingjie, and Liu Xiaobie, found it very surprising.

But soon enough, Wang Jiexi nodded his head. "She would do something like that!" Wang Jiexi couldn't help but think of their time in the tenth server, when defeating Tang Rou was a matter of seconds for him. Even a beginner could tell the enormous disparity of skill that existed between them. But despite such a frightening disparity, Wang Jiexi could only defeat Tang Rou's character and not her fighting spirit. As Tang Rou became more clearly aware of this disparity, Wang Jiexi sensed only an increased excitement from her.

From then, Wang Jiexi knew what kind of person this was. And then later there was the Challenger League, when Tang Rou once again refused Tiny Herb's invitation, Wang Jiexi took another step in understanding how different Tang Rou was from the crowd.

Understanding how different she was from the crowd and then looking at the things these reporters were chattering about, even Wang Jiexi felt that they were laughable.

The reporters clearly felt that Tang Rou breaking her word like this and destroying her self-image would prevent her from continuing to exist in the Alliance, that she would have no more future.

"No powerhouse team would want a player with such a bad reputation ruining their image."

Wang Jiexi heard this sound, spoken with confidence.

It was true, these words are very reasonable. But the problem was, the "future" of which you speak is entirely different from the future in Tang Rou's eyes. This player, different from the rest, is absolutely not walking the normal, expected path of a pro player.

Powerhouse team?

This person had already rejected Tiny Herb twice now, a rejection with no hesitation or leeway. It was evident that Tiny Herb had nothing that attracted her. The so-called powerhouse team was nothing in her eyes.

These group of players that Ye Xiu found all had their quirks and defects, but they were all extremely reliable people! Thinking about this, Wang Jiexi discovered that he subconsciously admired them. But facing the reporters' questions, he sensibly evaded.

"Well, perhaps there's some reason she won't honor her commitment! I'm not too sure, so I can't very well say anything," Wang Jiexi said.

"Then what do you think about Fang Rui saying that he could take on eight of you?" One reporter also dragged this statement over.

To this, Wang Jiexi just smiled a little. "I look forward to our next battle."

To think that trash talk like this would provoke some reaction from Wang Jiexi, the reporters found that they were too naive. And from Wang Jiexi, they couldn't find any interesting topic to discuss. They could only turn their attacks to the other two from Tiny Herb. Tang Rou's actions once again became the focus of their questions.

"I'm pretty happy she didn't quit. I look forward to battling her again." Liu Xiaobie only looked at the result, not the process.

"No matter what, her courage and determination is worth learning," Gao Yingjie said.

Society's morals were degenerating day by day!

The reporters lamented. They couldn't even hear strong condemnation of Tang Rou from Tiny Herb's players?

Chapter 1197: Consequences

The storm caused by the 1v3 didn't pass after the end of the competition. It could be said that for the reporters, the real excitement was only just starting.

Several reporters, Ruan Cheng at the lead, were enraged to the core by Tang Rou's attitude, and they immediately began to write all sorts of articles condemning her. Esports Time, the publication for which Ruan Cheng wrote, was a bimonthly publication, so there was still a week before the next edition's release. He couldn't wait that long, and impatiently posted on his personal blog to begin a crusade against her, calling this whole thing a scandal and provoking a big reaction. The other major media outlets also reported on this matter, attacking from various angles.

But amidst all this, quite a few reporters gave understanding toward Tang Rou. Chang Xian, for example, clearly stood on Tang Rou's side, looking down upon Ruan Cheng and all those other reporters. But the problem was, the company he worked for, Esports Home, had strict requirements of its subordinate reporters. Articles from invited reporters could have the warning "this does not represent the views of this publication" attached, but articles from their own reporters faced constraints.

It wasn't that Esports Home couldn't have a position, but this time, Tang Rou's actions were extremely controversial. Destroying one's prior commitment like this was impossible to put in a good light. Up through now, Esports Home emphasized their impartiality in the circle, so for this situation, the conclusion of their discussion didn't express a clear position, and they played a bit for both sides. With this, Chang Xian's article expressing clear support for Happy and Tang Rou naturally wasn't suitable and was shot down by the editor-in-chief three times. Chang Xian was a passionate young person. After all this hassle, he was tempted to just quit this and not write, but then he thought, if he did that, then wouldn't the voices supporting Happy and Tang Rou become even weaker?

So Chang Xian dug through numerous articles written by his seniors, studying them to learn how to guide an opinion under these kind of circumstances so that when touching upon both sides at the conclusion, there would be a subtle leaning toward one side. These sort of games couldn't hide from the experienced editor-in-chief, but as long as it wasn't too obvious, a slight bias wasn't a big problem. After all, a robotic article with no position would appear to lack judgment and influence.

On one hand, Esports Home placed strict limitations on their own articles, but on the other hand, they used this topic to draw many eyes. Esports Home invited two pieces from outsiders, one was the article posted by Ruan Cheng to his personal blog, and for the other, they found the famed commentator Cha Xiaoxia.

Ruan Cheng's position was obvious. As for Cha Xiaoxia, that was someone who already publicly declared himself a Happy fanboy. This sort of commentator generally wouldn't be invited to write about a team of which he was a fan, but now Esports Home specifically invited him, undoubtedly to counter Ruan Cheng's position.

Cha Xiaoxia didn't disappoint. He was warm and understanding toward Tang Rou, while cold and mocking towards Ruan Cheng and his people.

There were all sorts of voices, but overall, the indisputable truth of breaking one's word generated mostly negative discussions of Tang Rou. Esports Home's Chang Xian tried to express a vague position, Cha Xiaoxia flew a clear banner in her support, and a few others expressed understanding of her actions, but in the end they couldn't gain the upper hand. In the end, even they had to admit that Tang Rou's behavior was improper in some areas. They could only express their understanding, but they couldn't describe her as completely faultless or justified.

Amidst the storm of criticism, real consequences quickly appeared. Various businesses who had taken an interest in Tang Rou all withdrew their intentions of making a deal. Even some sponsors who had already signed contracts with Happy expressed their extreme dissatisfaction with Tang Rou's speech, putting a heavy question mark on the potential of future cooperation. Happy… Because they were just entering the Alliance, not many sponsors would directly sign a long contract with them. The standard was a one-year contract, and then depending on their performance and results this year, they would make further plans. And now, this negative attention was not something that the sponsors liked.

And then, the Alliance paid attention to this storm as well, and with "improper words and actions" as their reason, they gave Happy and Tang Rou a fine. The Alliance was very sensitive about matters of image. After all, in the beginning, video games were called "electronic heroin." Even though public perception had greatly improved, the Alliance didn't dare let their guard down.

Even though all of this had been somewhat expected, the ferocity of it all surprised Chen Guo. Especially the fine from the Alliance, it was like adding oil to the fire, making the condemning voices grow even louder.

What a pain!

Chen Guo was in low spirits. But when she arrived at the training room, she saw Ye Xiu and Wei Chen sitting in front of a computer in serious discussion.

That's good, they haven't been affected by this. Chen Guo was glad, and her admiration of the mental strength of these old veterans increased. With their fearless attitude toward attacks, the spirits of the others will stabilize quickly. A team really needed this sort of guiding compass presence!

As she thought this, Chen Guo walked over toward them to listen to what they were discussing.

"Tsk tsk tsk, these dumbasses, do they not do any background research before writing this stuff?" Wei Chen was saying.

"That sort of info probably isn't publicly available! More importantly, they don't have that sort of imagination!" Ye Xiu lamented.

"Well, that's true… Hey this… This one's pretty harsh," said Wei Chen.

"That's what I call poison!" Ye Xiu said.

"They really don't know how to spell death!"

"Forget the small shrimp, but the bigger fish are definitely done for," Ye Xiu said.

"The first one to be taken care of will definitely be Ruan Cheng," Wei Chen said confidently.

"He's really doing this diligently," said Ye Xiu.

"He'll probably lose his job immediately?"

"Who knows!"

.

"Think he'll be directly killed?" Wei Chen said.

"That's probably an exaggeration!" said Ye Xiu. "We're talking about a proper businessman here."

"But this is his own daughter! For her to be attacked like this, even killing wouldn't be enough to resolve the hate."

"I think it'd probably just be…"

"Ahem!!!" Chen Guo loudly coughed, angrily interrupting this shameless discussion. And here she was thinking that they were discussing some serious topic, only to find that they were just dreaming about what kind of powerful retaliation Tang Rou's background could help her execute.

"Boss is here?" Wei Chen turned his head and casually greeted her before going back to cheerfully look at those articles and discussions about Tang Rou.

"I came to see what you two were busy with over here!" Chen Guo said.

"Oh, Little Tang's really being attacked! How do you think her old man will help teach these guys a lesson?" Wei Chen actually tried to drag Chen Guo into the discussion as well.

"Shame on you! Little Tang already said that she was taking this upon herself, when has she ever used her background to get something?" Chen Guo said.

"You can't put it like that. We all know Little Tang's domineering attitude, but this must be taking a toll on her dad's heart! He has to take care of a few of them as a warning, don't you think?" Wei Chen said, particularly confident.

With that, Chen Guo couldn't find any rebuttal. She could only believe that Tang Rou absolutely would not turn back and beg her family to save her, but like Wei Chen said, even if Tang Rou didn't need it, the Tang family might act anyway.

Just as she was hesitating, the door behind her opened and Tang Rou walked in, talking to someone on the phone.

"Yes, I'm fine, don't worry about me, just leave it!"

She hung up the phone, and the other three in the room looked at each other. This phone call sounded like it was from Tang Rou's family, and was probably about this situation. What was the Tang family going to do?

Looking at the three people who were in a daze, Tang Rou waved her phone. "My dad's also worried about this!"

"What'd the old man say?" Wei Chen asked, filled with respect. "Bankrupt Esports Time first?"

"The new edition of Esports Time hasn't even come out yet!" Ye Xiu said.

"Even if you can't chase the monk, you still have to tear down the monastery," said Wei Chen.

"What nonsense is this!" Chen Guo said.

Just as she said this, her cell phone rang. Chen Guo answered, still with a hint of anger in her voice. "Yes?!"

"Is this Boss Chen?" A male voice spoke on the other end.

"Yes, who's this?" Chen Guo checked the phone number on the screen, but it was an unknown number.

"This is Tang Shusen," the other person said.

"Hm?" Chen Guo quickly thought about this name, it seemed a bit familiar!

"I apologize for the trouble Tang Rou has caused you. My daughter's personality is just like that, very strong!" the caller said.

OH!

Chen Guo's heart skipped a beat. Only now did she react to who this was, and she immediately answered, "Mr. Tang, sir, please don't talk like that, we…"

"Ahhhh!" Tang Rou evidently figured out who the caller was from Chen Guo's words and attitude, and she rushed forward and snatched away Chen Guo's phone.

"Dad, what are you doing!" Tang Rou said loudly, her face revealing an extremely rare expression of embarrassment.

They couldn't hear what the caller said, but Tang Rou answered, flustered, "I know, I'll take care of it myself. You go to your meeting!"

"Yes, alright."

"How many times have I said it, my class is called Battle Mage, Battle Mage! Battle God is a title, it's referring to one especially powerful character in this class."

"Yes yes, the player controlling it is more important, you're right."

"Yes, he's in our team now."

"Yes, the unspecialized Lord Grim. You know a lot about this!"

"Talk about what! You guys don't speak the same language." Tang Rou shouted.

Ye Xiu and the other two looked at each other. Listening to that, it seemed that Tang Rou's father had researched Glory, and even wanted to talk for a bit with God Ye Xiu?

"Dad, please stop making such a fuss, if you can't beat Frost Forest then let Secretary Wang find you a guide."

Sweat! The three others wiped at their sweat. This level of skill was really a bit low.

"I can beat it!"

"I can't carry you! You're in the eleventh server. Even if my character returned to the normal server, I can only go to the tenth server, so we wouldn't be together."

"No no, don't come over, if I have time I'll make a character over there and find you, okay! We need to start practice, I'm hanging up now."

"Yes yes, see you!" Tang Rou finally hung up the phone. She let out a long breath, and then looked at the other three, embarrassment still showing on her face.

"Uh… He recently also got a Glory account, and he plays it sometimes in his spare time," Tang Rou explained helplessly.

"I could hear." Ye Xiu nodded.

"What's his account name? I can give Wu Chen a heads up, take care of him a bit?" Chen Guo tried to be serious.

"If he wants to be an experience baby, then just leave him to me!" Wei Chen said with all the air of someone trying to curry favor.

"Can we please just start practice?" Tang Rou was almost crying.

Chapter 1198: The Observation Period Ends

The discussion about Tang Rou continued to be omnipresent, but in the end there was no mysterious power that intervened and stopped all of it. Her father gave her true non-interfering support and freedom. Even when something like this happened, he didn't instantly stand up to protect her.

Tang Rou, facing all of this expected criticism, didn't defend herself. She didn't expect or hope for any understanding. She withdrew and just dove even further into Glory.

Compared to Tang Rou, Happy's current situation didn't look too good,either. The criticism the team received was secondary; more important was Happy's score on the points ranking after eight rounds.

There were 38 rounds in a season, eight rounds meant that over one-fifth had passed. Happy currently had 31 points, ranked at 14th place.

For a new team that just joined the Alliance, a score like this perhaps wasn't bad. Team Miracle, who had also just joined this season, only had 21 points and was ranked 18th. Last year's new team Heavenly Swords only had 25 points, two places behind Happy.

But Happy wouldn't be satisfied with this kind of point score or ranking because only they knew that their goal to win the championships in their first year absolutely was not just a shameless piece of trash talk.

If they wanted to win the championships, they first had to ensure they made it to the playoffs.

And right now, Happy had 31 points after 8 rounds, average 3.875 points per round.

"Let's look at last season's final point rankings." During Happy's team meeting, Ye Xiu analyzed the current situation in the League for everyone.

"Last season, in eighth place was Hundred Blossoms, with a final score of 190 points, averaging 5 points per round. But last season, because of the game update, many teams' scores went down. If we look at Season 8, Team 301 Degrees in eighth place had 214 points, averaging 5.63 per round. And then looking at our season now, after eight rounds, the seventh and eighth place Tyranny and Hundred Blossoms each have 47 points, which is an average 5.875 points per match. Compared to previous seasons, the situation in the Alliance this season appears to be harsher.

"If we use the current scores after 8 rounds as the standard, a match average of 5.875 means 223 points after 38 rounds. This could very well be the threshold for entering playoffs this season. Right now, we only have 31 points. Subtracting 31 from 223, in the next 30 rounds, we'll need an average of 6.41 points per round to reach that threshold.

"The situation is grim! 6.41 points isn't very easy to get. As soon as we lose a team competition, that means there's no way to get 6.41 points for that round. What then? That means we'll have to make it up through other rounds. So, our goal for each round absolutely should not just be 6.41 points, we need 7, 8, or even more points, in order to guarantee that we raise our score.

"The end of eight rounds marks a line. From the statistics of previous seasons, we can see that in the beginning rounds of a season, most of the teams prioritize remaining cautious, observing each other, learning more about the situation, and testing each other. There aren't too many unexpected surprises in battle. But after around the eighth or tenth round, they're done sounding each other out, so the teams begin to individually target specific areas to work hard, and that's when the real chaotic fighting begins. The Rookie Block, powerhouse teams capsizing in the gutter, many players' conditions inexplicably decreasing, in reality, these aren't without cause. It's because after the early period of observation, all of the teams start putting real effort in. Whoever plays their moves better will have the last laugh. If competition only compared aces and God-level characters, then wouldn't the champions be decided as soon as the team rosters were revealed for the season?

"Let's work hard, and welcome the chaotic fighting to come! We will be the ones laughing until the end!"

After the situation was analyzed and understood, they began discussing their battle plans for their opponent in the next round.

In the ninth round, Happy would be playing an away game against the other team that had debuted this year, Team Miracle.

The end of eight rounds meant that Miracle had already played eight matches. And in these matches, what kind of of impression did they leave on their opponents? Ye Xiu began to take them apart in his analysis.

Glory Pro Alliance Season 10 Round 9 was on the evening of November 1st, and this day was also the release date of the new edition of the bimonthly Esports Time. Esports Time's position and opinions were expressed much more clearly than Esports Home's were. It was relying on this kind of style that they managed to claim their spot of territory in the area of esports media reporting. And Ruan Cheng, as a head writer for Esports Time, took thorough advantage of the resources at his disposal. The big topic for this edition of Esports Time was exposing Tang Rou's conduct.

Ruan Cheng named this incident the biggest scandal in Glory history and described it in all sorts of flamboyant, unrestrained language. Many of her performances in the eight rounds to date were carved as proof that she was human scum.

An angelic appearance, a dirty heart…

Ruan Cheng's words were extreme. After Chen Guo received this edition, she swiftly destroyed it. It brought down spirits too much, and besides, they still had a match tonight. And although Ruan Cheng thoroughly attacked Tang Rou, he didn't discover her family situation, which almost made Chen Guo anticipate the Tang family standing up and giving Ruan Cheng a scare. This guy was just too despicable.

That night, the match was held at Team Miracle's home stadium in City M. This team that purchased its players for only 5000 yuan didn't appear to be a particularly wealthy team. Like Happy's, they rented their home stadium. City M wasn't home to any other Glory teams, so this stadium naturally didn't originally have the specialized holographic Glory projection technology. However, the amount of resources a team possessed was an important criterion considered by the Alliance when approving a new team to join. Teams that applied didn't get the same financial support from the Alliance that teams like Happy that won the Challenger League did. But Miracle was able to successfully pass the checks and enter the Alliance, which then led people to believe that this team wasn't particularly short on money.

The projection technology in Miracle's home stadium was impressive. At this time, before the match began, the host was accompanying the projection to introduce the players and characters of two teams.

After eight rounds, many teams found a strong sense of deja vu in Miracle's roster: Excellent Era!

Of course, this wasn't just because they had three players from Excellent Era, but also because of the class composition of this team.

Aside from the Elementalist, the Striker, and the Sharpshooter, who were the former Excellent Era players, the first-string players of this team were a Battle Mage, a Launcher, a Spellblade, and a Cleric.

This was entirely the same as the roster of the old Excellent Era. What was different was that old Excellent Era had Battle Mage, Launcher, and Spellblade as their core, while the current Miracle had these three classes as the orbiting moons, and the transferred players from Excellent Era, He Ming, Shen Jian, and Wang Ze became the central axes.

Among them, He Ming became Miracle's captain. This former sixth player in Excellent Era probably never would have thought that he'd have the chance to lead a team himself. But Team Miracle? To be honest, leading a team like this, He Ming didn't feel particularly well-off. Meeting Shen Jian and Wang Ze here was a sort of consolation, a reassurance that at least he wasn't the only person to be met with such misfortune.

At Excellent Era, these three had just been teammates, but after they all fell and landed here, their relationship became much closer. These three would group together to wallow in their misfortune together, sometimes talking about the good old days they spent in the powerhouse that was Excellent Era. As of now, their other former teammates had all scattered. These three admired Liu Hao and Guo Yang, who had managed to enter Wind Howl and now had a certain position in that team. Especially Liu Hao, who had now become part of their main roster, and had performed quite well in the past eight rounds. Wind Howl, who had managed to obtain him through a free transfer, all felt that they got a great deal from this.

Aside from this, the Cleric player Zhang Jiaxing had gone with Xiao Shiqin to Thunderclap and was also doing very well there. This season, Thunderclap was playing more and more smoothly. They were actually ranked second on the current leaderboard with 61 points, losing only to Samsara and were earning lots of attention.

As for Sun Xiang, that genius-level being, He Ming and the others didn't bother to envy his fortune at Team Samsara. Looking around, it seems that the three of them had drawn the shortest straw.

The three were all depressed about landing in Miracle, but they didn't dare neglect this team. In this weak team, if they were careless and became relegated, then their futures would become even more awkward and uncertain. And so, these three players worked quite hard in Miracle. Right now, they were in 18th place with 21 points, with a solid lead above Bright Green and Seaside. They even beat Void in an away game 7 to 3, one of the rare upsets in the first eight rounds.

And this round, their opponent, Happy…

He Ming, Shen Jian, and Wang Ze had complicated mixed feelings toward Happy. Things were a bit simpler for He Ming, as he had already left Excellent Era during the season that the team was relegated, and he hadn't experienced the sweeping pain when Excellent Era fell to Happy in the Challenger League. Looking at Happy, the only complicated feelings were toward his former captain Ye Xiu and former teammate Su Mucheng. As for Shen Jian and Wang Ze, who had experienced the Challenger League, Happy could be said to be the chief culprit of their current miserable situation. If there had been no Happy, then perhaps Excellent Era would currently be a big player, lifting high its three All-Stars and shining brightly in the playoff tier.

"We cannot lose this match!" October 27th, during a small meeting between the three of them five days before their match, Shen Jian declared.

But He Ming and Wang Ze didn't say anything. That person in Happy's roster was a shadow upon them.

"That… won't be too easy…" Wang Ze hesitated for a moment, but said it. In the current leaderboard, Happy had a lead of ten points above them. Pro players wouldn't feel that a match outcome was decided because of a point difference. For Wang Ze, the scary thing was still that person. In front of that person, he felt that he had no way of relaxing his hands and feet, that any of his movements would be thoroughly scrutinized and seen through.

"Right now, they're bruised and battered. It's a perfect chance for us to earn points," Shen Jian said.

He Ming and Wang Ze froze, and then suddenly understood.

That's right! That Tang Rou in Happy had really stirred up a lot of trouble this time. If she'd been in the old Excellent Era, she probably would have already been kicked out, and even if not, she'd be buried and hidden. Happy was currently in a rough time, and these waves wouldn't calm down again so quickly. November 1st was the ninth round and also the release date of the new edition of Esports Time. There would definitely be articles about this.

Let them see the articles during the day, then battle them at night. This rhythm was quite excellent!

Chapter 1199: Team Miracle’s Sacrificial Pawn

Team Miracle's home stadium.

After the two teams were introduced, the players on both sides entered the venue and met in the center of the stage, shaking each other's hands and greeting each other warmly. It looked as if their relationship was friendly and joyous.

He Ming was Team Miracle's captain. He gave a most amicable greeting towards his former captain Ye Xiu, particularly showing his concern for the recent 1v3 controversy.

"That guy Ruan Cheng is too outrageous!" He Ming said indignantly. "He's talking nonsense again in today's issue of the Esports Time. He really is unbearable. Did you guys see it? If you guys haven't, I have one here. It's truly infuriating."

He Ming held a copy of today's issue of the Esports Time and promptly took it out with who knew what motives. He directly opened the conversation with an article about Happy, asking in a concerned manner about Ye Xiu and the rest of Happy's opinions.

Ye Xiu didn't brush away his good intentions. Even though he had already seen the article, he still took it.

"Is one copy good enough? I've got more, if you guys need more!" He Ming said. The members of Team Miracle seemed to have all conjured up a copy in their hands.

"Team Miracle really likes to read! What a good practice," Ye Xiu said.

"You're too kind," He Ming said modestly.

"Just one copy is enough. You guys can keep the rest!" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Hey! There's no need to be polite between us! Take them take them." He Ming signaled Team Miracle's players to hand over their copies of the Esports Time to everyone in Happy. After handing the copies over, they didn't give Happy an opportunity to refuse. He Ming led Team Miracle down from the stage, while waving towards Ye Xiu. "See you in the match."

"See you in the match…" Ye Xiu waved his hand and then led Team Happy back to their seats.

On Miracle's side, the group was stealthily glancing towards Happy's side.　　

"They're reading it! They're reading it!"" someone yelled out excitedly. Quite a few people from Happy were taking a look at the Esports Time paper that they had shoved into their hands.

　

"Hehe…" He Ming, Shen Jian, and Wang Ze looked at each other and chuckled as if they had won.　

The official match soon started. The first competition would be the individual competition. The players to be sent out by the two teams appeared on the large screens in the stadium.

Happy would be sending out Wei Chen, Warlock Windward Formation.

The three bros in Team Miracle whispering in each other's ears suddenly froze. Hadn't Ye Xiu always gone up first? Why'd they change it up today? Their Team Miracle had sent up their Spellblade Xiang Yuanwei. Of their six players in the individual rounds, he was their weakest. Team Miracle's plan had been employing the principle of Tian Ji's Horse Race, throwing their weakest to face Ye Xiu. How could they have known the other side would suddenly switch up the order?

Wei Chen?

This player could be considered an elderly person in the competitive scene. He had appeared an extremely limited number of times this season. Why was he sent out against their Team Miracle? Was this contempt?　　

He Ming and his two bros were furious. After all, they had once been part of a powerhouse. Even though they had fallen, they weren't about to let others stomp on them as they pleased.

"Yuanwei!" He Ming called out to Yuanwei, "Play fast! Fight fiercely!"　　

"Okay," Xiang Yuanwei nodded his head. He had originally been their throwaway piece. As the time drew near, he stepped onto the stage.

He Ming and the others had been planning on giving up this fight, so they hadn't put a lot of thought into it. They just listened to whatever Xiang Yuanwei wanted for a map and didn't object to it.

The map was Sky Garden.

The terrain wasn't complicated, but it was an exceptionally beautiful map. Spellblades had a lot of flashy moves, so they would sometimes reap surprising results from this map. Xiang Yuanwei didn't seem to have given up despite being a throwaway piece. He still put in quite some thought into choosing a map.

The match began. The two characters moved towards the center from their starting corners.

Xiang Yuanwei listened to his captain's advice. He didn't play any fancy tricks and quickly went forward to take the initiative. As for Wei Chen, he pretended to charge forward wildly for a short distance, then amidst the crowd's boos, he shamelessly hid inside a thicket of flowers. But it seemed that he still felt like it wasn't enough cover, so he had his character lie flat on his stomach. The large screen cut to Windward Formation's viewpoint. He was carefully looking around from the cracks between the flowers like an evil ghost.

The boos from the crowd intensified.

　

Team Miracle wasn't very popular, but they still had fans. In these moments, they obviously had to give their support to the home team. Wei Chen's despicable ambush was immediately condemned by them. Everyone hated how the referee didn't just directly red card the guy away for such dirtiness. Happy had previous history for this! The crowd impatiently hoped to see this scene again.

Happy had a previous offense before, so the referee really was paying close attention to them, his demands more strict. The referee saw Wei Chen setting up an ambush and subconsciously started checking the time.

Xiang Yuanwei's Spellblade rushed forward, but the thicket of flowers chosen by Wei Chen was too thick. Xiang Yuanwei rotated his Spellblade Halis's viewpoint left and right, passing over Windward Formation's hiding spot several times, but he failed to notice him. The crowd was feeling even more anxious than the player.

1v1 maps weren't very big. Sky Garden didn't have complicated terrain. Since he couldn't find his target, he had Halis raise his sword in the air.

Fire Wave Sword!

A wave of raging flames rolled forth, leaving scorch marks everywhere in its path. The frail flowers and grass were instantly burned by the Fire Wave Sword and turned into ash.

After this sword came another.　

Earthquake Sword!　　

The magic waves from the sword intent raised up the earth, uprooting the grass and flowers, lifting them up and then pressing down. Even though it wasn't as clean as Fire Wave Sword, it would still be obvious if anyone was hiding there.

But Windward Formation was still nowhere to be found.

Halis turned around and pointed the tip of his sword in a different direction.

Xiang Yuanwei wasn't throwing around his skills randomly. His wave swords always aimed at areas lush with flowers and grass, letting him cover a wide range of possible hiding locations. Just from these two wave swords, it could be seen that this player was quite familiar with this map.

The third wave sword was aimed directly at Windward Formation's hiding spot.

Ice Wave Formation!

A wave of ice surged forth, freezing any plant it touched. The next wave of ice shattered these frozen plants, sprinkling ice crystals onto the ground.

Windward Formation still isn't going to move?

Everyone looked towards Wei Chen's Warlock. Sure enough, this time, he could not sit at ease any longer. Windward Formation scrambled to dodge, rolling backwards in an extremely ugly manner.

Ice Wave Sword had a limited range. With this backwards roll, he was able to escape from the wave sword's range while also staying hidden.

Too crafty!

Everyone thought to themselves. However, Xiang Yuanwei wasn't just using these wave swords to scout out the area. Whenever he released a wave sword, his viewpoint spun quickly, observing the movements of the grass and wind at every location. The moment his Ice Wave Sword came out, Xiang Yuanwei noticed a rustle from the flower thicket at the end of the ice wave.

Xiang Yuanwei was the weakest in Team Miracle. In the past eight rounds, he had only appeared once in the team competition. However, just because he was weak didn't mean he didn't work hard. Even if he was just a sacrificial pawn, he would still try his best, choosing his best map. It didn't matter who his opponent was. He would strive to win.

Seeing a rustle from the thicket of flowers, Xiang Yuanwei didn't wait for Ice Wave Sword to finish and immediately moved towards in that direction.

Electric Wave Formation!

After Windward Formation rolled out of the way of Ice Wave Sword, he just happened to be within the formation's range. The ball of electricity shot out lightning, automatically chasing after Windward Formation, who was still hiding in a bush. The lightning shot through his body, the flash sweeping away the surrounding flowers. Windward Formation, who had been lying in ambush, was completely revealed. He cut a sorry figure, pressed onto the ground by the lightning. The crowd instantly erupted into cheers and laughter.

Too awesome!

Seeing someone so shameless in such a sorry state was too satisfying!　

The crowd's emotions reached a high point, but Xiang Yuanwei wasn't happy just because of this. He wanted to win, and it was still too early to tell. It was just an Electric Wave Formation, not a serious blow.

What was important was that he had finally located his opponent's position. Xiang Yuanwei had Halis rush forward, brandishing the shortsword in his hand.

Storm Wave Sword!

　　

This wave sword was the fastest among all wave swords. A powerful whirlwind roared out from Halis's sword, ripping apart any plants in its path. By the time these shredded plants drifted down, who knew how far away the Storm Wave Sword's sword intent would be at.

Trapped by the Electric Wave Formation, Windward Formation was unable to dodge this extremely fast attack. The Storm Wave Sword didn't seem to be striking him; it just looked as if it flitted by him like the wind. But immediately afterwards, numerous thin arrows of blood shot out from Windward Formation's body.

After these two skills, Halis was finally in position. Spellblades kiting around the target at the farthest range possible wasn't a good choice because the speed of wave swords wasn't very fast. If they were too far away, the opponent could easily dodge it. Thus, compared to their skill's attack range, Spellblades needed to fight at a slightly closer range. As for exactly how much closer, that depended on the player's hand speed and fighting style.

Xiang Yuanwei's most comfortable and favorite distance was at two-thirds of his wave swords' range. At this moment, his Halis had finally reached this position.

Earthquake Sword!

This low-level skill had a short cooldown, allowing him to use it once again. At a distance of two-thirds, dodging this attack would require faster reaction speed and hand speed, and these just happened to be what old generals lacked.　　

"He's playing well!!" Down from the stage, Team Miracle's unfortunate three were grouped together in a very good mood. Even though Xiang Yuanwei was their sacrificial pawn, it didn't mean they had no hopes for him. Seeing that he was playing well, these three saw this lower skilled player in a new light.

"Sending such an old guy onto the stage, what is Ye Xiu thinking!" Shen Jian sighed.

"Probably to stabilize the situation? Old generals are better at dealing with pressure, after all!" He Ming had been thinking about the meaning behind Wei Chen being sent out the entire time.

"But in the end, he's going to lose?" Shen Jian laughed.　

"Our Team Miracle isn't that easy to bully!" He Ming was quite excited. When things were going well, he was very willing to be in character, viewing himself as a glorious member of Team Miracle.

But at this moment, the situation suddenly changed.

Xiang Yuanwei had just gotten into his favorite distance and was about to have Halis continue his onslaught, when he was suddenly engulfed by a plume of purple fire.

Warlock skill: Shadow Flames!

Chapter 1200: Death’s Door Opens Wide

Shadow Flames dealt primarily dark element damage, with supporting fire element damage. However, no one would focus on the damage for Warlock skills. The control skills, and status effects inflicted by Warlocks were the most uncomfortable to deal with.

Shadow Flames was no different. Apart from the first wave of health this skill seared off, it would inflict a six second long Flames effect, a damaging status that did damage every two seconds. This status damage also interrupted chants. The Wave Swords of Spellblades were instant, but Wave Formations were chanted. With Shadow Flames, a Spellblade's rhythm would be heavily disrupted.

But when was this Shadow Flame unleashed?

Everyone was so focused on Halis' Wave Swords and Wave Formations that no one ever noticed.

Xiang Yuanwei was also shocked, suddenly afraid of being too reckless. But if he didn't charge, Wei Chen wouldn't let this chance go. An explosion of Curse Arrows shot out from the flower bush, clearly having been charged for a long time.

Shadow Flame didn't affect the character's movement, so Xiang Yuanwei hurriedly had Halis dodge, hoping to throw his own attack back as he did, but that was when he realized that, out of all the instant cast Wave Swords, only Waltzing Wave Sword was available.

Waltzing Wave Sword, as the name implied, didn't strike in a straight line. In a team competition, it could often create unexpected effects, but right now it was a 1v1 fight with just a single target. No matter what arc the attack made, the destination was the same. Apart from being able to use it to ambush others in specific situations, Waltzing Wave Sword would just be giving the opponent ample time to dodge when fighting face to face.

However, apart from this Sword, the other Wave Sword skills were all in cooldown.

Xiang Yuanwei immediately realized that he had most likely fell into a rather terrifying trap. His Wave Sword skills were almost all on cooldown, and his Wave Formations were under restriction from Shadow Flames. These six seconds were purposefully created by his opponent, so how could the other let him go so easily?

Even as he struggled with himself for this split second, Waltzing Wave Sword was still sent out. With the attack, flowers and grass flew everywhere, and it left a clear arc across the ground. If you couldn't dodge that, then you really didn't have any right to stand on this stage. Xiang Yuanwei really had no choice. He didn't have the time to adjust himself, so he could only strike back like that to give his opponent a little pressure, even if it was miniscule.

And then, retreat...

Xiang Yuanwei hurriedly had Halis back away, wanting to get some distance. He knew that danger could come from anywhere around him. His opponent didn't just hide his character, but used such a simple action to lure him into action and strategically beat him down.

Sly old fox!

Xiang Yuanwei commented on Wei Chen as he had his character escape. Speaking of which, he had thought that his opponent would be Ye Xiu and his head was filled with the strange ever-changing style of the Unspecialized! Yet he had ended up meeting a Warlock, and an endlessly shameless Warlock, too.

Halis was continuously moving backwards and Xiang Yuanwei didn't dare have his character turn. He still had to keep an eye on what this shameless Warlock would do to try and disrupt him. Yet, what was most surprising, was that the other didn't do anything. The flora was completely silent, as if Windward Formation had suddenly disappeared.

What was this about?

After jumping back twice again, Xiang Yuanwei had Halis stop his retreat, confused.

The audience wanted to cry.

Xiang Yuanwei couldn't see what Windward Formation was doing in the bushes, but they could! Windward Formation, this shameless Warlock, was currently flat on the ground, charging up a spell. Players familiar with with Warlock class immediately recognized the endlessly gathering energy. Death's Door, this was the Warlock's level 70 ultimate, Death's Door!

Using the cover from the terrain as well as a psychological understanding of his opponent, Wei Chen fearlessly and directly started chanting a time and mana consuming skill, Death's Door.

"Attack already!!!"

Many members of the audience was already shouting desperately, even the members of Miracle, Xiang Yuanwei's teammates, had stood up, fists clenched.

However, Xiang Yuanwei had his Halis carefully, cautiously observe his surroundings as he inched forwards towards the bushes Windward Formation was hiding in, sword raised.

Caution was good, but caution at a time like this just made the audience so desperate they wanted to curse.

It was only until the bushes Windward Formation was hiding in were no longer sufficient to cover up the miasma gathering at the tip of Death's Hand that Xiang Yuanwei realized something was wrong. If he still didn't know what this was by then, then he couldn't be called a pro player at all.

Run?

Too late!

Death's Door had a very wide area of effect, in addition, Windward Formation was a Warlock with a terrifying attack range. This Death's Door wouldn't give him any chance to run.

He'd have to go for it!

Xiang Yuanwei was quick at coming to a decision. If he couldn't run, then he would advance and find a way to interrupt the skill. Death's Door was a skill that had to be maintained even after being activated. They could be interrupted any time from when they began chanting to the end of the skill.

GO!!!

The audience roared as one. They all felt that at this distance, with the Spellblade's attack range, there really wasn't anything to be afraid of.

Xiang Yuanwei thought the same.

Halis charged forwards, magic pulsing around his blade.

Attack!

The short sword swung out!

Boom!

A thunderous noise that seemed to pierce dimensions boomed.

A black, spinning door that led to another world rotated slowly, set up directly in front of Halis.

Holy crap!!

Countless audience members fell out of their seats.

This Death's Door was actually placed between the two.

This way, if Xiang Yuanwei had realized what was happening and turned to run like a noob, then he might really be able to run out of Death's Door's range.

However, he was a pro player, and his experience told him that running was impossible, so he tried to close in to interrupt and ran directly into the door of death.

The Death's Door was probably delighted and surprised. It probably never had such easy prey before in its life. Its miasma tentacles barely stretched out of the door and were already at Halis' shoulders.

Xiang Yuanwei didn't even have the time to attempt a dodge before he was caught by the tentacles of miasma. Then, he was easily pulled into the door.

Death's Door came quickly and left quickly, too. In a 1v1, Death's Door was primarily focused on damage. As for its control abilities, Warlocks had to continuously maintain Death's Door so even if they trapped their target, they couldn't send out other attacks.

However, Death's Door's attack, coming from another, demonic dimension, wasn't anything easy to deal with. Apart from the damage, the target would be thrown about and disoriented.

Chaotic Rain, Hexagram Prison, Grasping Phantoms...

Wei Chen very calmly, with a not all that fast hand speed, sent out the skills he had long since prepared one by one.

Halis was inflicted with countless negative status effects. He was sometimes confused, sometimes bound, sometimes controlled, sometimes imprisoned...

Wei Chen had a very good rhythm to his attacks. If a veteran like him couldn't even control his own rhythm, then there was no point in him continuing to fight on the pro scene. No matter how experienced, he wouldn't be able to utilize it.

Xiang Yuanwei refused to give up, but his struggles never managed to turn the tides. Halis still fell in the end.

Wei Chen won and Xiang Yuanwei left the stage, depressed.

His heart was filled with what ifs. If he did this… if he only did that...

However, there were no ifs in competition. These ifs could all be turned into experience and help the player grow.

Wei Chen was naturally delighted when he came back. He took the boos from the audience as cheers, walking as if he was ten years younger.

"What other result could you expect with me at the helm?" After returning to the bench, he accepted everyone's praises and complemented himself without any semblance of modesty.

"Amazing!" Ye Xiu didn't even send him one word of mockery.

"What's up today? How come you're being so nice to each other?" Chen Guo was surprised. It was downright unnatural that Ye Xiu and Wei Chen didn't mock each other.

"Hahaha…" Ye Xiu chucked, but didn't explain.

Hearing these praises, Wei Chen took his fill of boasting and, when he had enough, he shook his head. "I'm going to go to the bathroom."

"Hm?"

Gazing at his retreating form, everyone was stunned. Something like that was something everyone should've dealt with before the match! Only one individual battle had gone by, it hadn't been long.

"He… didn't win as easily as it might seem," Ye Xiu suddenly said.

"Ah?" Chen Guo was confused.

"He didn't say a single taunt for the entire match," Ye Xiu sighed.

Chen Guo continued to be stunned. Gazing at Wei Chen's retreating figure, Chen Guo felt as though she saw a well-hidden exhaustion in his form, despite the arrogance he had came off stage with.

As for over here...

"I'm going up, then!" Su Mucheng stood. She was the second player to go up on Happy's side.

"Good luck," everyone said.

"It's Su Mucheng." Over at Miracle, the unlucky three looked to their former teammate's name, flashing across the screen, and then saw Su Mucheng walk towards the stage.

"Leave it to me." Wang Ze seemed very confident. He had been arranged in the individual competition and had hoped to be set against Su Mucheng.

"Good luck, the time to prove yourself has come!" He Ming said to Wang Ze.

When Wang Ze was in Excellent Era, he couldn't count as a core player. Pros in his position all had the desire to prove themselves.

However, Excellent Era was no longer here, and he didn't have to fight for his position in the team anymore. Instead, he had to prove himself to the entire pro circle. The All-Star level ex-teammate of his, Su Mucheng, was the best opponent he could ask for.

It was because this sort of clash gave people something to talk about and was very eye-catching.

"I have an ace up my sleeve!" Wang Ze went up, full of confidence.

Chapter 1201: An Ace That Isn’t Cool at All

Wang Ze hadn't been a senior player during his time at Excellent Era. When Ye Xiu was still there, he had been a rookie, appearing a few times as a sub starting season 8, before following Excellent Era to relegations.

Team Excellent Era's players were rather sought after, but at that time, the relegated Excellent Era hadn't given up yet. Drawing in Thunderclap's Xiao Shiqin steadied their hearts, and as a result, the vast majority of Team Excellent Era's players chose to stay.

Wang Ze was one of them. However, unlike his other teammates who had the choice to accept an invite or stay with the team, he had no choices because no one had showed any interest in him.

To Wang Ze, this was a slap to his face. Even though he didn't feel like he was particularly amazing, he still had confidence in his own skill, yet no one was interested in him?

Wang Ze cared quite a lot about this issue. At that time, he had been in the competitive scene for two years, but he failed to attract enough attention in his few appearances on stage. He very much wanted to be acknowledged.

But in the third season of his professional career, what made him even more depressed was that the powerhouse Excellent Era had actually lost to the Internet cafe team Happy in the Challenger League.

That moment had been a dark one for everyone in Team Excellent Era. After Excellent Era disbanded and the team members parted ways, Wang Ze had been quite terrified because he hadn't received any invites when Excellent Era had been relegated the previous season. And in their last season, Excellent Era had been playing in the Challenger League. The attention towards them had been limited, and he had truly feared that no one would be interested in him.

Wang Ze had hoped for an invite, but none came. He had watched as his teammates left him one after the other, watched as Excellent Era collapsed, and watched as someone took over.

At that time, the players who had yet to leave all received invites from the new boss, who called for them to hang on for one more year and return to the Pro League anew.

Wang Ze remembered clearly that Qiu Fei, who had just been promoted from the training camp, decisively chose to stay.

Idiot...

Wang Ze had thought to himself. That season, if there was one person who was particularly eye-catching in Excellent Era, it would be the new rookie Qiu Fei. He was a youth with a bright future ahead of him. He didn't need to worry that he would have nowhere to go. However, Qiu Fei had actually believed in the new investor's plans and chose to stay.

But what did the new Excellent Era have?　　

Su Mucheng had left along with her Dancing Rain. Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf had left. Xiao Shiqin and Life Extinguisher had returned to their mother team.

The remaining Excellent Era was no longer a powerhouse. How could breezing through the Challenger League be so easy?

Wang Ze had already wasted a year. He had no intentions of wasting away in the Challenger League. Unfortunately, he still hadn't received any invites. Staying was at least one path that would let him continue as a pro player.

Wang Ze wasn't willing, but he also didn't want to resort to this last straw. Luckily, Team Miracle came around and showed interest in him. Wang Ze didn't hesitate to pick his new team. In his eyes, being able to remain in the Pro League was better than anything else.

Thus, Wang Ze joined Team Miracle. Afterwards, Shen Jian joined too, cursing and swearing after wandering around in a circle. Shen Jian's situation had been better than his. He had received invites from the start, but he wasn't able to negotiate well enough with any of them, leaving Team Miracle as his only choice left. Along with feelings of helplessness for not getting recognized for his talents, he and Wang Ze were packaged together and sent to Team Miracle. Over there, He Ming was waiting for them with his status as the core player, after being traded away for Xiao Shiqin when Excellent Era relegated and fighting in the Pro League for a year.

　

The three were former teammates, who had gathered together again at Team Miracle. No one had been delighted at that. Instead, a feeling of being cheated had sprung up in their hearts.

But they had already fallen into the hole. If they wanted to get out, they'd have to rely upon themselves. Each carrying their own thoughts and hopes, the three began their journey with Team Miracle. Wang Ze hoped that he would be able to get recognition for his skill this season. Even if Team Miracle was relegated in the end, he would at least have invites waiting for him.

　

His opponent this round was Su Mucheng, an All-Star. If he could beat her, it would be definitive proof of his skill. And towards this former teammate of his, he felt like he knew the key to winning.

　

After the five second countdown, the match began.

Map: Desolate Town 7.

Desolate Town was a series of maps. If all 17 maps were put together, the map would be a complete town. But in reality, especially in a 1v1, the complete town was too big, so it was split into 17 parts. These 17 parts were of different sizes. Desolate Town 7 was the smallest among them, suitable for a 1v1.

As former teammates, the three from Miracle knew which maps Su Mucheng favored. Wang Ze mainly wanted to bump into Su Mucheng today, so he had prepared a map specifically for her. Desolate Town 7 was a map that Su Mucheng was good at, and as her former teammate, he knew how Su Mucheng liked to play in this map. This was why Wang Ze had chosen it. He wasn't hoping his opponent was unfamiliar with the map, but rather familiar with it. That way he would have a greater understanding of his opponent.

The two characters headed towards each other from their spawn corners. Wang Ze's Sharpshooter was called Kashiben, a character provided by Team Miracle. It was worse than his former Team Excellent Era character, and he had spent a lot of effort to adjust it to his preferences and habits.

Kashiben moved forward quickly, looking far into the distance onto the clock tower in the town.　　

The clock tower was this map's highest point. By seizing the high ground, one would have nearly complete coverage of the map. Desolate Town 7 was the desolate map with the most narrow and winding alleys, which wasn't too favorable for long-ranged gunners. Su Mucheng had been forced to be good at this map because too many opponents wanted to utilize this map to restrict the Alliance's Number One Launcher. As a result, Su Mucheng had to specifically practice and study this map until it actually became one of her best maps.

The clock tower was a location that Su Mucheng frequently occupied. She had the high ground there, allowing her to easily catch her opponent's position. Then, she could utilize her long-ranged capabilities to attack from afar. It was one of her most used tactics.

But… not today!　　

Wang Ze thought to himself. Their relationship as teammates was mutual. Since he had chosen this map, Su Mucheng wouldn't be so stupid as to go to it. She would intentionally avoid the spot she liked the most because her teammate knew about it.

Once she gave up on her usual plan, what would she do?

According to her habits and preferences, Wang Ze bravely made a prediction. He was currently heading over to verify it. He believed that his prediction should be correct. As a gunner class too, Wang Ze trusted that his understanding of Su Mucheng's thought process was very thorough.

　

Kashiben traveled through the small alleyway. Wang Ze's strategy was very clear. But from time to time, he would still take a glance at the clock tower. After all, it was possible that Su Mucheng would be stubborn. However, Wang Ze would be even happier if that were the case. The route he chose was a dead spot for the clock tower. If Su Mucheng went to the clock tower, he would give her a big surprise.

A flawless plan! Wang Ze felt satisfied with himself.

But at this moment, Su Mucheng appeared.

Utilizing Aerial Launcher, with a few ups and downs, she landed on the clock tower. Thinking that she wouldn't go over there, Wang Ze nearly exposed himself. Luckily, Wang Ze noticed her actions in time and hastily rolled to a dead angle in the clock tower's view.

　　

So she actually went there.

Wang Ze calculated the time. For Dancing Rain to make it onto the clock tower right now, she had to have taken a straight line to there, not wasting any time.

Was she not afraid that he would take advantage of that location?

Wang Ze was confident, but he didn't think Su Mucheng was stupid. As a result, when he saw Su Mucheng suddenly make what seemed to be a brainless move, Wang Ze stopped to think about it.

If Su Mucheng understood his intentions for picking this map but still made this choice, what was she plotting?　

There were two possibilities.

First, she didn't think much of Wang Ze's strength, so she did as she always did.

Second, she guessed how Wang Ze would respond, so she had set up a trap and was intentionally luring the snake out of its hole.

Su Mucheng wasn't stupid nor was she an arrogant person, so it was most likely the second possibility.

Setting up a trap and luring him out.

Wang Ze smirked. This was the Su Mucheng that he knew.

It was just that this time, he wouldn't fall for it.

Su Mucheng perhaps knew where the dead angles were from this clock tower, but did she know which of these dead angles allowed for direct attacks to the clock tower?

Wang Ze didn't think Su Mucheng knew.

Because only long-ranged classes had the range to reach her from those spots, and very few long-ranged players would choose this map. As for Su Mucheng, she had never encountered a long-ranged opponent on this map. This wasn't Wang Ze guessing. He had looked through all of Su Mucheng's data on this map.

　　

Detailed and thorough analysis, understanding, and preparation. These were Wang Ze's trump cards. Perhaps they weren't very cool, but they were practical.

Dancing Rain was still looking around from up on the clock tower, or perhaps she was guessing where Wang Ze would attack from.

No need!

Wang Ze smiled. He swiped his mouse, and Kashiben readied for a Thunder Snipe.　　

Sharpshooters had lower range than Launchers. Only Thunder Snipe was the exception. However, Wang Ze didn't want to attack from too far away in this situation, otherwise Su Mucheng would have time to react and dodge it.

The sniping spot he had chosen was the perfect distance.

At this range, if she didn't know ahead of time, by the time she heard the sound of the trigger, it would be too late to dodge. Even more so in a situation where Su Mucheng couldn't even see where it was coming from. Trying to react just based on sound was even more impossible.

Dancing Rain's forehead and long hair could be seen clearly through the ten-fold magnified sniper scope.

Gunshot!

A spurt of fresh blood flowed out from that forehead, instantly covering his scoped view with red.　　

"Tsk tsk, this type of attack should just instant kill her." Wang Ze sighed. After using the skill, he retracted his sniper rifle.

"Huh? What's that?" Wang Ze saw a bright flame in the sky spiraling towards him.

Chapter 1202: Familiar Rhythm

This is?

Wang Ze panicked for a moment, but he quickly calmed down again. Judging from the flight path of this whirling flame, it couldn't hit his position no matter what.

At this moment, a gunshot sounded.

Bang!

After a gunshot, there was the sound of an impact. The spinning flame in the air vibrated, but it wasn't extinguished. It now flew forward at a higher speed, and after this collision, there was a clear change in the flame's trajectory. Originally, it had been unable to reach Kashiben's position, but now, it was enough.

Boom!

There was a sudden roar in the sky. Wang Ze had long figured out what this was, but he hadn't thought that Su Mucheng would have such an outrageous technique.

After being hit by the Thunder Snipe, she instantly predicted Kashiben's position.

And then right after being sniped, while her body still wasn't stable, she was able to immediately launch a Heat-Seeking Missile, and then because this missile wasn't able to fly a far enough distance, she accurately fired another shot to support and extend the range of this missile. There was another important point here: Dancing Rain normally used a hand cannon, which launched powerful cannon shots that were impossible to aim with such precision. This meant that after firing the missile, she must have switched Dancing Rain to use a gun…

How was Su Mucheng this strong?

As her former teammate, Wang Ze thought that he had studied Su Mucheng enough, but he had no idea that Su Mucheng's technique was even more terrifying than he imagined.

The howling Heat-Seeking Missile fell toward him. Although Wang Ze was already frantically controlling Kashisen to dodge, the shockwaves from the mushroom cloud created by the missile's impact had a wide range. Kashisen was unable to avoid the explosion and was sent flying against a wall.

Boom boom boom!

The attacks of Launcher Dancing Rain came flying from the clock tower.

Occupy the high ground, capture the opponent's position, fire from an extremely long distance.

All of this was Su Mucheng's familiar rhythm, and it was a rhythm that Wang Ze had specifically studied, but now, he still fell into it.

Dodge!

Wang Ze desperately controlled his character, entering one of the Clock Tower's dead angles.

It's no use!

Even though it was a dead angle, Su Mucheng used all sorts of methods to send her firepower there. The AoE skills of a Launcher allowed her to somewhat disregard the precision of her attacks, as long as they landed close enough, they could deal a lot of damage and restrict the target.

I can't hide in a dead angle, I have to move and shake her off…

But isn't this the rhythm that every one of Su Mucheng's victims on this map would fall into?

Amidst the roaring cannonfire, Wang Ze hesitated.

What to do?

He had no plan.

He hadn't prepared for any events deviating from the script he had imagined. He had been completely caught off-guard by how Su Mucheng had instantly determined his position from his sneak attack.

For this match, Wang Ze's original plan was to use accurate sneak attacks to snipe Dancing Rain shot after shot. But now, after only one shot, his position was exposed. All he heard were cannon shots, all he saw was fire.

Where could he go?

Wang Ze originally thought he knew this map very well, but now it was all fuzzy in his mind, the various routes all tangling together, preventing him from finding the exit path among them.

But if he just let his character stand here, he could only watch his health bar steadily exploding away.

Wang Ze had Kashisen charge out, but should he continue to figure out a way to hide and dodge, or should he turn and fight directly? Wang Ze still wasn't certain, and he didn't have the time to reason things out. On this map, Su Mucheng's attack rhythm was extremely skilled. Whether Wang Ze ran or counterattacked, she had enough experience and technique to respond.

Ace card?

Did Su Mucheng not have one on this map?

And it was the exact same as Wang Ze's, the most simple: familiarity.

Familiar map, familiar attack rhythm.

Wang Ze's response didn't pose any difficulty for her at all. With all her skill at her fingertips, she bombarded him.

And Wang Ze seemed to have fallen into a battle for survival. He wasn't acting like he was trying to achieve victory, he was just trying to survive under the cannonfire.

The match had already lost its suspense from the moment Wang Ze revealed the position of Kashisen.

Individual competition round 2, Happy won.

"Beautiful!" Chen Guo energetically welcomed Su Mucheng as she came offstage.

"Who knows what the opponent thinking, picking one of your best and most familiar maps, how stupid." The fruits of victory were in hand, and Chen Guo wanted to make it known. As Su Mucheng's super fan, Chen Guo knew which maps she was good at, and she recognized Desolate Town 7. She'd even tried to imitate Su Mucheng's playstyle on this map.

"He's not stupid, it's just that I'm not stupid either," Su Mucheng laughed.

"In any case, we won." Chen Guo was proud.

Wang Ze, coming offstage, was in extremely low spirits. He had prepared thoroughly for this match, he had been confident, but it ended up like this? His strategy was still only on the first step when it received a headache-inducing attack, and he had been attacked from there until the end, blasted upon the ground.

He Ming and Shen Jian knew the hard work Wang Ze had put into preparing for this match. Seeing his disappointment now, they too were upset. But this was competition. Everyone worked hard, but in the end, there was always one side that would fail.

"I was still too overconfident," Wang Ze said with a bitter smile. "I thought I understood the opponent's strength, that I had a trump card that could get me victory. But I never thought that, under circumstances I don't understand, the opponent improved even further…"

"This is why Glory is limitless!" The unfortunate trio lamented, in a heavy atmosphere.

"Captain, I'm going up!" Right then, Miracle's third individual player had already stood up, Miracle's Launcher, Guo Shao.

Yes, Guo Shao, a name that sounded arrogant. Before the arrival of these players from old Excellent Era, he had been the core player of this new team.

An arrogant name, a position as core player, but Guo Shao wasn't that kind of person.

When experienced players joined, he happily gave up his position as core and captain. Passionate, with energy and ideals, Guo Shao was a Glory youth that had longed to play in the professional scene. And now, he had finally raised his sails to set forth on this journey.

"I wonder who my opponent is?" Guo Shao lifted his head to look at the projection screen. He carried this kind of excitement for every match.

The screen quickly displayed the names for the third battle of the individual round.

Happy, Ye Xiu, Lord Grim.

"Excellent!" Guo Shao was even more excited.

He Ming and the others exchanged looks, smiling bitterly.

What an innocent youth, he really has no idea of the terror and cruelty of the pro scene!

"Good luck!" The three still said some encouraging words, but in their hearts they already had no hopes for this match.

"Don't worry, seniors!" Guo Shao gave the three of them a thumbs-up.

"Go, go! You have to win!" Against their true thoughts, the three cheered him on.

Guo Shao went onstage, and on the other end Ye Xiu was already ready.

Log on, enter map.

"This is great, I actually have the chance to fight Senior Ye Xiu!" As soon as the characters finished loading, Guo Shao couldn't wait any longer and began expressing his feelings.

"Then do your best!" Ye Xiu never refused to interact with anyone onstage.

"Don't worry, senior!" Guo Shao shouted.

Offstage, He Ming and the other two facepalmed. Why are you telling the opponent not to worry!

Ye Xiu sent a smiley face emoji, and Lord Grim rushed forward.

The map was Desolate Town 28. In a 1v1, there was some amount of cover, but not many twists and turns, which made it rather suitable for a Launcher. Guo Shao's map choice wasn't out of the ordinary.

Ye Xiu didn't sidestep, he directly charged forth, and quickly saw that the opponent was doing the same.

Boom boom!!!

With the sounds of cannonfire, Guo Shao's Launcher Berk took the lead in attacking. Ye Xiu controlled Lord Grim to dodge, having no way to retaliate.

Guo Shao fired his attacks at the very limit of his attack range. Although Lord Grim could use a Launcher's low-level skills, that didn't mean he had the full long range of a Launcher.

The extremely long attack range of a Launcher was something they got only after switching classes. Their special skill learned when changing class at level 20, "Artillery Mastery," increased the range of all of the attacks and skills of this class, as well as the area they could damage.

"Haha, Senior's class doesn't have the range of a Launcher!" Guo Shao actually had the time to type a message, but Berk's attacks never stopped.

"You want to lock me outside of this range?" Ye Xiu replied.

"Seen through so quickly by senior."

"It's a very obvious plan. But it's not that easy!"

After sending the message, Lord Grim begin to charge forward.

Guo Shao immediately had Berk jump backwards while simultaneously covering a large area with his firepower, stopping Lord Grim from reaching him.

"Hit!" Lord Grim was covered by the large area of firepower, and Guo Shao was excited.

"But I'm closer…" Ye Xiu replied as Lord Grim ducked through the cannonfire. Although he suffered some damage, the distance between the two was pulled closer.

"That's not good." Guo Shao's Berk used Aerial Cannon to increase their distance.

"You can't run!" Under Ye Xiu's controls, Lord Grim used a Slide Kick, dodging the cannon shots coming right at him, and once he got up, he used a Shining Cut. His character sprung forward amidst cold light, and then he followed with a Charge, forcing his way through the Stingers falling from the sky.

Three skills used in an instant, all attacks with high-speed movement. The distance between the two characters was instantly squeezed so that they were almost right next to each other.

"Senior is really tough!" Guo Shao cried, his character changing direction to get away.

Lord Grim suddenly used another skill.

"Ah!" Against his controls, Berk started rushing toward Lord Grim.

"He can even use Taunt!" Guo Shao shouted.

The Taunt status forced the target to charge toward and attack only the taunter. Although it couldn't interrupt an attack, it was a powerful move to disrupt the opponent's rhythm, especially during a team competition when coordination was required.

Right now neither side had a team, so there wasn't that effect, but Guo Shao's Berk in this bit of time had no way to leave with his free will.

Collapsing Mountain!

Lord Grim swung his blades down, Guo Shao saw that he had no way to retreat, so he simply aimed his cannon at Lord Grim.

The cannonball flew out, but Lord Grim's Collapsing Mountain suddenly changed to a Falling Light Blade, and he plunged downward.

After dodging the cannon shot, the Falling Light Blade landed right upon Berk. Guo Shao hurriedly tried to Quick Recover, as the Taunt status finally wore off, but Lord Grim was already right next to him.

Slide Kick!

Guo Shao's reaction was very fast, he actually had Berk use a Sharpshooter's skill Slide Click. Even if he couldn't hit Lord Grim, at least he could slide past and start pulling apart the distance again.

But he hadn't expected Lord Grim to step to the side. Before he started fully sliding, Lord Grim stomped down in place, and at that moment, Berk slide right there.

After Lord Grim stepped on his opponent, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shifted forms and sent a flurry of shots to his face.

Sharpshooter skill: Punisher.

"You're about to lose!" Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1203: The Winery on Wuchuan Path

Ye Xiu's prediction was of course made with reason.

Out of the 24 classes, Launchers were ranked at the bottom in close combat ability. They were never absent in the voting for "which class is weakest in close combat," and their votes were never low, at about the same rank as Summoners.

Now that he was being stepped on by Lord Grim, an unspecialized with an immense number of low level skills and an extremely fast rhythm, no one thought Ye Xiu's words were unreasonable.

"Not necessarily!" But Guo Shao didn't agree.

Once Punisher was over, Lord Grim had only just moved his foot away when Berk immediately rolled and stood. However, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had already transformed into a spear, striking forth like a viper.

Clang!

Yet, what everyone heard was the clash of metal on metal. This sound was most commonly heard when parrying.

And, for Launchers, there was only one move they could use in parrying, if nothing unexpected happened.

Swing!

Each of the 24 classes had a knockup skill, which could be learned from the beginning. What Launchers used was this hand cannon swinging skill, Swing. Using this skill, Guo Shao managed to parry Lord Grim's Dragon Tooth.

Berk had already jumped up, cannon shots flying, aimed downwards and propelling him backwards.

However, Lord Grim truly had too many low level skills. Even if the movement skills he had used before were all still in cooldown, he had other choices.

Berserker skill: Colliding Stab!

Lord Grim dashed forth with his sword. Berk, even with the help of Aerial Cannon, couldn't match up to the speed of this dashing stab. He was immediately impaled on the blade and a combo followed after.

The unspecialized's fast paced close combat capabilities wiped the floor with Zhang Jiale and crushed Sun Zheping. Now, the one facing this was a rookie, using a Launcher, who was weak in close combat.

There was no suspense to this anymore.

However...

"Nothing is certain yet!" The rookie Guo Shao still didn't give up.

"Your spirit is admirable!" Ye Xiu praised, "If so, then I'll have to be more careful…"

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella changed forms rapidly, skill after skill pushed onto Berk. Guo Shao was trying to find an opening, but there was none to be found. Every possibility of escape had been completely sealed off.

"How terrifying," he was still lamenting, his morale seeming to be completely unaffected, but at a time like this, his Berk had already fallen.

Guo Shao didn't give up, but he didn't find a single opportunity either…

Walking out of the competitor booths, Guo Shao looked at Ye Xiu on the other side.

"Senior is so strong!" Guo Shao called out loudly, giving a thumbs up.

"Is he crazy, praising his opponent like that?!" He Ming and co were close to jumping up, nervously looking at the audience. As expected, the audience had exploded into commotion. As for Ye Xiu, he just waved and went off stage.

In the individual competition, Happy won with a flawless 3 to 0.

However, Guo Shao, who had just returned to the player bench, didn't seem at all affected by this gap.

"Let's all do our best!" Despite just having lost, he was here encouraging his teammates.

"You little!" He Ming's face was dark. As the captain, he had to say something.

"How could you compliment your opponent like that? Aren't you boosting their morale? Ruining ours?" He Ming scolded.

"Because he really is strong, so I didn't really think much of it," Guo Shao said.

"..." Guo Shao's forthright reason made He Ming incapable of scolding him further.

"Just don't do it next time…" he could only reply, deflating.

They lost all three rounds of the individual competition...

He Ming exchanged glances with his two old teammates. If everything had gone according to their original plan, then they would've given the first match to Ye Xiu, Wang Ze would strike down Su Mucheng in the second match, and then the third match would be given to Guo Shao, who was rather skilled. If he did well, they might've even ended things with a lead of 2 to 1, but now, reality seemed very far from their expectations.

"We're counting on you for the group arena," Wang Ze said.

He Ming and Shen Jian were going to be a part of the group arena.

"How come I feel that Happy doesn't seem affected by the magazine?" Shen Jian gazed towards Happy's bench. Did they not look at those magazines after getting them?

"Wei Chen, Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu are all experienced and mature players. Being able to adjust their emotions isn't unexpected from them," He Ming analyzed, feigning calm. "In the group arena, Tang Rou will definitely come up. She'll be affected by it."

"What if she's not participating today?" Shen Jian asked.

"Er, then the other younger players would definitely be affected," He Ming said.

"There's also that Fang Rui," Shen Jian reminded him.

"Fang Rui isn't all that used to the Qi Master yet, so his strength will be reduced," He Ming assured.

"Yeah…" Shen Jian nodded. In reality, they had gone over these things who knows how many times before the match.

"I'll be going first, Jia Xing will take the middle and you'll be our last line of defense," He Ming announced the lineup at the end. Jia Xing was Miracle's Battle Mage player, his character was called Prideful Sorcery.

The short break between the individual competition and group arena passed quickly. Under the signal given by the big screen, He Ming stood, bracing himself and walking towards the stage. On Happy's side, the first player to go up wasn't Tang Rou who used to always lead the charge, but Fang Rui.

After seeing Fang Rui, He Ming felt a little more pressure. The other was an All-Star level player, after all.

Relax, he's still getting used to the class switch. Focus yourself, don't get anxious, you have plenty of chances.

He Ming recited to himself in his heart as he walked onto the stage and into Miracle's Competition Booth. On the other side, Fang Rui also entered his booth. The projection began to display images of the map that would be used for this match.

Wuchuan Path, a small map with a Wuxia style, was a map that didn't have many obstacles for the three pro players of Miracle. That was usually how group arena maps were chosen.

The two characters soon spawned at the two ends of Wuchuan Path. In the center of the map, there was a winery with a large flagpole outside the door. A golden character meaning "alcohol" was stitched into the accompanying red flag, fluttering in the wind, very eye catching. The winery proved its worth of having such a flag, though. The winery had three large courtyards, pridefully taking up the center of the map. In terms of area, it made 90 percent of the map. Desolate muddy earth surrounds the winery, and when the winds blew, the sand and dust kicked up could turn the sky yellow.

With the winery in the center, the two characters would meet directly. The winery became a place that could be used to execute ambushes and sneak attacks. Knowing that his opponent was the Master of Dirty Play, Fang Rui, He Ming instantly felt like the winery was filled with danger. However, Miracle's three wouldn't be unfamiliar with a map they chose. And for this map, the focus of it was the structure of the winery. He Ming had his Elementalist, Rullo, approach the winery, but didn't charge inside. Though the two characters were the same distance apart from the winery, their movement speeds were different. If a Qi Master wanted to take this advantage, they could activate Qi Flowing Cloud and increase their speed, getting into the winery before an Elementalist.

Fang Rui would definitely use the terrain to his advantage. He Ming knew this with certainty. Thus, before he stepped into the winery, he stopped for moment and went over the entire structure of the winery clearly and completely. After making an organized judgement, He Ming's Elementalist, Rullo, walked into the winery from the side door.

Immediately inside was a massive courtyard with both square and long tables. The were cluttered with many small taverns. However, no NPCs would be in an arena map. A place that should've been bustling was devoid of life, giving an eerie feel.

He Ming didn't stay in the courtyard long, intending to have Rullo go further inside, when he suddenly heard a popping noise.

What was that?

He Ming's had very precise judgement, and he turned his view to the place the noise came from. All that was there was a wall, so the sound must've come from behind that wall.

Was it an accident? Or a trap?

The gears in He Ming's head turned quickly. Rullo walked over, but didn't immediately go through to the other side, but stuck close to the wall.

This doorway led to a rather narrow corridor. Thinking of this terrain, He Ming had an idea.

Rullo flashed into the doorway, staff waving and then, with a point, an Ice Wall appeared in the corridor. Only then did He Ming have Rullo dart inside.

"How cautious!" Fang Rui's taunt appeared in the channel. As expected, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was inside the corridor. However, he had been trapped at the other end by the Ice Wall.

"If this is how it's going to be, you can't hit me either!" Fang Rui sent a rofl emoji, as if He Ming's Ice Wall was a really stupid decision.

He Ming remained unruffled by the other's trash talk. He was glad he was so careful. If not, then he might've already been ambushed by Fang Rui's Boundless Sea.

"If neither of us can hit the other, then I'm leaving!" Fang Rui said as Boundless Sea turned to leave.

How could He Ming let this dirty playing opponent go so easily after catching him? Ice Wall could block movement and attacks, but it couldn't block an Elementalist's control over the elements.

Rullo raised a hand and elemental power began to gather in the air, curling up from the ground, eventually gathering in Rullo's mind. Skill: Absolute Focus. After activation, it would turn the next skill into an instant cast.

After that, he pointed his staff and the level 70 Elementalist ultimate, Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, was activated through the Ice Wall. Fang Rui, who was in the middle of his escape, realized something was wrong, and hurriedly had Boundless Sea roll backwards, taking a small amount of damage. When he looked again, the lightning and fire had completely blocked off his escape route. Charging through wasn't a good idea. Under the player's control, if a target tried to simply charge through Heavenly Thunder Earthen Lightning, then it wouldn't just be damage they'd take, but they'd also be rooted, so in the end they still couldn't go anywhere.

"How shameless! Take this!" Fang Rui sent as Boundless Sea turned and dashed forwards, his palm striking the Ice Wall.

If Ice Wall wasn't destroyed by an attack, then it would remain for quite a long time, even longer than Heaven Lightning Earthen Fire. However, Fang Rui didn't want Boundless Sea to stay here and admire the scenery, waiting for time to pass. If he were trapped in this small space and let He Ming chant a few more AoE spells, then he wouldn't have a chance at dodging.

Fang Rui didn't mind using this powerful skill to immediately shatter the Ice Wall.

Chapter 1204: Fang Rui, Figured Out

Pa pa pa pa!

Boundless Sea's Flash Burst smashed into the ice. Spider-web like cracks instantly spread, and in the next second, the ice wall shattered into tiny bits of ice.

But by this time, He Ming's Rullo had finished casting another spell.

Thunder Apocalypse!

Lightning crashed down from above, one bolt after the other. He Ming had calculated Fang Rui's options and positioned Thunder Apocalypse such that Boundless Sea was perfectly centered inside.

Dodge?

With the denseness and speed of the lightning bolts, dodging was extremely difficult.

Reinforced Iron Bones?

It would increase his defences and give him Super Armor, but lightning bolts produced a short paralysis effect, completely different from the hit stun from physical attacks. Reinforced Iron Bone's Super Armor would not be enough to move freely inside Thunder Apocalypse.　　

Qi Guard!

Fang Rui chose to use this Qi Master defensive skill. Boundless Sea's two hands traced an arc from the top of his head to his sides, forming a defensive qi barrier.　

However, with Thunder Apocalypse striking the shield, the Qi Guard wouldn't last long. It was unable to ward off the destructive might of Thunder Apocalypse. Moreover, this purely defensive position gave He Ming time to cast another spell.

　

Blizzard!

It wasn't enough time to cast a powerful spell. He Ming had good judgement and cast a relatively fast spell, layering Blizzard on top of Thunder Apocalypse.

Boundless Sea's Qi Guard shattered in an instant.

Piercing Lightning!

He Ming didn't hesitate and threw out an instant-cast. The distance between Rullo and Boundless Sea was extremely close. For an Elementalist with weak close combat abilities, it could be considered a very dangerous distance, but it was because of this short distance that Fang Rui could do nothing about this Piercing Lightning. Lightning element spells were the fastest spells.

A bolt of lightning pierced through Boundless Sea. The knockback from magic attacks should not be looked down upon. Piercing Lightning pushed Boundless Sea back a step, and Thunder Apocalypse and Blizzard had yet to fade away. The elemental spell formation set down by He Ming was giving Fang Rui an extremely difficult time.

He Ming activated Mobile Cast. In the end, Elementalists needed to maintain a distance away from their opponents. Before the two DoT spells completely dissipated, Rullo retreated while casting his next spell.

And Boundless Sea? Paralyzed by Thunder Apocalypse and slowed by Blizzard, Fang Rui didn't have any good ways to escape from his predicament. However, he couldn't let He Ming continue casting spells. Forcefully eating the damage and seizing the gap between DoT ticks was one way.

Qi Blade!

He Ming hadn't expected Fang Rui to be able to find an opening to let out an attack while under the barrage of two DoT skills. Even though he had yet to fully switch classes, his ability to grasp openings showed why Fang Rui was an All-Star.

Having activated Mobile Cast and in the middle of a cast, Rullo's movement speed was very slow. Qi Blade was a rather difficult skill to dodge too, so He Ming immediately canceled his skill and cast a Teleport.

Rullo suddenly disappeared. However, Fang Rui's reaction speed was quick. As the master of playing dirty, his first thought was that the opponent was behind him.

Boundless Sea turned around. Sure enough, Rullo was behind his back and had thrown a Fireball at him.

At this point, Thunder Apocalypse had ended, but Blizzard still remained. Although Blizzard's damage could not be compared to Thunder Apocalypse, the slow effect was a headache. Boundless Sea's movements were slowed, and He Ming had boldly teleported to a short distance between them and attacked. No matter how fast Fang Rui reacted, with his character unable to respond, he had no way of dodging.

Bang bang bang!

The Fireball struck Boundless Sea and exploded. Fire element spells dealt the most damage out of all four elements. Fireball was only a low-level skill, but its explosiveness couldn't be ignored.　

Rullo wasn't close to being done yet. He Ming was extremely focused, carefully and attentively watching Boundless Sea's situation, planning every step of his offensive.

After Fireball was a Dark Missile.

It was a low-level dark element spell. Dark element spells were neither fast nor strong, but they had strange effects.

Dark Missile followed closely behind Fireball and stabbed into Boundless Sea.

The dark element wasn't Rullo's main element. This Dark Missile was only at level one, so its damage was limited. However, its effect still came into effect. After being struck by Dark Missile, Boundless Sea spun 180 degrees.

It was just a turn of the body, but in a high-level match, it was an exploitable detail.

Having your back turned to the opponent could be considered as a short Blind as you wouldn't be able to know the opponent's next action.

No matter how fast your turned, you would always be a half beat behind. Fang Rui was an experienced veteran though. He wouldn't make such a rookie mistake. It didn't matter what was going on behind him; he immediately had Boundless Sea roll forward.

Unfortunately, this sort of experienced response wasn't outside of He Ming's expectations.

Elemental Power!

During this tight window, He Ming had Rullo cast the lowest-leveled Elementalist skill.

It was the slowest of all 24 knock up skills because it required a cast time. However, of the 24 knock ups, it was one of two long-ranged knock ups. As long as it was cast and the target was within its range, there was no way of defending against it.

In exchange for the downside of needing to cast the spell, this Elementalist knock up was given a powerful upside. Boundless Sea was inside Elemental Power's range. As soon as he finished rolling, he was lifted into the air.

Raging Flames!

A pillar of fire erupted from beneath Boundless Sea, swallowing him whole. Rullo continued to wave his staff. From the light gathering on his staff, the next spell had to be a powerful one. Rays of light burst forth, radiating waves of red fire. The magic condensed onto the tip of the staff and then ignited fiercely. The flames danced and swayed, letting out the cry of a bird.

New Elementalist Level 75 skill: Fire Bird!

Bang!

A blazing fire bird flew towards Boundless Sea, who was falling down after being knocked high into the air by Raging Flames, and engulfed him.

Boundless Sea burned as he flew backwards and crashed into a wall behind him. His health fell at a visible rate. The Fireball left an imprint on the wall, slowly dissipating from the burning Boundless Sea. Fire element spells didn't have much else other than overwhelming damage.

This fight was truly surprising.

Even though Fang Rui had switched classes, he had a shining All-Star title on him. No one would dare to underestimate him. During this period of adjustment, his Qi Master had been doing quite well too. Even though there were comments about his problems here and there, Fang Rui's win rate during these past eight rounds was quite good.

And now it looked like his honeymoon period was over!

　

After eight rounds of observation, Happy's rookies had yet to crash into a wall, but Fang Rui had already been completely seen through. Fang Rui wasn't able to display his dirtiness this fight and after being caught by He Ming, he was being beaten senselessly. At this rate, He Ming would achieve a perfect win.

The applause from the crowd was thunderous. After losing three individual competition rounds, there was finally a show worth seeing.

I really am a useless dim sum!

Fang Rui was sullen. In the previous press conference, Ye Xiu had given him a snide remark calling him a useless dim sum. He knew that Ye Xiu was just joking, but starting from the previous round, Fang Rui knew that his rhythm had been completely seen through. In face of Wang Jiexi, he wasn't able to find even a chance of winning. And in this match, He Ming, who was clearly a level lower than Wang Jiexi, was completely crushing him too.

Fang Rui was the master of playing dirty, but just because he was dirty didn't mean he had no pride. Right now, he was feeling wounded. Switching classes could be a reasonable excuse, but he didn't want to lower his expectations for himself because of this excuse. If he lost his heart, he would only lose again and again.

"You really have some skill…"

After being roasted into a half-dead state by the Fire Bird, Boundless Sea had dropped to the bottom of the wall, but Fang Rui still typed these words in chat.

He Ming ignored them. After Fire Bird, Rullo drew an Ice Line, trapping Boundless Sea in the center. Afterwards, he calmly started casting a new spell. There was still some distance between his Elementalist and Fang Rui's Qi Master. Rullo was sitting comfortably outside Boundless Sea's attack range. If Ice Line wasn't triggered, it would last for 12 seconds. 12 seconds was more than enough time for any spell, so just obediently sit there in prison!

　　

He Ming felt pleased with himself. His was very satisfied with his playing this fight. This is the way to victory, right?　　

Bright light gathered onto his staff again, clearly another large spell.

"Are you addicted to high-level skills?" Fang Rui chattered.

"Take a look at this move!" Fang Rui sent a shouting emoji.

What move? He Ming's mind rapidly turned. He was at a completely safe distance. No Qi Master skill could reach him. Qi Masters had no such skill, nor did any of Fighter classes. He Ming had very carefully considered everything beforehand.

"QIGONG BLAST!!!" Fang Rui shouted the skill he used for morale support. Boundless Sea flipped over his palm and placed it on the wall behind him.

The imprint burned onto the wall by the Fire Bird crumbled. With a boom, an ugly dog hole was split open.

　

"Come at me!"

Fang Rui shouted in the chat as he had Boundless Sea run through the dog hole.

Chapter 1205: The Labor Pains of Class Transition

He Ming was dumbstruck.

Rullo's fearless chanting of powerful spells instantly became purposeless. That ugly doghole seemed to split the entire world into two.

Boundless Sea had vanished. That doghole didn't seem that big, yet he had very precisely darted right through. Fang Rui's mechanics were extremely precise, but how he got so good at worming through holes was a mystery. He Ming didn't know of any training with this sort of content, and he believed that Wind Howl wouldn't have something like that either.

His wonderful lead, broken, by this doghole? He Ming couldn't accept that. He immediately cancelled the high-level skill he was casting and hastily adjusted his character's position. Though the hole wasn't big, an Elementalist could utilize their elemental power so long as they could see.

But when he got there and looked at that hole...

Complete darkness. He couldn't see anything on the other side.

He Ming's face clouded over. That bastard had blocked the hole? What sort of technique was this! That was way too low, wasn't it!?

The structure of the map quickly flashed through He Ming's mind, and he immediately brought up what the terrain was on the other side in his mind. If he went around through this corridor, then that would be too far. He'd have no idea where Fang Rui would stash his Boundless Sea by the time he got there. The fastest way was still to retrace his steps out of the corridor and climb over the wall!

He Ming immediately came to a decision. Rullo hastily retreated backwards. Just looking at the hole made him irritated. Swiftly, Rullo's staff raised and he chanted a Fireball.

Boom….

The Fireball accurately flew through the doghole, sending waves of fire inside and smashing against whatever was blocking it.

He Ming didn't want to waste time here. He had randomly flung a skill just to vent a little before Rullo hastily dashed away. But suddenly, his character seemed to slip from his control and was flung towards the doghole.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

He Ming immediately realized what it was, but apart from seething about this dirty play, he couldn't do anything about it.

Rullo was flung horizontally towards the doghole, but naturally wouldn't be able to fly right through. In the end, he crashed against the entrance, his health even slipping a little.

Pulse Break: Break Intelligence.

Flash Burst!

Boundless Sea's hand came through the hole and these two skills were consecutively blasted onto Rullo. With this Qi attack, even the walls were shaking. Then, both of Boundless Sea's hands came through, grabbing onto Rullo. With a yank, the parts of the wall around the doghole shifted out, almost to the point of shattering. The enlarged doghole was enough for Rullo to get through, and he was immediately thrown to the ground by a Back Throw from Boundless Sea.

The crowd was dumbstruck. The big screen wasn't even sure which shot to show this from, so it just ended up replaying this moment from several different angles at once.

Rullo, having clambered to his feet, had already been completely closed in on by Boundless Sea. Teleport was still on cooldown, so he couldn't pull away. Qi Master's had the weakest close combat ability out of the four Fighter classes, but it was better than Elementalists. Now, Fang Rui didn't bother with any tricks and had Boundless Sea teach Rullo a lesson with his fists.

No, it wasn't exactly with his fists. Qi Master skills were primarily palm strikes and jabs, very rarely punches. When they connected, it seemed light, without much strength, but they played with the inside of the body. Those light strikes injected internal energy, and the damage it dealt wasn't second to any physical punch.

With the slaps and hits, He Ming's Rullo didn't look like he was losing in a very ugly way. On the contrary, all the dust that had gotten on him when he was thrown to the ground had been struck clean. At the same time, his health bar was also being cleaned.

He Ming didn't want to be slapped to death by Boundless Sea like this. Fang Rui's Qi Master was still riddled with holes because he wasn't familiar enough with his class, and he was hindered by the habits he had spent years cultivating as a Thief player. Now, when he was attacking, he'd show a lot of openings when comboing. This was no secret. It even appeared in the news!

And what He Ming had to do was to not miss the opportunity when it came!

Rullo swung his staff. Even Elementalists could swing their staffs for normal attacks. He Ming fought back as much as he could. He couldn't just stand there against Fang Rui's palm strikes like a sitting duck!

His efforts weren't for nothing. When the dust on his robes had mostly been slapped clean, Boundless Sea finally stumbled.

Piercing Lightning!

This instant cast spell blasted forth. At such a close distance, Fang Rui wouldn't have time to dodge no matter how quickly he reacted. Boundless Sea, struck by Piercing Lightning, went numb.

　

In that short time, Rullo once again activated Absolute Focus and then followed up with a cast-free level 75 ice element ultimate: Absolute Zero.

They were simply too close. Although Piercing Lightning's short paralysis had passed, Fang Rui didn't have the time to escape Absolute Zero's range. Instantly, Boundless Sea became an ice statue. One of his legs was still in midair, suspended in his fleeing position.

He Ming let out a breath of relief.

Absolute Zero had the longest freezing time out of all ice element skills of the 24 classes. When maxed out, it would freeze for up to 8 seconds.

He Ming didn't rush, having Rullo pull away. In 8 seconds, he didn't rush to attack, because attacks would reduce the freeze time of Absolute Zero. In a one on one, it was best to use these 8 seconds to prepare to launch an offense.

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea maintained that rather silly pose, forced to watch as He Ming's Rullo escaped to a position and distance suited for an Elementalist's attacks.

　

Fang Rui was helpless.

Like a rookie that met the Rookie Block, he had met the labor pains of transitioning between classes. He had met it last round and hit it this round too. Even after using his masterful dirty play to save himself from the torrent of attacks and complete a counterattack, he still revealed an opening that the opponent was able to grasp.

He had been too greedy...

Fang Rui criticized himself. With how well he was settling in, it was better for him to just use simple and fast methods to stall his opponents and chip away at them, like with Zhou Guangyi. The problem was that such simple methods would be easily seen through by pro players. Fang Rui didn't have an infinite amount of tricks like that to use. The current him was at his wit's end.

Fuck, if only I were still a Thief...

No, he had already come this far, how could he still have thought like that? Having these thoughts meant that his determination and will weren't enough! Now that he had switched classes, he had to completely become a Qi Master. The tricks he had as a Thief couldn't be employed anymore.

Couldn't be employed?

After confirming this to himself, he suddenly had a doubt.

Could they really not be employed anymore?

A second doubt rose from his heart.

What a joke. Thief and Qi Master, two completely different classes that had no similarities whatsoever.

The classes might not have similarities, but… what about the thought process? Could the Thief's playstyle and strategies not be used by a Qi Master at all?

Imagine if he were a Thief, who had acquired the skills of a Qi Master.

Thinking from this angle, Fang Rui's eyes suddenly lit up.

What if he were still a Thief, but had a bunch of Qi Master skills?

These thoughts boiled in his head, a movement of ideas that not even Absolute Zero could freeze.

"It's about time." He Ming, advantage back in his hands, typed in the chat. It felt pretty good to have this sort of advantage against an All-Star level player. He took note of Absolute Zero's timing and, without wasting any time at all, a rather long chant was finished and a skill flew out!

Fire Storm!

Elementalists had ice, fire, light and dark element spells, but because they only had a limited number of skill points, they couldn't learn all the skills of all the elements. Usually they would choose two elements to focus on and spent their leftover points on some helpful skills from the other two elements.

He Ming's Elementalist focused on light and fire. The fastest light and the fiercest fire. Fire and light could be called the most offense oriented combination for Elementalists. Rullo's equipment naturally would would prioritize buffing light and fire. As for Ice and Darkness, He Ming mostly used them for their effects.

Now that Boundless Sea had been frozen by Absolute Zero, he was about to receive the fiercest attack.

It was unfortunate that the strongest of hs skills, Fire Bird, was still on cooldown. He Ming didn't have many options.

The Fire Storm whirled in and Boundless Sea quickly got out of Absolute Zero's effect, but at the same time, Lightning Hell fell from the skies.

For a fire and light Elementalist like Rullo, how could he lack the level 75 spell, Lightning Hell?

And this ultimate of light element spells had inherited the most distinct characteristic of its element: a quick attack with a short chant.

Lightning Hell had to be chanted, but the chant went by like a weak, low level spell.

The time it took for Fire Storm to devour the effects of Absolute Zero was enough to finish Lightning Hell's chant. A bolt of lightning fell just as Absolute Zero faded. Boundless Sea had no way of dodging.

One bolt, two bolts, three bolts, four bolts...

A full six bolts of lightning struck. The lightning bolts actually didn't strike soon after one another, but, for Lightning Hell, so long as one struck, the target would be locked on, and the rest would be directed towards the target by the system.

Boundless Sea, after taking the first strike, had then taken all five other strikes.

After two ultimates, Boundless Sea had once again taken heavy damage. The damage from the attacks he sent at Rullo, almost like he was patting the dust from him, was easily returned full force.

"Want to run?"

Seeing Boundless Sea darting through after escaping from Lightning Hell, Rullo pointed his staff and a Fireball sped out.

Boundless Sea practically lunged forwards to dodge the Fireball, then coming to a roll, jump, crouch, then roll. Boundless Sea rapidly moved forth using this weird method.

He Ming was stunned.

This was quite an unusual way of movement, but you couldn't call it weird. This was actually rather common.

Thieves liked to move in this way. Since traps were the main skills of Thieves, they had to crouch to set the traps, so the character would use crouching movements and maintain low set movements like rolling. Staying close to the ground allowed Thieves to maintain the form they needed to set traps. It was both convenient and discrete.

But this set of movements for these skills had appeared on a Qi Master?

"Hahahaha, are you going crazy from longing for your Thief?" He Ming sent a rofl emoji, yet that was when he suddenly realized that something was pulsing in the air.

Qi Blade!

Chapter 1206: The Thieving Qi Master

Qi Blade!

One could easily imagine how blurry a cluster of qi without light effects could be when it streaked across the air. One needed to observe the character's movements to predict and dodge this skill, otherwise, it would be difficult to get a grasp of the distance.

However, He Ming failed to notice Boundless Sea's Qi Blade movement, so the cluster of qi arrived before Rullo's face.

It's too late to dodge!

Rullo was struck by this silent Qi Blade and stumbled. Most of the crowd wasn't observant enough to discover the Qi Blade and thought Rullo's shiver was some kind of starting action to cast a spell.

Boundless Sea, still rolling on the ground, leapt up into the air almost around the same time as the attack hit. By the time he pushed both of his palms forward, a portion of the gathered qi had already shot out.

Sky Piercing Strike!

The powerful qi attack billowed the dust on the ground and blasted right into Rullo's head. It wasn't as if He Ming didn't react. He had tried to dodge it, but he was too late. He thought the distance between him and Boundless Sea had been pretty safe, and he felt confident in handling any Qi Master attacks with ease. However, he soon realized his mistake when the Qi Blade was right in front of his face. Even a powerful skill like the Sky Piercing Strike was covering another attack?

What sort of fighting style was this? Was it related to the movement style he used as a Thief?

He Ming was an experienced pro player; even though he didn't have a complete understanding of what Fang Rui was doing, he was able to find the key idea. All of this rooted from the movement style of a Thief.

This particular movement method not only allowed the Thief to plant their traps quicker, but also to conceal them better. Otherwise, any idiot would be able to figure out that a Thief was planting a trap when they suddenly bobbed down from running to dig up a hole. What use was a trap if its location was known?

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was using this exact same movement method. Even though he had no traps to plant, he achieved the effect that Thieves wanted: his attack was like a trap; it would stay hidden until it suddenly popped up.

This was Fang Rui's strength.

The former Number One Thief, Fang Rui, had impeccable control over this sort of rhythm.

He was now applying this to the Qi Master. Despite having only used two skills, he felt that they were effortless.

Stupid! Why didn't I think of this earlier?

Among all the long ranged attacks, were there any attacks that were as easy to conceal as the Qi Master's qi attacks? They had no sound and the visual effects weren't flashy. This was just like a moving trap. The Qi Master was truly dirty! Such secretive methods were too satisfying!

After being enlightened and changing his perspective, Fang Rui interpreted the honorable and righteous Qi Master class in this dirty way. No Qi Master through the course of Glory had interpreted their class in such a way.

After the Sky Piercing Strike, Boundless Sea followed it up with a leap backwards. However, this leap was towards Rullo's direction.

"What is he doing?" Rullo nearly flipped over from the blast of Sky Piercing Strike. After he finally straightened up again with difficulty, He Ming saw Boundless Sea jump backwards towards him. Is that his back?

Whenever Boundless Sea landed, he squatted, and it seemed like Boundless Sea's hand was hitting the ground?

Shit!

His camera shook. Although He Ming didn't do anything, Rullo was tossed into the air.

Seismic Throw! Fang Rui had hid it with his back, why was he so dirty!

The target within Seismic Throw's range wouldn't simply bounce around like one would in a trampoline. Qi was involved in this quake, so all the targets within range would be overturned.

When Rullo fell, He Ming immediately performed a Quick Recover. After landing on the ground, Boundless Sea rolled. As he turned around and got up, he pushed both of his hands out. The Qi Drill rushed towards Rullo, who was still getting up.

I can only Teleport!

He Ming's mind was clear and knew that only this skill could help him avoid this attack. He immediately cast it, but he was still too slow. The spiralling qi drilled through Rullo, whose body spun with it. With a boom, he was pinned to the wall behind him. Fang Rui finally took revenge for the Fire Bird that had blasted him against the wall.

This guy!

He Ming was getting a little nervous. Fang Rui's fighting style suddenly changed from the style that he had observed for the previous eight rounds. It was rather common to take the advantage to attack while transitioning between rolls and jumps. However, no one was as thorough as Fang Rui when it came to using all of these postures just to hide his attacks.

When he finally noticed the Qi Blade, it was already in front of him.

When he noticed the Sky Piercing Strike, a portion of the qi had already come out.

When Fang Rui launched Seismic Throw, Fang Rui's back was facing him to conceal his attack.

As for Qi Drill, the concealing jumps for the Seismic Throw also became a method to close up the distance for this skill. Furthermore, he could complete the inputs for the skill while rolling, so he could launch it when he got up. Even if the Elementalist had Teleport, he couldn't use it because he couldn't make his move in time.

How were these attacks of a Qi Master? These were literally traps a Thief would set down one after another for the opponent. The only difference was that the traps weren't waiting for the opponent to trigger it because the current "traps" were more proactive.

Boundless Sea was moving around once again. Those rolls and jumps of a Thief made him seem like a hound as he leapt towards Rullo.

Ice Walls!

He Ming immediately controlled Rullo, who just fell from the wall, to launch this skill among the remaining skills he had left with the ice element. He needed this to block the opponent because he… needed time to think!

He Ming had never seen this Qi Master's fighting style before, so he couldn't interpret and counter it immediately. He needed more time to observe and analyze Fang Rui's attacking methods.

The Ice Walls cut off Boundless Sea, who couldn't attack Rullo directly. Take a detour? Then this would only turn into a childish game where two people surrounded a table and ran in circles.

Last time, the person who was in panic was him, but this time, it was the opponent, right?

Don't panic, I still have the advantage.

He Ming looked at both of the characters' health and recovered his confidence. In terms of health, he still had the advantage.

But what should I do next?

Boundless Sea was nearly done smashing his Ice Walls into pieces, but He Ming didn't have his character do anything.

"You can't run." Fang Rui sent a smirking emoji. The Ice Wall shattered at this instant, but Rullo also happened to have disappeared.

"I predicted this much!" Boundless Sea continued to jump backwards. His back became the defense to concentrate his Qi once again. However, without waiting for him to turn around, a bolt of lightning shot through his back.

Boundless Sea, who was still jumping backwards, froze in midair and fell.

The audiences were stupefied.

Frankly speaking, they didn't really understand what was going on this fight.

That was because normal players who watched from the bird's eye view without enough skills weren't able to experience what sort of effect Fang Rui's changed style had made. For them, He Ming should be able to dodge all of these attacks, but he was still hit.

This was like Vanishing Step, dead angle strategy, or false combos. Only players who were placed in the situation would know the difficulties that they were facing.

He Ming was like this right now.

However, this was soon followed by raising the Ice Walls, Boundless Sea charging ahead, and Rullo moving with Teleport. Boundless Sea then held up his back and sent himself towards Rullo's direction without bothering to look back.

Was he looking for death?

Everyone thought in such manner.

Boundless Sea was indeed struck down by Rullo's spells.

"Sigh, it seems that I've committed a lowly mistake…" Fang Rui turned around. He was so deeply absorbed in figuring out ways he could secretively launch his attacks that he forgot that since he was sneaking around, he needed to ensure that he wasn't attacked by the opponent.

His backward jumps this time was too careless and predictable.

The audience thought Fang Rui was seeking death, but at that instant, He Ming was very nervous. Although he had Rullo immediately launch a Piercing Lightning, he truly feared that Boundless Sea had been hiding another skill, so before Piercing Lightning was released, that skill would have struck him first.

However, that didn't happen!

The Piercing Lightning shot Boundless Sea down, and He Ming's heart was at peace. He started to make use of this opportunity at once. Spells were set up on a grand scale, and Boundless Sea was stuck in it once again.

"Die!"

As he watched Boundless Sea's decreasing health, He Ming felt some sort of urge he never had before. It was as if he would lose if he failed to finish off his opponent in this wave of attacks. Even if his character's health was still that much ahead, but the thick sense of danger still enveloped around him tightly.

Glory!

The two large letters finally popped up onto the screen. He Ming felt as if he was released from great burden. No matter what happened, he still managed to take this round with a decent outcome. Rullo still had over half of his health.

Fang Rui, who lost, left the stage, but he wasn't dispirited. Although he lost, he saw a miraculous future ahead. If this weren't a formal match, he would definitely continue to shamelessly squat at the computer for another round with the opponent. He wanted to quickly confirm whether this future was possible.

After seeing Fang Rui's face flushed with pride, his teammates saved their thoughts of comforting him.

"It seems that you've discovered something?" Ye Xiu asked. The others weren't surprised at Fang Rui's attitude despite his loss since they had listened to Ye Xiu's interpretation of Fang Rui's sudden adjustment in middle of the match.

"Yup, do you think it has any future?" Fang Rui humbly consulted him. The person before him was the master of all classes. He was proficient in both the Qi Master ad Thief, so he should be able to give out pertinent suggestions.

"Seems pretty good, you just have to avoid those sort of disgusting mistakes," Ye Xiu said.

"That was only an accident." Fang Rui took that matter as an exception. At the time, he was so deeply enthralled by his new discovery that he allowed such a careless mistake to occur. Such mistakes wouldn't occur again, so after receiving Ye Xiu's approval, Fang Rui became even more excited.

"I really want to investigate it now, who's the next one? Quickly finish the match! I'm in a hurry." Fang Rui yelled.

Mo Fan stood up, but didn't show any show any reaction towards Fang Rui's shouts. He only walked quietly towards the stage.

"Walk faster!" Fang Rui yelled at his back.

Mo Fan's figure distinctly froze, but then, in a very awkward manner, he actually started to walk faster…

Chapter 1207: Charging Ninja

He Ming, having defeated Fang Rui, let out a breath of relief. It wasn't just relief for this matchup, but the overall situation of the group arena.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, the three All-Star level players had all come up already. That meant that the rest of the group arena only consisted of the rookies they had picked up.

He Ming wasn't underestimating these rookies, but he definitely doubted that they would be harder to deal with than those three All-Stars. He had sent off Fang Rui with quite the lead. With only two rookies left for Happy, Miracle was already on their way to victory, right?

Just as he was basking in his triumph, the opponent's character had appeared on screen.

Deception… that Ninja that got a red card?

This was the deepest impression Mo Fan had left on people after eight rounds. Apart from that, he hadn't won a single match, so, naturally, people wouldn't pay that much attention to him.

As for He Ming, he had met Deception quite long ago. In the online game, when they were fighting Ye Xiu, Deception had been one of Ye Xiu's helpers.

Yes, helper, that's what He Ming thought. He didn't know all the specifics of what had happened between Deception and Happy.

He remembered this guy. He Ming's impression of Deception stopped there though.

Apart from that, he knew that getting a red card meant he didn't understand the rules of pro matches. Glory wasn't football or basketball. It was very, very rare that someone would manage to violate the rules, never mind get a red card. He had yet to win a match too, so he wasn't all that strong.

A helper of Ye Xiu's who didn't know the rules very well and was average in strength.

That was He Ming's full understanding of Mo Fan, and in this week of preparations, Mo Fan wasn't their main focus. If he had to be categorized into important and unimportant, then he'd be thrown to the unimportant side.

Now, this unimportant guy was coming onstage.

He Ming readied himself with his spirits high. From a basic overview, he could tell that Mo Fan was a very patient player, who often relied on ambushes.

Yes… That's Happy for you.

He Ming couldn't help but think.

The match soon began. The map was still Wuchuan Path. There was no point in comparing his speed to a Ninja's, it would definitely be Deception who got there first. This time, He Ming decided not to bother rushing. His Rullo walked over slowly. Wasn't his opponent a very patient player? Then let him wait some more! He Ming was very relaxed.

But soon enough, when he still had some distance to go from the winery in the center of Wuchuan Path, He Ming saw Deception.

What on earth?

He Ming was surprised for a moment. Shouldn't this person have stashed himself in a corner of the winery to observe in silence and wait for a chance to ambush? That's what he had always done before, so how come he's changed his strategy today?

So what if he did?

He Ming didn't look too much into it. Mo Fan truly wasn't a name that could make him feel pressured.

Deception charged and Rullo met him.

Electric Ring.

He Ming first had Rullo put this skill on himself. Ninjas were very likely to close in with a skill like Shadow Clone. The presence of this skill was often worrying. Afterwards, Rullo fired off a Fireball. Starting with low level skills was practically a universal traditional starting strategy.

Deception quickly changed directions, dodging the Fireball, and his hands then began rapidly moving in front of his chest, forming hand seals. He Ming was stunned for a moment and couldn't help but think of the last match. A Ninja's hand seals were a very exposed way of activating skills because every Ninja skill was triggered through a different set of hand seals. One could figure out the skill through looking at the hand seals. However, since the speed of the hand seals was directly related to mechanical skill and hand speed, if a player was fast enough, then the hand seals would be nothing more than a blur. It'd be impossible to tell if they had bent one finger or two and therefore impossible to accurately determine the skill. They could only guess from there.

With a pro player's hand speed, they could all reach that standard. Mo Fan's mechanics were pretty good too. His hands blurred, leaving a few afterimages, then the seals were completed. Instantly, over ten copies of Deception appeared.

Ninjutsu: Shadow Dance.

His first move was a level 70 skill. If this were the All-Star level player Li Hua, He Ming would feel surprised, but this player was just a rookie who not only failed to earn a single victory in the past eight rounds, he also didn't even know the rules clearly. To He Ming, there was only one way to describe this: childish.

A bunch of shadow clones charged at Rullo. He Ming didn't give ground, and elemental power immediately gathered in Rullo's mind with an Absolute Focus, before instantly casting the level 70 high-level skill: Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire.

The bunch of Deceptions were immediately enveloped in an array of lightning and fire. He Ming let go and went wild, directly having Rullo use a high-level skill to neutralize Deception's high-level skill.

The shadow clones were destroyed one by one under Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, disappearing into smoke.

Five, four, three...

He Ming silently counted. Shadow Dance wasn't like Shadow Steps with real and fake forms. It could be said that they were all real forms. When the skill ended or when the shadow clones were killed one by one, the last one left would be the Ninja's real body.

One!

He Ming locked onto the last Deception and stopped controlling the Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. He was preparing to follow up with some new skills, throwing forth a new wave of attacks. Who would have expected that before Rullo even finished casting, the last Deception would be killed just like that too.

How!

He Ming was really shocked this time. If this one was killed too, then that meant there were still clones present. Where were they? Why didn't he see them?

Rullo whirled around, turning his head. After looking at his surroundings, he didn't see anything.

He Ming then realized something, but, too late...

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Deception shot right out of the ground, his ninjato striking Rullo's chin, yet very unrealistically it did not cut his face off, but threw him into the air.

Ninjutsu: Bird Fall!

Deception curled up in midair, darting higher. When he stretched out his legs again, he directly kicked off of Rullo's shoulders. After using the jump, he then executed a Neck Bind. The rope attached to the hilt of the ninjato had already wrapped itself around Rullo's neck. Deception landed lightly, his arms crossed in front of his chest, binding Rullo behind him and dragging him to the ground.

He Ming, who hadn't thought much of Deception, panicked. These three skills, like a falcon swooping on a rising hare, didn't leave any openings whatsoever. In the previous second he was being ambushed and in the next, he had been bound and thrown to the ground. His character hadn't been killed yet, but the abruptness of the Ninja's assassin-like skills made He Ming's heart leap into his throat.

After falling to the ground, he turned his head and saw Deception rapidly forming hand seals. He didn't have the time to look closely, hurriedly having Rullo roll sideways to a stand. Several streams of water shot out, a Hundred Streams just missing He Ming.

He Ming was just starting to feel relieved when Deception struck with a Flame Cut, ninjato ablaze.

Jump back, back, back!

A skill like Teleportation required too many inputs, so He Ming could only jump backwards. The Flame Cut swept down, almost striking. Rullo jumped thrice before finally stopping.

"How excessive," Ye Xiu exclaimed from the sidelines. To dodge that skill, one jump was enough. He Ming had panicked and made unnecessary actions. The extra two jumps didn't do anything to get him to a safer distance. On the contrary, because of the excessive nature of these actions, he was unable to dodge the next attack.

By the time the extra two jumps were over, Deception's Storm Shuriken had already arrived in front of him. No matter how fast he jumped, he couldn't beat the speed of a skill.

It was too late for He Ming to take back those two jumps. Rullo was sent flying by the Storm Shuriken. Deception charged forwards in pursuit, and threw another Shuriken before using Shadow Clone technique, sending his real body right next to Rullo. Then came a Cicada Shell Double Slash, the force of the two karate chops successively struck Rullo. Rullo hadn't even flown the full distance he was meant to when he got struck down by Deception halfway.

What is going on?

He Ming was rather confused. Against Fang Rui, he had met a style Fang Rui had never used; against Mo Fan, he also met a fury that had never been displayed by this player in the past eight rounds. Wasn't this person meant to be a player who played dirty, hiding in the shadows, waiting for a chance to strike? How come he had become so fierce when it came to him?

Rullo was once again knocked flat on his back. He hurriedly rolled to a stand, but Deception's attack came once again.

Teleport!

He Ming didn't think too much, getting his character to pull away first. However, Teleportation didn't actually take the user very far. Just as Rullo landed, he turned to look and saw Deception's hand seals forming constantly, taking one step out and somehow managing to immediately close their distance.

Ninjutsu: Ground Shrinking Technique!

Ninjutsu: Moon-Slaying Sakura!

With one step forward, before even entering attack range, Deception activated the Level 75 high-level skill Moon-Slaying Sakura. Deception's ninjato transformed into broken cherry blossoms, swirling forth. He Ming didn't know what to do. Run? Not possible. Dodge? He had just used his dodge skill.

Ice Wall!

Seeing that the other still had some distance to go, He Ming hurriedly summoned a wall of ice in front of himself. Deception had already arrived by then, and the thin petals imbedded themselves into the wall. Instantly, a crack could be heard, and a hole was made in the Ice Wall.

Though it was just a hole, the Ice Wall counted as having been broken through by the system. Deception didn't avoid it, directly charging forward and shattering the rest of the Ice Wall. His ninjato had stabbed Rullo already and broken cherry blossoms flew by, slashing open flowers of blood. In that moment, it seemed that Rullo was being torn apart.

What on earth was this?

He Ming really, truly, didn't understand. How come, when it came to him, none of the opponents were like what he researched? Against Fang Rui, he was in the lead, he had the advantage, then since Fang Rui didn't use all those new tricks at first, He Ming won.

This time, Mo Fan was different from the very start. Fiercely attacking, relentlessly attacking, not giving a single chance for retaliation. He Ming was an Elementalist. What Elementalists were most afraid of was someone closing in and not giving them any chance to pull away. This time, he couldn't shake the other off at all. What suspense was there left?

Mo Fan finally gained a win. A complete and straightforward win.

Chapter 1208: The Issue of Communication

"Hey! This kid's really playing this match with spirit!" In Happy's player area, everyone was overjoyed.

Mo Fan was still that silent, still that uncommunicative, so even though they chose him to go onstage, no one knew how he planned to fight. But this match, he won beautifully. Seeing He Ming's cold face as he came offstage on Miracle's side, it was clear how depressing that match had been for him.

"Not bad at all." Happy's players showered him with praise, but sadly this was the group arena, so for now the victorious Mo Fan had no way of receiving everyone's congratulations. As for how the next battle would play out, no one knew.

Looking at Miracle's player area, they saw their second player standing up.

Jia Xing, Battle Mage, character Prideful Mage.

"What a villain-like name, as soon as you hear it you know he's going to lose!" As Fang Rui expressed this, Jia Xing walked onstage.

The map was still Wuchuan Path, and if nothing out of the ordinary happened, the two characters would still meet at the winery at the center of the map. Because, as of right now, neither of them had taken a roundabout route or slowed their, they both rushed right toward the center.

However, as he approached the winery, Jia Xing still hesitated for a moment.

He had seen that in Mo Fan's fight with He Ming last round, he had fought a bit differently from his previous appearances. But would he regain his normal style in this battle?

After a moment of thinking, Jia Xing still controlled Prideful Mage to enter the winery more cautiously.

He constantly turned his camera from left to right, treating every corner of shadows as a place where the enemy could be waiting to ambush him.

Where was the opponent?

The crowd knew better than Jia Xing did.

Mo Fan didn't control Deception to hide in one corner. After he arrived at the winery, he first took a circle around outside, and after failing to discover the opponent's character, only then did he enter the winery. He was still moving around, evidently looking for the opponent.

He took an extremely active attitude. Clearly, for this battle, he was using the same new playstyle he had used in the previous battle, preparing to find the opponent and face them head-on. But because this map had this winery at its center, with twisting paths, the two didn't meet so easily.

"This kid, what's up with him today?" Fang Rui asked, slightly confused.

Ye Xiu shook his head. He wasn't clear either.

Last round, Mo Fan changed his normal playstyle. It was unexpected, but looking at the battle situation as a whole, the change he made was very reasonable, because last round his opponent was an Elementalist. Using this sort of active, aggressive, close-up style to attack fit the typical logic.

But in this round, the opponent was a Battle Mage, a class that was very good at direct confrontation, yet Mo Fan still used the same method he had last round. This led people to feel that his adjustment last round wasn't a decision made after seeing the class of his opponent, was it?

The two characters were playing hide and seek in the winery, and the crowd, with their omniscient view, were the most anxious. Especially one time when they were one wall apart, but one went left and the other went right, passing each other by so closely, provoking all sorts of sighs from the audience.

Finally, the two characters met in the lane formed by the gap between two courtyard walls.

Mo Fan was calm, but Jia Xing jumped. He thought that the opponent had been hiding somewhere, only for him to just boldly appear before him like this.

What was going on, Jia Xing already had a general guess. Since we've met like this, let's just fight!

The lane wasn't very wide. The two characters met, were stunned for a second, and suddenly charged forward.

Whoosh!

The Ninja had some long-range skills. As Deception rushed forward, he had already thrown out a Shuriken.

Prideful Mage twisted his body to dodge. His movement didn't slow, and his spear was already lifted.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Happy's Tang Rou often used this as a powerful opening move, and Jia Xing felt that it was a suitable move for this current terrain, and so he directly used this powerful skill as he sprinted forward.

Surrounded by a rippling magic aura, Prideful Mage rushed forward with his spear. The sound of his footsteps against the limestone-paved path rang in the air.

In the narrow channel, the magic flow from the Dragon Breaks the Ranks filled the space, and it looked like there was no place for Deception to hide.

But…

Mo Fan turned his camera, and Deception instantly ran toward one of the walls at the side. Jump up, stab ninjato into the wall, use that to jump up again, and Deception was already flying in the air. The Dragon Breaks the Ranks passed below him, and the aura was enough to send his clothes flapping, but it didn't affect his body. Here, he was outside of the attack range of Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

As Deception twisted in the air, his two hands were flying to form seals.

Ninjutsu: Shadow Dance!

Mo Fan didn't hold back, directly using a powerful attack against the opponent. Dozens of Deception's shadow clones chased the silhouette of Prideful Mage behind the Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

But Prideful Mage suddenly jumped up, turning in midair.

Seeing Deception dodge the Dragon Breaks the Ranks so nimbly, Jia Xing immediately stopped the attack. He anticipated that the opponent would immediately try and attack him, so he borrowed his lingering momentum and jumped up, twisted. Magic fluctuated around his spear, and he swung it down.

Shattering Heaven and Earth!

Powerful attack, another powerful attack, Jia Xing also retaliated with a powerful attack.

The shadow clones of the Shadow Dance hadn't had the chance to all attack Prideful Mage when this powerful attack enveloped all of them.

Shadow clones, how much life could they have? They definitely couldn't resist this bold level 75 Battle Mage attack, which produced waves of magic enough to stir a mountain. In an instant, these clones were dissipated into light, leaving not a single one.

Not a single one?

This situation was very similar to when He Ming earlier used Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire to blast away all of the shadow clones. Not a single one remaining meant that Deception had already hidden somewhere that was out of sight.

Underground?

Prideful Mage's spear already thrusted downward, but no, he wasn't there…

Everyone saw, Deception was coming at him from behind, using skills like Shadow Clone Technique to instantly send himself to this position.

The ambush of a Ninja was of course silent and stealthy. As soon as Prideful Mage's spear hit nothing, Jia Xing knew that something was wrong, but it was already too late to react, Deception had gotten behind him.

Annihilation!

The Ninja's knock up skill sent Prideful Mage into the air.

And then, Ninjutsu: Flickering Charge!

The rapidly moving silhouette seemed to flash in the air, chasing Prideful Mage with attack after attack. As Flickering Charge was executed, Prideful Mage's body was still floating in the air. He hadn't had the time to fall back down, but he suddenly waved the hand that wasn't holding his spear.

A purple shadow flew forth.

This Battle Mage had the Witch's low-level skill Night Cloak.

Night Cloak's Grab effect was extremely good, but Mo Fan's reaction was fast. Deception swiftly jumped backward, and this Night Cloak hit air. But immediately afterward, a burst of something that looked like stardust scattered in front of them, and Deception was unable to dodge it cleanly.

Disperse Powder, another Witch skill.

Using these two instant Witch skills, Jia Xing won back the initiative. The speed-lowering effect of Disperse Powder had a significant impact on the Ninja, who relied on agility.

Jia Xing easily controlled to dodge Deception's follow-up attack, and then he began his counterattack.

Just in this narrow alleyway, the Battle Mage and the Ninja began a fierce confrontation.

The two competed in observation, reaction, hand speed.

Neither of them thought to use some opening to retreat and adjust before coming back. It was as though the entire map were limited to just this little area and leaving would be dying. The two traded blows, both refusing to back down.

But the Ninja class, in terms of style, wasn't entirely suited for this sort of hard, direct battle. Compared to the opponent, he was at a disadvantage.

But the battle was still that intense. The disadvantage was only evident in the speed at which the health of the two characters decreased. But no one dared to confidently say right now who would win and who would lose. In this sort of confrontation, one slip-up could be seized by the opponent to reach a new high. An advantage right now could be completely turned around by such a high.

This was Miracle's home game, and so there were more supporters of Miracle and Jia Xing.

Right now Prideful Mage had the slight upper hand, but no one dared to relax. They worried, their hearts raced, every clash made them jump.

"At a time like this, wouldn't it be better for him to adjust his rhythm a bit?" At Happy's player area, the players were discussing the situation at hand.

"From the way he's acting, it looks like he's prepared to fight like this until the end," Ye Xiu said.

"This Battle Mage seems quite tough, Mo Fan really should've used his normal playstyle to wear him down," Fang Rui said.

"Yeah…" Ye Xiu agreed, but the problem was, no one knew what Mo Fan was thinking. Worse, even after he came offstage they still might not get an answer. Lack of communication was always Mo Fan's biggest problem.

At last, this battle ended with Jia Xing's victory. Prideful Mage still had just under a third of his health left, not a bad situation.

Over at Happy, they were sighing. For this battle, Mo Fan's health had lagged behind at the start, but if he had used his normal style for this battle instead of the direct confrontation, he might have had a greater chance.

Watching Mo Fan walk back step by step, Happy's members maintained their silence, all the way until he returned to the player room.

"Not bad," Ye Xiu put simply.

Mo Fan looked at him, didn't say anything and headed back toward his own seat.

Ye Xiu gave Su Mucheng a meaningful look. At Happy, the only one who could have any bit of communication with Mo Fan was Su Mucheng.

Su Mucheng smiled. She twisted her head to look back at where Mo Fan heading back to his seat and called, "It's a bit sad that you lost, how come you played in such a rush?"

Mo Fan stopped and looked back, but his gaze landed not upon Su Mucheng, but upon Fang Rui.

"In a hurry," Mo Fan said.

Everyone was stunned.

"You useless dim sum! Are you looking for death! Hurry up and kneel!" Ye Xiu hit Fang Rui on the head.

"My mistake, my mistake!" Fang Rui was weeping and crying. The others didn't know whether to be angry or amused. This communication issue was really a big problem!

Chapter 1209: Who’s Under Pressure

In the group arena, two of Happy's people were down, and Miracle's second player still had a little under a third of his health left. This was a relatively common situation in a group arena. This around 30% health lead wasn't enough to let Miracle relax or have confidence in their victory. They all couldn't help but look at Happy's players, observing their movements.

Happy's third player, Tang Rou, had already stood up. She turned back to place on her seat the copy of Esports Time that the Miracle players had harassed them to take.

Starting from the first player Wei Chen, all the way to Mo Fan, Happy had already sent out five players. What effect did the Esports Time have on their spirits? To be honest, if they hadn't seen Tang Rou putting the magazine down just now, Miracle almost forgot about this whole thing. From those five players, they really hadn't seen any effect at all…

Was it that Fang Rui and Mo Fan's unusual performances today were provoked by the Esports Time? That possibility would really be a slap in their face.

But no matter what, the next player from Happy was the one at the center of the whole controversy, Tang Rou. There was no way she was entirely unaffected by this? The attacks from Ruan Cheng's article in Esports Time were extremely aggressive.

"There's no way a rookie can take that kind of pressure," He Ming said.

"But… she seems very calm," Shen Jian said.

"She wouldn't be so nervous that she can't even walk?" As He Ming spoke, he followed Tang Rou with his eyes as she entered the competitor booth.

The group arena continued, same map, the characters loaded and entered.

"Don't wander around inside, let's just meet outside. We're in a hurry." Tang Rou actually first sent a message in the chat.

"What's that all about? What 'in a hurry'? Tang Rou never has the habit of chatting during a match, does she?" He Ming said with some confusion, only to hear a rattling crash from Happy's player area. Everyone immediately looked over, and saw Fang Rui fallen upon the ground, covered in dust with a depressed expression.

"This this… this is just too mean, this…" Fang Rui was saying. Miracle couldn't hear clearly, but Happy's players were all laughing. Tang Rou's "in a hurry" was of course a very pointed comment. No one thought that she would actually tease Fang Rui in such a way! Fang Rui felt overwhelming pressure, these guys were all "in a hurry" to deliberately push the responsibility of loss onto him!

While Happy was all joyful, Miracle became even more stunned.

What was going on?

A 30% health lead wasn't considered much, but it couldn't be completely ignored? Happy was clearly in a bad situation right now, but they really seemed to be quite happy, this… did they have some ace up their sleeve? In a hurry? In a hurry for what?

Miracle's members exchanged looks, no one understood what this was about. Meanwhile, the two Battle Mages onstage had almost arrived at the center of the map.

Tang Rou sent an invitation for a direct fight, but her opponent Jia Xing ignored her. In a situation where a player had the health advantage, they generally wouldn't go to fight the opponent directly, they would prefer to play some tricks, and Jia Xing followed this normal thought process as well.

Tang Rou's Soft Mist, like Deception last round, first took a circle around the winery. Upon failing to discover Prideful Mage, she had no choice but to enter the winery.

A large courtyard with three entrances and exits. Jia Xing was relatively active, not waiting in one place. The two wandered around, and before long they met. Tang Rou's Soft Mist rushed forward without any hesitation, but Jia Xing's Prideful Mage decisively retreated, swiftly finding a shadowy position he had passed earlier from which he could launch an ambush.

One step, two steps, three steps…

Jia Xing silently counted the rhythm of Soft Mist's approach, his eyes focused on the spot where Soft Mist would appear.

Boom!

A thunderous sound. The walls of the winery courtyard weren't particularly sturdy. If even a Qi Master's qi could break it, how could it pose any difficulty for the powerful magic aura of a Battle Mage?

Soft Mist directly blasted a large hole in the wall, and from her pose, it was clear that she wanted to cut off the path and intercept Prideful Mage. A lucky hit, for as soon as she came through, she saw Prideful Mage holding his spear, staring intently at the other opening and sneakily hiding.

Happy had so many experts at playing dirty, skilled at waiting, ambushing, and laying traps. Tang Rou, growing up in this sort of team environment, of course, understood these tactics. Seeing Prideful Mage's position, she immediately guessed his intentions.

But would Tang Rou care that much? We meet, so let's fight!

Soft Mist, Dragon Breaks the Ranks, charged toward Prideful Mage.

At this point, Jia Xing had seen Soft Mist breaking through the wall, turning, and rushing toward him without hesitation. He immediately controlled Prideful Mage to dodge. If this little shadowy corner were hit by that Dragon Breaks the Ranks, it would likely collapse.

Tang Rou's rhythm was of course very fast, Soft Mist's spear twisted and chased Prideful Mage, continuing to batter him. Jia Xing wanted to avoid the spear, but he couldn't find the space and could only harden his skin and meet her attacks.

The two Battle Mages were immediately tangled together. Confrontations between players of the same class were both monotonous and fierce, but this time, Jia Xing didn't have the chance to feel any boredom, he only felt the ferocity. Because this was too familiar, he needed to make more calculations. He didn't even have to time to think about too many problems, as Soft Mist attacked too rapidly, too ferociously, he had no chance to plan anything. He could only input controls nonstop, almost unconsciously, all the way until his Prideful Mage fell.

He lost?

Jia Xing finally regained his wits. The battle just now seemed like an empty fog, as though his brain completely stopped turning, and only his hands kept working.

And now, he had already fallen. The word "GLORY" would not be sent to his screen.

Jia Xing walked out of the player both. How long had this battle taken? He felt lost. He only had one feeling: fast, very fast, extremely fast.

How did it turn out like this? Shouldn't she be…

Only now did Jia Xing think about how stress-ridden Tang Rou should be. Her performance should have been subpar. But he hadn't felt that at all; Tang Rou's attack rhythm was still as determined as ever.

Jia Xing didn't feel it, and the Miracle members offstage didn't see it either.

The unfortunate trio exchanged looks. If even Tang Rou hadn't been affected by this whole affair, then there was no point in mentioning any of the other players in Happy. The situation they had been relying on to win this match didn't exist at all?

"No matter what, let's get these two points first!" He Ming said.

Shen Jian nodded. He was Miracle's third player for the group arena, the anchor of the team.

"Be careful." He Ming added, unable to relax.

"Yeah…" Shen Jian nodded. He couldn't relax either, and so he didn't have the confidence to say any bold words to settle their hearts. Seeing Jia Xing's dazed expression as he came offstage, Shen Jian's heart started beating more rapidly.

"How was it?" Shen Jian told himself that the opponent was a rookie, that there was nothing to panic about, and at the same time, he tried to get some report from Jia Xing.

Jia Xing, who had been beaten so pathetically that his mind was empty, of course had nothing to talk about. His face showed only an expression of loss, and Shen Jian could only carry his various emotions of suspicion and alarm as he went onstage.

The battle began.

The blank-minded Jia Xing had still made some contribution, knocking away 10% of Soft Mist's health. With that sort of direct fighting earlier, it was inevitable that both sides take some damage.

And so Miracle's advantage in the group arena, starting from the 50% that He Ming had, was now whittled down to only 10%.

10%...

Staring at this advantage, Shen Jian didn't have much confident. His Striker walked forward, but his heart was jumping. He wasn't a rookie. He had experience in professional battles, but to put all of the pressure of the group arena on him, Shen Jian discovered that he wasn't as strong as he thought he was.

The opponent is a rookie. The opponent has already lost 10% health. The opponent is suffering the heavy pressure of public opinion. None of these reasons were enough to boost Shen Jian's confidence.

A core player was a position, but it was also a responsibility. Every pro player anticipated having this kind of position, but not everyone could take on this kind of responsibility. Sometimes, it was because they didn't have enough ability, such as in old Excellent Era, Shen Jian never had enough ability to become the core player. And now, in Miracle, as an experienced player born in Excellent Era, Shen Jian became a core player for this team alongside He Ming and Wang Ze. but now, with the weight of the group arena upon his shoulders, Shen Jian found that he couldn't calm down. His main thoughts were not about how to achieve victory, but… what if he lost?

His mental state was a mess, but it wasn't so bad that it affected his basic movement ability. Shen Jian's Striker Lethe quickly arrived at the winery at the center of the map. He didn't directly find Tang Rou to battle. After tumbling into the winery courtyard, he found a place to crouch and wait.

"What is he doing?" Offstage, He Ming was scowling.

Playing dirty? That wasn't Shen Jian's strong point! Before the match, he had never expressed wanting to use such a playstyle.

He Ming was stunned, Wang Ze didn't understand either. These two teammates had no way of knowing the jittery feelings Shen Jian was experiencing onstage, they could only exchange glances.

In the match, Shen Jian sent a message in the chat. "Where are you? Come out and let's decide this!"

Confuse the enemy, hide your true intentions, this was what Shen Jian was thinking. But for those in this field, this sort of dirty playing was really a bit out of place?

"124, 131" Clean and direct, Tang Rou sent out the coordinates of Soft Mist's position, not dirty at all.

Then, what would Shen Jian do?

The viewers looked over, only to see Shen Jian's Striker Lethe sneak out of his corner, looking like he was really about to run over to the position Tang Rou indicated.

If that was the case… then what was the point in crouching at the beginning?

Those who had some understanding were all confused by Shen Jian's actions.

"What's this guy playing at?" Fang Rui asked, mouth agape. After all, this was one of Ye Xiu's former teammates!

"He's probably… playing dirty?" Ye Xiu said.

"Are you trying to insult me?" Fang Rui was unhappy. Dirty playing wasn't this low-level! He refused to recognize this as dirty play.

Chapter 1210: Title is Spoiler

124, 131.

Shen Jian's Striker Lethe headed towards the coordinates mentioned by Tang Rou, but he wasn't moving fast or slow. His wading in the mud and water showed the uncertainty in his heart. When he was almost at the destination, he didn't directly show his face. He searched his surroundings as if he were looking for a good spot to set up an ambush.

His opponent had justly and honorably declared her position, but he was stealthily creeping forward preparing for an ambush. Most people usually despised this sort of dirtiness. Luckily, this was Team Miracle's home ground, so the boos from the crowd were more subdued.

Shen Jian looked around for awhile before finally finding a position that he liked and then sprinted towards it.

No one?

His gaze moved towards the coordinates 124, 131, but there were no signs of Soft Mist.

"You liar!" Shen Jian was furious. He felt like he had fallen for a trick. This had to be a trap, yes, a trap. As he lashed out in chat, he immediately had Lethe quickly leave.

"What, you've arrived?" Tang Rou replied back in chat.

Shen Jian ignored her. Don't even think about using words to distract me, Shen Jian thought, forgetting that he was the one who had started this conversation.

"You're too slow. If I didn't walk around for a bit, the referee would punish me," Tang Rou said.

Shen Jian didn't believe her, but the crowd knew she was telling the truth. After Tang Rou announced her location, Soft Mist stood there waiting the entire time. However, Shen Jian's Lethe kept dilly-dallying. When he had almost reached her location, he started looking for an ambush spot. Tang Rou had waited for quite a while before she had Soft Mist start moving around.

"I'm on my way back. Just wait there." Tang Rou said.

Shen Jian was suddenly in a panic. Lethe spun around, his gaze sweeping over his surroundings, searching for Tang Rou's location. The crowd stared blankly at him. Wasn't this supposed to be a fight between two players? From the looks of it, why did it feel like he was playing hide and seek!

Shen Jian didn't just stand there like an honest person. After spinning around twice, he felt like there were too many places for his opponent to come out from. There weren't any ambush spots nearby, which meant that she had run away...

The home crowd was Team Miracle's, so they endured it once more.

Quite a few people were looking forward to how the show would continue forward though because the escape route chosen by Shen Jian just happened to be Soft Mist's return route. The crowd had a bird's eye view of the situation, so they could see it very clearly.

The two sides finally met face to face. This surprise encounter once again made Shen Jian panic, but Tang Rou didn't even greet him before attacking.　

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

A dragon instantly appeared in front of him.

Shen Jian's Lethe moved backwards to dodge and evaded it. His character glanced around. It seemed like he was searching for an escape route.

The match has already reached this point, and you're still thinking about running away?

How is he planning on playing this match?

This time, the crowd had no answer and boos gradually started coming out. It wasn't that the those who played dirty couldn't accept running away, but those who played dirty weren't this gutless in a direct confrontation either. Running away needed to have a clear tactical intent, but Shen Jian? The crowd couldn't see even a glimpse of a plan. From the start, he had appeared overcautious the entire time. He was now faced with his opponent's spear, yet he was still like this.

Can you win with this sort of attitude?

Bang!

A Falling Flower Palm pushed forward. Shen Jian wasn't able to react in time, and Lethe shot backwards. However, Lethe was surrounded by walls on three sides. Lethe slammed into a wall and then rebounded back. Soft Mist's Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart welcomed him and pinned him back to the wall.

"What is he doing?"

The crowd wasn't just booing. Angry curses were starting to be thrown out.　

Even He Ming and Wang Ze, Shen Jian's former teammates, his two pals after coming to Team Miracle, were also having trouble watching.

"What's wrong with him?" He Ming asked Wang Ze. Who could Wang Ze ask? It looked like Shen Jian was the player being pointed at by everyone, fearful and nervous from the pressure. As for Tang Rou's Soft Mist? Her temperament, playstyle, and drive were no different than before. Shen Jian's gaze shifted towards Happy's player area. An Esports Time was quietly sitting where Tang Rou had been sitting at before.

What's going on? Did I give her the wrong one?

He Ming didn't dare to believe it. The other players on Happy might not be affected, but he had trouble believing that a rookie like Tang Rou would feel nothing from the pressure of the public.

"Little Tang is playing quite relaxed," Ye Xiu commented on Happy's side.　

Would Tang Rou be affected by this pressure? It wasn't just Team Miracle who cared, Happy cared even more. And from this match, it couldn't be said that Tang Rou was completely unaffected because there truly had been some changes.

For example, in the dialogue in this match, the previous Tang Rou wouldn't have bothered with topics unrelated to the match. But now, she could mischievously tease Fang Rui and chat a few words with Shen Jian. This was a change in attitude. She wasn't impatient to prove the public opinion wrong, but rather player in a more relaxed way. With her personality, she might not be able excite her full potential, but controlling and adjusting her emotions purposefully was a more mature transformation.

Shen Jian's cowardice put him in a stifled position. His ten percent health instantly disappeared and then he started falling behind, losing to panic. Under this vicious cycle, he suffered a crushing defeat to Tang Rou.

"What were you doing?" He Ming ruthlessly berated Shen Jian. It wasn't like they couldn't afford losing, but in the end, Shen Jian had only been able to take away 20 percent of Tang Rou's health. This sort of trash performance was practically the same as giving away the point. He Ming couldn't understand what had happened to Shen Jian. Why did his playing suddenly take a dive? Their Team Miracle had prepared amply for this match, and seeing that their opponents were at the sharp end of the public's stick, their mentality going into the match had been quite solid. The rookies that joined the Alliance along with Team Miracle might have lost, but they performed very well. On the other hand, it was Shen Jian, their anchor for the group arena, that had lost in such an embarrassing manner.

Shen Jian didn't know how to explain himself. He had been given such a heavy responsibility, but it turned out that he had no confidence with this heavy responsibility. It was truly very shameful. In Team Miracle, he had acted quite arrogant as a capable senior. He didn't want his lofty image to crumble this easily.

"We can't lose this team competition! We can't be shaven clean by them, can we?" He Ming saw that Shen Jian hadn't responded. He didn't say anything more and started encouraging the team for the following team competition.

However… they had been quite confident about this match, but in the group arena and individual competition, Happy annihilated their forces. The psychological advantage held previously by Team Miracle had disappeared long ago. In particular, each of them hiding a copy of the Esports Time and then giving the copy to their opponents wasn't exactly a good-looking move, yet their method was completely ineffective and might end up being laughed at later. In this round, everyone in Team Miracle felt like they were clowns.

"Happy's team strength is much worse than their individual strength. Their teamwork isn't good. This is our chance." He Ming said.　

However, everyone already knew this. He Ming repeating it didn't do anything.

He Ming didn't know what to do with their downed spirits. In reality, his confidence had been killed too. It was just that he was the team captain, so he kept reminding himself not to show weakness.

"What's there to be afraid of! At worst, we lose! We're just a new team with new players. Go in with a learning attitude!" At this moment, the punk Guo Shao jumped out and yelled. He was still bursting with life, filled with hope towards this following team competition. He actually dared to say something like "At worse, we lose!" Perhaps no team captain would ever say these words, but that was the truth, and it actually eased the players up quite a bit. Even Shen Jian seemed to have relaxed. He didn't belong to the "new players" category!

"We can do this!" Guo Shao might as well just jump into the crowd and start cheering for his teammates. He attracted quite the attention from the crowd.　　

The team competition began shortly afterwards. Guo Shao's words had been quite effective. With the attitude of "At worst, we lose," Team Miracle's players let loose. But the problem was that once they let loose, they couldn't keep it together. In the end, they were a new team too. They had problems with teamwork because of their lack of experience. He Ming, Shen Jian, and Wang Ze were experienced players, but they weren't experienced as core players. Their ability to keep things together clearly couldn't compare to Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui, who had all once been top core players in their teams.

Their home map advantage wasn't able to help them. In the end, Team Happy won the team competition, sweeping Team Miracle 10 to 0.

The other matches taking place that same day ended in succession. In the ninth round, an extremely unusual scene appeared. There were unexpectedly 5 perfect wins this round, and all of them were away game victories.

Team Happy versus Team Miracle: 10 to 0.

Team Blue Rain versus Team Conquering Clouds: 10 to 0.

Team Tyranny versus Team Lightly: 10 to 0.

Team Samsara versus Team Bright Green: 10 to 0.

Team Tiny Herb versus Team Seaside: 10 to 0.

Apart from Team Happy and Team Miracle, the other four matches were all strong versus weak team matchups. However, the weak teams had the home game advantage. Not being able to win even a single point was very surprising. The public opinion believed that as the league developed, the disparity between the top teams and weak teams was growing larger and larger. The powerhouses prospered in the current scene, receiving more resources than weak teams and then using these greater resources to further strengthen their team. Under this cycle, the strong teams became stronger, while the weak teams became weaker. The new teams without any strong financial backers seemed to have difficulty breaking through these strong teams. Team Heavenly Swords had initially been looked at highly because of their strong backing, but who would have thought that their boss would be personally taking up the banner. Their expectations for Team Heavenly Swords would have to wait until after this boss lost his interest in playing.

Chapter 1211: Strong Performances

Apart from the five perfect 10-0 wins, the other matches in Round 9 were very orderly, three 2-8 losses and two 7-3 wins.

The three 2-8 losses were the home teams Heavenly Swords, Parade, and Radiant losing to the visiting teams Misty Rain, Void, and Hundred Blossoms respectively. As for the two 7-3 wins, 301 and Royal Style took down Wind Howl and Thunderclap relying on their home field advantage.

In the end, the weaker teams weren't able to pull off any upsets in Round 9. However, 301 and Royal Style, the two mid-tier teams that were on the edge of making it into the playoffs last season, utilized their home field advantage to beat Wind Howl and Thunderclap, rather surprising victories.

After Round 8, Thunderclap had been in second place, but their lead over the lower ranked teams hadn't been that high. With this loss, they immediately slid down to fourth place, while Blue Rain and Tiny Herb with 69 points and 66 points took second and third. Samsara's consistency and dominance once again placed them in their own separate tier. Their point total was 77, 8 points ahead of the second place team. After Thunderclap was Misty Rain in fifth with 59 points, Tyranny in sixth with 57 points, Wind Howl in seventh with 57 points, and then Hundred Blossoms in eighth. After Happy took a huge win over Hundred Blossoms, beating them 9 to 1, Hundred Blossoms adjusted rapidly. After two rounds, they were back on their feet, quickly making their way back to the playoff zone.

After Hundred Blossoms was Void, 301, and Royal Style placed outside of the playoff zone. With Happy winning this round 10 to 0, they moved up one spot from fourteenth to thirteenth, but the distance between Happy and the eighth place Hundred Blossoms was 14 points. The teams in the relegations zone were Seaside and Bright Green. After Round 7, these two teams were locked into last and second to last. The gap between these two teams and the teams ahead of them were pulling farther and farther apart. It looked like there wouldn't be any suspense as for who would be relegated this season.

The post-match reports for Round 9 didn't focus on a single team or person but rather how weirdly orderly the point distribution was. The media really wanted to about the dominance of powerhouses because of the several 10 to 0s, but the problem was that of these five 10 to 0s, one of them just had to be Happy, a truly irksome presence. Happy was without a doubt unrelated to this topic, but they just had to show up at this moment. The issue of dealing with Happy gave the media huge headaches. In the end, it was still Esports Home with the talent. Samsara, Tiny Herb, Blue Rain, and Tyranny were used to describe the untouchable dominance of the powerhouses. On the other hand, Happy was singled out as the representative team of wildly inconsistent and incomprehensible team.

They could crush Hundred Blossoms 9 to 1, but also lose 3 to 7 to Radiant and Parade. Yet after those losses, they could achieve perfect 10 to 0 wins over Heavenly Swords and Miracle. Figure out a team's strength from their win records? In Happy's case, it seemed extremely unreliable.

In these nine rounds, Samsara had obtained the most 10 to 0s with three perfect wins. Next, with two perfect wins, was Tiny Herb and then Happy. But Happy was also among the teams who were annihilated 0 to 10. It was as though Happy just had to stick their nose in everything.

The Esports Home concluded with a serious reminder to all teams in the Alliance: Be wary of Happy.

This sort of spotlight onto them was quickly met with backlash by people such as the Esports Time's Ruan Cheng. The Esports Time was biweekly, so he had no way of immediately writing an article through the Esports Time and could only use his personal blog to express his opinions.　

Tang Rou breaking her promise wasn't going to be forgiven so easily by him, but repeating the same thing again and again would tire out the readers. In fact, it might help her through reverse psychology. Ruan Cheng was a master though and had a subtle grasp of the pace. He wouldn't constantly stick in reminders, but he would never forget to raise the topic seemingly by accident at the appropriate time to avoid readers from forgetting about it. Because of Tang Rou, Ruan Cheng had turned into a through and through Happy hater. However, he was still a public figure and had to care about his reputation, so even if he had to paint Happy black, he had to back it up with logic, feigning reason and hiding his individual bias.

As a result, under Ruan Cheng's artful writing, Happy became a shit stick that harmed others without benefiting themselves, supported clearly and logically.

Why did his writing seem so reasonable? Because what Ruan Cheng wrote was really just a reiteration of the Esports Home's negative opinions of Happy in an uglier way. However, due to the influence of his writing style and the push from other journalists who were also unhappy with Tang Rou, Happy was generally viewed in a more negative light.

Two 10 to 0s?

One Heavenly Swords and one Miracle. Both these teams had certain ties with Happy. Snatching all ten points from them could also be considered quite vicious and merciless of Happy.

Some of the sillier comments even took those words "vicious and merciless" to describe Happy, seeming to have forgotten that any team wanted to win as many points as possible in a competition.

But dsepite these negative comments, Happy's pace became steadier and steadier.　　

In their tenth round home game versus Royal Style, a 9 to 1 victory.

In their eleventh round away game versus Seaside, Boundless Sea returned to the first time to his old home. The Seaside fans familiar with Boundless Sea saw their team's former symbol walk onto a path never to return under Happy's Fang Rui. Amidst the unrelenting boos from the crowd, Happy wasn't polite and sent away Seaside 10 to 0.

Two huge victories in two rounds. Happy had won 19 points, rising up two places on the rankings currently at eleventh place. Their distance to the playoff zone had shrunk to 10 points. Right now, Team Void was eighth. At the end of Round 9, the fifth place Team Misty Rain performed poorly in Round 10 and Round 11, falling out of the playoff zone at tenth place with 65 points. Even Team 301 was ahead of them.

Hundred Blossoms continued to perform consistently, winning 7 to 3 against the away team Blue Rain. Yu Feng's departure from Blue Rain had been quite controversial. Many fans thought he was being greedy. He had been one of the three core players of Team Blue Rain. Wanting an even higher position than that was endless greed.

This time, Yu Feng directly confronted Team Blue Rain, proving that he had the qualifications for an even higher position. Although his Berserker lost to Huang Shaotian's Blade Master in the final round of the group arena, Hundred Blossoms had opened poorly. By the time Yu Feng had to face Huang Shaotian, he was only at 30% health. But in the following team competition, Yu Feng became the most eye-catching player. His display of power pierced through the tactical net sown by Team Blue Rain. In the end, Hundred Blossoms won the team competition. Having won 7 points, they now had 71 points, rushing ahead to sixth place on the rankings, leading Tyranny by 1 point.

Blue Rain wasn't the only powerhouse that lost in the eleventh round. Tyranny lost their away game to Thunderclap 3 to 7, putting them at seventh place with 70 points. Thunderclap was third continuing on their radiant path this season. Apart from them, Tiny Herb lost to Void 2 to 8. Through this victory, Void broke into the playoff zone, while Tiny Herb was surpassed by Thunderclap, placing Tiny Herb at fourth.

In fifth place, Team Wind Howl won their away game 8 to 2 against Team Misty Rain, sending Team Misty Rain out of the playoff zone.

As for those outside of the playoff zone, Bright Green and Seaside were stuck in the relegation zone. Lightly, Miracle, Conquering Clouds, and the other low-tier teams had clearly become targets to snatch points from.

The weak teams were of no use to be looked at. Thus, the ups and downs of the rankings depended on the confrontations between the strong teams. Samsara led in first place with 94 points, 13 more points than Blue Rain. Their position this season was practically untouchable. Thunderclap had originally been this season's biggest surprise. After ten rounds, Thunderclap was still stuck in the second echelon teams outside of Samsara, running neck and neck with Tiny Herb and Blue Rain.

Team Wind Howl's momentum this season had been astonishing, but from their performance these eleven rounds, they were like loud thunder but small raindrops Even though they weren't like Happy who would sweep a team and then get swept, their inconsistency was a reality. After Hundred Blossoms' first four rounds, they became more and more stable, beating Blue Rain this round. Yu Feng had proven himself. Hundred Blossoms also showed that they had the ability to beat a top team.

Afterwards was Tyranny. No one had any hope for them dominating like last season. Tyranny was determined to keep rotating in their subs to the extent that it was rare for all four heavenly kings to be on stage at the same time. Their win record was also fleeting. When they were facing weak teams, they weren't weak, but facing strong teams, they weren't too strong either. Many were disappointed in them, feeling helpless about the issues of age.

Void relied on their good performances these two rounds to return back to the playoff zone. Their victory over Tiny Herb had boosted their morale considerably. The air around them was very different from before in their post-match conference.

The teams ten points away from qualifying for playoffs were 301, Misty Rain, and Happy. Team 301 was always like this, pacing back and forth in and out of the playoff zone. When the end of the season came, if their luck was good, they would make it to playoffs. If their luck was bad, they wouldn't. As for Misty Rain and Happy, they would be fighting each other in Round 12. This match would determine who would be closer to the playoffs.

From the current trend, Misty Rain had performed poorly two rounds in a row, losing to 301 and Wind Howl. As for Happy? After losing to Tiny Herb in Round 8 and Tang Rou refuse to keep her promise, Happy started taking points like crazy. Over the ninth, tenth, and eleventh round, Happy had unexpectedly took 29 points in total, even beating Samsara in terms of points, who had obtained 27 points in these three rounds.

Happy had matched with Miracle and Seaside, who weren't strong teams, but Royal Style was a mid-tier team with an All-Star watching over. Royal Style even upset the roaring Thunderclap 7 to 3. But facing Happy, Royal Style was swept 9 to 1.

Happy is coming!

The Esports Home highlighted Happy's recent momentum. As for people like Ruan Cheng, who hated Happy, there was not much they could say. Happy's win after win was slap after slap to their faces. They were waiting, waiting for Happy to capsize. That way they would wantonly throw stones at them while they were down.

This upcoming match was looking to be a good opportunity. In Round 12, Happy would be facing Misty Rain, a team with the strength to make it to playoffs. If Happy couldn't pass this obstacle, let alone losing points to their direct competitor, Ruan Cheng's group could directly say that Happy were just paper tigers that could only topple pushovers.

Chapter 1212: The Number One Ninja

November 22nd, Glory Professional Alliance Season 10 Round 12. Happy played their home game against Misty Rain, and once again the television chose to live broadcast Happy's match.

In this round, there were many matches between powerful teams, such as Wind Howl versus Void, Tiny Herb versus Hundred Blossoms, Blue Rain versus Thunderclap and so on. But in the end, they chose to broadcast this match between two teams that currently weren't in the playoff zone. They took into consideration the current situations of these two teams.

After eleven rounds, Happy's claim of aiming for the championship was still treated as a joke, but with their current ranking, people had to notice the potential this team had to make it to the playoffs. With a performance stronger than Samsara's in three consecutive rounds, they finally met a strong team, and everyone was curious as to whether or not Happy could continue their strong performance. Misty Rain had performed poorly in the past two rounds, instantly sliding from fifth place out of the playoff zone, and they urgently needed to regroup. So, the collision of these two teams was a bit more exciting, and was therefore chosen to be broadcast.

The attendance rate at Happy's home games continued to rise. Because of Excellent Era's many years of operation in City H, there was already a strong Glory fanbase. The old Excellent Era shut down and New Excellent Era was in the Challenger League. Many fans continued to follow Excellent Era matches, but many who liked watching professional matches slowly began to watch Happy's home matches. Happy's strong performance in the past three rounds incited even more attention and excitement, and now that they were facing the relatively strong Misty Rain, there was quite a crowd that came to watch the match in-person.

The players were introduced as they came onstage. Misty Rain, on Happy's home turf, actually received a decent amount of applause.

After Misty Rain let go of their Sharpshooter Lu Yining, the twin flowers Shu Keyi and Shu Kexin became part of Misty Rain's main force. Half of Misty Rain's positions were now occupied by females, and they finally became a veritable woman's army. This unique scenery naturally inspired unique attention.

"Haha, the Shu twins are very popular right now! They can receive such a welcome even at an away game." Television commentator Pan Lin noted the current atmosphere of the stadium.

"Their skill is very high," Guest Li Yibo said.

After the away team, the home team players came onstage. In terms of female players, Happy only had one fewer! Su Mucheng and Tang Rou were both part of Happy's main force. Su Mucheng's popularity in City H really didn't need to be mentioned. Her appearance always caused the audience to reach a peak in energy. But Tang Rou… after the 1v3, her supporters drastically diminished. Never mind neutral audience members, even many of Happy's supporters didn't like to see her anymore. The applause after her introduction was always scattered and lacking, and the atmosphere was so cold that it was awkward.

"Ah, the welcome received by the home players is even less than what the away players received, this is really…" Pan Lin lamented.

"Tang Rou is very talented, but the way she dealt with this incident was really…" Li Yibo also gave a half-sentence lament.

After the introductions of the two teams, what came next were of course the polite greetings and interactions between the teams onstage.

"Welcome back." Even though she was Misty Rain's captain, Chu Yunxiu didn't follow the custom to shake hands with Happy's captain, Ye Xiu. Instead, she went to her close friend Su Mucheng and gave her a hug.

Ye Xiu was left hanging with his hand still extended, smiling awkwardly, but from the side someone suddenly appeared to shake his hand. "God Ye, it's been a while."

"It's been a while," Ye Xiu answered, smiling. This small and scrawny man before his eyes was Misty Rain's Li Hua, the current number one Ninja in Glory. He entered Misty Rain in Season 7, appearing on the main roster that year, and that season he and Sun Xiang were the most attention-grabbing rookies. But the styles of these two were exactly opposite, one was bright and eye-catching, charging at the frontlines of battle; the other preferred to lurk in unnoticed shadows, launching sudden attacks when the opponent was defenseless.

That season, Sun Xiang had snatched the title of Best Rookie, and the next year he joined the powerhouse Excellent Era, taking up One Autumn Leaf, a top account in Glory. And then his team was relegated, and failed to fight through the Challenger League, and only now in Samsara this season did he have a strong chance of winning. Sun Xiang's pro career could be said to be extremely unfortunate and frustrating.

And Li Hua, who debuted the same year, had spent all his time working hard in Misty Rain. After his abilities were recognized, the team began working hard to build a character for him. The Ninja Dark Forest was voted into the All-Stars along with Li Hua in Season 8, and again in Season 9. And in this season, Misty Rain's strategic style changed, and experts could all tell that it now revolved around Li Hua. This skinny little man played an extremely major role in Misty Rain. But after shaking hands with Ye Xiu, he backed away and quietly stood to the side. If no one introduced him, it would be hard to imagine that this person was also an all-powerful top player in Glory.

Chu Yunxiu finally broke apart from her hug with Su Mucheng. She turned to look at Ye Xiu and casually slapped the right palm he was extending. "What, you want a hug too?"

"I don't dare," Ye Xiu grinned.

"If you want a hug, then hug!" And Chu Yunxiu really came over to give Ye Xiu a hug, just like that.

"Welcome back!" she said, patting Ye Xiu's back.

"Haha, in a while you won't be so welcoming," Ye Xiu laughed.

"Give it a try," Chu Yunxiu laughed coldly and pushed him away.

To the side, Fang Rui also opened his two arms. "Come! The embrace of love," he called.

"Get out. The player is as dirty as his playing." Chu Yunxiu ignored Fang Rui.

The players continued to move, shaking hands with each other down the line. When the Shu twins came to shake Ye Xiu's hand, their feelings were a bit complex. Last year during the Christmas event, they really wanted to tear out the heart of this person in front of them. For this round against Happy, the two were already secretly planning to give this God a proper retaliation.

"How about it, do you regret joining Misty Rain? You should've come to our Happy!" Ye Xiu said as he shook their hands.

"We're ahead of you in ranking," Shu Keyi said.

"Not for long," Ye Xiu smirked.

"Just wait and see!" The sisters glared at Ye Xiu, not at all afraid.

The greetings were quickly completed. The first players in the individual round stayed onstage while everyone else returned to their player areas.

Happy, Ye Xiu, Lord Grim.

Misty Rain, Li Hua, Dark Forest.

"What a coincidence, Senior." The easily-overlooked Li Hua was set up with Ye Xiu again.

"It is!"

"I hope to learn from you in this match," Li Hua said politely.

"Likewise."

After this exchange of meaningless words, Li Hua paused. He clearly still wanted to say something, but he couldn't find the right words. After silently thinking for a while, the judge already declaring that they could enter their player booths, Li Hua finally said a third pointless sentence. "Good luck, Senior."

"Good luck."

The two headed toward their respective competitor booths.

"Ye Xiu, Happy once again sends out Ye Xiu for the individual competition… So far he has almost always appeared in the individual competition. He already has ten consecutive wins, this is the twelfth round," Pan Lin said.

"In other words, this season, he hasn't lost a single 1v1," Li Yibo said. Right now was Round 12, and Ye Xiu was heading toward his eleventh straight win in his eleventh individual appearance, the answer was clear.

"With such a powerful 1v1 ability, why doesn't he anchor the group arena?" Pan Lin didn't understand, since that was how most teams set it up.

"Probably to lessen his burden, Ye Xiu isn't young anymore. Tyranny's already rotating their players," Li Yibo said. In a question of age, Tyranny always had to be mentioned.

"Then if Ye Xiu continues with this pattern and rhythm, this season's King of Dueling award will be uncontested," Pan Lin said.

"Uh… For now, his unspecialized class gives him too great of an advantage. We'll see everyone's professional ability!" Li Yibo said.

"Even if everyone is able to adjust, that doesn't necessarily mean they can beat Ye Xiu if they meet! With his current win streak, even if he loses the next few rounds, there's a good chance that no one can surpass his 1v1 record," Pan Lin said.

"We need someone to hurry and break his consecutive win record first!" Li Yibo laughed.

"Alright, let's watch Li Hua."

The two characters loaded onto the map. This was Happy's home game, so of course Ye Xiu was the one choosing the map. He had already chosen all of the maps with nothing on them, so this time he had to pick one with some terrain features.

This time, Ye Xiu chose the Hillside map. It was still flat with no barriers or obstacles, but the flat surface was slightly tilted, which of course would cause some changes.

The two characters spawned at the two ends of the map, at the same height. Since this was a map with no barriers, the two of course wouldn't try any strategic maneuvers. They both charged straight ahead, at the same time staring at the opponent's position. There was much strategy involved in choosing a position to stand on the Hillside map. Because there was a slope, this would affect many skills and movements like jumping and rolling. To seize the high or the low ground, this was a question that had to be considered.

The two players were both paying attention to this, so they both stayed at the same elevation, neither one gaining an advantage. Ye Xiu didn't launch an attack as soon as he was in range. Lord Grim continued to rush forward all the way until he was in the Ninja's attack range, but even then, Li Hua didn't control Dark Forest to attack, either.

Shining Cut!

Lord Grim suddenly swept forward with his blade, instantly springing forward and greatly reducing the distance between the two.

Li Hua was no longer quiet. Dark Forest waved his hand and a Shuriken was sent flying toward Lord Grim. Next, his two hands were already rapidly forming seals, preparing the next step of attack.

Ninjutsu - Shadow Dance!

This powerful Level 70 attack saw increasing direct use among Ninjas. It could be used as a main attack, or to hide movements and confuse the opponent. In any case, with a Shadow Dance, a Ninja suddenly had many options available. It didn't necessarily have to be used as a pure attack skill.

Immediately, over a dozen Dark Forests charged at Lord Grim together. As the number one Ninja in Glory, his mastery over this powerful Ninja skill didn't need to be mentioned. The live broadcast cut to Li Hua's camera view, which was constantly switching. It was clear the Li Hua was jumping nonstop between clones to achieve the best possible control over them. The fourteen shadow clones formed an impressive array to surround Lord Grim.

Chapter 1213: A Continuously Updating Record

Pu!

A cloud of purple smoke exploded, and Lord Grim disappeared into it. Facing Dark Forest's Shadow Dance, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim surprisingly throw down the Ninja skill, Smoke Bomb, to counter it.

However, the purple smoke was only a cover; it didn't allow him to turn invisible. Dark Forest's shadow clones charged into the smoke. Li Hua switched his viewpoint around even faster. The purple smoke only lowered his visibility, it didn't make him blind. With so many shadow clones and so many eyes, Li Hua kept on switching between clones until he found Lord Grim soon afterwards.

Li Hua was calm. All of his shadow clones gathered into one spot and marched forward together.

Numerous ninja blades stabbed towards Lord Grim.　　

Hit!

Surrounded on all sides, Lord Grim had no way of dodging, and the numerous blades pierced into Lord Grim. However, Lord Grim poofed into smoke and became one with the surrounding purple fog.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Li Hua reacted. If not for the Smoke Bomb affecting his vision, with his skill as the Number One Ninja, he could easily distinguish between a fake and a real body. However, he had fallen for it. All of his clones had gathered into one spot, but their attacks only hit a clone.

Where's his real body?

A purple shadow flashed out from the purple smoke. Because of the closeness in color, the shadow could only be seen by relying on the disturbances in the flow of the smoke.

Witch Skill: Night Cloak.

The group of Dark Forest clones were bound together by the Night Cloak.

Earthquake Sword!

The earth tumbled in the smoke, and a Spellblade Earthquake Sword swept over the bundled together Dark Forest shadow clones, rocking them wildly. A grenade rolled over.

Boom!

The grenade exploded and the shadow clones poofed one after the other. These clones didn't have much health. After taking heavy damage, they faded away. Lord Grim could finally be seen. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella extended outwards, curving at the top - an Exorcist's scythe.　

Rising Emblem!

A blue ring of light floated above the ground, and the remaining shadow clones rose into the air. Lord Grim rushed forward, sweeping at them with his scythe. The frail shadow clones instantly disappeared. The only one remaining was Dark Forest's real body.

Collapsing Mountain!

The attacks didn't stop as Lord Grim swung his blade.　

Li Hua didn't dare fight head on. Dark Forest quickly formed a hand seal and then disappeared.

There was no substitute straw nor a shadow clone left behind, yet to suddenly disappear could only mean...　　

With a Collapsing Mountain to quickly drop to the ground, Ye Xiu didn't pause, immediately having Lord Grim leap backwards.　　

Dark Forest drilled out of the ground, Underground Tunneling Technique.

Lord Grim had leapt backwards, but it didn't seem to be enough. However, the sword in his hands suddenly pointed in front of him.　　

Falling Light Blade!

Lord Grim didn't dodge. When he jumped back, he readied this skill, timing it so that it would clash with Dark Forest's ninja blade.

Ding!

Dark Forest tumbled back, while Lord Grim was left hanging in the air.　　

Storm Shuriken!

Dark Forest didn't wait to stand up and threw a Storm Shuriken at Lord Grim.　　

A sword light flashed. A Sword Draw accurately connected with the Storm Shuriken.

However, the word Storm indicated this shuriken's might. It wasn't something a Sword Draw outpriotized. Storm Shuriken broke through the Sword Draw and stubborn continued onwards.

Moonlight, Full Moonlight Slash.

Two beautiful arcs and two clear rings. Lord Grim quickly used the Ghostblade's two combo slash, and with these three consecutive skills, he was able to knock down the Storm Shuriken.

Lord Grim was still in the air. Dark Forest stood up and attacked.　　

Ninjutsu - Flickering Pursuit.

The difficult-to-see shadow arrived in front of Lord Grim in the blink of an eye. One attack, hit. His shadow flickered, and he appeared behind Lord Grim. Another attack...

Third hit!

Dark Forest's Silver weapon, Sixteen Dark Nights, stabbed silently without light. But this time, the blade didn't strike the body. Lord Grim had grabbed it.

It wasn't possible to do such fine movements through normal inputs, which meant it was a skill.

Back Throw!

Dark Forest's head crashed into the ground. Li Hua was dumbstruck. He was in disbelief. To be able to grab someone in the middle of Body Pathway Derangement, what type of judgement and mechanical skill did he have?

After falling to the ground, Dark Forest was stepped on by Lord Grim, who fired at his head repeatedly, Punisher!

Dark Forest immediately rolled in an attempt to get up and Lord Grim also jumped back, but Lord Grim was prepared for his roll.

Long ranged attacks used at close range were too fast to dodge.

Dark Forest, who was in mid-roll, was unable to dodge Lord Grim's bullet and was hit.

The damage wasn't high, but… it stunned. This was a Spitfire's Stun Bullet. Lord Grim calmly chased after him and started attacking.

"Tsk…" the commentator Pan Lin sighed, shaking his head.

"The unspecialized's skill options really make it difficult to defend against!" Li Yibo said. "He has too many similar skills at his disposal. For example, knockup skills, knockback skills, charge skills, skills that every class possesses. However, these classes usually just have one or two of these skills, but he has access to all of them. Just take knockup skills. Every class can get 4 low-leveled ones, but he gets 24. The available options that he has is too much. For the average player, just these 24 knockup skills is enough to juggle them in the air endlessly until death."

"But I've never seen him play like that." Pan Lin said.

"Of course, he's playing against pro players, after all. They shouldn't be getting juggled to death. I didn't raise this example to talk about this though. I'm pointing out that with so many options, he has practically no cooldowns because most of the time, he can find a similar skill to substitute what he wants. Low-level skills have short cooldowns too. This one's on cooldown, but that one is off cooldown," Li Yibo said.

"Mm, we understand Coach Li's reasoning. In reality, it isn't his class that's crucial, but the weapon in his hands. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella eliminates the cooldown required for switching weapons, allowing him to freely use whatever class skills he wants," Pan Li said.

　　

"Yes… without the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, it's not possible to play in this way." Li Yibo said.

The discussion going on between these two wasn't anything new. Ye Xiu already had eleven consecutive wins. These problems could be seen in each of his wins. Fortunately, Happy's matches weren't always the broadcasted highlight matches. If not, this discussion would be repeated so many times that the viewers would have insects crawling out of their ears.　　

The Stun Bullet into comboed Li Hua found an opening and used Substitution Technique to escape. But right when he turned around, he saw that Lord Grim was already in front of him.

"See," Li Yibo yelled, "Charge, Shining Cut, and then Colliding Stab, what class can use so many movement skills in a row! The distance gained by Dark Forest using Substitution Technique should have completely safe against any class, but Lord Grim was able to use three high-speed movement skills to instantly close the gap."

Pu!

While Li Yibo was chattering, Dark Forest was pierced through by Lord Grim's Colliding Stab and then with a fling, Dark Forest crashed into the mountain wall.

"Sigh, there's no suspense!"

"This map indeed isn't very suitable for Ninjas."

"Ye Xiu is also very cunning. All the maps that he chooses force the other side to have a direct fight with him, however, none of his opponents can defend against the unspecialized's offensive."

"But he hasn't met another God yet."

"That's true, the Gods are always the anchors in the group arena…"

Pan Lin were already declaring this as Ye Xiu's victory ahead of time. Reality proved their predictions true. In the end, Li Hua was unable to stop Ye Xiu from continuing with his record.

"12 consecutive wins…" Pan Lin said.　　

"Yeah…"

Happy won the first round of the individual competition. Ye Xiu's 12 consecutive wins was added to Glory's history books. Not only was he setting this record, he was continuously updating it. Just like what Pan Lin sighed, "How many consecutive wins is he going to stop at?"

After Ye Xiu, Happy's Ninja, Mo Fan, went on stage. The map that he chose was incomparably complex. Deception appeared and disappeared like the gods and devils, eventually grinding down the opponent to death. His victory wasn't easy though. In two of his ambushes, the other side was the one who controlled the flow, especially the second time. He was almost burst to death. At this moment, Mo Fan's reason for choosing a Ninja showed. Smoke Bomb, Substitution Technique, Shadow Clone Technique, Ninjas had quite a few escape skills.

After Mo Fan was Su Mucheng. Her artillery fire helped Happy win another match, completing the individual competition with a clean 3 to 0. The strong team Misty Rain seemed unable to stop Happy's recent momentum, which annoyed those like Ruan Cheng who wanted to ridicule Happy.

"You guys are playing well!" Boss Chen Guo led the applause, celebrating their three wins in the individual competition.

"Good, next up, watch us!" Fang Rui stood up and shouted. He often went on stage in the group arena appearing as the lead of the group arena.

Under Fang Rui's lead, Happy won another 2 points in the group arena.

The crowd cheered. Happy was on its way to a 10-0! The map chosen for the team competition was more important, which also meant that the home team had a greater advantage. As Happy improved, their teamwork was becoming better and better. With the individual competition and group arena won, the fans were very confident for the team competition.

The players going up for the team competition were all actively preparing for it, whether that be calming their emotions or stretching their shoulders and fingers.

"Nervous?" Ye Xiu suddenly asked the person next to him.

"What are you joking?" Wei Chen turned his head as if he had heard the greatest joke of the century.

"That's good," Ye Xiu chuckled.

"Got any cigarettes? Hand me one," Wei Chen said.

"Smoking is prohibited…" Ye Xiu said.

"Sigh, back then was the best… now we can't even smoke." Wei Chen looked up at the spacious stadium. When he had been competing, there hadn't been such beautiful stadiums nor had there been so many rules.

"Let's go!" Ye Xiu patted his back.

"With this old man, this match will be a piece of cake!" Wei Chen said, standing.

Chapter 1214: Observer Wei Chen

The players sent up for the team competition walked onto the stage.

Happy - Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Tang Rou, Wei Chen, Fang Rui.

Misty Rain - Chu Yunxiu, Li Hua, Shu Kexin, Shu Keyi, Feng Xiangming, Bai Qi.

Misty Rain's lineup for the team competition was rather unusual. Their team composition consisted of an Elementalist, Ninja, two Sharpshooters, and a Cleric.

Over the course of Glory history, all sorts of systematic analysis and experimentation had been done. In the early days, there had even been five Blade Master team comps, but these types of team comps quickly faded away. According to the current Glory meta, a team composition should have at least a melee class, a long-ranged class, and a healer with two other classes to build on this base.

But in Misty Rain's team comp, their melee classes weren't pure melee. Whether it was Taijutsu Sharpshooters or a both long and close ranged Ninja, none of these classes were true melee classes, yet this unconventional team composition was Misty Rain's main force. Their tactics revolved around this team comp.

According to past data, Misty Rain's team comp didn't seem to be reliable. Facing strong teams, their team had yet to win a single match. They had even lost their home game against Team 301, a team considered weaker than them.

even those who won, never expressed their disapproval of Misty Rain's innovative tactics. The one with the most persuasiveness was Team Tyranny's Master Tactician, Zhang Xinjie. In their 6-4 match against Misty Rain, Tyranny had lost their points in the individual competition and group arena, but in the post-match press conference, Zhang Xinjie focused more on Misty Rain's performance in the team competition.

"Very flexible with lots of variations."

This was Zhang Xinjie's evaluation of Misty Rain's team comp and playstyle. It was very simple, only six words, but was just how Zhang Xinjie spoke. Everyone knew that Zhang Xinjie would never talk about anything without reason. He might not say that something was nine, but if he said it, then it was definitely nine, and not eight or ten.

As a result, Misty Rain's team comp and playstyle led to quite a bit of discussion.　

Tactics were never secrets because you had to use them on stage for everyone to see. Thus, many tactics were common among everyone. The difference between strong teams and weak teams was an issue of a team's execution.

The analysis and discussion towards Misty Rain's tactics leaned towards the positive side, which meant their rather poor win record was because of their execution. After all, this was the first season Misty Rain started running this playstyle. They needed time to practice and familiarize themselves with it.

Every opponent each round was a sharpening stone for Misty Rain. However, no team was willing to become their stepping stone. Happy wasn't willing either.

Happy had carefully discussed and analyzed Misty Rain's playstyle in their prepwork. In the end, they arranged this team lineup to counter it. Wei Chen would be appearing for his first time in the team competition in Round 12. His Warlock was undoubtedly a crucial part to Happy's strategy.

Wei Chen, who was sitting in the player booth, wasn't calm. The stadium and the seats, none of these were the same as when he had played competitively back then. Even though he was an experienced old general, in reality, he was new to the modern Glory competition. The seat under his butt felt uncomfortable and the sealed player booth felt stuffy.

A cigarette would be great… Wei Chen thought to himself, but when he looked around the interior of the player booth, he could clearly see a sign prohibiting smoking. Fuck, this senior won't smoke, but just dangling a cigarette in my mouth is fine, right? Wei Chen felt indignant. He felt out a cigarette from his pocket and put it in his mouth.

The five second countdown passed, and the two teams loaded into the map.

The map was Mud River Peninsula and was split into four sections, linked together by a narrow piece of land. The separation between these four sections could be crossed; they were just a collection of small or large swamps. The center of the map also had a circular swamp. Characters could go into the swamps and not receive damage, but their movement speed would be slowed by 70%. This map was clearly a restrictive map. Apart from the swamps, there were lots of trees that could be used for protection. Happy had clearly chosen this map to restrict Misty Rain's long-ranged classes.

Happy loaded into the northwest corner of the peninsula, while Misty Rain loaded into the southeast corner.

Wei Chen sucked in a deep breath and had Windward Formation set out according to the strategy the team had prepared.

Team Happy's five players split up into three groups as they moved forward. Tang Rou, Su Mucheng, and An Wenyi went straight ahead, while Ye Xiu and Wei Chen circled around from the left and right.

The middle group moved more slowly to match the pace of the two circling from the left and right. The three groups were constantly updating each other with their positions as they advanced.

The team competition maps were much larger than the 1v1 maps, but that didn't mean the two sides would take a long time to find each other. The middle group were gradually starting to see the circular swamps in the central region appearing within their sight, but they were intentionally slowing their pace, so since they had yet to see Misty Rain, they knew that Misty Rain took a roundabout path.

The middle group informed Ye Xiu and Wei Chen, the two on their left and right.

"I know, they're on my side…" Wei Chen had been just about to notify them!

Windward Formation was hiding in a shrub on the side. Misty Rain's five characters hadn't scattered and were concentrated in one place, preparing to traverse through the swamps to directly cut across to the southwest region. If they moved along the swamp line, they would get to the rear of Happy.

Too bad they've been found by this senior.

Wei Chen peeped at them, while delightedly plotting what he should do next. If Happy had been together, then ambushing them while Misty Rain was traversing through the swamps would be the most optimal choice, but since he was alone...

Wei Chen hesitated.

Even though his Windward Formation had an abnormally long range, that was only relative to his class. Misty Rain had two Sharpshooters, whose natural attack ranges were above Mages. Even with Windward Formation's increased cast range from his weapon Death's Hand, he had no advantage over these two Sharpshooters.　　

"Misty Rain is forcefully traversing through the swamps. Do you guys think I should attack or not…" Unsure of what to do, Wei Chen asked for the opinion of his teammates.

"They have two Sharpshooters. You won't be able to suppress them!" Ye Xiu replied.

"Stealthily place a Death's Door to their side?" Wei Chen said.

"Windy Rain's spells will instantly blow it up," Ye Xiu said.

Stealthily placing a Death's Door was a concept that only existed among the normal players. Death's Door made a huge disturbance when cast and required the caster to control it. Pro players could easily deduce the enemy Warlock's position.

"Then what do I do?"

"We'll prepare an ambush at the Half Moon Rock in the 9 o'clock position, while you go back on your original path and cut to their rear," Ye Xiu replied.　

"They're probably… about a minute away from the Half Moon Rock, assuming that they directly move in that direction," Wei Chen calculated from Misty Rain's movement speed.

"Good, that's enough time. Are you fine?" Ye Xiu said.

"No problems here," Wei Chen replied.

"Don't appear in front of them too early," Ye Xiu said.　

"Hahaha, hilarious," Wei Chen replied. He didn't hurry to move his Windward Formation into position. He continued to crouch inside the bush, watching as Misty Rain's five players moved through the swamp towards the southwest corner.

"They've passed through." After Wei Chen sent the message, Windward Formation finally left the brush.

Half Moon Rock.

Situated at the link between the northwest and southwest region, Tang Rou's Soft Mist leaned on the outer edge of the rock with her spear propped up. In just one step, she could launch an attack on any passing characters. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain leaped to a spot three-quarters of the way up the Half Moon Rock. In one jump, she would be able to reach the top of the rock, letting her suppress the enemies with her firepower from the high ground. An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands didn't need to find an attacking position. He just moved into a position between the two characters to support them.

"In position."

"In position."

"In position."

The three players each confirmed that they had reached their chosen positions.

Would they succeed in ambushing Misty Rain?

The suspense was unfolding before them. The live crowd and the viewers watching the broadcast waited for the moment to happen.

After Team Misty Rain crossed through the swamp, their movement speed returned to normal, and they quickly advanced forward. Soon, the Half Moon Rock was within their sights. Wei Chen's Windward Formation reached this area one step ahead of them. He once again found an ambush spot in a shrub by the road and observed Team Misty Rain's movements.

"They've arrived."

"They've slowed down. They're probably wary of the Half Moon Rock."

"They've changed direction. They're not heading towards Half Moon Rock."

"Fuck, they're coming my way."

"Then you're the bait! Go lure them into our ambush!" Ye Xiu made a firm decision.　

"How evil." Wei Chen cursed, but he also approved of this decision. Windward Formation suddenly scurried out of the bush.

Bang!

Lower Your Head, None Dare Attack!　　

Having changed from male to female characters through a backdoor, the Shu sisters immediately fired at Windward Formation.

Windward Formation rolled and crawled frantically, moving in a beautiful S path.　　

Bang!

An incomparably powerful sounding gunshot sounded.

Lower Your Head directly mounted Thunder Snipe and fired a heavy shot amidst None Dare Attack's rain of bullets.　

Windward Formation wasn't able to avoid the snipe. Blood spurted from his wound. Both person and blood tumbled forward.　　

"How fierce…" Wei Chen didn't forget to give a remark when he was hit.

"Keep up the good work," Ye Xiu encouraged him.

"Where the fuck are you?" Wei Chen asked. Ye Xiu wasn't among the ones who confirmed they were in position.　　

"I'm ready to help you at any moment," Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen turned around to look. Misty Rain had started speeding up, looking as if they wouldn't rest until he died. The two Sharpshooters shot a hail of bullets, putting Wei Chen's reactions to the test. Windward Formation was instantly hit by several bullets.

Fuck, if this was ten years ago...

Wei Chen's reaction speed and mechanical skill weren't able to keep up. He suddenly realized that he might not be able to complete his mission as bait.

"Help!" Wei Chen immediately called for help.

Dancing Rain leaped onto the top of Half Moon Rock, propped up her heavy cannon, and started firing!

Chapter 1215: Suppression From Map and Skill

Explosive artillery fire headed straight towards the center of Misty Rain's formation. The AoE covered by her attacks could not be ignored. The five Misty Rain players immediately had their characters dodge, instantly pulling their formation apart. They weren't planning on giving Su Mucheng an opportunity to burst them all at once.

As the Misty Rain players avoided the artillery fire, they didn't loosen their attacks towards Windward Formation. They seemed to have no intention of firing back at Dancing Rain.

As a result, Su Mucheng also switched targets. Her dazzling artillery barrage fired towards Windward Formation.　　

Everyone was struck dumb.

Windward Formation wouldn't take damage from his ally's attacks, and the light from the artillery fire made his figure flicker, appearing and disappearing intermittently. This was Zhang Jiale's famous Hundred Blossoms style.　

Team Misty Rain was suddenly unable to effectively locate and attack Windward Formation. The Shu sisters immediately switched targets, and their bullets fired towards Dancing Rain at the top of the Half Moon Rock.

Su Mucheng didn't retreat. Dancing Rain only dodged the necessary incoming attacks, while taking the attacks that wouldn't affect her much. At the same time, a white light glowed around her. Little Cold Hands, who was hiding behind the Half Moon Rock, had started doing his work.

Without any danger of being attacked and only needing to focus his healing on Dancing Rain, An Wenyi's weaknesses were completely covered up. Under these conditions, An Wenyi's healing displayed an extremely high level of skill. Dancing Rain's health was maintained at a steady state.

Dancing Rain continued to provide cover for Windward Formation.

Chu Yunxiu realized that something wasn't right.

With the Shu sisters switching targets, Windward Formation was no longer under any pressure. Thus, Su Mucheng could easily switch targets too, yet why was she still protecting Windward Formation?

Absolute Focus!

Chu Yunxiu immediately had her Windy Rain activate a skill. Just when she was about to cast a high-level spell, Windy Rain was suddenly entrapped by an array of light. All of her skill icons turned gray, meaning they could not be used.

Spell Shackle!

Chu Yunxiu was startled. This was an Elementalist skill. If it had come from the enemy team, then it could only have been from their unspecialized, Lord Grim, and his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's mage form.

Where was Lord Grim?

Spell Shackle was a silence. It did not stop her character from moving. Chu Yunxiu whirled around, but she couldn't see any signs of Lord Grim.

There's only one possibility...

Chu Yunxiu's gaze locked onto the dazzling light created by Dancing Rain.

The flickering of the light created a facade, falsely making it seem like the covered target was moving. In reality, Windward Formation might not be moving and might actually be casting some sort of powerful spell. Lord Grim had entered the light cover as well and sealed her attacks with a Spell Shackle. His intentions were obviously to protect Windward Formation...

Chu Yunxiu instantly read and understood Happy's strategic intentions.

"Focus your fire onto Windward Formation!" Unable to attack, she immediately sent down a command in their team channel.

The Shu sisters didn't really understand why they should, but they followed their captain's orders. The two Sharpshooters switched fire back to Windward Formation, but where was he positioned at? The two weren't able to accurately grasp his location.

Chu Yunxiu felt a bad premonition in her heart. Although the Sharpshooters attacked fast, their coverage was small since they didn't have any AoE skills.

"Scatter!" At this moment, she could only take precautionary measures. Windward Formation was most likely casting a spell such as Death's Door.

Chu Yunxiu's prediction was absolutely correct. At this moment, an evil aura condensed into Death's Door right in the center of Misty Rain's formation.

The light screen from Dancing Rain's Hundred Blossoms style suddenly dimmed. Misty Rain's players could now see that inside this light screen, Lord Grim had his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella open, shielding Windward Formation.

How did he suddenly get there? It had to be from some instant movement skill like Shadow Clone Technique. But the issue wasn't the process, but rather the result.

Death's Door had been summoned, and it was now starting its work. Black tendrils extended out of the door, grabbing towards Misty Rain's five players.

Yes, five!

Chu Yunxiu's "Scatter!" had been too late. Everyone in Misty Rain was still inside Death's Door's range.

Some were still closer than others though.

Shu Keyi's Lower Your Head stepped back a few times and reached the safe zone. She was the farthest away, being able to escape from the Death's Door with just a few steps. The closest was Li Hua's Dark Forest. However, Ninjas had the most escape skills out of any class! Substitution Technique into Shadow Clone Technique into the Assassin's high speed dash, Shining Cut, Dark Forest was the second to escape.

The remaining three were in a more difficult situation. Being farther away from the safe area than Shu Keyi, their characters weren't able to escape so quickly. All of them were running away and dodging for their lives!

Interrupt Death's Door!

This was the first thing that popped into Shu Keyi's mind. However, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestation Umbrella being wide open like that was rather discouraging. Shu Keyi tried moving around to adjust Lower Your Head's attack angle, but unfortunately, this wasn't something that could be done in an instant. If she moved left, she would be blocked by the Half Moon Rock. If she moved right, she would be inside Death's Door's range, and she obviously couldn't force her way into there. And if she circled around, by the time she got into position, Death's Door would already be over.

Helpless, Shu Keyi discovered that while she had escaped, there was nothing she could do.

This...　

This had to be planned!　

Being able to escape so easily yet unable to attack Windward Formation, Shu Keyi felt like this wasn't luck. This was the enemy team fully utilizing the map and their skills to meticulously squeeze the amount of space available to maneuver.

Li Hua, the second to escape from Death's Door, was in an even more awkward position. He wanted to hurry and break Windward Formation's spell, but he was suddenly in the same predicament as Shu Keyi.　　

They could only watch as their teammates struggled to escape from Death's Door, while they seemed to be stuck in a crack, unable to move even a single step.

Even if I can't interrupt him, I can't just do nothing!

Li Hua's Dark Forest shot to the left and leapt onto Half Moon Rock.

The Number One Ninja's ninjato skills were undoubtedly extremely high. Watching Dark Forest's agility, quickness, and fluidity was a sight to enjoy. The crowd couldn't help but wish that there was no top to reach.

Happy wished for that too, but unfortunately, that wasn't reality. Dark Forest quickly scaled Half Moon Rock, heading towards Dancing Rain.

Facing melee attacks, Dancing Rain could not forcefully take the hits like before. After all, she was a Launcher, a long-ranged class. If the harassment was enough to mess up her aim, then it was equivalent to her being suppressed.

Su Mucheng immediately used Aerial Fire, and Dancing Rain jumped off of Half Moon Rock. Li Hua didn't stop to rest. Dark Forest jumped in midair, attacking Dancing Rain with Flickering Pursuit. But just before he did this, he threw a Shuriken. His target, Windward Formation!

Jumping over the Half Moon Rock, Li Hua found an angle at which he could avoid the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's shield and directly attack Windward Formation.

"Beautiful! Too beautiful!" the commentator, Pan Lin, yelled in admiration.

"Yes, outstanding," Li Yibo followed up. Of course, he had to expound on it. "Happy's tactical formation is quite remarkable. The two who escaped from Death's Door were stuck between Half Moon Rock and Death's Door, unable to interrupt Windward Formation's cast. Unfortunately, they ignored a point. For Li Hua's Dark Forest, Half Moon Rock can't be considered a cover. Even though it required a bit more time, Li Hua was able to successfully break through!"

"A brilliant play," Pan Lin continued to give praise.

As the two praised, the Body Pathway Derangement struck Dancing Rain multiple times, and that Shuriken was more than enough. While it's true that Lord Grim could turn his umbrella around and block it, an opening at the front would appear, and the three escaping from Death's Door definitely wouldn't miss such an opportunity.

Death's Door, interrupted!

Fortunately, this was Happy's home stadium. If not, the cheers and applause from the crowd would have shaken the stadium. The commentators, Pan Lin and Li Yibo, continued to praise Li Hua. As for Li Hua, he discovered that below, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was running back, waiting for him. Soft Mist, who was hiding behind Half Moon Rock, suddenly charged out, not towards his Dark Forest, but away from the Half Moon Rock.

Li Hua turned around. To Dark Forest's back was Half Moon Rock. He was completely cut off. He had no idea what the situation behind him was.

Li Hua was startled. Seeing Lord Grim, who had been ready for him, he realized that he had made a mistake.　

He had been lured away from his team, and with how the enemy team was prepared for him, they didn't seem to be planning on letting him go back so easily.

This was the enemy team's true goal.

Li Hua understood now. He knew that the effect of him leaving the group was extremely large. Misty Rain's tactics revolved around him. Their team composition consisted of mainly long-ranged classes. Without him filling in the gap, their tactics were useless.　

Shit...

Li Hua looked at Lord Grim, who didn't wait for Dark Forest to land before starting his attacks.

I have to hurry up and get away. Li Hua thought to himself. Then, he heard a crackle as Dark Forest was suddenly lit on fire.　　

Sacred Fire?

Li Hua watched in astonishment as his skill icons turned gray.

He hadn't seen any indication of the fire. This meant that the other side had precisely calculated Dark Forest's fall speed. The instant Sacred Fire burned, Dark Forest would land directly into it.

What type of calculative ability and mastery of timing is this?

Li Hua turned his gaze toward the rear of Half Moon Rock at the Cleric, who had always been viewed as weak.

Chapter 1216: Dark Forest Rock Climbing

This Sacred Fire sealed all of Dark Forest's skills, while simultaneously gluing the mouths of Pan Lin and Li Yibo shut.

Just a second ago, they had been wantonly praising Li Hua's brilliant play, and now the two suddenly stopped talking.　　

If the two failed to realize Happy's tactical arrangements by now, the two weren't qualified to be professionals. Their awareness towards the situation was more sensitive than the vast majority of people, but they got it wrong and were now in a difficult position.

The two looked at each other in the eye, too embarrassed to say anything.

Li Hua might have been the key to victory, but… he was the key to Happy's victory, not Misty Rain's. He had fallen into Happy's trap.

The effects of this trap quickly emerged.

Tang Rou's Soft Mist entered the fray and charged towards Team Misty Rain. Wei Chen's Windward Formation didn't flee either, attacking from the sides. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain bombarded them as well. These two were both using Screen Cannon tactics, coordinating with both sides, attacking here while also helping Ye Xiu over there.

Without Li Hua, the rest of Team Misty Rain was thrown into disorder. Although the three long-ranged classes had fierce offensive prowess, facing Soft Mist's unwavering push, their formation was forced to scatter. Their teamwork was having trouble flowing.

"The weaknesses in Misty Rain's tactics have been exposed…" Li Yibo began commentating. He directly jumped to the current situation as if his previous mistake in praising Li Hua weren't his words.　　

"Yeah…" Pan Lin followed along with Li Yibo's pace.

"Li Hua needs to hurry and get back to the others," Li Yibo said.

"But he's being pressed hard by Ye Xiu," Pan Lin said.

"Yes, he just lost to Ye Xiu in the individual competition. He doesn't have the mental advantage in a 1v1. What's more, Ye Xiu is also receiving assistance from Su Mucheng and Wei Chen," Li Yibo said.

"However, Ninjas have the advantage, if they're only looking to escape," Pan Lin said.

"That's true. However, since Happy had this planned out beforehand, then they should have countermeasures prepared. I think Ye Xiu is quite confident that he can force Li Hua to stay here," Li Yibo gradually started waving his banner towards Happy, stealthily reconstructing his image of having acute foresight.

As the two spoke, the Sacred Fire on Dark Forest wore off, but it hadn't been very long since he escaped from Death's Door. The Assassin skill, Shining Cut, could be used again, but his other escape skills such as Substitution Technique and Shadow Clone Technique were still on cooldown, and Li Hua didn't know whether he had the time to wait for them to refresh.

Lord Grim's offensive was ferocious. Su Mucheng and Wei Chen would also help from time to time. In fact, most of their attention was focused on this side. They were only coordinating with Tang Rou to help harass and restrain the other side.

I can't wait!

Li Hua quickly came to a conclusion.　　

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Li Hua used this skill regardless of the timing. In response, Lord Grim jumped away and blasted the ground.

Dark Forest tunneled to below Half Moon Rock. He had used this skill as an underground movement technique. Although the distance he moved wasn't far, it was enough for him to reach Half Moon Rock.

Li Hua leaped up and stabbed his ninjato into the rock. Dark Forest began quickly scaling Half Moon rock.

Bang bang bang! Boom boom boom!　

The gunfire behind him echoed. Lord Grim chased after him with long-ranged attacks, and Dancing Rain had shifted her attention over too.

Li Hua could not just simply move upwards. His movements would be too predictable. As a result, Dark Forest leapt left and right on Half Moon Rock, adding in many irregular horizontal movements as he climbed to make it harder for the enemy side to catch him.

Li Hua prayed that he played well. At this moment, Lord Grim dashed to below Half Moon Rock and jumped up.

"Wah…"

"Ooh.."

"Woah…"

The crowd made all sorts of astonished noises.

Lord Grim leaped up and took out a knife… the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella also had a ninjato form. Their skilled climbing made the crowd curious: Li Hua or Ye Xiu, who was faster?

In this situation, Ye Xiu was obviously faster because he had no obstructions. He could simply move upwards in a straight line. On the other hand, Li Hua needed to dodge attacks and add in horizontal movements. And because Dancing Rain's attacks were AoE, his horizontal movements had to be fairly large, further increasing the amount of distance Dark Forest needed to move.

In practically the blink of an eye, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim reached Dark Forest's height.

Li Hua's heart froze. Today, his heart kept freezing. His heart was going to be frozen stiff at this rate.

He could only clench his teeth and persevere through. He started moving horizontally even more, but because he had to dodge Lord Grim, his movements were much easier to predict for Su Mucheng. As a result, Li Hua had no choice but to start making circular movements. He clearly wanted to get over Half Moon Rock as fast as possible, but in order to do so, he needed to climb downwards from time to time.

Li Hua wanted to cry, but a short moment later, he suddenly realized that at this rate, he could just circle over the Half Moon Rock from the side...

Being forced to do this was quite tragic, but it was a feasible solution!

Li Hua continued to work hard at it. Suddenly, he heard a motor sound from behind him. He turned around to look and saw Lord Grim flying over with Rotor Wings.

"Fuck!"

The usually gentle and quiet Li Hua cursed loudly. He was truly under a lot of pressure.

Lord Grim flew in front of him and stabbed a ninjato into the Half Moon Rock.

Attack him!!!

A loud voice called out to him in his heart. It wanted him to attack this nearby, irksome presence, but his reason stopped him.

Go reunite with your teammates, an even stronger voice called out to him.

It was like there was a devil and an angel in his mind scuffling**! But the winner was quickly decided.

Dark Forest climbed up, but Lord Grim also leapt up, directly towards Dark Forest.

Dark Forest spun around his ninjato, dodging Lord Grim. He stepped on his ninjato and was just about to jump up, when Lord Grim's umbrella turned into a spear. Lord Grim dropped down as his evil spear stabbed upwards...

In the end, Dark Forest was unable to escape from the spear. All sorts of applause, laughs, and butt related words poured out from the crowd.

Circle Swing!

Lord Grim threw Dark Forest in a circle, smashing him into Half Moon Rock. Then, because of his position, Lord Grim stepped on Dark Forest, forcing him down as he moved up.

"Does that do damage?" The crowd was curious to why Lord Grim stepped on him.　　

"He's still attacking!" Someone discovered that as Lord Grim stepped on Dark Forest, he was also jabbing jabbing jabbing with his spear. His target was, of course, Dark Forest's head.

Dark Forest dropped to the ground with a face covered in blood.

Beaten up… Dark Forest failed to make it over the wall and was now being beat up violently. However, this tussle helped win him some time. Li Hua was now confident that he could wait for his escape skills to come off cooldown.

The east side darkens, the west side brightens, close a door, another door opens, Li Hua heard comforting thoughts from his heart.

Rock climbing really is a good way to stay alive! Li Hua thought to himself. He even wanted to climb some more, but Ye Xiu wasn't going to give him the same opportunity twice. This time, he attacked even tighter.

Li Hua kept trying. Chu Yunxiu and the others obviously weren't going to wait for Li Hua and do nothing. They were also trying to rush over, but Soft Mist was standing in their way. It really was difficult for these long-ranged classes to break through. After several unsuccessful attempts, Chu Yunxiu decided to have everyone split up and take a roundabout route.

The four from Misty Rain started spreading out and circled around Soft Mist. Tang Rou could only bite onto one person.

However, Tang Rou didn't target anyone. Her Soft Mist suddenly retreated.

"Not good…" Chu Yunxiu suddenly had a realization - she had made a mistake. By circling around, if they went too far away and Happy couldn't chase them, then...

Too late. Soft Mist's retreat was a signal. When Misty Rain shrunk back, Happy didn't pressure them. They also withdrew and then focused their efforts onto Dark Forest.

With Soft Mist returning, waving a spear in her hands, and Dancing Rain and Windward Formation pulling back to behind the Half Moon Rock, Li Hua's heart wasn't merely frozen. It was dead.

So those were the enemy's original intentions… I was too naive!

After wearing him down, they suddenly focused their attention onto him.

Ninjas weren't high-health high-defense classes to begin with. Once Dark Forest was caught up in their wave of attacks, he was quickly washed away. Chu Yunxiu and the others were hurrying over, and at this moment, they had just gotten past the Half Moon Rock.

Everything had been calculated perfectly.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist, the two melee characters, cut straight into Misty Rain's ranks and picked off their healer.

No matter how fierce the three ranged characters attacked, they had no way of forcing the two melee enemies apart. This was their weakness. Compared to melee classes, they lacked knockback and knockdown type skills.

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou ignored the attacks from the three ranged characters.

This… they're planning on trading!

Those with the knowledge could see it.

Happy had the numbers advantage, so they planned on sacrificing one of their characters for Misty Rain's healer. When one side had the numbers advantage, it was difficult for the other side to do anything about this type of trade.

Misty Rain was helpless...

By the time their sixth player arrived, this trade had already been completed. Lord Grim and Misty Rain's healer died.

Why Lord Grim?

If a trade was being forced to happen, then Misty Rain would obviously choose to trade for the bigger threat. In the entire Alliance, all nineteen teams would most likely choose Lord Grim in this situation.

But Happy's determination could be seen from this. If they were even willing to trade their strongest player, then they must be extremely confident towards what followed next.

In the end, Team Happy won the team competition.

10-0. Another 10-0. This was Happy's fourth 10-0 this season.

This was an achievement for a top powerhouse. However, top powerhouses being 10-0ed by other teams was very illogical.

Happy…

Chapter 1217: Voice Chat Rules

10 to 0, this result silenced all those who were hoping to see Happy capsize. Ruan Cheng of Esports Time had come to watch this match in person, but upon seeing this result, he skipped the post-match press conference entirely.

Happy's performance this match was indisputable. Their strategy in the team competition had been tailored to fight Misty Rain, and they were able to build their strategy around the unique features of the map in a beautiful manner. No matter how aggressive a reporter was, they couldn't find anything to criticize Happy with in this match. In the end, reporters had to follow logic. As of now, no one hated Happy enough to attack them out of nowhere.

The press conference ended with a host of congratulations. With these ten points, Happy rose two places on the leaderboard. After twelve rounds, they were now in ninth place, only one step away from the playoff zone, and it was a step that couldn't be smaller, only one point.

Happy was closing in on the eighth place Void, who currently had 71 points. In the eleventh round, they had used their home advantage to defeat Tiny Herb 8 to 2, but in this round's away game they lost to Wind Howl 1 to 9..

A number of people were already looking forward to next round's match.

Round 13, Happy would play their away game against Conquering Clouds, which wasn't any unbeatable team. And Void, meanwhile, would be playing their home game against the team which Happy had just swept, Misty Rain.

If Void wanted to maintain their lead over Happy in the rankings, they needed to have a showing just as strong as Happy's was this round. And the just-finished Happy versus Misty Rain match had been a clear tactical guide in fighting Misty Rain. BOX-1, trapping Li Hua outside of Misty Rain's tactical maneuvers would cripple the team. But strategy was something that everyone knew. The important part was execution. Comparing Happy and Void's next respective opponents on paper, most people anticipated that Happy would surpass Void next round.

But Misty Rain wasn't the only team that Happy had managed to surpass.

After twelve rounds, the seventh place team was the team that had previously been swept by Happy, Hundred Blossoms. They now led Happy by only 3 points. If these two teams had the same points score, Happy would rank above them by virtue of their prior victory. In round 13, Hundred Blossoms would be facing a strong team too, Wind Howl. If they didn't make good use of their home field advantage, it was likely that Happy would surpass both them and Wind Howl. Right now, Happy was accumulating points in a frightening manner.

In round 12, Samsara defeated Radiant 10 to 0, preventing Happy from having the honor of being the only team to have four 10-0 wins. Samsara's performance was as strong as ever.

In addition, Tiny Herb, Tyranny, and Wind Howl all earned high-point victories. But Blue Rain, who had played their home game against Thunderclap this round, had earned a powerful 5 points in the individual competition and group arena, only to lose the team competition. In the battle between two Master Tacticians, this time Xiao Shiqin took the lead.

In the post-match press conference, Blue Rain's Yu Wenzhou took responsibility, but the reporters didn't give him too much blame. Because Yu Wenzhou hadn't made any mistake, he… it was only because his hand speed wasn't enough, he couldn't issue directions and battle at the same time. After all, against a team with a Master Tactician like Xiao Shiqin, the battle strategies were constantly evolving in complex ways. It wasn't enough to solely rely on team cohesiveness and strategic habits. There needed to be someone directing the team members so that they knew the tactical intentions. Yu Wenzhou's hand speed in the pro circle was indeed subpar, and in this match that required a high hand speed to give directions, he was truly powerless.

And in the post-match press conference, Yu Wenzhou could only helplessly offer these words: "The opponent was very smart, accurately pinpointing my weakness."

Typically, for the post-match press conference, the losing team would go first, followed by the winning team. But in this round, both teams tied with 5 points, so the away team went first, then the home team.

When Yu Wenzhou made this statement, Thunderclap was already preparing to leave, but later there was still a reporter who managed to chase down Thunderclap's Captain Xiao Shiqin. Xiao Shiqin personally confirmed that in this round, Thunderclap's strategy was to increase the variability of their fighting, with the intent of forcing Blue Rain into making adjustments. Thunderclap would attack the flaws that appeared when Blue Rain couldn't adjust fast enough, or the flaws revealed by individual people…

Use complex and variable tactics and put greater pressure on Yu Wenzhou's slow hand speed.

Xiao Shiqin's targeted strategy sparked some controversy. Some people felt that this was just another way of attacking the opponent's weaknesses, and there was nothing wrong with that. But others felt that using tactics to create this effect was low-level and uninteresting. Strategy should display intellect and cleverness, and this sort of method changed that.

Thus, this reignited the calls to allow voice chat in matches. But as soon as those arguments surfaced, there were quickly others who said that if that happened, then trash talk would be spewed nonstop…

Immediately, everyone's first thought was of a certain other person on Team Blue Rain. His trash talk wasn't especially hurtful, but unrestricted voice chat would be ideal for him.

Once this person was mentioned, this person who had forced the Alliance to specially modify the rules of battle, those calls to open voice chat were weakened. But quickly, other people proposed, what if voice chat was opened just for members of the same team?

A team voice chat could only be used to give directions. There would be no way to launch trash talk attacks.

But there was no way to present this kind of voice chat in a broadcast. The sound of each team chat couldn't be simultaneously broadcast, and cutting back and forth between the two would be unpleasant to listen to. The Alliance had always used text chat up until now so that they could show the teams' communications to the audience, and this was also a reason why they never used voice chat in competition.

However, typing instead of focusing solely on putting in combat inputs weakened the intensity of the competition.

At this point, these arguments started surfacing as well. After all, the debate over voice chat had been ongoing for a very long time now. This Blue Rain versus Thunderclap match just showed another problem caused by the lack of voice chat.

Yu Wenzhou was able to survive in the Glory Alliance through his unique methods. The Alliance, for its part, hoped to see competitors of all types. But now, the existence of players like Yu Wenzhou was being strangled.

With Thunderclap's battle results, did that mean that in the future, all teams would use these complex, changing battle strategies to face Blue Rain? After all, this wasn't something that only a Master Tactician could do. Even tactical duels were becoming competitions of hand speed. Was there any intelligence in pro matches anymore?

There were more and more angles of questioning, and the issue rose from just Yu Wenzhou to extend to all of the various teams' shot callers. Without voice chat, they were forced to input extra keyboard controls. This wasn't like trash talking, where if you didn't want to say anything you could just not say anything. Issuing orders was a matter of victory or defeat, something that absolutely had to be done. Because of the rule preventing voice chat, they bore a greater burden upon their hands. It was unfair to these players.

The players that directed strategies needed intelligence. But because of the competition rules, hand speed became a factor, even though it shouldn't have anything to do with tactics. It was completely unreasonable!

The voices of doubt became stronger and stronger, and so the Alliance finally made an official response, saying that they would begin discussion and investigation into the issue of voice chat.

Hearing the Alliance's solemn recognition, many people calmed down. With the calm, the sounds of complaints and mockery quickly came as well. It wasn't long before many people pointed out that, if the Alliance changed the rules again because of this, then Blue Rain would have two people who forced the Alliance to change the rules. Blue Rain didn't acknowledge this interesting fact, but regarding the opening of strategic voice chat, Team Blue Rain was in clear support.

The Alliance needed to do research, so there was no way for a result to appear in a short period of time.

Soon, it was November 29th, Round 13.

Happy played their away game at Conquering Clouds, and didn't disappoint their supporters.

9 to 1, Happy won, Ye Xiu's individual win streak was now up to 12. The 1 point they lost this round was from Su Mucheng's mistake in the individual competition.

And after this round, Happy finally stepped into the playoff zone. Void, who had previously been one place above them, had also done quite well this round, defeating Misty Rain in their home game 8 to 2. It was clear that they had learned from Happy's strategy against Misty Rain in the team competition, causing Misty Rain to eat a big loss in their two consecutive away games.

Happy earned 9 points, Void earned 8, so the one point difference between the two teams was erased. As it happened, both Happy (Xingxin) and Void (Xukong) started with the letter X in their pinyin names, so the next step was to compare order of appearance in the dictionary, in which Happy took the lead.

But at this point people had already realized, in the upcoming Round 14, Happy and Void would be directly facing off against each other.

Hundred Blossoms, who were within range of catching up to Happy, had also done fairly well this round, winning 7 to 3 in their home game against Wind Howl. For now, they still led Happy by one point. And Wind Howl continued their path of ups and downs, some people even summarizing their performance as "home game dragons, away game bears."

But for now, this conclusion was a bit reckless. People mostly paid attention to Wind Howl's away game loss to 301, but 301 wasn't any weak team, and it shouldn't be shocking that they could win their own home game. Right now, 301 was in tenth place with 76 points, only 3 points behind Happy and Void. Next round was Happy and Void's battle, so it was very possible that it would be 301 who would surpass them both and make it to the playoff zone.

Wind Howl wasn't so terrible, but their current slippage was undeniable truth. They had now fallen to sixth place, surpassed by Tyranny.

Tyranny, Samsara, and Happy were the three teams that had won 9 to 1 this round. Blue Rain and Tiny Herb had lost their away games 4 to 6.

Blue Rain had lost to Royal Style, and their loss in the team competition once again caused people to pay attention to the issue of voice chat. This battle, Royal Style had definitely learned from Thunderclap and used lively and variable strategies. But over the course of the battle, Blue Rain's loss this time wasn't because of Yu Wenzhou's hand speed. Blue Rain's players didn't need their captain's reminders to respond every time they encountered the slightest change. Master Tacticians were known as such because even if they followed the same general rules for strategies, their tactics would be more complete and effective.

Blue Rain lost to Royal Style, but Tiny Herb lost to Thunderclap.

After losing many points in the individual battles, Thunderclap once again made a comeback in the team competition. Their record in the team battles was as tyrannical as Ye Xiu's in the individual battles. Right now, they had 12 wins and 1 loss; the only difference from Ye Xiu was that their wins weren't consecutive.

Chapter 1218: All-Star Voting

Thunderclap's strength in the team competition guaranteed their strong showing on the rankings. Right now, they were tied with Blue Rain with 90 points. Because the two had tied in their match against each other, their ranking was determined by alphabet, with Blue Rain (Lanyu) in second place and Thunderclap (Leiting) in third.

Samsara led the pack with 113 points, a score so high that people had already lost the desire to try and catch up.

After 13 rounds of competition, they entered the month of December. The yearly voting for All-Stars began with the new season and ended in December.

The earliest votes cast were based on the players' performances last season; the strong players in last season's playoffs would gain favor. Then, after entering the rhythm of the new season, one or two stunning plays could invite a lot of votes. Tang Rou was a perfect example of this.

A rookie who had just entered the Alliance, after an exciting 1v2 in the second round, was swiftly pushed into the ranks of the All-Stars. Of course, her beautiful appearance contributed to this as well.

However, after the 1v3 incident and her clear revocation of her word, Tang Rou's popularity instantly died down. Even many of the team's fans couldn't look at her anymore, how much support would she have left from everyone else? Instantly, Tang Rou's name went from daily rising in the All-Star voting to complete erasure.

And right now, the highest-ranked player was still Zhou Zekai. Last season, the team had won in the playoffs, this season they maintained a powerful lead, and Zhou Zekai's performance was indispensable. He led the rankings with no competition.

And compared to last year, the biggest change on the leaderboard was the return of a few names, the most significant of which were the ones who had gone to Excellent Era last season. These three all had their dedicated fans and were immediately pushed onto the leaderboard. Aside from the unwavering support of their loyal fans, there was the effect of their performances this season.

Xiao Shiqin was the most eye-catching of these three. Everyone knew Xiao Shiqin's major contributions to Thunderclap's shocking accomplishments this season. Although Xiao Shiqin wasn't like Zhou Zekai or Sun Xiang, who were core players based on their technical skill, Thunderclap's outstanding performance allowed Xiao Shiqin's tactical skill to shine and draw attention, attracting scores of fans. Right now, on the All-Star voting leaderboard, Xiao Shiqin was in third place, much better than his rankings in previous seasons.

Su Mucheng and Sun Xiang were both ranked around tenth. With their fanbase support and their performance, they hadn't seen any big ups or downs.

But if you wanted to name someone who was only rising more and more rapidly, you'd have to say another returning name - no, strictly speaking, the name wasn't returning. What was returning was the person.

Ye Xiu. Never mind his accumulated popularity from previous years, just looking at his ongoing twelve consecutive individual win record, this kind of player would gain enough attention to be pushed onto the rankings. As he achieved wins round after round, the ballots cast for Ye Xiu only increased. Happy's recent strong performance gave him a boost as well. Right now, Ye Xiu was at number 6 and was still in the process of beautifully rushing upward.

One could see how influential he was just from the recent in-game interest in unspecialized. It got to the point where the Glory developers added a strong reminder in-game, notifying the players who didn't choose a class at level 20 just how difficult their existence thereafter would be. Without naming names, they reminded everyone not to try and imitate a certain person because this certain person was an exceptional player with exceptional talent and an exceptional self-made weapon.

Despite this, the enthusiasm of the players couldn't be stopped. Quite a few players started playing with the equipment editor to try and make a Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, which suddenly caused the prices of level 5 equipment materials to rise.

With some people returning to the leaderboard, others would of course be pushed down.

There was one such person in Happy. Fang Rui changed classes, which his former Thief supporters couldn't accept. The players of his new class, Qi Master, even though they saw that Fang Rui held the All-Star Qi Master Boundless Sea, his Qi Master performance… to be honest, up through now there was still nothing very convincing about it. As for his recent crawling and rolling Qi Master style, a number of Qi Master players felt that it was disgusting, and it didn't inspire any imitations.

Also kicked off the leaderboard was Hundred Blossoms' Zou Yuan. He had been pushed onto the All-Star leaderboard through nostalgia for two years in a row. But now that he was finally gradually bringing out a new character, he was shoved downward by the fierceness of the competition. Unfortunately, he was helpless about this.

Another player squeezed off the rankings was Royal Style's Tian Sen.

Peaceful Hermit, this former pinnacle God-level character. Ever since the All-Stars began, this character had made it to the leaderboard no matter the controller. But finally, because of the team's slipping performance through the years, he vanished for the first time from the top 20.

Regarding this, Peaceful Hermit's current user Tian Sen was extremely helpless. Year after year of hard work, but the team still saw no improvement and hovered at the middle. Now that there were more and more challengers, they were finally kicked off the altar.

Tian Sen and Peaceful Hermit's fall conjured many sighs.

There was another old general pushed off the leaderboard, Tyranny's Lin Jingyan. This old, long-time All-Star finally had his position stolen away.

Tyranny's near-miss of the championship last season had originally garnered much sympathy, and at the start of this season, the ballots for Tyranny's players surged upward. But, after that wave passed, their performance in this new season was factored in. Tyranny was rotating their roster for these matches, and the old veterans, no longer having regular appearances, began to slow in the rankings. The position of Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing was still relatively stable, while Lin Jingyan had dropped off the rankings. There was Zhang Jiale too, currently at a precarious 23rd place, at high risk of being replaced over the course of December. Just off of the votes, the rankings for many players were very close. A single explosive performance could bring enough ballots to surpass him.

But overall, the changes to the rankings couldn't be called large.

Xiao Shiqin, Su Mucheng, Sun Xiang, and Ye Xiu's returns weren't any surprise. Compared to last year's Lu Hanwen and Gao Yingjie entering the rankings as rookies, this season, there was no such entirely new blood breaking into the rankings. Tang Rou originally had this potential with her explosive performance in the second round and her steadiness thereafter. She was a very strong rookie. But unfortunately, after that 1v3 incident destroyed her reputation, she naturally didn't have much chance in this kind of popolarity voting.

Right now, the one who was in more of a dilemma was the Alliance. The All-Star voting was just for excitement; a good performance onstage could increase votes, but in the end, that wasn't the only determining factor. However, the Alliance's yearly awards were entirely based on the players' real performance onstage, based on numbers and statistics.

And from the statistics, among this season's rookies, Tang Rou faced no competition. But when they thought about giving the "Best Newcomer" award to this player with a ruined reputation, the Alliance felt the pressure would be extremely large. Right now, there was still over half a season to go before these awards were given, but there were already people worrying about this issue, which was a sign of just how outstanding Tang Rou was right now among the rookies.

December was the last month for voting the All-Stars, and looking at the current ballot counts, no final judgment could be made based off the rankings as they entered December. Because more and more players would save all of their tickets until December, waiting until the voting was just about to close so that they could see the entirety of the players' performances before casting their votes.

Would December see any player powerfully slaughtering their way onto the leaderboard? This was something to watch when the league reached December. Before, there was also something else to watch in December, the winter transfer window. At that time, the Alliance didn't have as many teams, so when they began in September, the season would be halfway over the time it was December. That was the original reason for why they set the winter transfers in December. But now, the season often wasn't even half over by January. After discussing this for several seasons, in Season 10, the Alliance finally decided to move the winter transfer window to January.

In comparison, the Glory new server opening now had almost no effect on the pro teams. The only ones who were busy were the guild workers of the various large clubs, who before December would have to prepare their strength to enter the new server to compete for resources and advertise for the club.

Happy now already had its own official guild department. After half a year of development, the personnel organization was already finalized. And to a new guild like Happy, the opening of this new server was beyond important. In the old servers or in the Heavenly Domain, Happy was constantly playing catch-up, but in a new server, everyone was starting at zero, so they had a greater chance at achieving an advantage.

After Wu Chen organized the work for the new server, he solemnly gave Chen Guo the list of people who would be expanding in the new server. Boss Chen was generous, knowing how crucial the work in the new server was, gave the new server employees additional bonuses with a flourish of her pen.

As of now, the guild department was relatively well-developed, and Happy's R&D department had expanded slightly. Finding technical researchers was difficult, but didn't all of the big teams have to deal with this? The R&D would sometimes experience changes of personnel, and sometimes people would leave their jobs.

When Chen Guo failed to find enough suitable R&D candidates, she started paying particularly close attention to this area, and her efforts weren't wasted. In November, there was a small adjustment at Thunderclap, and an R&D researcher left his job for personal reasons. Chen Guo instantly pounced on him, but this person's personal reason was that he wanted to return to his home city to work, and his home city unfortunately was not City H. Chen Guo had no way of satisfying that requirement, and so she could only watch with her eyes wide open as this rather skilled R&D researcher returned to his home City K and entered Hundred Blossoms.

The second time, it was Royal Style whose personnel was changing, with two R&D researchers leaving one after the other. Chen Guo made some inquiries, and after confirming that it wasn't for a reason like "returning home" that they had no way of satisfying, she approached them in-person in City B.

This time, Chen Guo's actions were truly swift and fierce. Heavenly Swords was in the same city as Royal Style, but by the time they began to approach them, one of them had already reached an agreement and signed with Chen Guo. With one of them already taken, Lou Guanning of course couldn't try and pull some evil trickery, but the remaining one didn't want to live modestly with Happy and cleanly slammed down a checkbook. After Chen Guo knew, she didn't have any words. Being able to get one researcher was good enough, and she could only hope that the person they got wouldn't have any regrets after learning that he'd missed the opportunity to enjoy the riches of Heavenly Swords.

Although from the looks of it, this new R&D researcher who had now been at Happy for ten days, Wang Sen, seemed quite at ease.

Chapter 1219: Lord Grim's Counter

December 6th. Glory Professional Alliance Season 10 Round 14. Team Happy greeting the visiting challengers Team Void.

This was a confrontation between two direct competitors. In Round 12, it was because of this reason that the Happy versus Misty Rain match had been chosen to be broadcast. However, this time, the broadcast chose Wind Howl versus Thunderclap. Reportedly, when the internal esports broadcast team had their meeting, the commentator Pan Lin expressed his opposition towards broadcasting Happy's match. Pan Lin's partner, Li Yibo, also had the same opinion.

This reasoning was very pompous, but even though Pan Lin hadn't explicitly stated the true reason, everyone knew what it was. Wasn't it because they were afraid of being slapped in the faces again after misreading the situation in another Happy match?

But then again, Team Thunderclap's tactics were top-tier too! Just take that round where the complex and changing tactics forced Yu Wenzhou to make such a statement. Could these two partners see through that? In the post-match interviews, those experienced Glory reporters hadn't noticed it. They hadn't noticed it until Yu Wenzhou's grudging comment. Only then did they ask Xiao Shiqin for verification.

The level of the commentators need to improve...

Constantly getting slapped in the face was embarrassing for the broadcast team too, but there was no one better to choose. After all, to be a commentator and guest duo, just having knowledge wasn't enough, the two needed to be compatible. Commentating required speaking eloquently at an appropriate pace. Zhou Zekai and Huang Shaotian were extremely skilled players with far more knowledge of the game than Pan Lin and Li Yibo, but could those two become a commentator duo? Could they? Could they?

Compatibility was the most important.

Right now, Pan Lin and Li Yibo formed their best commentator duo.

As a result, the Happy versus Void match was not chosen to be broadcast.

Team Void's core still revolved around their Ghostblade duo. Their new rookie last season, the Exorcist Ge Caijie, cemented his position even further, becoming the two Ghostblades' most reliable partner. As for Team Void, the team put in great efforts to upgrade Ge Caijie's Exorcist character, Blue Exorcist.

When Team Void heard that Team Royal Style was shifting around their characters and that people from their R&D department had left, Team Void had been very excited. Team Royal Style may have only been a mid-tier team, but their R&D department was at the forefront of all things related to Exorcists. Their Peaceful Hermit did not have the votes to make it into this season's All-Stars at the moment, but his lack of votes was mainly because of the team's poor win record. In terms of raw stats, Peaceful Hermit still stood as the King of Exorcists.

Team Void wasn't heroic enough to directly purchase Peaceful Hermit, but hiring two experienced members from their R&D team would be excellent too.

But when Void made their move, they were stunned when they learned that one of the two R&D team members had already gone to Happy and the other to Heavenly Swords. Void had been just one beat too slow, missing this opportunity for two long-awaited helpers. With their cheeks were streaked with tears, they could only rely on their current R&D team to continue developing their Exorcist.

Their Blue Exorcist was a bit weak, but their player Ge Caijie didn't complain. In the current state of the Alliance, where rookies nowadays were fickle and demanding, this was a rare sight. Ge Caijie had a maturity and composure that exceeded his young age.

In the first round of the individual competition, Void sent out this second-year rookie. His win record this season in the individual competition was exceptional. Out of 12 matches, he had 10 wins and 2 losses.

If it weren't for Ye Xiu's 12 consecutive wins, Ge Caijie would have been the player with the highest win rate. In this match, the number one and number two in 1v1s would be clashing. The match was filled with topics to talk about as soon as it began. In comparison, the opening for the Thunderclap versus Wind Howl game was very ordinary and dull. Team Thunderclap didn't have anyone too noteworthy for their individual competitions.

"Senior, I hope to learn from you." The respectful Ge Caijie didn't forget his manners.

"Mm, let's see who'll be the one to change up our win rates," Ye Xiu replied. It could be seen from his words that he had paid quite a bit of attention to this rookie. He at least knew that in 1v1s, Ge Caijie was second only to himself.

The countdown finished, and the two characters loaded into the map.

Happy's home game. Ye Xiu's choice of maps was in the same style as always. The two characters didn't dally around and directly headed towards the center of the map.

Lord Grim used long-ranged attacks to initiate. Ge Caijie's Blue Exorcist evaded them, while swinging his arms, throwing the scythe in his hands.

It was just an ordinary Spirit Guidance without any additional talismans, clearly meant as a probing attack. Ge Caijie didn't let down those who praised his steadiness. He didn't immediately rush in to take the initiative. Although it was unanimously held that the Exorcist was the counter of the unspecialized, what happened when Royal Style faced Happy? Tian Sen impatiently had Peaceful Hermit set out to fulfill his mission as Lord Grim's counter, and the match ended with Royal Style losing to Happy 1 to 9. The two didn't face each other in the individual competition, and in the team competition, Peaceful Hermit seemed to be the ill-fated one and was the first to be killed.

Exorcists were only counters in theory. To prove this theory, real results were necessary. Ge Caijie believed that Ye Xiu was more familiar than anyone else about why Exorcists were considered Lord Grim's bane. There was no way Ye Xiu would not be on guard. Before Ge Caijie began, as the one widely considered as a counter to his opponent, he had to be ready to face an opponent who was at his 120%.

Lord Grim easily dodged the Spirit Guidance scythe, but Ge Caijie immediately used Spirit Guidance again, having the scythe return to him and attack Lord Grim from behind. Lord Grim didn't even look back before being sliced into smoke.

Shadow Clone Technique!

The real body flickered to a position several units forward. Along with an arc of cold light, Lord Grim instantly arrived in front of him with a Shining Cut.

Blue Exorcist had just thrown out the weapon in his hands with Spirit Guidance, so he couldn't even parry it with an attack of his own. However, Exorcists were a class that didn't need their weapon to utilize their skills. He pinched with his hands, and a talisman appeared, letting out thin strands of cold qi. Blue Exorcist jumped back while pressing the talisman towards Lord Grim.

Ice Talisman was an ice element skill with freeze effects. This skill could not be ignored. Lord Grim, who had been pressing forward fiercely, had no choice but to retreat.

The Ice Talisman failed to hit its target and shattered into fine pieces. Blue Exorcist pinched his hands again, and a new talisman appeared.

Fire Talisman!

Fire after ice. Blue Exorcist didn't leave any gaps between his two talisman attacks. His rhythm and skill linking was immaculate.

Retreat again?

Impossible. Ye Xiu hadn't forgotten about the scythe flying back. Dodging to left seemed to be the most logical course of action, but… if he did that, Blue Exorcist would simply conjure another talisman and throw it there, forcing him into a position with nowhere to run.

As a result, Ye Xiu chose to continue pressing forward!

Colliding Stab!

Lord Grim used a Berserker skill to quickly cover some distance. The Fire Talisman wasn't like the Ice Talisman. Forcefully taking the hit was bearable. Ge Caijie clearly wasn't prepared for Ye Xiu's choice of action. Lord Grim stabbed Blue Exorcist and continued forward, pushing them away from the returning scythe. Then, he rolled to the right.

Boom!

Lord Grim was struck by the Fire Talisman and his body was set ablaze, taking damage over time.

The scythe returned to Blue Exorcist's hands. All Ye Xiu got was damage from Colliding Stab, which wasn't as heavy as the damage from Fire Talisman. It was better than nothing though.　

Sky Strike!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella changed forms and slashed upwards.

Ge Caijie's heart jumped, but not much. He placed the scythe in front of him and blocked the Sky Strike. Then, he pushed out and threw a Lightning Talisman.

Lord Grim jumped back to dodge it. Blue Exorcist swiped with his scythe, and a blue light rose from the ground. A Rising Emblem threw Lord Grim into the air.

Boom!

Lord Grim quickly adjusted himself while in the air and fired an Anti-Tank Missile at Blue Exorcist. Blue Exorcist was just about to follow up, but was forced to back away. Lord Grim relied on the recoil from it to shoot back and threw a grenade at the same time.

After several quick exchanges, neither side had lost much health or won any big advantages. Compared to normal, being able to fight evenly with Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was very rare. But now, many people had higher expectations of Ge Caijie.

Exorcists were considered to be counters to Lord Grim because of their new Level 75 skill. However, Ge Caijie had yet to use it.

Was he waiting for a more opportune moment?

Everyone understood the logic, but they weren't as patient as Ge Caijie. They wanted Blue Exorcist to hurry up and use it.

How could finding an opportunity be so easy though? A careless usage wouldn't get the desired effects. It would just be wasting the skill, and Ge Caijie would no longer have the threat of it anymore. And Ge Caijie could clearly sense that Ye Xiu was being very wary of this skill. Some of his decisions carried this sort of vigilance. The might of a counter could already be seen! It wasn't just as simple as using a powerful skill to make the opponent kneel.

"You really have patience!" Even Ye Xiu couldn't help but sigh.

"I'm looking for an opportunity." It seemed like Ge Caijie also couldn't resist chatting.

"There won't be any," Ye Xiu said.

"No one can be certain of that," Ge Caijie said.

When he said these words, Blue Exorcist's scythe swept up and then down, while his other hand readied another talisman. Not to Ge Caijie's surprise, Ye Xiu didn't dare use something as simple as parrying to defend. Lord Grim jumped back.

Spirit Guidance!

The scythe that was swinging down suddenly flew out from his hands. Lord Grim hadn't jumped far back enough.

But Ye Xiu was able to pull some distance away. At this moment, he seemed quite relaxed. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up, ready to shield against the attack. The instant the two weapons were about to clash, Ye Xiu noticed Blue Exorcist's left hand quickly touching the scythe.

Not good!

Ye Xiu knew the situation wasn't good, but it was too late to make a different move. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and the scythe collided. Talisman energy swiftly moved up the scythe handle, linking the two weapons together. The energy moved through the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. When the light suddenly blossomed, a faint "封" (Seal) character could be seen.

Exorcist Level 75 skill: Seal Talisman.

Effect: Seal the targeted equipment for one minute.

Chapter 1220: Title is Spoiler

The Seal Talisman had no damaging effect, but it brought this one minute of status effect.

What did one minute mean in Glory?

A 1v1 duel where one side was much stronger than the other would generally end within one minute. When the two sides were relatively evenly matched, then it would depend on the players' individual habits and styles, so time duration wasn't a good statistic to keep track of. Still, assuming the characters met in direct confrontation, it would usually take over 3 minutes to determine victory.

Ye Xiu, in his individual matches, typically played with this kind of rhythm, and this match with Ge Caijie was the same. After they had each tested the waters, the two of them began fierce combat.

Talismans were the Exorcist's unique method of combat. They either directly used the talisman to attack, or they would attach the talisman onto their weapon, causing the weapon to have certain damage bonuses or effects based on the talisman. In fact, they could attach the talisman to the weapon and then use Spirit Guidance to throw away their weapon, turning it into a long-range talisman attack.

Just now, Ge Caijie had, at the very last moment, suddenly slapped a talisman onto his scythe, causing his attack to have a talisman effect. But whether it was ice or fire, Lord Grim had successfully parried and the attack hadn't landed, so the talisman couldn't have dealt any damage. But the talisman that Ge Caijie had used was the Seal Talisman.

The Seal Talisman was used on equipment. With this attack, Lord Grim's parry actually sent to Ge Caijie the target he wished to attack.

It all sounded very simple.

However, when the Spirit Guided scythe shot out toward the opponent's parry, he had to activate the talisman in the instant just before they made contact. The difficulty of such control was extraordinary.

Ye Xiu was hit. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was sealed and was now unusable.

It was unusable, which meant that the equipment stats would be temporarily deducted from the character, as though the character hadn't equipped this equipment at all. And for the equipment that had special additional effects, these effects would also all be eliminated.

For now, sealing the weapon or sealing the shoes were viewed as the most worthwhile ways of using this skill.

Most of a character's attack power came from the weapon, and most of a character's movement speed came from the shoes. These two equipments, from ordinary players to the professional circle, were always prioritized, because they each decided a character's advantage in one particular attribute.

Sealing the weapon was like pulling out the opponent's fangs; sealing the shoes was like breaking the opponent's legs.

And now, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was sealed. For Lord Grim, it wasn't just a matter of pulling out his fangs. The shapeshifting ability of the umbrella, after being hit by the Seal Talisman, was also eliminated.

The Exorcist was said to be the counter to Lord Grim exactly because of this reason. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella's greatest characteristic could be eliminated by the Exorcist.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was the true source of the headache that the professional circle felt toward Ye Xiu and Lord Grim. And now, in front of Ge Caijie, this problem was eliminated. During this one minute, Lord Grim held in his hand an unchanging weapon that had no bonus attributes at all.

"Beautifully done!" Even Ye Xiu couldn't help but express his admiration of Ge Caijie's exciting action.

"Thank you," Ge Caijie answered, but his playing wasn't polite at all. He had to use this one minute properly. The Seal Talisman had a cooldown of 7 minutes, there was no way it could be used a second time in an individual battle. This was also why Ge Caijie had been so cautious in the beginning. He couldn't afford to waste this skill.

The scythe was swiftly swung down again, and his other hand was already preparing another talisman at the same time. This was the technique that any high-level Exorcist player should have; putting the talisman on the weapon first and then attacking was what an ordinary player would do. Pro players needed to begin their attack first, and only when they felt their attack was a sure hit would they suddenly attach a talisman. This way, they could conserve their talismans and also allow variation in their attacks.

The scythe flashed down, but there was already another flash before his eyes.

Sword Draw?

Ge Caijie had seen very clearly, when he had applied the seal, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was in sword form, and now it could only use sword-type skills.

However, without weapon attributes and just relying on the skill itself, whether the damage or the speed or the priority or so on, they would all decrease drastically. A skill like this could be completely ignored.

Shatter!

Blue Exorcist didn't even dodge. This Sword Draw, whether it hit another attack or it hit himself, it would break into shattered fragments of swordlight. It wasn't even worth defending against - without weapon attributes, it was too small and weak.

Ge Caijie was sure of this. But when the light of the sword hit his body, significantly faster than his own attack, Ge Caijie realized that something was wrong.

A sealed weapon essentially had an attack speed of zero. Even the famously quick Sword Draw shouldn't have this kind of speed now…

Ge Caijie had no time to think of anything - Blue Exorcist's body was already inadvertently thrust backward.

This was the momentum from the Sword Draw! But by Ge Caijie's calculations, in this situation, there was no way for the Sword Draw to have this kind of power…

Did he…

There was only one possibility!

Ge Caijie watched, eyes wide, as Lord Grim waved his hand and that Myriad Manifestations Umbrella smoothly shifted into spear form and a Dragon Tooth chased toward him.

How could this be?

Ge Caijie was utterly stunned. Unable to dodge this Dragon Tooth, he was hit.

"You don't need to be that surprised, do you?" Ye Xiu said. A Sky Strike leapt out, sending Blue Exorcist into the air.

But as expected of the most stable and calm player of the new generation, even when he was shocked, he quickly steadied his heart. The midair Blue Exorcist swiftly used a talisman and swung his scythe with Spirit Guidance.

Lightning Talisman!

When the scythe hit the ground carrying this talisman, lightning instantly flared around the scythe. Lord Grim had no way of continuing to attack Blue Exorcist from this position, he could only dodge first.

Blue Exorcist hit the ground, the Spirit Guided scythe had already returned to his hand. He turned and stared at Lord Grim over there, and more accurately, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella that was in Lord Grim's hand.

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, spear form.

"This… isn't the one from before…" Ge Caijie saw through what had happened.

"Yup. You guys throw around the word "counter" so much, if I didn't make any preparation, wouldn't that just be too dumb?" Ye Xiu chuckled.

"Two Myriad Manifestations Umbrellas…" Ge Caijie was a bit speechless. It wasn't that he hadn't thought of such a possibility before, but wasn't Happy relatively poor? This Silver weapon, even though the R&D departments of the various teams hadn't figured out how it was made, they all understood that this was definitely a high-cost item. A Silver weapon like this, with Happy's conditions and grassroots background, there was no way they could make a backup copy, was there? If they only made one to counter the Exorcist's Seal Talisman, that was rather wasteful. But on the other hand, even if the Seal Talisman hadn't managed to stop him, wouldn't this at least greatly increase the burden on Happy? To make an extra copy of such a high-cost weapon, who knew how many fewer Silver equipments the other characters now had? In that regard, this at least had some use in suppressing Happy.

Just as Ge Caijie was thinking all of this, he heard Ye Xiu speak. "Yup, two Myriad Manifestations Umbrellas, one level 70, one level 5."

Ge Caijie froze.

"Using a level 5 weapon to fight is really a struggle! So I was very anxious seeing you holding back for so long. Next time be more bold, come up and directly use a Seal Talisman, I'll let you stick it right on," Ye Xiu said.

With that, Ge Caijie could only laugh bitterly.

So this guy had just casually used a level 5 weapon to play around with him, this was really…

But was Ye Xiu always using the level 5 weapon earlier? Ge Caijie didn't believe it. A level 5 weapon, he definitely would have noticed that something was wrong with the damage dealt. So Ye Xiu, in reality, had secretly switched his equipment at some point, just like how later when he swapped back the real umbrella after the false one was sealed, which Ge Caijie hadn't noticed at all.

"It looks like this Seal Talisman being able to hit you was also an opening you purposely left," Ge Caijie said.

"Selling you an opening was just as difficult as finding an opening on you," Ye Xiu admitted.

"Since that's the case, then why…" Ge Caijie said.

"You'll know soon enough," Ye Xiu said, as Lord Grim charged forward.

Indeed, Ge Caijie knew soon enough.

He now knew just how much Ye Xiu had restrained himself when playing earlier, all because of the existence of the Seal Talisman. Ge Caijie now had regrets. If he just hadn't used the Seal Talisman and saved this threat as a deterrence, this battle might have been much easier! And no? The Seal Talisman was tossed out without achieving its effect, and an unrestrained Ye Xiu was truly too terrifying…

Ge Caijie parried for his life, but before him, even God-level players had fallen one after another to Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. Ge Caijie found that he couldn't do any better than them. He had only lasted earlier because of his class, because his class had a skill that the opponent feared.

The Exorcist was truly Lord Grim's counter, but in order to serve as a true counter, the skill had to be effective! When the skill didn't achieve its effect, the counter melted into scattered clouds. After all, this was an ultimate move that could only be used once in seven minutes.

"See, if I didn't make you use up that Seal Talisman, fighting you would've been so tiring!" As Ye Xiu spoke, Lord Grim had already sent the final attack.

"I understand…" Gai Caijie answered. Blue Exorcist, under an attack that couldn't be resisted, fell.

First battle of the individual round, Happy won. Ye Xiu had now won 13 consecutive individual battles.

Was he using this sort of method to announce his powerful return? Some people discussed this possibility.

But that was too cheap, wasn't it? What sort of top core player would play in the individual competition instead of the group arena? Some people thought this way.

It was true. Every team's best player, like Zhou Zekai, like Huang Shaotian, like Wang Jiexi, they all appeared in the group arena to try and win those greater 2 points. They might occasionally appear in the individual competition, but none of them would treat the individual competition as their main battleground like Ye Xiu did.

And so, just like this, he continued his win streak.

"This is the strong bullying the weak!" someone sighed, indignant.

The feelings were complex. Was this person a fan or a hater? If it was the strong bullying the weak, what did that make those powerful veterans whom Ye Xiu had defeated?

Chapter 1221: Lucky Steamed Bun

The crowd clapped!

The deep mind games and probing from both Ye Xiu and Ge Caijie weren't really understood too well by the crowd, but those who were sitting right spot noticed Lord Grim switching umbrella forms.

Truthfully, when they saw it, because the movement was too fast, the ones who saw it didn't really know what happened. Luckily, the two players in the match spoke to each other and revealed the important points in the match. As a result, when the reveal came out, quite a few crowd members suddenly remembered and yelled out excitedly, "I saw it! I saw it!"

They realized that the movement they saw was Lord Grim switching umbrella forms.　　

"I saw it once!"

"I saw it twice!"

"I saw it three times!"

"Four times!"

People started competing with each other, and it quickly got to the point where it just became empty shouting. Weapons couldn't be switched too often because there was a cooldown. The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's most important feature was that switching forms allowed it to bypass this issue. In this 1v1, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been switched out at least twice. He had used the Level 70 umbrella at the start of the match, used the Level 5 umbrella when he feigned an opening, and then switched back to the Level 70 one afterwards.

In any case, Ge Caijie lost the match. This was Happy's home stadium too, so the applause was thunderous. What's more, this was another strong opening, foretelling that Happy's momentum would continue tonight. After achieving a perfect win over Team Miracle in Round 9, who was the happiest about Happy's crazy winning streak? Happy's fans of course! The number of seats filled in Happy's home games increased round after round. More and more people were starting to seriously recognize Team Happy's strength.

10-0!

The crowd cheered for a 10-0. For a new team facing a frequent playoffs contender like Void to have shouts for a 10-0, Happy's position in the league nowadays could clearly be seen. Happy could beat Hundred Blossoms 9-1, Misty Rain 10-0, so why couldn't they beat Void 10-0 too? The fans reasoned it in this way.

However, whether Happy won the second round of the individual competition wasn't something Ye Xiu could influence. Steamed Bun. Team Happy's second player to be sent out was already standing up, jogging excitedly over towards the stage.

"10-0!" Steamed Bun hollered along with the crowd. The crowd instantly became even more fired up.

Team Void. Their second player was Li Xun, an Assassin, his character was called Ghost Lantern.

Li Xun was also a rather popular player. He was currently the only Assassin player who liked to use Life-Risking Strike for a one hit KO. Starting from Season 5, ever since he joined Team Void, he was obsessed with the thrill of an instant kill.

But he was the only Assassin player like this, which wasn't without reason. In the current state of Glory, the chances of finding an opening for a Life-Risking Strike were becoming smaller and smaller. Even if Li Xun refused to give up on it, he could not stubbornly revolve his entire playstyle around it. Life-Risking Strike was a method only used when he saw an opportunity for it, or perhaps in certain situations, he would be more willing than other Assassins to gamble everything.

As a result, he wasn't suitable for playing in the group arena, so Li Xun quickly consolidated a spot for himself in the individual competition.

The second round of the individual competition began. The map was Nine Pine Forest, which had nine pine trees distributed across the map. There was nothing else besides those pine trees. Because it was a 1v1 map, the size of the map was very small, so these nine pine trees filled up a lot of the space, allowing for numerous tactics through their positions.

But from the looks of these two, it seemed like neither of them had any intentions of finding a strategic spot on a large pine tree. The two ran straight towards the center of the map, where two pine trees neighbored each other, and started fighting.　

A brick to start with.

"Old trick!" Li Xun shouted. This Assassin, who loved one hit kills, was also someone who liked to talk. He tried to use words to distract his opponent's attention to make it easier for him to realize his pursuit of a one hit kill. This was the general consensus towards Li Xun's trash talk.

As for Steamed Bun, from the data on him, initiating with a Brick was practically guaranteed. As someone who liked to trash talk, how could Li Xun not say anything about it?

"Haha, then do you dare stand there and let me hit you with a brick?" Steamed Bun replied. Steamed Bun's trash talk was always the same, swift responses without any thought behind them. In more normal conversations, he might suddenly say something off the rails. Steamed Bun's trash talk talent was something Li Xun needed. The sort of crazy talk that left the opponent utterly confused was much more effective at diverting the opponent's attention than ordinary trash talk.

While the two talked, Li Xun's Ghost Lantern dodged the brick and dashed over with a Shining Cut. He was taking the initiative.

Steamed Bun's reaction wasn't slow. He immediately had Steamed Bun Invasion jump back and open his palms.

Ghost Lantern nimbly leapt to the side to dodge the Sand Toss.

Shadow Clone Technique!

This was a Ninja skill that could be used as an instant movement skill. All Night Walker classes would want to learn it. Li Xun suddenly used it at this moment, and Ghost Lantern instantly appeared behind Steamed Bun Invasion. The crowd cried out in fear.

Life-Risking Strike?

It looked like it could be used, but if Li Xun was so trigger happy with his Life-Risking Strike, Team Void probably wouldn't support his playstyle. Li Xun's Life-Risking Strikes didn't always succeed, but the success rate was relatively high. Team Void could benefit from it, which was why they firmly supported him.

The match had just begun, and he had gotten behind his opponent with a Shadow Clone Technique. Was he going to use Life-Risking Strike?

As someone who loved this type of extremely dangerous playstyle, Li Xun was clearly someone who liked to take risks. However, the problem was that using Life-Risking Strike in this situation wasn't a question of risk. Instantly killing a full-health Brawler with a Life-Risking Strike was impossible. Even if Li Xun had his Assassin Ghost Lantern stack health because of his playstyle, Brawlers were a plate armor class. Their health growth was 3.5, which wasn't bad among the 24 classes. On the other hand, the Brawlers were weak in their Spirit stat, which only had a 1.5 growth for them.

The key point was that he couldn't instant kill him. If Steamed Bun Invasion had been a Summoner or an Elementalist, Ghost Lantern might really have just used Life-Risking Strike.

Cutthroat!

It was a fast low-level skill, but a back attack gave it a considerable increase in damage.

Cold light swiped towards Steamed Bun's neck. This attack was just the beginning. What followed would certainly be a combo. If done well, he might even be able to end it with a Life-Risking Strike and end it one go.

Those familiar with Li Xun and those who supported him were all hoping for this scene to happen.

However, the Cutthroat missed!

Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly crouched, dodging the attack.　　

What incredible awareness!

Everyone sighed one after the other. He saw through Shadow Clone Technique and even predicted a back attack!

What's more, he crouched, which meant that he could immediately counter attack!　　

Sure enough!

Steamed Bun Invasion rushed forward.　　

Tyrannical Chain Punch! He directly let loose a powerful skill!

Everyone watched in astonishment as the crouching Steamed Bun Invasion rushed forward and pinned Ghost Lantern's shadow clone to the ground. But before Steamed Bun could even punch, Ghost Lantern's shadow clone poofed into smoke.

"Huh?" Steamed Bun was puzzled.

The entire crowd was dumbstruck.

"What are you doing?" Li Xun was dumbfounded as well. He didn't even have Ghost Lantern pursue him after the Cutthroat despite having the opportunity to do so. This Tyrannical Chain Punch was making his head spin.

There was no need to doubt Steamed Bun's speed, and Li Xun, who was his opponent, could sense that this Tyrannical Chain Punch had started sooner than his Cutthroat. If Steamed Bun Invasion had turned around and used it, then dodging the Cutthroat would have actually been extraneous. He reckoned that he would have a difficult time dodging this Tyrannical Chain Punch. However, Steamed Bun actually didn't realize that he had used a Shadow Clone Technique and wasted a high-level skill on a shadow clone. Of course, that was probably why his Tyrannical Chain Punch had been faster than his Cutthroat. Steamed Bun didn't know there was a threat behind him, so he immediately pounced on his opponent up ahead.

Li Xun didn't know whether to laugh or cry. Truthfully, he hadn't even thought that his opponent wouldn't notice the Shadow Clone Technique. After all, his character wasn't a Ninja, and the only below Level 20 Ninja skill that required hand seals was Shadow Clone Technique. Even though Li Xun would do his best to hide it, pro players had sharp eyes. Such an irregular motion on an Assassin was very easy to notice.

But today, he had actually met someone who failed to notice it.

"So it was a Shadow Clone Technique. You punk. I got tricked." Steamed Bun Invasion climbed back up from the ground and turned around, glaring at Ghost Lantern behind him.

All sorts of thoughts ran through Li Xun's mind. He had no idea how to respond.

"You really got lucky…" Li Xun said.

"Luck? That's a part of skill," Steamed Bun said. He was clearly just going along with it. He had no clue what had just happened.

"Lose! You're a bringer of bad luck!" Steamed Bun's godly logic turned "you got lucky" into Li Xun being a bringer of bad luck. Steamed Bun Invasion charged forward.

"Let's see just how lucky you are!" Li Xun shouted. Ghost Lantern activated Swift Movement and then started sprinting. He moved so fast that there seemed to be a trail of dust behind him. In the blink of an eye, he reached Steamed Bun Invasion's side.

Leaping Blade!

Ghost Lantern's dagger flicked upwards. Leaping Blade was the Assassin's knockup skill.

Steamed Bun Invasion turned around and swung his arms, Slapping the dagger aside.

This guy! His hand speed and reaction speed weren't slow, but he himself seemed a bit stupid. He's definitely a good prey for a one hit kill.

Li Xun rapidly thought to himself. In this day and age, an opportunity for a one hit kill was something that had to be created. Finding someone as naturally stupid as this person was too hard to find in the pro scene.

Perfect prey!

Chapter 1222: One Hit Certain Kill

Heart-Piercing Stab!

After the Leaping Blade was slapped aside, Ghost Lantern immediately followed with a Heart-Piercing Strike that stabbed towards Steamed Bun Invasion's chest.

Steamed Bun Invasion stepped diagonally to avoid it and swung his arm horizontally, latching onto Ghost Lantern's neck. Tiger Flips the Mountain.

A huge amount of power surged forth, and Ghost Lantern was flipped into the air. However, a wound also appeared on Steamed Bun Invasion's waist.

Mother and Child Stab!

When Ghost Lantern had been thrown into the air by Tiger Flips the Mountain, Li Xun quickly sneaked in this attack.

It was a trade, but Li Xun was very unhappy with the outcome.　　

He was someone who liked one hit kills, and Life Risking Strike was an attack that traded health for health, so for him, his health was equivalent to damage. Health was an extraordinarily precious resource, so even though it was an even trade, in his eyes, he had lost out. Li Xun had his own idea of an acceptable trade, but this trade wasn't one.

Steamed Bun didn't care about Li Xun's feelings though. Mother and Child Stab didn't really do anything other than deal damage, so with Ghost Lantern in the air, Steamed Bun Invasion had the initiative. Steamed Bun wouldn't let go of this opportunity and continued his attacks. He leaped up with a Powerful Knee Strike, smashing his knee towards Ghost Lantern.

　

Ghost Lantern simply jumped to the side while in the air and avoided the attack.　　

Air Jump. Only Assassins, who had access to this passive skill, had the ability to jump in the air. Other classes could only jump once off the ground. With this double jump, Ghost Lantern dodged the Powerful Knee Strike and returned with a kick downwards towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

Diving Arrow!

The Assassin skill, Diving Arrow, shared a few similarities with the Striker skill, Eagle Stamp. Diving Arrow didn't have as high of a priority, but it was far faster than Eagle Stamp. After the first kick connected, his two feet kicked him another four times in an instant, forcefully sending Steamed Bun Invasion flying to the side.

For Assassins, as soon as a single hit connected, the following combo would be linked together extremely fast. After the Diving Arrow, Ghost Lantern suddenly left behind an afterimage, flickering to Steamed Bun Invasion's side and piercing him with his dagger.

Flickering Stab!

This Level 65 Assassin skill was a displacement skill, but it was rarely used as a movement skill because the displacement was extremely small. It was only one step, a distance of one unit. But this single step was no different than an instant movement. When an Assassin used Flickering Stab, he might originally have been in front of you, but the attack would come from the side. If the Assassin were to the side of you, then the stab might turn into a back attack. Hever, more often than not, the Assassin looked to still be one step away, when his dagger was already in your chest.

Steamed Bun Invasion was hit once again. By this time, Ghost Lantern had landed back on the ground. He kicked upwards and struck Steamed Bun Invasion's ankle.　

Ankle Break!

It didn't deal much damage, but it lowered the target's movement speed by 30% for 5 seconds. During these 5 seconds, trying to escape from an Assassin's pursuit was nigh impossible.

Splitting Water Stab, Heart Piercing Stab...

All kinds of assassination skills struck Steamed Bun Invasion one after the other. Blood splattered onto the pine tree. In an instant, countless red spots appeared on the surface of the tree.

This really is easy.

Li Xun smirked. Team Void had obviously done their research on Steamed Bun's tendencies. He knew that from time to time, he would make an extremely unusual and surprising move, but under his fast and tight offense, it didn't matter what type of crazy imaginative tricks he had. If there aren't any openings, what can he do?

Blade Storm!

Li Xun used another high-level damage skill. Blood splattered even more crazily.

That's enough.

Li Xun thought to himself. With the Blade Storm, Steamed Bun Invasion was forced back by the momentum.　　

Steamed Bun Invasion was under hit stun as he slid back, while Ghost Lantern also couldn't move due to the ending lag from Blade Storm. This sort of safe period was often built into high-level skills.

However, players would always try to find a way to get around this safe period to seize the initiative.

As a pro, Li Xun obviously had these thoughts as well. When he used his high-level skill, he had taken the terrain into consideration. The final stab sent Steamed Bun Invasion sliding backwards, but he would only slide back at most four units before slamming into the pine tree behind him, extending the stun by a tiny amount. More importantly, the distance between the two would stay close, only four units.

This is more than enough!

The experienced Li Xun laughed confidently. His Ghost Lantern used As the Shadow Follows.

As the Shadow Follows was a high-level Assassin movement skill. The user didn't have much control over it though. After picking a location, the character would move at an extremely fast speed towards that location.

As the Shadow Follows to close these four units of distance and then Life-Risking Strike!

When he used As the Shadow Follows, he had thoroughly burned down his health. The damage dealt by this Life Risking Strike would be more than enough to instantly kill Steamed Bun Invasion.

An afterimage was left behind as Ghost Lantern moved three steps. One more step and Steamed Bun Invasion would be dead.

Three steps might have been more ideal. This thought suddenly popped into Li Hua's mind. Because at this moment, he saw Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly move. The hit stun had ended. The extra stun from slamming into the tree hadn't been enough for Ghost Lantern to complete all four steps.

Four steps might not be perfect, but it's enough.

With just a distance of one step, what skill could be faster than As the Shadow Follows? Instant movement skill? Shadow Clone Technique? Substitution Technique? At this distance, there wouldn't be enough time to activate those skills, let alone the fact that Steamed Bun Invasion didn't have access to those skills.

Li Xun loved to take risks, but he never lost his calm. Daring but careful was the reason why he was an outstanding pro player.

One hit certain kill!

Yes, one hit certain kill, but the one to be killed was...

Li Xun looked flabbergasted at the afterimage left behind below the tree. He stared in astonishment at the Steamed Bun Invasion in front of him. The sharp claws on his fists were pierced through his Ghost Lantern's chest.

Li Xun turned around to take a look.

Within this one step, Ghost Lantern had moved one-third of a step, while Steamed Bun Invasion had moved two-thirds of a step.

Thus, Steamed Bun Invasion's attack had been faster. That Life-Risking Strike had been prepared for after that two-thirds of a step.

"Holy shit, I finally got a chance to use it," Li Xun saw Steamed Bun's message in the chat.

Followed by: "Huh? How are you dead? My god, this skill's that powerful??"　　

This skill's that powerful?

As Li Xun's point of view fell along with Ghost Lantern, he saw that afterimage from below the tree disappear.

Flickering Stab?

Tooth for Tooth?

How long has it been since I used Flickering Stab? He activated Tooth for Tooth at that time? After stealing the skill, he used it just a step before his death and then killed me instead?

If it was Flickering Stab, then for a distance of one step, it was faster than As the Shadow Follows. If this had all been a part of Steamed Bun's plan then Li Xun would have been shocked at how terrifying he was, but seeing Steamed Bun's words, Li Xun could only feel that it was ridiculous. This match was ridiculous. I actually lost like this?

What type of stupid luck was this!!

Li Xun sat there in a daze for a long time. The referee had to come over and remind him.

Li Xun walked out of the player booth. As for the crowd, there were traces of hesitation in their cheers. The problem was Steamed Bun's final words. If he hadn't said those words, everyone would have thought that he had planned everything, waiting there patiently for Li Xun to make his final move. But with those last words, the marvel of this spectacular play instantly disappeared. Everyone had the same thoughts as Li Xun: he won just like that?　　

In any case, a win was a win. As Happy's supporters, there was no reason not to be happy about a win, right? Even if the win had been so comical and absurd that even the winner didn't really understand the situation. Speaking of which, this winner who didn't understand why he won seemed to be quite happy with this victory. After coming out of the player booth, he ran around the stage once.

"Victory!!" Steamed Bun yelled.

The crowd cheered and clapped.

"10 to 1!" Steamed Bun shouted.

10 to 1! Everyone echoed his words. But they soon had a realization. What the fuck was 10 to 1?

Fortunately, Steamed Bun immediately noticed his mistake.　　

"10 to 0!" he corrected himself.

10 to 0! This time, there was no problem and everyone cheered.

After running around in a circle, he bumped into Li Xun, who was coming down from the stage. He went over and extended his hands out without any signs of embarrasment.　

"You played well!" Steamed Bun said.

"You… you played well too," Li Xun said. In all honesty, he had wanted to say "you fucker," but the goddamn referee just happened to be nearby.

"Keep trying," Steamed Bun patted him and then ran back to this team. As he passed Team Void, he waved at them. The Team Void players looked at one another, unsure what to do. Luckily, Steamed Bun quickly passed by them.

After finally returning to his team's seats, Steamed Bun celebrated with everyone.

"Mm, as long as you win, it's good," Ye Xiu nodded his head.

For this match, it was too embarrassing to say that this win was due to Steamed Bun's crazy imagination… it could only be said that his Tooth for Tooth, which he had used on Flickering Stab for some inexplicable reason, gave Steamed Bun good luck.

Yes, luck.

The key factor to this win was luck. It was something that could eclipse hard work and talent: luck.

"With this kind of luck, he could have probably won just lying down!" Wei Chen sighed.　

These words were somewhat exaggerated, but it could be considered as a strong comment towards that fight.

The loser on Void must be feeling very wronged, right? Ye Xiu looked towards Team Void. But then again, if Li Xun didn't like one hit kills, this sort of luck might not have happened.

In the end, luck only worked when the differences in skill weren't that large. Lying down and winning would never actually happen.

Chapter 1223: The Old General’s Way of Winning

Two battles of the individual competition were now over. Whether through luck or strength, Happy now had a 2-0 lead. For this upcoming third match, the digital displays showed the players' names and the players stood up. After a pause from the audience, there was suddenly a small wave of cheers.

"Old Wei, can you really do this?!" In the audience seating near Happy's player area, someone hollered at him.

Wei Chen evidently heard it. He turned in the direction of the shout, swept his gaze over, then lifted his index finger and waggled it in that direction. Void's players were dumbstruck. Waving your index finger wasn't as much of an insult as showing your middle finger, but there was at least some scorn in the gesture. To do this towards your own home audience, what was he thinking?

But what surprised them more was that the audience members whom Wei Chen gestured at, although they were boiling and starting hooting at him, were in an undisguised laughing and joking mood.

Anyone could tell, it wasn't that they didn't support Wei Chen. This was a sort of good-natured teasing between close friends and people who knew each other well. If people didn't have a close enough relationship, they couldn't crack such jokes.

To have such a relationship with fans?

Void's players continued to stare. It seemed somewhat unacceptable, but in their hearts there was a bit of… envy. They didn't have this, thus they felt envy. It was a very natural thing.

In this kind of atmosphere, Wei Chen went onstage. Happy's fans didn't have this same kind of relationship with the other players of Happy. The reason for this was that after everyone became pro players, only Wei Chen still had the air of being close to the earth with them.

Even now, his Windward Formation would still make frequent appearances in the game.

His professional career had only lasted two years, but he had spent over a decade in the Glory game. This was a deeply-ingrained part of his life that had no way of being eliminated. Preventing him from going into the game would be even more difficult than preventing him from smoking.

Windward Formation wasn't an especially famous name, and it was clear that Wei Chen's primary role at Happy was just as a substitute, so he didn't receive much attention. His character in-game wouldn't be surrounded or gawked at to the point where he couldn't move.

Since he was playing the game, he couldn't avoid interactions with other players. So the understanding that many people had of Wei Chen didn't solely come from the Alliance, the team, or the official reports from the media. It came from casual conversations in the guild chat, or chatter from a dungeon raid.

And so Wei Chen became this particularly special pro player. Plus, he also carried a record of his own - he was the oldest pro player to date to participate in the Glory Alliance. People even asked him, since you're still coming to play even now, why did you leave a blank space of so many years?

Wei Chen couldn't answer this question.

He only knew, he stood here now. Even though he couldn't do much anymore, he would still put in his full effort. Because, he was a pro player.

Individual competition round 3, begin.

Happy, Wei Chen, Warlock Windward Formation.

Void, Yang Haoxuan, Launcher Translucent.

Yang Haoxuan, a pro player from Season 7, entering Void's training camp at age 15 and offered a professional contract at age 17 from Team Void. Now, he had worked at Void for four years, and wasn't even 20 yet.

"How young…" Wei Chen sighed.

The battle quickly began. Against a Launcher, Windward Formation's high attack range naturally wasn't much of an advantage, so as soon as the battle began, Wei Chen began strategic movement. He had chosen the map, so of course he was very familiar with it.

And Yang Haoxuan? When the match began, he did the same thing as Wei Chen, strategic movement. His character Translucent also took a roundabout path on the map. He quickly made his way to the center and didn't see the opponent's character, so he instantly understood what was going on.

Boom!

Yang Haoxuan immediately had his Translucent to fire a cannon shot, planning to use the sound to lure Wei Chen to expose the position of his Windward Formation.

But when Wei Chen heard the shot, he didn't look around, instead directly controlling Windward Formation to make a U-turn. Everyone saw that this new direction was exactly the direction towards Translucent's current position. The old veteran's hearing ability was still exceptional.

But after Yang Haoxuan fired this shot, he didn't have Translucent stand there motionlessly. He moved Translucent to a different position with a wider view like an oriole behind a mantis.

The method of luring a snake out of its hole.

Many viewers were used to seeing this kind of strategy. Wei Chen had been around for so many years, would he fall for it?

The audience saw from the omniscient view Wei Chen's Windward Formation, creeping bit by bit toward Translucent's original position.

The crowd was becoming anxious. They worried for Wei Chen, but Wei Chen was just foolishly going ahead, as though this possibility of a trap hadn't even occurred to him.

Windward Formation revealed himself, and the crowd sighed.

Yet Yang Haoxuan didn't begin his attack immediately. This strategy was so low-level that even ordinary players could see through it. Wei Chen had the judgment to make his way here through sound alone, how could he not know this sort of simple strategy? Especially now that he could see that the opponent's character wasn't here, it should be even more obvious to him. So Yang Haoxuan didn't think that Wei Chen was just hastily crashing over here, he had to have some defensive preparations. If he attacked immediately, he felt that the opponent's defenses would be at their highest, and he might not be able to achieve any good effect. Better to hide and wait patiently, wait until the opponent felt that this wasn't a trap and lower his guard.

And so Yang Haoxuan didn't move.

And so Wei Chen spoke. "I'm here already, come out and fight! What are you hiding and dawdling for? You think I'll just let down my guard?"

He's trying to trick me! I'm not moving, thought Yang Haoxuan.

"Yes, I'm talking to you! The one at position 45, 56," Wei Chen said.

Yang Haoxuan jolted, and glanced at the coordinates of his Translucent's position. Indeed: 45, 56.

The crowd burst into applause. What incredible judgment! To predict the opponent's movements so accurately and clearly, this demonstrated an incredible all-around familiarity and understanding of both the map and the opponent!

His coordinates were exposed just like that, Yang Haoxuan felt very awkward, but he knew that right now there were countless people watching them. If he just walked out like this, that would be too humiliating!

As he agonized, Wei Chen continued to yell. "What, you're still not coming out?"

The helpless Yang Haoxuan prepared to control his character to reveal himself…

"Haha, I know, you're actually at 48, 31!" Another message from Wei Chen suddenly jumped out in the chat. Filled with confidence, Windward Formation scurried in that direction.

Fuck!

Just as he was about to charge out, Yang Haoxuan brought himself to a screeching halt.

"This old fox!" Yang Haoxuan's forehead was covered in cold sweat. He had really been just about to reveal himself. Good thing he had spaced out for a moment. It looked like this round, luck was now on Void's side!

After thinking about Wei Chen's final shout of position 48, 31, Yang Haoxuan had Translucent walk out, preparing to carefully circle around and then bombard Windward Formation with continuous heavy firepower.

Yang Haoxuan took several deep breaths, bracing himself for the intense moments to follow.

But the crowd was filled with the sounds of tsking.

"Young people!" someone sighed.

Yang Haoxuan, among the esports players, couldn't be considered young. He was 20 years old, right in the middle generation that was at its peak. But compared to Wei Chen, who was older than him by over a decade, he really was just a young person.

The young person prepared for the upcoming intensity, but suddenly, a Hexagram Prison descended from the sky. Before he had time to dodge, Translucent was already locked in.

Shit!

Yang Haoxuan instantly knew that, in the end, he had been tricked.

Luring the snake out of its hole. Same strategy, different execution. The older the ginger the spicier it was!

With this ambush, Wei Chen gave himself an excellent advantage. And then, after several exchanges in this sneaky and complicated map, he finally defeated Yang Haoxuan.

A win in every individual match, 3-0!

The live crowd became a wave of excitement.

10-0!!

Countless Happy supporters were shouting. To win all of the individual battles, that was the rhythm of a 10-0!

Yang Haoxuan walked out of the competitor booth, downtrodden and depressed as he came offstage; on Happy's side, Wei Chen lingered inside for quite a while.

"That old thing, trying to act dull on the outside, but he's really passionate on the inside!" said someone in the audience, laughing. Because there was a relatively long break between the individual round and the group arena, the judge didn't immediately come to urge him out.

Wei Chen sat in the competitor booth, a cigarette stuck between his fingers, but eyeing the "no smoking" sign above his head, he still didn't dare light it.

"That was close…" Wei Chen's gaze turned to the computer screen, and he looked at Windward Formation's remaining health: 8%.

He won, but it wasn't easy. That ambush early on had greatly succeeded, instantly giving him a 30% health advantage, but in the end, his health had been whittled all the way down to 8%. This made Wei Chen rather unhappy, and in his heart, an agitated voice once again reminded him of that reality.

"I really am old…" Wei Chen said to himself. "And so, this is my win method.

"But 8% or 80%, does that matter? Tch, this isn't the group arena," Wei Chen muttered. He stood up and exited the competitor booth.

When he finally showed his face, the crowd burst into thunderous applause.

"That's right. A win is a win. As long as this is the outcome." Wei Chen smiled, and his heart suddenly felt lighter.

"Old Wei, you did it!!!"

As he walked along the side of the stage, the audience members nearby again cracked jokes with him. Some of them might not have actually known him well, but seeing other people do the same, they felt that Wei Chen was the type of player you could interact with like this, and so they followed along.

Wei Chen didn't disappoint them by refusing interaction. Towards those who were shouting at him, he responded, even cracking some dirty jokes like "this old man's still got it." He gave a wink and proudly and gleefully walked by.

"A small character like that, I can defeat him with a wiggle of my finger." Upon returning to Happy's player area, Wei Chen gestured with the tip of his little finger and spoke.

"Very strong," everyone praised him.

"You really should've given me a spot on the main roster. An old guy like you should rotate out and rest more!" Wei Chen gruffly patted Ye Xiu.

"Thanks!" Ye Xiu laughed. "But I'm still very young!"

"As long as you don't brag, that's best," Wei Chen said.

Chapter 1224: Void’s Ghost Duo

"What's wrong, are we planning to lose to Happy 0 to 10?" In Void's player area, looking at the current scoreboard showing Happy: 3, Void: 0, Void's Captain Li Xuan, the one called the number one Phantom Demon, finally couldn't sit around any longer.

As a member of the Golden Generation, he garnered attention in his very first season, and in his second season he gained an exceptional partner and helper. But in six years, what had they achieved?

Even for the little award of Best Partners, he couldn't compete with his fellow player from the Golden Generation, Su Mucheng. He had to wait until Ye Xiu retired and left before he could pick up that award.

The tacit understanding between the Ghost Duo wasn't any less deep than that between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. But the value of the Best Partners title wasn't limited to the partnership itself. It also considered how much this partnership brought to the team as a whole.

Void was a frequent participant in the playoffs. And the old Excellent Era? After losing to Tyranny in the finals of Season 4, they had never entered the finals again. On some level, Excellent Era and Void weren't that different in terms of their . But during Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng's many years at Excellent Era, the award for Best Partners always seemed to go to them without any competition at all. Their so-called strongest competitors, the Ghost Duo, had in reality never managed to put any pressure on them at all.

The reason was simple. Void's Ghost Duo, when in direct confrontation against Excellent Era's Long Spear Short Cannon combination, always came up inferior.

They'd never won the championship, they'd never even entered the finals. Even for an individual award like Best Partners, they'd been beaten down for so long. There was no way that Li Xuan felt no anger in his heart. What "number one Phantom Demon"? It sounded cool, but in Li Xuan's opinion? He wasn't even number one in one of the 24 classes of Glory. One of the 24 classes was called Ghostblade, and he, he was only the number one of the Phantom Demon branch of Ghostblade.

There were only around 200 Glory pro players, so on average, each class didn't have more than 10 players. The Ghostblade class was further divided into the three branches of Phantom Demon, Sword Demon, and Phantom Sword, so if they took an average again, there were only three Phantom Demons. And so, Li Xuan was the number one of three people. First among three, was that anything impressive?

To this, Li Xuan could only shake his head and laugh bitterly. Of course, to be the number one Phantom Demon meant that out of the millions of Phantom Demon players in Glory, he was the best. But Li Xuan truly had no interest in using those outside of the pro circle to comfort himself.

Number one was number one.

In the old days, no one said that Ye Qiu was the number one Battle Mage.

Li Xuan also wanted to become a true number one. But after so many years, he was still just the number one Phantom Demon. He couldn't even get the title of number one Ghostblade. But the one who was blocking him from this title was his own teammate, his closest friend and best partner since Season 5, Wu Yuce.

What was up with this?

Sometimes, Li Xuan would mock himself like this.

But even if they were best friends and partners, Li Xuan and Wu Yuce, who was the best Ghostblade player in the end? This question, even Li Xuan himself couldn't help but ponder sometimes.

To be honest, he had no way of giving a clear answer, and the outside world had debated this question for many years, only to find that both sides had their arguments. And within Void? Everyone carefully avoided this question, and when asked by the reporters, the two would by tacit agreement always praise the other as superior. But even so, they wouldn't talk themselves down too much, either. And so everyone could tell, their responses were just out of courtesy. Who was the stronger between the two of them, they themselves never gave a true answer.

For now, judging from their positions in the team and the All-Star vote rankings, Li Xuan was still in the lead. But some people felt that this was only because Li Xuan debuted a year before Wu Yuce, and thus had a head start.

Who was stronger? Who was the true number one Ghostblade?

In the past, Li Xuan had been very sensitive about this topic. Regarding his lead, although he'd never say it aloud, he had been secretly pleased.

But now, after so many years, he was used to it, he was numb to it, he was no longer interested in this question.

What he wanted was to be the true number one, the number one of the league, and not some number one Phantom Demon or Ghostblade.

And the dream of being this number one was too much more difficult than those other number ones.

In the blink of an eye, it was already Season 10 of the Glory Professional Alliance.

Last season, the team promoted a rookie, Ge Caijie, and everyone said that the Ghost Duo finally had a new reliable helper, that they had a lot to look forward to.

Li Xuan also carried such hopes as he entered Season 10.

But up through now, he hadn't seen any sign of his team's strong rise. Void was still struggling against the other second-string strong teams for a spot in the playoffs. And now, Happy, this new team, was actually their direct competitor, and in this current confrontation had a 3-0 lead…

"What is our goal?" Li Xuan said, looking at his teammates.

Void hadn't announced it to the public, but within the team, they felt that their roster was complete, and they had this strong rookie, Ge Caijie. They felt that this season was the season to taste the rhythm of charging for the championships. But playing up until now, they'd lost to Samsara, they'd lost to Wind Howl, they'd lost to Thunderclap, they'd even lost to Miracle. What kind of championship rhythm was this?

They'd lost to Miracle! And it had been their home game!

The seventh round of competition had been a harsh blow for Void.

Then what about now?

"Do we plan on losing 0-10 to Happy?" Li Xuan repeated this question.

"No…" Of course, his teammates could only reply like this.

"If not, then get your spirits up!" Li Xuan said.

"Yes…" everyone answered.

"Zhaolan, you're up!" Li Xuan nodded toward one of the players.

"Yes." Ge Zhaolan nodded and followed the orders to head onstage.

Void's Spitfire was named Transparent. It was instantly apparent that the name had a common source as Yang Haoxuan's Launcher Translucent. Indeed, these two characters were brought into the team by the seniors who established Team Void, and had always stayed in the team. But now, these two characters were just side characters in the team, largely because Void had never found any especially talented players for these two classes.

When Zhang Jiale retired from Hundred Blossoms, the team was caught off-guard and had no plan. They were entirely unable to find a replacement player and could only promote someone from within the team in a hurry. To some extent, this was a sign that the current Spitfire players weren't up to par. It wasn't that they were bad, it was just that they weren't outstanding enough.

Ge Zhaolan unfortunately was one of the Spitfire players who had been deemed not good enough. But the good thing was that he wasn't an especially ambitious person. He knew his position very clearly, and something like this didn't affect him. He continued to work diligently for Void. And now, Void needed him to show his strength.

They lagged behind the other team 0-3 after the individual round. In the group arena, Ge Zhaolan and his Spitfire Transparent would lead the battle for Void.

And Happy? Their first player in the group arena was Fang Rui, with his Qi Master Boundless Sea.

Happy's roster had basically been figured out by all of the opponents by this point. In the individual round and group arena, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, and Tang Rou would always appear.

There was no dispute over having the three All-Stars appear. Even if Fang Rui had been affected by his class change, it was exactly because of his class change that he needed more battles to improve more quickly. As for Tang Rou, despite her infamy, objectively speaking no one dared underestimate her strength onstage. But after that promise-breaking incident, people suddenly had higher expectations of her. As long as she didn't 1v3, in everyone's eyes it was a weak chicken performance. 1v1.5, 1v2, these performances were normally impressive, but if it was Tang Rou, everyone would just laugh and say: look, that person who wanted to 1v3, couldn't even do a 2.5, how weak…

In this match's individual round, Ye Xiu, Steamed Bun, and Wei Chen had appeared onstage. Thus, it was already clear who would be appearing in the group arena. Now, Fang Rui was first onstage.

The map selected for this group arena battle was relatively open, a bit better for unobstructed sight that Su Mucheng needed and the simple direct confrontations that Tang Rou liked. However, this map didn't have any of the complex features that Fang Rui needed for his dirty playing.

This was also a difficulty in picking a map for the group arena, and was also a factor to consider when deciding the player order.

Fang Rui was the sacrificed piece in Happy's selection of this map. After entering the battle, he had Boundless Sea charge right towards the center of the map. It looked like he wasn't about to try and force some dirty playing onto this relatively simple map.

The two sides' characters quickly met at the center of the map. A Spitfire didn't have too many demanding requirements of a map, and Ge Zhaolan, this rejected player, didn't have a particularly distinctive playstyle, he was right in the middle. Seeing that this was the map, he simply controlled his character to head right toward the center. When he spotted Fang Rui's Boundless Sea, he calculated the distance, and as soon as he entered the Spitfire's attack range, Transparent lifted his gun without any hesitation.

Gunshot, Boundless Sea ducked to the ground. That rolling and crawling Thief-like moving style once again appeared with this Qi Master Boundless Sea.

The audience applauded. This Qi Master style that Fang Rui had invented had already attracted attention and a few imitations.

To ordinary players without any sort of high-end in-depth background, they just made their best approximations, drawing a tiger like a dog. But in the professional circle, the Qi Masters who saw Fang Rui's current playstyle could only shake their heads. They didn't reject his style altogether, but this kind of style was just entirely different from their habits. This sort of rolling and crawling was only familiar to Fang Rui. If they had to do the same, they would all feel that it was strange.

And this kind of playstyle wasn't as simple as making such postures. After some detailed analysis by some so-called experts, they all concluded that this sort of playstyle was closely linked to Fang Rui own personal qualities.

Chapter 1225: Darkness and Light

What were Fang Rui's qualities?

If this question were posed to one hundred Glory players, approximately one hundred answers would be "dirty," without any hesitation.

This of course wasn't wrong, but the analysis by the so-called experts wouldn't be so unspecific. They used many technical details to pick out what qualities Fang Rui had, and the conclusion they reached was: this playstyle fits Fang Rui exactly, but possibly would not fit anyone else.

Those that supported this view included the previous Qi Master All-Star, Zhao Yang. Although he had already retired, he hadn't stopped paying attention to Glory, and the reporters that were close with him easily obtained his views on Fang Rui's Qi Master. Zhao Yang believed that even he himself had no way of playing Fang Rui's style of Qi Master, and that it truly was a unique style that arose from the player.

What would be the fruits of this playstyle?

As of now, Fang Rui growing accustomed to his new playstyle was an indispensable contribution to Happy's recent strong performance. After being thrown off by Ye Xiu's unspecialized Lord Grim, the various members of the Alliance now faced another playstyle that they couldn't immediately understand, that caused them just as much difficulty as Lord Grim.

Losing wasn't scary. But losing without knowing why you lost, that was scary. This meant that you had no way of obtaining experience and improving.

And because of Happy, the Alliance players felt this strongly. The unknown unspecialized, the chaotic Steamed Bun, and now this new playstyle from Fang Rui.

This new team was really very new. New people, new characters, even new playstyles.

How to counter this entirely new element? The teams all spent time to study and try and figure out. But each team had 19 opponents in the Alliance, not just Happy. In the end, no team would do too much study or have too much focus on just one team. They had to follow the rhythm of the match schedule. Whatever team they were about to face, they would focus on defeating that team. And so Happy took advantage of this; after stabilizing their style they accumulated points like crazy. Now at Round 14, their footsteps hadn't slowed at all. Void's first player in the group arena, Ge Zhaolan, went down rapidly, having only knocked away 37% of Fang Rui's Boundless Sea.

A beautiful opening. The cheers from the crowd sent the dejected Ge Zhaolan offstage.

Li Xuan sighed and shook his head, his gaze falling upon the one at his side. His closest friend, his best partner, but at the same time the one who was in conflict with him for the title of number one Ghostblade. Wu Yuce.

"It's up to you," Li Xuan said.

Void's next players were Wu Yuce and himself. Right now, Happy had a significant lead, with 2.63 people remaining.

Wu Yuce nodded. Without saying anything else, he stood up and resolutely headed toward the stage.

The Happy supporters in the crowd gave vocal support to their home team, and of course they would also boo the Void players to disrupt them. But Wu Yuce seemed as though he already had a natural defense against booing. His steps were very steady, and when he crossed paths with Ge Zhaolan, he even paused to say some words to him. He wasn't affected by the atmosphere of the stadium at all.

Wu Yuce quickly arrived onstage, entered the competitor booth, and logged on to his character.

Ghostblade, Carved Ghost. Among the recent All-Star characters, one of the only two female ones.

"Bring it, Miss Wu!" So when the battle began, Fang Rui immediately used this to trash talk.

Wu Yuce didn't reply, and Carved Ghost moved along the map. And Fang Rui? He didn't seem to hope for any response from Wu Yuce. As he tossed this bit of trash talk, he controlled Boundless Sea to rush forward.

In reality, Fang Rui wasn't too unfamiliar with Wu Yuce, as they had debuted the same year. But although both of them had proven themselves from the beginning within their respective teams, neither of them could compete with that other rookie from their year.

That year, Zhou Zekai made his dazzling debut on the professional stage. In his first season, he had carried the mediocre team Samsara into the playoffs.

What were Fang Rui and Wu Yuce up to during that time?

Fang Rui arrived at Wind Howl, initially as the successor to Lin Jingyan's Demon Subduer, but in that first season, Fang Rui revealed his talent for the Thief class. And so, he settled on becoming a Thief player, stepping on the road to becoming an All-Star player.

And Wu Yuce? When he first arrived at Void, the team had also wanted him to play a different class, but Wu Yuce refused to cooperate, insisting that he wanted to play Ghostblade. But Void at that time already had Li Xuan, a Ghostblade player from the Golden Generation. Wu Yuce's behavior was viewed as extremely unwise and provocative. He had been treated coldly at the beginning, until, by chance, he obtained an opportunity to go onstage. With that battle, the team finally began to reevaluate its position toward him, and they decided… having two Ghostblades wasn't impossible. From there, the double Ghostblade partnership was slowly established.

Neither of these two players' beginnings were as shining as Zhou Zekai's; they each had their own twists and turns, but they reflected the different attitudes of the two players.

Fang Rui was very casual. He played a Qi Master at Blue Rain, then was raised by Wind Howl to play a Brawler, and then when he finally became a full pro player, he found that Thief suited him, so he became a Thief… It could be said that Fang Rui was constantly compromising, but in the current pro player environment, if a player who hadn't yet made a name for himself wanted to be valued by the team, most anyone would choose this kind of compromise and obedience. And Fang Rui, his compromise and obedience was a bit more than normal, as evident by how many twists and turns there had been from his training camp days to becoming a full pro player. In the end, he succeeded. But this guy, after succeeding, changed classes again. With his current status and position, his class change generally wasn't viewed as compromise and obedience. Yet Fang Rui felt that this wasn't much different from what he had done in the past.

Wu Yuce didn't have much in common with Fang Rui. He hadn't gone along with the team's needs, instead stubbornly sticking to his choice. Most teams would perhaps directly give up on a player like this, but Wu Yuce's luck wasn't bad. He entered the team like this, maintained his decision, and then afterwards, he waited for an opportunity and seized the opportunity. His persistence paid off, and he too walked upon the road to becoming an All-Star.

Two entirely different paths, but they had both resulted in equally excellent All-Star players. And now, the two met. Fang Rui's playstyle was like his own character, casual, and so he became the master of playing dirty. Wu Yuce, on the other hand, was tough and unyielding, thus his Ghostblade also exuded a toughness from the bones.

Fang Rui only tossed that one word of trash talk when Wu Yuce first entered because Fang Rui was clear that this was someone who wouldn't be disrupted by trash talk at all. His personality was just that tough. As a rookie, he had dared to stubbornly refuse the plans of his team - this wasn't something that any player would be brave enough to do.

The two sides quickly met at the center of the map. Without any further interaction, they began fighting. Boundless Sea began Fang Rui's trademark Thief-style posture and movement, and before the opponent used a skill, a Qi Bullet was sent flying toward him.

Ghost Slash!

It was met by a Ghostblade's Ghost Slash. A magic aura rippled from the blade, directly travelling through the Qi Bullet.

The Qi Bullet wouldn't be complete dissipated by the priority of that attack, and it continued to fly toward Carved Ghost, but Carved Ghost's slash also continued toward Boundless Sea.

With a bang, the Qi Bullet landed upon Carved Ghost. He hadn't tried to dodge at all, doing everything he could to send this Ghost Slash onto Boundless Sea.

This guy!

Fang Rui grit his teeth. The Ghostblade wasn't very suited to hard and direct fighting, since it wasn't a class with high defense or health, but Wu Yuce still preferred this method, as it suited is personality.

But Fang Rui hadn't expected this kid would be so fierce right from the start.

He wanted to dodge this attack, but if he did, Carved Ghost's second attack would arrive instantly, and Wu Yuce would have the initiative. He refused to let that happen!

Fang Rui inputted controls and activated Reinforced Iron Bones on Boundless Sea, taking the brunt of Carved Ghost's Ghost Slash.

Qi Blade!

Boundless Sea sent this attack just when he was hit by the Ghost Blade. But at this point, Carved Ghost was still surrounded by the ghostly aura from using the Ghost Blade. Through the mist of purple, this Qi Blade carved a clearly visible path.

Carved Ghost leaned to the left.

Heh, it won't be so easy. Fang Rui smiled coldly. The Qi Blade suddenly twisted toward the right, instantly cutting Carved Ghost.

But even after taking this attack, Wu Yuce didn't stop attacking. Even as Carved Ghost was hit by the Qi Blade, the blade in her hand was still sent out.

Ice Seal Ghost Slash!

The difference between Sword Demon and Phantom Demon was that Phantom Demons summoned the Ghost God's power to create effects, controlling or damaging the opponent. Sword Demons, on the other hand, directly applied the Ghost God's power to their blades, increasing the damaging power of their slashes.

Ghost Slash, Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash, these were the three slashing attacks that Ghostblades could learn under level 20. And Sword Demons could apply any type of Ghost God power to these three slashing skills.

Carved Ghost's attack just now applied ice spirit power to the blade, thus creating an Ice Seal Ghost Slash. The blade emitted faint blue icy mist, which was sent several body units outward with the slash. Although Boundless Sea was already rolling, he was still hit by the icy mist, and his movement speed decreased significantly.

Flame-Bitten Full Moon!

Carved Ghost slid forward and made another slash, this time invoking the spirit of fire along the blade and using a Full Moonlight Slash. The enchanting fire spirit power swept in the shape of a full moon, but it wasn't very eye-burning. These flames conjured from magic weren't a pure scarlet, but carried some dark purple within. But their power would be even stronger, because it wouldn't just deal fire damage, it would also carry the dark damage inherent to a Ghostblade.

Flame-Bitten Full Moon, slash down!

Qi Guard!

A tangible protective shield suddenly expanded around Boundless Sea, blocking the Flame-Bitten Full Moon.

If Ghostblades were said to be naturally dark-aligned, then Qi Masters were naturally light-aligned. But the players playing these two classes right now…

The dark-aligned Ghostblade walked the direct and fierce path, while the light-aligned Qi Master was the representative of dirty playing.

Chapter 1226: A Loss, But A Spectacular One

he power of the Ghost God brought by the Flame-Bitten Full Moon battered against Boundless Sea's Qi Guard, but it could not suppress the radiance of the shield. The Qi Guard's defensive capabilities could hold against this attack.

Who would have thought that at this moment, a circle would appear below Carved Ghost? A wave of Ghost God energy suddenly rose and condensed onto the tip of his blade, supplementing the power of Flame-Bitten Full Moon.

Sword Boundary?

Everyone was stunned. No one had noticed Wu Yuce summoning this Sword Boundary.　　

Sword Boundary might be a low-leveled skill, but its supportive effects were top tier. Let alone a Phantom Sword Demon hybrid like Carved Ghost, even a pure Sword Demon would max this skill. This low-level skill had a very fast cast time. It could be used in between two attacks for a sudden damage buff.

Wu Yuce used it in this way. No one knew when he had cast the Ghost Boundary, but it had been set down after Flame-Bitten Full Moon. The buffs from Ghost Boundaries were immediate, and Flame-Bitten Full Moon dealt both physical and magic damage. Under the Strength and Intelligence buffs from the Sword Boundary, the power of the attack instantly shot up.

The radiance shining from Qi Guard dimmed.

Break!

The qi from the Qi Guard was consumed, and the remaining energy of Flame-Bitten Full Moon slashed towards Boundless Sea. Fang Rui immediately had Boundless Sea dodge, but Wu Yuce's follow up attack came soon afterwards.　　

Full Moonlight Slash!

This slash had finally come out. What Ghost God would be attached to it this time?

No ice. No fire. This Full Moonlight Slash was pitch black.

Dark Moonlight Slash. This time, Wu Yuce summoned the dark ghost. It stripped the light from the world, temporarily filling the area with darkness.

I can't dodge it!

Fang Rui instantly made this judgment. Wu Yuce's Carved Ghost had attacked one slash after the other. With even his Qi Guard forcefully broken, he had no way of dodging this attack.

If I can't avoid it, then we'll trade!

Just when the Dark Moonlight Slash was about to strike Boundless Sea, Boundless Sea raised his hands and used Sand Toss.　

The damage from Sand Toss was insignificant compared to the damage from a Sword Boundary buffed Dark Moonlight Slash, but it would at least induce a blind effect similar to the Dark Ghost.

Pu!

Boundless Sea was the first to be hit. Darkness surrounded him, and Fang Rui's screen turned black as if his monitor was dead. However, the sound in his ears was still as clear as ever, so he knew that the fight had yet to stop. Soon after Boundless Sea threw sand at Carved Ghost, he could hear the tiny pattering of the sand colliding.

Did it hit? Did it blind him?　

Fang Rui didn't know. He could no longer see anything, so he had Boundless Sea run for his life, while also shooting a Qi Bullet at a target he couldn't see. He just instinctively did something.

But soon, Fang Rui realized that his Boundless Sea was in the air.　

He wasn't Blinded? Boundless Sea was hit by another attack. Such a tightly linked combo clearly could not be done by someone who was blind. From this, Fang Rui inferred that Carved Ghost had not been blinded by the Sand Toss.

The viewers could see everything clearly. Not only did the Blind fail, Carved Ghost didn't even eat the miniscule amount of damage from the Sand Toss. After Dark Moonlight Slash, a shadow circled around Carved Ghost, blocking the tiny particles of sand.

Ghostblade skill: Shadow Image.

The unaffected Carved Ghost continued his assault. Shadow Claw threw Boundless Sea into the air, and starting from the ghost slash up until the Blind effect wore off, Boundless Sea never fell from the air.

"I say, don't be too savage!" As soon as the darkness disappeared, Fang Rui's spirits rose. Even though he had taken quite a bit of damage from the combo, it was far from enough to extinguish his morale.

Boundless Sea's back faced the ground, welcoming Carved Ghost's sword. His two hands formed a ball of qi in front of his chest.

He's sneakily charging his attack again!　

Quite a few people had gotten a grasp of Fang Rui's battle style now, and they were starting to discuss it.

Wu Yuce wasn't careless either. He knew exactly how long the Blind from Dark Moonlight Slash lasted, and once the effects wore off, if Boundless Sea's arms were suddenly raised to his chest, then...

Carved Ghost immediately slid to the side, adjusting his position first. He swung his sword, blocking off the angle at which Boundless Sea could attack with by twisting his body.

Who would have thought that Boundless Sea wouldn't twist his body. The ball of qi contained in his hands was let out just like that.

Sky Piercing Strike!

It really was Sky Piercing Strike. An intense wave of energy flew out towards the sky, leaving traces of spinning qi.

There was nothing in the air, so this Sky Piercing Strike obviously didn't hit anything. However, through its momentum, Boundless Sea suddenly accelerated towards the ground. The sealing attack from Carved Ghost missed.

Landmine Quake!

Right before Boundless Sea landed on the ground, his two palms once again charged up qi. He didn't even turn his view, and his two hands hit the ground before his body did.

The skill was released, and qi spread along the ground, striking everything within its range. Carved Ghost was no exception. The force coming from the earth shot up, flinging him to the side.

Quick Recover!　

Wu Yuce had Carved Ghost roll on the ground, but Boundless Sea, whose hands hit the ground, rolled faster! For this sort of rolling and crawling on the ground movement, who could be more skilled at it then this master of playing dirty?　

Carved Ghost was still flying in the air, when Boundless Sea reached his side.

Pulse Break: Break Intelligence!

One finger stabbed into Carved Ghost, lowering his Intelligence significantly.

Then, Flash Burst and Qigong Blast!

Two high-level skills landed on Carved Ghost one after the other. Qi whirled crazily around Carved Ghost, creating a cyclone of qi lifting the earth along with it. Carved Ghost didn't look like he had just been hit by an attack. It was like he was exploding forth with some sort of small Cosmo (Saint Seiya).

Fang Rui wanted to continue following up, but Wu Yuce quickly recovered. Being hit all of a sudden by such heavy attacks didn't seem to shake his willpower.　

What a spectacular and evenly-matched fight!

Quite a few members of the crowd stood up, clapping for this fight. The fans wanted their own team to win, but that didn't mean they wouldn't show respect. High-level matches were a joy to watch. For this type of fight, even if their own side lost, they would leave the field with the least amount of regret.

In the end, Fang Rui walked down from the stage with this attitude from the crowd. He had lost, but the applause he won was as if he had been the winner. Even though he didn't win, facing a strong opponent like Wu Yuce brought Fang Rui's brilliant performance to new heights.

When people discussed Fang Rui's Qi Master playstyle, people wondered whether this new playstyle would be able to stand the test of time.

New playstyles would always have surprising results when they first appeared because everyone was still new to them. The best way to test whether or not a playstyle could become mainstream was through time. In the ten years of Glory, countless playstyles had come and gone. In the current state of Glory, the meta had matured and steadied. New playstyles were usually short-lived. The number of new playstyles that could last was becoming less and less.

Fang Rui's Qi Master playtsyle had only been around for ten rounds. Could it truly become mainstream? The more conservative people weren't too optimistic about it. But in the fight that just ended, in the 1v1 against a skilled opponent like Wu Yuce, Fang Rui's playstyle shone as brilliant as ever. It could be considered to have passed a difficult test.　　

"Yay, I'm so happy!" Fang Rui clearly knew about the value of this fight. He had lost, but the implications for the future were huge. What's more, it couldn't really be said that he lost! He had taken out half the health of Wu Yuce's Carved Ghost. Fang Rui had achieved a 1v1.5, quite a good result. This was the group arena, which couldn't be judged from the outcome of a single battle.

"Mmhm, nice job," Ye Xiu said.

"I really want to go up and play another round!" Fang Rui gripped his account card, with his desire to continue written all over his face.

"You can go ask him if he wants to play all night with you after the match," Ye Xiu said.

"Okay okay, that's a good suggestion. I'll text him." Fang Rui took out his cellphone in a hurry. As for Happy, their second player was Su Mucheng, who walked onto the stage with a smile.

Dancing Rain started at full health, while Carved Ghost started at half health. Launchers, with their extremely long-ranged attacks, could be considered as Ghostblade counters to an extent, as Ghostblades had very few movement skills. In the end, in another spectacular fight, Dancing Rain won with 67% of her health left.　

Team Void's anchor for the group arena was unfortunately another Ghostblade. The Launcher's suppression over Ghostblades was still there. Su Mucheng usually played in the individual competition. Being moved to the group arena specifically for this match clearly showed Happy's intentions of countering Team Void's two Ghostblades.

A third of her health to take away Wu Yuce. Two thirds of her health to welcome Li Xuan.

Li Xuan was a Phantom Demon. He didn't have long-ranged attacks, and his opponent wasn't going to fight him at melee range. The boundaries that Phantom Demons could set down weren't really useful. He needed to take the initiative and find a way to close the distance between his opponent, but how could it be that easy...

The Ghostblade duo had been crushed in all sorts of ways by the Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng duo in the competition for Best Partners over many seasons. Ye Xiu? Even if he wasn't there, just Su Mucheng alone left them in pitiful states again and again. Su Mucheng was even nicknamed the Nemesis of the Ghost Duo.

This Ghost Duo wasn't in a general sense; it was specifically pointing towards these two from Team Void. Su Mucheng had much experience in dealing with Ghostblades, and was the source of much misery for these two.

From the looks of it, even after a season of absence, their nemesis was still a nemesis. She took out Carved Ghost's half health with a third of her health, and Li Xuan wasn't able to finish her off. Team Happy won the group arena with just two players.　　

"Ah…" Fang Rui would glance at his cellphone from time to time. Happy had won the group arena, but he looked depressed. "He hasn't replied back yet. It seems like he's not in a very good mood!"

With a lagging score of 0 to 5, who would be in a good mood?

Chapter 1227: The Two Towers

Of course Void wouldn't be in a good mood.

For the group arena, Li Xuan had tried to boost his team members' morale, but when he himself went up, he couldn't find his footing. He hadn't even gotten to see Happy's group arena anchor before being blasted down by Su Mucheng, which made the whole situation quite awkward. The good thing was that all of Void's players were old members, and the newer member Ge Caijie was a mature and stable individual who knew that Su Mucheng was always a source of suffering for this team's captain and vice captain. There was no bitterness because of this.

They were losing 0-5. In the confrontation between these two directly competing teams, Void was completely lagging behind. If they lost again in the team competition, then this round would end with a ten-point difference between the two teams. As soon as a difference reached double-digits, it would always seem rather insurmountable. Even a difference of 10 points would provoke a much different feeling than a difference of 9.

"I think, no one here wants to be swept 10-0 by Happy?" Thus, this is what Li Xuan said to his teammates.

"Lose the team competition and we'll be overtaken; win it and we'll maintain our tie. I won't say any more about what we need to do. Get your spirits up, everyone, this isn't the time to hang our heads in dejection. Remember last round, remember round 11, we have the ability to defeat any team!"

Last round, Void defeated Misty Rain 8 to 2. In Round 11, defeating Tiny Herb 8 to 2 was the highlight of Void's season thus far. Li Xuan hoped to remind everyone of how they had defeated strong teams in the past in order to summon their confidence.

"Let's go! Let's win these five points!" Li Xuan said. Turning his head, he saw that Happy's players for the team competition had already stood and were walking onstage.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, the pair that had completely defeated the Ghost Duo.

Fang Rui, who turned the light-aligned Qi Master into a dark and sneaky master of playing dirty.

Tang Rou, who hadn't been able to play in the group arena, had been waiting a long time to go onstage.

An Wenyi had always been seen as Happy's weak point, but after 13 rounds, had anyone managed to target this weak point to create any real danger for Happy? No, not at all, Happy's strategies always carefully created a protection for him. This kind of protection wasn't just a protection of his life and safety, it also protected his development. They tried to prevent any situations that An Wenyi couldn't handle, this was a principle that Happy's strategies always carried out, and it had already been analyzed by many specialists.

After these five, the sixth person was Steamed Bun, an incredible rookie who had demonstrated a level of luck approaching a miracle this round. Would he carry this luck to the team competition as well?

"Let's go!" Seeing that the opponent had already gone out, Li Xuan said this immediately.

Team Void, Li Xuan and Wu Yuce's double Ghostblade pairing would of course make an appearance. Then, there was the healer, necessary for any team competition; Void's healer was called Tang Lisheng, who used a Paladin called Soul Defender. As for the other three positions, Li Xun's position typically didn't change, and Ge Caijie's position was becoming more and more stable as he proved himself. He was even quietly becoming the axis around which Void's tactics revolved. For the final player, Void sent Yang Haoxuan, who had appeared in the individual competition earlier.

In this season, Void more often sent out Spitfire Ge Zhaolan as their sixth player, but in this round against Happy, they made special adjustments, sending out Launcher Yang Haoxuan instead, replacing Li Xun as one of the five players who would go onstage first. The intent of this adjustment was very clear. As expected, Void was extremely wary of Su Mucheng, so they also added a Launcher to their roster, so that both sides could be more equally matched in terms of long-range firepower.

The two teams' players went onstage. The team competition was the main event of each match, and there was a longer break beforehand to allow them to prepare. During this time, the players from each team often would chat while onstage.

"Why didn't you reply to my text?" Team Void's Wu Yuce received Fang Rui's greeting.

"My phone wasn't on," Wu Yuce answered.

"Oh, what time are you guys heading back?" Fang Rui asked. Void was in City X, rather far away from City H. Even though the Glory pro scene was rapidly developing, as of now, there was no team rich enough to have their own special charter plane or whatnot. Because Glory matches didn't have a set duration, it was rather difficult to make post-match plans. In order to let the players focus on the match, most guest teams would choose to spend the night at the city before leaving if their home city was far away.

"Tomorrow." Indeed, Void had made such plans.

"After the match is over, let's play a few rounds!" Fang Rui didn't send another text, and just directly asked for a match.

The others stared, dumbfounded, as they watched these two arrange a private fight before this match had even ended. To the side, the listening judge also felt that there was something wrong with this, but he also couldn't find a rule to prevent this, so he could only glare at the two of them.

Fang Rui was the only one proposing the fight. Wu Yuce, who was dragged under the harsh look of the judge simply because he was the one being invited, felt that he was unjustly wronged. He didn't say any more to Fang Rui, only tossing out a "we'll talk after" before heading with the rest of his Void teammates to the competitor booths.

Soon enough, the two sides were both ready and the countdown began. Five seconds later, the battle officially began.

The map was The Two Towers.

Void spawned at the northeast corner, Happy at the southwest. The two corners were directly opposite each other. The northwest and southeast corners were in a more sunken basin, and each corner had a rock forest. At the center of the map, the directly opposite ten o'clock and four o'clock directions each had a stone watchtower, from which this map took its name.

The two watchtowers were at the same height, and their distance from each other was within the firing range of a Launcher. These high points were clearly designed for a Launcher to use suppressive attacks with their firepower. Seeing this map chosen, Void could only grit their teeth. It was clear that Happy also knew that Su Mucheng was the greatest threat to their Ghost Duo, and they had chosen this map to maximize Dancing Rain's firepower coverage.

But in this round, Void also sent out a Launcher. Who didn't have firepower coverage?

"Go!"

Li Xuan gave his orders and Void's five swiftly began moving toward the map's center, wanting to get to the watchtowers as quickly as possible.

The two watchtowers were equidistant from the two teams' spawn points, for the sake of fairness. Void's players were confident that their movement speed wouldn't be any slower than Happy's, but as they rushed out of the northeast corner and the four o'clock tower came into clearer and clearer view, they suddenly saw a silhouette appear at the top of the watchtower.

Dancing Rain had one foot on the floor and the other propped against the guardrail of the watchtower. Shouldering her heavy cannon, her hair billowing in the wind, how was this such a valiant and heroic sight?

Su Mucheng's Launcher arrived at the 4 o'clock tower cleanly before Void.

How was she so fast?

Void's players weren't too confused. There was only one way she could arrive so quickly: Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain hadn't travelled at the same pace as the rest of the team; she had charged here alone to seize this watchtower. Travelling alone was always faster than travelling with a group. The movement speed of a character didn't just come from equipment - skills that aided movement would help increase a character's speed significantly. And Clerics and Paladins, these two healing classes, didn't have such skills. They were the short legs of the 24 Glory classes. The movement of an entire team, in order to protect the healer naturally couldn't be fast.

Void could have also sent their Launcher to move solo. But if both sides sent out one player in advance, then those two players would meet first. Yang Haoxuan duelling Su Mucheng… Li Xuan couldn't say that he didn't believe in his own teammate, but perhaps because he was always a victim of Su Mucheng, he dreaded her. And Yang Haoxuan was crucial for this team competition, so he didn't dare send him out to take on Su Mucheng by himself. Void moved as a whole team, and Su Mucheng boldly arrived first.

"How brave, everyone forward!" After giving a word of praise, Li Xuan ordered the whole team forward.

If they weren't shocked, that meant that they had predicted this situation. And if they had predicted this, would they have no plan? Void's five players instantly scattered, surrounding the 4 o'clock tower as quickly as they could. Tang Lisheng's Paladin quickly fell behind, and he looked a bit like a stumbling old man as he took the road furthest to the left. But after passing a certain point on the road, this character suddenly increased in speed drastically, starting to run with an unimaginable speed.

How?

After everyone was stunned for a moment, the display screen clearly identified in the close-up that this character was no longer Soul Defender. Void had actually boldly switched characters. The Paladin's sharp leftward movement wasn't to avoid Dancing Rain's attack range, but to reach the support zone. The Paladin left battle, and Li Xun's Assassin Ghost Lantern switched in. With a Swift Run and Swift Movements, wasn't this Assassin's movement speed a solid 1.5 times faster than the Paladin's?

With this, Void's plan couldn't be any clearer. They had guessed that Su Mucheng would arrive solo to claim a watchtower, so they gave her that chance. Then, they directly switched out their healer, five characters would attack at once to try to take Dancing Rain down first!

The two Ghostblades activated Ghost Step, the Exorcist Blue Exorcist used a Speed Talisman, the Launcher Translucent used Aerial Cannon, the Assassin Ghost Lantern felt that Swift Run and Swift Movements weren't enjoyable enough and used a Shining Cut as well. Five characters, through their individual methods, reached their top movement speeds, instantly converging upon the 4 o'clock watchtower. Their positions had also clearly been planned in advance. From Su Mucheng's high ground, she could stop one of them, but she couldn't simultaneously attack all five.

And so Su Mucheng ignored four of the players and focused her firepower on Li Xuan's Phantom Demon, Crying Devil.

Under the firepower suppression, Crying Devil naturally couldn't continue forward easily, and quickly fell behind the other four. But those four had already swiftly approached the 4 o'clock tower, and Yang Haoxuan's Translucent was already occasionally lifting his cannon to fire attacks toward Dancing Rain at the top of the tower.

"Successfully in position!" As expected of the fastest class, the Assassin. Even though he had a late start because of Tang Lisheng's Paladin, he had actually reached the bottom of the tower first. As he reported in the chat, Li Xuan controlled Ghost Lantern to circle around the base to reach the stairs behind it. But when he circled around, Li Xun instantly came to a halt.

This… this… aren't there too many people here?

Behind the watchtower, one, two, three, four… Happy's four players were in formation and waiting for him…

Chapter 1228: A Risky Move

Li Xun's shock couldn't described with just words. Speaking of which, only Team Void's six players didn't know about the four Happy players hiding. Even the Team Void players sitting at their bench had seen Happy's movements through the viewers' omniscient view. Unfortunately, they couldn't inform their teammates on stage. They could only run around in circles anxiously like cats on a hot tin roof.

As for the crowd?

They didn't feel shocked like Li Xun. They could only wait expectantly for Team Void to rush forward and run into an unexpected situation. And now, the time had finally come.

This was the climax of the script!

When Li Xun's Ghost Lantern ran past the watchtower and came across Happy's four players, the crowd fired up.

Li Xun only needed a glance to understand what had just happened because the four characters waiting here were Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion.

Yes, no healer. They had no one slowing them down. Happy came up full force. It wasn't just Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain, but everyone. As for Little Cold Hands? He had probably switched with Steamed Bun Invasion as soon as the match started… the starting spawn point was also the support zone.

1v4?

Li Xun wasn't that naive, but what should he do now? He had run here as fast as he could, so his movement skills were all on cooldown. He couldn't escape nor could he beat them. He had to hurry and inform his teammates of his situation.

"Trapped!"

Li Xun chose to use the most concise way possible to notify his teammates as Happy's four character threw themselves at him.

Trapped? Did they need a reminder? Team Void's four other players weren't far from Li Xun's Ghost Lantern, so they saw the ambush from Happy's four players. Everyone was stunned.

Ghost Lantern was surrounded in an instant. Team Void was now at a huge disadvantage.

How did this happen?

Li Xuan wasn't famous for his tactical skill, and he didn't like to take risks. He quickly felt the difference between the two team's tactical levels.

The difference was "risk"!

When the match started, Void could have sent their Launcher, Yang Haoxuan, to fight for this position, but because they didn't want to risk it, fearing that Yang Haoxuan would be suppressed by Su Mucheng. Thus, the team spread out further to be safer.

As for Happy? They directly abandoned their healer and made a beeline towards this position to get there as fast as possible. Without Void knowing, Happy arrived, while having Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain make a feint towards the high grounds. Happy had played extremely risky. If Void hadn't impatiently tried to take down Dancing Rain and continued their advance forward, even if Dancing Rain held the high grounds, being without a healer wasn't something that a skilled support character could make up for. In fierce close combat, Launchers could not stop a relentless offensive.

Unfortunately, Void didn't do this.

They did not dare risk it, but they did not steadily advance forward either. When they saw Su Mucheng take the high grounds, they viewed it as their opportunity to victory, so they started moving full speed ahead, even switching out their healer for a damage dealer midway.

The risk they took had been after seeking for stability. Compared to Happy, who risked it all at the start, their risk had been much smaller. 　　

Ghost Lantern was instantly surrounded. Void's other four players immediately understood the situation too.

What should they do?

"Rescue!"

Li Xuan typed a single word in chat.　　

They had no choice but to save him. Li Xun alone probably had no chance of escaping a 4v1 situation. If he died, it would become a 5v6. Although Void could have their sixth player sub in, it would still be a 5v5. However, Happy would have an extra player as a backup, allowing them to play more forcefully to take the initiative. Forcing the two sides to trade would be disadvantageous for Void.

Thus, at this moment, Li Xuan didn't choose to retreat, instead calling for everyone to hurry over. After all, the rest of Void wasn't that far from him. With a ghost boundary placed down, Li Xuan felt like he should be able to quickly find an opening for Li Xun to get away.

Ice Soul!

Li Xuan's character was the number one Phantom Demon in Glory, Crying Devil. The Silver weapon in his hands Four Heavenly Wheels strengthened three elements, Fire, Ice, and Darkness. The glittering ice crystals swept over the darkness of Ghostblades. The cast time was extremely short too; the Ice Boundary was set down almost instantly.

However, almost instant meant it wasn't instant. The moment the Ice Boundary started to form, Li Xuan saw a grenade at his feet.

The grenade exploded. Crying Devil dodged it, but the Ice Boundary failed to be placed down. Li Xuan looked upwards and saw Dancing Rain's long hair and clothing fluttering in the wind at the top of the watchtower.

She really is our nemesis! Li Xuan sighed, but...

A shadow flickered past Crying Devil, practically the instant the grenade exploded. Ice crystals flowed from the tachi in his hands; it just wasn't as dazzling as Four Heavenly Wheels.

Carved Ghost's weapon, Heavenly Crimson Lotus strengthened fire element skills. His Ice Boundary wasn't skilled very high either, so the ice crystals swirling around Heavenly Crimson Lotus didn't look as glamorous. Moreover, compared to Crying Devil, Carved Ghost's cast time was a bit slower. But at this moment, the phantom soul from Heavenly Crimson Lotus flew out, forming the Ice Boundary. The area surrounding Ghost Lantern froze into ice.

Who could be more skilled at coordinating with boundaries than Void's Ghostblade duo? Whether it was each other's thoughts, habits, or characters, the two had reached the point of perfection. They no longer needed to speak to communicate.

Crying Devil, the number one Phantom Demon, had just been cover. The one to actually lay down the Ice Boundary was Carved Ghost. In that instant, Void completed an extremely beautiful display of teamwork.

How could Happy not retreat from an Ice Boundary?

The threat of Carved Ghost's Ice Boundary might be slightly lower, but its effects couldn't be ignored.

However, Happy didn't retreat.

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea swung both his arms, creating a Qi Guard. This Ice Boundary had been blocked by it. The two opponents who fought intensely in the group arena once once again clashed in the team competition.

The ice energy struck the Qi Guard, but the power of Carved Ghost's Ice Boundary was limited. It evidently could not break through Boundless Sea's Qi Guard. The skill used to try and save Ghost Lantern as soon as possible was blocked.

Missing this opportunity, Ghost Lantern took more damage. Li Xuan's Crying Devil charged forward to place down another boundary, when he heard the whistle of missiles flying above his head. Dancing Rain let out all of her firepower towards the two Ghostblades.

The two dodged, one to the left and the other to the right. They ignored Dancing Rain and continued to charge towards the encirclement. Ge Caijie's Blue Exorcist waved his hands and took out his scythe. Lightning descended from the sky and gathered on the scythe. He had clearly placed a Lightning Talisman on it.

Qi Guard was unable to completely block this attack. A Soul Guidanced weapon had very high priority. It couldn't be blocked by a normal attack, but among the ones that could, another Soul Guidance was naturally included!

Inside the encirclement, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella left his hands and spun towards the scythe.

The two skills collided. It could be seen that Lord Grim's Soul Guidance priority was slightly weaker. After all, he wasn't an Exorcist. However, this collision stopped Blue Exorcist's attack from reaching its desired location. Although it didn't completely block it, it helped the others in Happy dodge this attack.

After this collision, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was recalled back by Lord Grim and started hitting Ghost Lantern's head again. Along with a Fling, Ghost Lantern was thrown out. However, before Void could be happy about it, they saw that the others in Happy had prepared in advance for this toss and were already heading towards there. Ghost Lantern wasn't even able to land on the ground before Steamed Bun Invasion grabbed him with a Strangle.

Happy focused their attacks, while moving with their target. Turning around the watchtower dumbfounded Void's Launcher. Yang Haoxuan had just been about to launch a Satellite Beam, but with this turn, he no longer had any vision of them. However, he wasn't able to stop himself in time and the Satellite Beam was still completed. In the end, it awkwardly landed on Carved Ghost's head, who was chasing after them. On the watchtower, Su Mucheng took advantage of this Satellite Beam and shot him tumbling with a Laser Beam.

Carved Ghost and Crying Devil crossed each other and switched positions, while also using Ghost Step, which had gone off cooldown. The two characters sprinted, leaving afterimages behind them, but Happy suddenly caught them off guard.

Shatter the Lands!

Tang Rou's Soft Mist leapt high into the air and let loose a high-level skill.

Who dared to take this skill head on? The two Ghostblades could only retreat. Soft Mist didn't continue fighting, after her attack got rid of them, she immediately went back to attack Ghost Lantern. Ta ta ta ta, Lord Grim fired a Gatling Gun to follow up. A shower of bullets spilled out happily.

Void was having a headache!

They thought that their Ghostblades, who specialised in controlling the field, would be able to quickly let Li Xun escape. Who would have thought that they would be forced into such a pitiful position. As a result, not only did they fail to rescue their teammate, they fell into a trap. They wouldn't be able to get a healer to support them in a short amount of time, but Happy? It was already Round 14. Everyone had seen Lord Grim suddenly wave his umbrella and cast a few heals before. No one would disregard his healing.

"Retreat!"

They had just yelled "Rescue!" and in the blink of an eye, it had turned into a "Retreat!" It couldn't be said that this was Li Xuan hesitating. The circumstances had changed. Seeing that rescuing wasn't working and fighting would be difficult, they could only let go of one of their players and save their own lives so they could fight another battle.

Who would have thought that while Void had given up, Happy hadn't. Sensing Void's intentions, Happy abandoned Ghost Lantern and chased after them.

Chapter 1229: Team Void’s Launcher

Team Void was still a pro team; even in retreat, there was strategy. They could not ignore the enemy as they backed away, and saw Lord Grim and Boundless Sea standing nearly mirrored, opening their palms with almost identical stances...

Cloud Grasping Fist!

And it was two at the same time!

Of Team Void's four players, besides Yang Haoxuan's Translucent, everyone else was within range of these two grabs. Luckily, they noticed their movements in time and hastily scrambled around frantically. If Cloud Grasping Fist could not be interrupted, the only other way to escape from it was to run around constantly so the enemy couldn't pinpoint them. The qi released by Cloud Grasping Fist was completely invisible.

The attention of these three players were entirely focused on the two Cloud Grasping Fists, when they saw Yang Haoxuan roar in chat: "ABOVE!"

Above?

The moment they saw the message, they felt an abnormality in the lighting of their field of view, but it was already too late do anything. A Satellite Beam descended from the sky.

The three had only been focused on the two Cloud Grasping Fists, so for a moment, they forgot about Dancing Rain, who was above them. And the price for their mistake was painful. The central Satellite Beam struck Crying Devil, and the following smaller beams thoroughly disrupted their rhythm.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou's Soft Mist seized this opportunity to force her way into their ranks. Although her charge didn't hit anyone, her follow-up Tyrant's Destruction sent Blue Exorcist, who was busy dodging the rotating beams of light, flying away.

Blue Exorcist lost his balance. However, Tyrant's Destruction wasn't a grab skill that locked the body. As Blue Exorcist flew in the air, Ge Caijie hastily regained his balance. In this instant, Ge Caijie's calmness showed. The Soul Guidanced scythe flew out, not towards Soft Mist, nor was it to stop Happy's counterattack. Instead, it was thrown to its max distance, towards Steamed Bun Invasion, who had pinned Ghost Lantern to the ground was beating him up.

Lock Talisman!

A Talisman, which could help Li Xun break out from the assault, was attached to the scythe.

Li Xun and Ghost Lantern had already been abandoned, but because of the change in circumstances, Ge Caijie calmly made this decision. With Team Void's rhythm disrupted, this was a decision to disrupt Happy's rhythm. If Li Xun was saved, he could form a pincer attack with the rest of Void and again open up the enemy's formation. This was the best case scenario for Void's current situation.

Suddenly, a "biu" sounded. Ge Caijie looked up and saw a beam of light fire from Dancing Rain's cannon and accurately strike the scythe.

Soul Guidance had high priority, but the burst from Laser Beam was not weak either. This Laser Beam was unable to completely stop the scythe dead on its tracks, but it knocked it towards the ground. With a hum, the scythe stuck into the ground about half a unit away from Steamed Bun Invasion. The talisman on the scythe activated, but it didn't do anything. As for Steamed Bun Invasion? He didn't react until now. If Su Mucheng hadn't shot down the scythe, Steamed Bun, who was in the middle of beating up Ghost Lantern, would have most likely been hit.

If the attack had connected, the Lock Talisman would have taken effect. Void would briefly have a 5v4 situation, and the tides would turn. Ge Caijie's calm, swift decision was truly terrifying, however...

Looking up at that Launcher at the top of the watchtower, Ge Caijie was filled with awe.

He had joined the Alliance last season, just when Excellent Era had been relegated from the league. As a result, he had never fought against Su Mucheng's Launcher. Although there was quite some controversy over Su Mucheng in the public eye, Team Void had suffered under her hands and had nothing but praise for her. When Li Xuan and Wu Yuce, his two seniors, had heard about Team Excellent Era getting relegated, Ge Caijie clearly heard them let out a "sigh of relief". The person who had given these two All-Stars such pressure was Su Mucheng.

What type of player is she?

Ge Caijie had always been curious about Su Mucheng.

And now, after personally going into battle against her, Ge Caijie could finally feel just how unbearable of an existence this top supportive player was. Li Xuan and Wu Yuce probably had the strongest feeling of this unbearableness.

Ge Caijie had nearly reverse the situation with Soul Guidance, but because of Su Mucheng's Laser Beam, his attack had been blocked. Team Void had scattered like sand. Right now, Yang Haoxuan, who had been picked for the team competition specifically to counter Su Mucheng, felt very ashamed of himself.

His purpose was to restrict Su Mucheng, but what had he done so far?　

When the match started, Team Void had not sent him out to fight for the high grounds. Yang Haoxuan knew what the team had been worried about, but he didn't have the confidence to stand out and take the initiative to express that he could do it. If he had displayed this kind of courage and confidence, Yang Haoxuan knew that the team would have certainly given him the chance to prove himself. However, he hadn't. He had even felt glad that the team hadn't forced him to carry out this task. This was Yang Haoxuan himself not confident in himself, but at the same time, it was the shadow that Su Mucheng had placed in their hearts.

After the two sides started fighting, Su Mucheng occupied the high grounds and had an amazing field of view and position. However, it wasn't like Yang Haoxuan was sitting there doing nothing. He could also utilize his long-ranged attacks to suppress Su Mucheng. But from the looks of it, it seemed like he wasn't doing anything. At least, in the crucial moments, he hadn't displayed any usefulness. On the other hand, Su Mucheng had repeatedly disrupted Team Void several times.

It shouldn't be like this. What should I do?

Yang Haoxuan told himself that, but in this chaotic situation that he could readn't clearly, he wasn't able to make a precise and effective judgement. In the end, he was just a long ranged attacker, standing at the farthest and safest position, a decoration for their team's offensive prowess. Change the tides? Yang Haoxuan had neither the courage nor the confidence. Even if he had the ability to make a difference, the probability of it happening was unlikely.

Yang Haoxuan's Translucent stood there far far away as if he were truly translucent. Sometimes, he would throw some AoE attacks towards where the Ghost Duo were attacking. Sometimes, he would nervously look upwards to observe Su Mucheng's actions and then send a few attacks towards her.

"Yang Haoxuan, what exactly are you doing!"

Finally, Wu Yuce yelled out in the chat. This enduring vice-captain very rarely gave any orders or directions, perhaps he was intentionally avoiding it. After all, Team Void's Ghost Duo was a pair with debate over who was better. Wu Yuce didn't want to exceed his place and disrupt the balance by meddling in other people's matters. He very carefully kept a certain distance away from captain Li Xuan. His voice was oftentimes even less heard than the regular team members during a match.

But now, this vice captain had done what he rarely ever did. He spoke. Let alone, Yang Haoxuan, even the others felt a shiver in surprise.

"Focus on Su Mucheng. Don't bother with anything else!" Wu Yuce said with unwavering certainty.

Yang Haoxuan tensed up. He looked upwards with practically zero thought behind it and saw Dancing Rain aiming at a target from the edge of the watchtower. Yang Haoxuan didn't even think and shot a Laser Beam towards her.

An involuntary action was the fastest. Yang Haoxuan lifting up his head and Laser Beam was practically simultaneous because he had done it without any thinking at all.

When Su Mucheng saw Translucent look towards her, she didn't think the attack would be so fast. Laser Beam's speed was extremely fast too, flashing in front of her in the blink of an eye. Even if Su Mucheng wanted to dodge, it was too late. The Laser Beam struck her ferociously, pushing her off the watchtower.

"Beautiful!" Their captain Li Xuan was busy, but he took the time to praise Yang Haoxuan. Picking Yang Haoxuan to counter Su Mucheng was proof of his capabilities. Everyone approved of him. The problem was that he lacked the courage and confidence to face Su Mucheng.

Su Mucheng was said to be Li Xuan's and Wu Yuce's nemesis, and when they faced Su Mucheng, they cowered at times. How could the other players not show fear for Su Mucheng in this kind of atmosphere? What's more, Yang Haoxuan was a Launcher, while Su Mucheng was an All-Star Launcher. All Stars were chosen out of popular vote, but where did popularity come from? The foundation came from skill, so it was also a form of of recognition towards a player's skill. Thus, Yang Haoxuan always felt like he couldn't compare to Su Mucheng. That was in addition to Team Void's atmosphere. Putting him to face Su Mucheng? Not having confidence or courage couldn't entirely blamed on him. So the team tried to encourage him. When they saw this attack, their team captain immediately went out of his way to praise him.

Sure enough, this Laser Beam woke up Yang Haoxuan. Even though it didn't instantly make him feel like he was invincible,he had to do what he needed to do. His mind suddenly cleared up.

Wu Yuce had roared at him to focus on Su Mucheng and nothing else, but this was just to point out how important it was. How could pro players only single mindedly work on one task? As a result, the instant Dancing Rain was blasted away, Translucent shifted his attention back to the other battles, providing support for his team. From time to time, he would pay attention to Dancing Rain.

Dancing Rain was pushed out of the watchtower, but Su Mucheng reacted extremely fast. She fired several cannon shots to counteract the knockback from the Laser Beam and slow her descent. Then, she used the Mechanic's Rotor Wing, putting her back on top of the watchtower.

In Glory, character skill trees could be reset as long as you spent the money. Normal players might try to avoid doing so to save money, but pro teams wouldn't care about this bit of money. Whether it was to test out new skill setups or picking skills specifically to counter opponents, resetting skill trees was a common practice. Sometimes, it was possible to make surprising changes to one's playstyle. Li Xuan's Crying Devil was as Phantom Demon, but it wasn't like he had never reset his points and reallocated it as a Sword Demon. This sort of situation wouldn't happen too often though. After all, his Phantom Demon was his best character.

Su Mucheng had probably reset her skills to learn Rotor Wings specifically for this match! As Yang Haoxuan guessed, Translucent's cannon once again aimed towards the air.

Chapter 1230: Caution at the End

Boom!

The missiles flew out from the chamber and towards Dancing Rain, who was on top of the watchtower.

Fighting with the lower ground was very difficult, and many skills couldn't even be used. For example, Heat-Seeking Missiles would never be able to get so high and Stingers couldn't be launched so far either, otherwise these AoE attacks would easily send Dancing Rain toppling from her perch.

Yang Haoxuan, with the lower ground, was at a disadvantage. However, right now, his helplessness from before had been completely swept away, his attacks determined and confident, his aim precise. Three Anti-Tank Missiles were shot towards Dancing Rain's landing point.

Boom boom boom!

The three missiles exploded on the side of the watchtower just as Dancing Rain was landing. Dancing Rain, still airborne, couldn't dodge so far. The force from the three consecutive explosions threw Dancing Rain even higher. Su Mucheng hurriedly had Dancing Rain carefully bring her cannon muzzle around. She had to adjust Dancing Rain so that she could still remain on the watchtower when she landed.

As expected of Su Mucheng!

Yang Haoxuan fell into awe at Su Mucheng's mechanical skill, but he didn't plan on just admiring it. Translucent took out a gatling gun with a swish to follow up with another attack to the airborne Dancing Rain and send her completely off the watchtower. Currently, her Rotor Wing's wason cooldown, so there was no way she could fly back up.

Ratatatatatatata….

　

The sound of bullets came rapidly, the frequency was so high that it was a little unbelievable… The rpm of this skill depended on equipment stats, not mechanics. Such high rpm meant that this couldn't be a skill from Translucent.

Tatatatata!

The bullets formed a line, shooting out from under the watchtower. On the other end of the line was Translucent's left hand, which was holding his gun.

Thud thud thud!

With sound of bullets hitting flesh, blood splashed everywhere. Translucent's left hand wasn't really blasted into smithereens, but it still couldn't take the momentum. Immediately, the bullets he was shooting into the air went off target.

"Damnit!" Li Xuan was depressed, cursing.

Yang Haoxuan had already done very well. His amazing performance had almost succeeded in throwing Dancing Rain off from the watchtower, yet this time, it was Li Xuan and co who failed. In this most crucial time, they didn't give Yang Haoxuan the support he needed, allowing Lord Grim to destroy Translucent's offensive, with the exact same skill.

　

There was only one chance!

Under Su Mucheng's precise manipulation, Dancing Rain landed accurately back onto the watchtower.

　

"You should never neglect my presence!" Ye Xiu pointed out methodically but sarcastically. It was clear that the opening Void had given him this time was far too big.

　

Yes, too big.

Void's members were so focused on the trouble Su Mucheng was giving them that they had forgotten Su Mucheng was always only ever a supporting character, and the person she was supporting was the true core of the team.

Ye Xiiu...

They had somehow forgotten Ye Xiu and given the opponent's core player such a large opening.

This mistake meant that Void had to suffer the terrible consequences. Dancing Rain, back on the watchtower, immediately threw out a Stinger. The stingers rained down like flower petals thrown by a goddess, and then Gatling Gun swept over them wildly, creating small pits in the ground. Yang Haoxuan's Translucent dodged around with his heavy cannon, flowers of blood occasionally blooming on on his body.

Not grasping the chance meant an even worse blow.

Under Dancing Rain's cover, Happy focused everything onto offense. Tang Rou's Soft Mist broke right through the Ghost Duo's "Slash and Boundary", beginning a direct conversation with Crying Devil. Wu Yuce's Carved Ghost wanted to come to the other's support, but Crying Devil suddenly vanished from sight, Lord Grim clocking the way with his umbrella.

Ge Caijie suddenly felt that this was a good chance, hurling a Sealing Talisman towards the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. However, that was when he saw a message pop up in the chat: "Boss, careful!". A Brick smacked the back of his head and Blue Exorcist was stunned.

At the same time, Li Xun's Ghost Lantern was blown flying by a Flash Burst. Li Xun had wanted to sneak attack Boundless Sea, but Fang Rui was the master of this kind of dirty play. Noticing Li Xun's intentions, Fang Rui had purposefully given the other an opening. Li Xun's Ghost Lantern had came over all delighted, but went back, ridden with internal injuries.

Void's formation had been completely ruined, and the result was clear. Happy took advantage of the chaos Void had been thrown into, switching targets several times, and giving each member of Void a warm greeting.

This made Void depressed.

Happy, with the absolute advantage, didn't rush and hurry to get rid of a single opponent first, but open fired on all of Void.　

If they focused their attacks and wiped out one of Void's members, then their healer would be forced to switch in. They wouldn't know what would happen in that short period of 4v5, but so long as they endured until their healer came, then they'd fight a 5v5 with a healer and have a chance to turn things around, even if they might be one character short.

But now, Happy launching an attack on everyone in Void's team cruelly deprived them of this unknown chance.

Void knew that they couldn't let Happy chip away at them like this, but apart from Yang Haoxuan's Translucent, none of the others had much of a chance to escape. Yang Haoxuan was trying to deal with Dancing Rain's supporting fire from above. After Wu Yuce had yelled at him, he had found his courage and was performing exceptionally well. They really couldn't have him leave to switch out with the healer.

They had to risk it!

　

That was when Li Xun suddenly activated Life-Risking Strike.

With how much of a mess Void was right now, there was no way to give him support and increase his chances of success. Under these circumstances, Li Xun still used this skill. Everyone immediately realized what he was doing.

He was sacrificing himself. If he managed to hit, then that would be amazing for their team, if he didn't, then Ghost Lantern, with only a sliver of life left, would soon make a noble sacrifice and their healer would be switched in.

As for ignoring Ghost Lantern and purposefully keeping him alive? That wasn't possible. If they kept a character they didn't dare get close to alive, then that would be equal to giving themselves a huge handicap. If Happy did decide to do that, then that would be like deciding to kill their own characters.

The situation ended up going in the most predictable direction.

Li Xun's Life-Risking Strike didn't hit and Ghost Lantern was immediately killed. Void's healer, Tang Lishengi's Paladin, Spirit Guardian, was switched in from the closest support zone, hurrying over.

　

However, in this short time, Happy switched tactics. They began to focus all their attacks onto one person. Could they manage to wipe out one of Void's players before their healer arrived?

This became the deciding factor, and everyone watched with wide eyes.

Void's core Ghostblade Duo weren't very tanky. Ghostblades utilized the power of the Ghost God to fight, finding their strengths in Spirit and Intelligence, then Strength, then Vitality. Then, their armor was cloth armor. Against physical damage, Ghostblades weren't much better than Elementalists and others.

At the same time, the Ghost Duo's Wu Yuce was a very headstrong and forceful fighter. In this moment, his playstyle had been grasped by Happy, and they immediately caught Carved Ghost and began to beat the other down.

Void was practically going crazy, trying to save him, however, Happy clearly didn't plan on switching tactics now. In the end Carved Ghost was finally caught by Steamed Bun Invasion's Strangle and thrown against the wall of the watchtower, allowing Happy to put everything into destroying him. During their offensive, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim's presence once again shone through. Though it might be weak, it was better than nothing. The unspecialized Lord Grim was able to provide an important healing role. Void had realized that upon seeing Happy's no-healer arrangement.

They had realized, but they couldn't do anything against it. It wasn't like they could change Lord Grim's skill build.

In crucial moments, the few tricks Lord Grim had was enough to help Happy stabilize the situation. Wu Yuce's Carved Ghost eventually fell against the wall.Tang Lisheng's Spirit Guardian ended up being just one step too late.

6v4, currently a 5v4 on the field.

Void didn't want to give up though. Spirit Guardian healed the remaining three characters like crazy. Void was planning to make a final charge.

And then, Happy dispersed.

Yes, even Dancing Rain, on the watchtower, jumped down of her own volition, using her cannon to adjust her position in the air, gliding down smoothly.

Happy, who had the advantage, could retreat with ease, and at the drop of a hat.

Speaking of which, wasn't the direction they were retreating in the direction of the support zone on that end?

Seeing Void's healer arrive, Happy decided to not rush things and ran off to get their healer on the field, too. They really weren't planning on giving Void a single chance.

At the start, Happy had thrown their healer away to get to the best positions quicker, very brave, very crazy.

Yet, after getting the absolute advantage, Happy became cautious again. They, who were two people ahead of Void, went back to get their own healer.

Void couldn't stop the retreating Happy, chasing after them as the shadow of defeat grew within their hearts.

When Happy got to the support zone, Steamed Bun Invasion switched out for Little Cold Hands. Then, when they turned back to continue, Void's spirit had pretty much died. The battle ended quickly.

　

10 to 0!!!

The audience erupted.

Another 10 to 0. Happy really did it. After completing a 10 to 0 against Misty Rain, this time, they got another 10 to 0 against Void. Who would doubt Happy's strength now? If they did, they were probably blind! 10 to 0 after 10 to 0 couldn't be luck speaking!

The Happy supporters in the venue cheered wildly, raising an open-palm hand into the air, waving.

Five!

Their opened palms represented the number "five".

Five times!

This was the number of 10 to 0s that Happy had achieved so far. Such a flawless record was something that many powerhouses couldn't boast having. Currently, Happy was the only one, right?

Just as Happy's fans were excitedly confirming this with each other, a shocking piece of news came from another finished battlefield. Team Samsara, having also achieved a flawless victory against Team Heavenly Swords, had obtained their fifth 10 to 0 of the season as well.

With the thought that one of these 10 to 0s were won from Happy, everyone immediately felt that this was exceptionally annoying.

Their archenemy! Many people had this thought.

Chapter 1231: Round 14 Finished

The antagonizing glares from Happy's supporters shifted straight towards Samsara. From this, it could be seen just how powerful an existence Happy was in their hearts, and Happy's recent performances on the point rankings lived up to these hopes.

After losing to Tiny Herb in Round 8, Happy began their win streak. Starting from Round 9 until the recently completed Round 14, Happy had won six rounds in a row. Four of Happy's six perfect 10-0s had taken place within these six rounds, and their other two 9-1 wins were domineering enough too.

During these six rounds, Samsara had achieved three 10-0s, two 9-1s, and one 8-2. Comparing their total points gained in these six rounds, Happy actually beat Samsara by 2 points; it was needless to say the other teams as well. Happy had unexpectedly taken the lead in the Alliance. Let alone Happy's fans, no one would take Happy lightly. Those who had hoped for Happy to fall couldn't help but feel nervous. Happy's achievements were too far off from their expectations.

After Round 14, Happy had taken another 10 points, moving up one place in the rankings with 89 total points and stepping down on Hundred Blossoms, who had been in seventh. More importantly, outside of the playoffs zone, Happy now led the ninth place Void by 10 points.

Team Void was very disappointed. The thought of Happy suddenly being ten points ahead of them, despite having the same points just the round before, had never crossed their minds. They couldn't blame any one person. In fact, over the course of the match, there had been no lack of highlights, matching vulgar post-match comment: we performed well, but our opponents performed better.

To be more specific, Void's long-time nemesis, Su Mucheng, was as domineering as ever, giving Void a huge headache. This was practically something that Void had never found a good solution to in their many years of existence. Then, there were the team competition strategies. Happy took a huge risk but succeeded with a beautiful opening, while their carefulness at the end thoroughly destroyed any last thoughts from Void. They had utilized their home map advantage extremely well.

"We lost to Happy. I can only say that this isn't the end. I look forward to our next match together," Team Void's Li Xuan said, concluding Void's post-match press conference.

Happy versus Void, a clean sweep.

Samsara versus Heavenly Swords was an even cleaner one.　

In this round, Tiny Herb, Blue Rain, and Tyranny, the traditional three powerhouses ended their matches 9-1 against opponents much weaker than them. Apart from them, Misty Rain beat Hundred Blossoms 7-3 after losing to both Void and Happy in Round 12 and Round 13.

Even so, Hundred Blossoms still held onto 8th with a total of 83 points, just inside the playoffs zone. On the other hand, despite winning this round, Misty Rain's four consecutive losses had lost them a lot of points. Misty Rain was still 10 points behind Hundred Blossoms, sitting at 11th with 73 points. Their hopes for playoffs were becoming dimmer and dimmer. It seemed to be proof that their unconventional playstyle didn't work in the pro scene.

Between the 11th place Misty Rain and the 9th place Void was Team 301, who lost 3-7 in their away game versus Miracle.

Team Miracle was currently at 14th place with 50 points. If not for the other new team Happy being so demonic, they would have certainly received much more attention. Up until now, as a newly joined team, Miracle was doing very well. They just happened to catch a good opportunity and fished up three experienced Excellent Era players. Their original lineup wasn't without its bright spots either. Guo Shao had received quite a bit of attention, especially out of all the new rookies this season.　

Royal Style, who had previously been strong contenders for the playoffs, had thoroughly fallen. They had been beaten by Tiny Herb 9 to 1 this round and were currently in 12th place. Their position on the rankings didn't seem that bad, but what about their total points? With a total of 58 points, they were 15 points away from the 11th place Misty Rain, let alone the points difference between 8th.

Team Royal Style had been a team that had contended with Team Excellent in the finals of the Season 1 championships, but now they had fallen to such a level. But then again, the former three-time championship winners, Excellent Era, had been relegated and disbanded. In comparison, Royal Style was doing much better, at least they were far away from the relegation teams.

The two relegation teams, Bright Green and Seaside, had 27 and 23 points. The third to last place Team Radiant had 41 points. Their fates seemed to have already been decided.

Seaside wasn't too surprising. These past few years, they had always been struggling in and out of the relegations zone. However, Seaside used to have an All-Star player and character on their team. They had never swam in the playoffs, but they had been a solid mid-tier team.

Zhao Yang retired, and Boundless Sea was sold. They had been mourned for a time. Seaside hadn't given up though. They could only respect Zhao Yang's decision to retire, but for Boundless Sea, they knew that as a mid-tier team, raising an All-Star level character as well as a suitable player was a big burden. And just a single All-Star was no longer enough to carry the team in the increasingly competitive Alliance. A God like Zhou Zekai was someone who could only be chanced upon. What's more, Zhou Zekai had a team of skilled teammates supporting him before winning the championships. In order to further solidify their dominance, Samsara even added in Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf to their roster.

Seaside's resources were limited. Pouring in their resources for a luxury like an All-Star was something they couldn't support. Selling Boundless Sea had been a show of their decision to walk a more steady path of improving the strength of the team as a whole.　

Hope is beautiful, but from the looks of it, Seaside hadn't really improved. In these fourteen rounds, they had even lost to Bright Green, their brother who was just as bad as them and sitting at 23 points.

The post-match press conferences for these two terrible teams were cold and deserted. The remaining reporters who stayed had great opportunities to ask whatever they wanted.

Did Team Seaside have any plans?　　

When a reporter asked this question, Seaside's captain, Zhang Lintao, showed an expression of perplexion, mumbling and faltering through it without actually saying anything.

Compared to these departing weak teams, the fans paid more attention to those fighting for the championship throne. The most watched match this round was Wind Howl versus Thunderclap. The Alliance also chose to broadcast this match. In the end, Thunderclap continued with their steadiness in the team competition, winning 6 to 4. Thunderclap relied on their five points from their team competition victory to steal the win from Wind Howl. At the end of the match, there cameras zoomed in oneTeam Wind Howl's team captain,Tang Hao, kicking a bottle of water away as he returned to his seat.

Anyone could see that Tang Hao was unhappy with this match.

2 points in the individual competition and 2 points from the group arena, giving them a 4 to 1 advantage. Wind Howl went into the team competition in high spirits, but in their home game, Wind Howl was downed with their tails behind their legs against Thunderclap.

Did Thunderclap have All Stars?

Xiao Shiqin was obviously considered one, but in the group arena, he didn't win against Tang Hao. There was no one in Thunderclap who Tang Hao cared about, yet in the team competition, this group of nobodies crushed them in the map that their Wind Howl had chosen.

"This is a disgrace!!" In the post match press conference, Tang Hao fully expressed his dissatisfaction. He didn't point his fingers at anyone, but rather his discontent towards his team as a whole for losing to Thunderclap. Even if Thunderclap was at 3rd place, in Tang Hao's eyes, Thunderclap wasn't a strong team.

"If a loss like this happens again, I really don't know what we'll have to fight in the championships," Tang Hao said.

Becoming the champions was Tang Hao's goal and Team Wind Howl's goal. They weren't satisfied with just being frequent playoff visitors. But this season, Wind Howl's performances had been inconsistent. Their momentum this season couldn't even compare to last season's. After thirteen rounds, they were only at 6th with 86 points. Although they weren't far from the other teams above them apart from Samsara, this wasn't enough for Tang Hao. Even in the regular season, he hoped to reach the same heights as Samsara. But after fourteen rounds, Samsara had 123 points, while Wind Howl had 90 points, a difference of 33 points.

Samsara. Samsara was supposed to be their only opponents. Thunderclap? How could a sudden upstart stop Wind Howl's advance? But Thunderclap really did stop them. How could Tang Hao not be unhappy?　

After fourteen rounds, although Happy's recent six round point total surpassed even Samsara's, Samsara still stood far above in the rankings with 123 points. Even the second place Blue Rain was only at 99 points, an entirely different tier than Samsara.

What was even more terrifying was that Samsara had gone through a devilish schedule in the early parts of the season. The teams that could threaten them had already fallen under their hands. Their upcoming opponents might try to study them, but the disparity in strength would only result in them giving their points to Samsara as expected. It was hard for people to think that these teams could drag down Samsara.

The suspense for this season was ending too fast, no?

Much of the media, players, and commentators expressed similar thoughts. Samsara's advance could not be stopped. There seemed to be no saving Bright Green and Seaside either. Those spots could be considered as locked into position. Then, next up, the only thing left to look at were the spots for the playoffs.

301, Void, Misty Rain, these three teams were outside the playoffs zone but they were still on the offense.

These three teams are going to need to work hard!

The people silently praised. If these three teams didn't put in more effort and make some chaos in the playoffs zone, this season's regular season would be too boring!

Chapter 1232: Round 15

After Round 14 ended, numerous reports and commentary appeared over the next two days. Scenes such as Tang Hao kicking a water bottle after a match were also reported, but those didn't make the headlines.　

Tang Hao had yet to reach the point, where he could lose but still be the central character. The headlines sung for the winners.　

Happy's fifth 10-0, Thunderclap's team competition record, and Samsara's fifth 10-0 would not be neglected. 123 points in 14 rounds, leading the second place team by 24 points, these were absolutely ridiculous achievements. This dominance cemented their place as the true central characters this season. Even though there was competition, the Esports Home's headlines displayed Samsara's 10-0. Happy would have to give way. Even Thunderclap's team competition record was inferior in front of Samsara.

Team Samsara had won all 14 matches, while Thunderclap had lost to Royal Style in Round 9. Thunderclap was one missing from a perfect win streak, a pity.　

The headlines gave more than enough respect towards the bellwether, but the detailed discussion consisted more of Happy and Thunderclap. After all, Samsara's perfect win had been against Heavenly Swords. To everyone, this win should be easy as pie without any worries of losing. What was there to talk about? However, Happy and Thunderclap were different. Happy had a perfect win over Void, while Thunderclap made a comeback against Wind Howl. Those matches had high-level content to talk about.

After discussing these two team's performances this round, everyone agreed by chance that how long their momentum would continue for would be something to pay attention to.

Next round, Happy would be challenging Lightly in their away game, while Thunderclap would be welcoming Misty Rain in their home game.　

No one questioned Happy's strength anymore. Facing the 16th place 46 point Lightly, victory seemed to be there's already. People were simply wondering whether Happy would be able to pull off another 10-0. As for Thunderclap versus Misty Rain, given Misty Rain's recent ups and downs, as well as their questionable unconventional playstyle, Misty Rain would would be facing Thunderclap, who excelled at the team competition. Very few people had hopes for Misty Rain.

In fact, more people were looking towards the round after, Round 16, because Happy and Thunderclap, these two teams that had given them the most surprises this season, would be facing against each other in Happy's home game.

Get out of the way, Round 15!

Quite a few people had these sorts of thoughts.

But time couldn't be skipped. Each round needed to be played one at a time. Round 15 couldn't just pass by in the blink of an eye. On 12/13, Round 15 began on schedule, and the broadcast chose Hundred Blossoms welcoming Void as the highlight match.

In the end, Hundred Blossoms barely beat Void 6-4. There were no changes in their placings on the rankings. Eighth place and ninth place were neighbors, but the difference between them were night and day.

A rather surprising result this round was Blue Rain losing 4-6 to Parade in their away game. Blue Rain had a huge lead after the individual rounds, but unexpectedly lost in the team competition. With this loss, Blue Rain instantly slid down from 2nd to 5th. And right below Blue Rain was Happy, who had advanced another place once again this round.

Happy won their away game against Lightly 9-1; everyone felt that it was a pity they couldn't get one more point for a 10-0. Coincidentally, Samsara also got a 9-1, although their opponents were 301.　

Tyranny and Tiny Herb won 8-2 against their mediocre opponents. Another surprising result was Wind Howl, who had the situations reversed by Thunderclap last round, once again stumbled, losing their home game against Royal Style 7-3.

This time, Tang Hao didn't kick a water bottle, but in the post-match press conference, he didn't even show up. His attitude showed just how unhappy he was with Wind Howl's recent performances.

Wind Howl had lost three rounds in a row, and their placings were dropping. Right now, they were at 7th place, lower than Happy by 5 points.

But to be fair, Wind Howl's opponents these three rounds had been Hundred Blossoms, Thunderclap, and Royal Style, all fairly strong opponents. With the team competition's 5 points lost in each of those rounds, Wind Howl had obtained 3, 4, and 3 points. Using comparisons like 8-2, 7-3, looked to be huge disparities, but because the team competition was worth 5 points, these were the most common results.

In an 8-2 win, if the losing side had won the team competition, it would turn into 3-7. In a 7-3 win, if the losing side had won the team competition, it would be a 2-8.

In reality, the wide disparity between points was a result of the way the rules were set up. It was completely different than a 7-3 or an 8-2 in football.

Wind Howl's three consecutive losses were these point differences. It could be said that their strength still had a solid foundation. However, three consecutive losses still raised some doubts over them, although in comparison to the public, Wind Howl themselves had a huge reaction to it. After two losses in a row, their captain Tang Hao couldn't bear it anymore and kicked a water bottle. After their third loss in a row, he wasn't even in the mood to show up for the post-match press conference.

"I think our loss streak ends here…" With their captain not there, vice captain Liu Hao spoke up in the press conference.

Yes, Liu Hao.

　

The former Excellent Era vice captain had switched to Thunderclap and became Thunderclap's vice captain. In the summer, he transferred to Wind Howl and gradually created a position for himself. After their original vice captain Fang Rui left, Liu Hao was appointed vice captain.　

After all, Liu Hao was skilled, and he had plenty of experience. He had acted as vice captain and as captain before, so he had experience in leading. At Wind Howl, he was seen as someone who would be a great help to Tang Hao.

For example, Tang Hao had gotten angry and didn't show up to the press conference, while Liu Hao talked fluidly as if he were used to be in this position. It was as if their captain didn't exist.

Everyone was a bit astonished at his bearing, but then again, of course Liu Hao was used to this because when he had been in Excellent Era, their captain Ye Xiu never showed up for press conferences. It was always him who had to face the media as the vice captain. Liu Hao had experienced his team's captain not participating in the press conference countless times. How could he not be calm?

Experienced with the media, he resolutely expressed that they would definitely win next round. The reporters quickly checked next round's schedule. Next round Wind Howl would be facing Heavenly Swords in their home game. These three rounds never really showed whether Wind Howl was truly weak. Next round, as long as their mentality was fine, they shouldn't have any problems winning against Heavenly Swords. However, Team Wind Howl's team captain and core, the Tang Hao who succeeded the senior as the junior, seemed to be undergoing an unbearable setback!

"I'm not worried at all," Liu Hao continued to speak calmly, "Our captain thirsts for victory more than anyone else, so he also feels more ashamed than anyone else when he loses. But when the match comes, he'll still be striving for victory. That I believe without a doubt."

A good answer!　　

Wind Howl's PR team felt very gratified. They were especially moved by their vice captain this time. Thinking of their previous Wind Howl vice captain for many years, Fang Rui… what an irresponsible guy! He would often babble nonsense in the press conference without the bearing of a vice captain at all. The PR team wanted to rush up and beat him up numerous times.

As the PR team, they looked at things from their perspective, and to them, the difference between Liu Hao and Fang Rui was light years apart. As for Fang Rui being an All-Star, what did that help? It didn't!　　

With Liu Hao's skillful response, Wind Howl's captain Tang Hao's attitude after three consecutive losses didn't garner any particular attention. When the press conference ended, Wind Howl's PR team gave Liu Hao a huge thumbs up and started chatting with this newly appointed Wind Howl vice captain.

This was the scene for Wind Howl, but how about Blue Rain, who had been upset?

Blue Rain's performance in the early season had been quite strong. Apart from their loss to Samsara 3-7 in their away game, whether it was Tiny Herb, Tyranny, or Wind Howl, they always had the last laugh.

But after the early season, Blue Rain was a team whose honeymoon had clearly ended. In Round 11, they lost to Hundred Blossoms 3-7 in their away game. In Round 12, they had a beautiful 5-0 lead in their home game, but Thunderclap won the team competition to even it up 5-5. In Round 13, they were knocked down by Royal Style 4-6 in their away game. In Round 14, Blue Rain unexpectedly lost to Parade.

From their performances these few rounds, Blue Rain had stayed at 2nd place. It could be seen just how strong Blue Rain's opening in the early season was. However, in an instant, this 24 point difference disappeared. After the end of Round 15, Blue Rain dropped three places from 2nd to 5th. They were now only 5 points away from Happy, who was in 6th. 5 points. In Glory, this could be a difference of just a single round.

Blue Rain's decline wasn't just this past match, but rather during this phase. However, no one had been so frustrated to the extent of kicking a water bottle like Tang Hao. In their post-match press conferences, their captain and core replied calmly to the reporters' questions as always.

Where did Team Blue Rain's problems lie?

This was what everyone was wondering.

"I think, it's just a matter of bad luck," Team Blue Rain's captain, Yu Wenzhou, smiled.

"If we keep saving up all the good luck like this, then I think it'll be a good thing when the playoffs come around!" Yu Wenzhou continued.

Saving up luck...

The reporters didn't know whether to laugh or cry. This was a completely unscientific explanation! However, speaking of playoffs, Blue Rain's recent performances had truly started to worry people about their playoffs spot. They never directly said that they would definitely win. They just gently took out the word "playoffs" as if it were as simple as eating food.

This was also a form of confidence!

Chapter 1233: Thunderclap’s Secret Weapon

After the early season ended, all sorts of twists and turns started appearing.

Blue Rain, Wind Howl, Misty Rain, and Void, these powerhouses all experienced different degrees of setbacks. In comparison, Tyranny, who had a disappointing start, stayed firm in this smoke-filled battlefield.

Tyranny had only obtained 47 points in the first 8 rounds, tying with Hundred Blossoms for 7th and 8th place, right at the edge of the playoffs zone. But in their next seven rounds, Tyranny obtained 58 points. Not only did their performance not decline, it went up.

Of course, a part of that was because Tyranny's opponents weren't that strong. However, facing these mediocre opponents, Tyranny won quite a few 10-0s and 9-1s. The points they should have gotten were gotten. That was the sort of air they gave off. On the rankings, they had quietly climbed to 3rd place.

Placed ahead of them was Tiny Herb with 106 points. They had the same consistency as Tyranny, rarely losing points against weak teams. However, against strong teams, Tiny Herb faltered. The other top five teams, Samsara, Blue Rain, Tyranny, Thunderclap, could bump into Tiny Herb in the regular season, the playoffs, or the finals.

But in these fifteen rounds, Tiny Herb always lost to these four teams, whether it was their home or away game.

If you said that Tiny Herb's strength didn't belong there, then that would be false. If you looked closely, you would see that in these four rounds, the final point tally was always 4-6.

This meant that Tiny Herb always won two individual competition rounds and the group arena, but lost in the team competition. If Tiny Herb had won the team competition, their matches against these four teams would have been 9-1.　　

Team competition...

Tiny Herb's weakness seemed to be obvious. It looked like there was something stopping them in the team competition, stopping them from beating the top teams. From the statistics, people discovered another surprising fact. Tiny Herb had yet to lose a group arena. Even in their 2-8 match against Void, their points had been through the group arena.　

Apart from Tiny Herb, no one else had achieved such a feat this season.　　

The strengths and weaknesses of many teams had been exposed. While everyone was discussing these enthusiastically, they could not ignore Happy's existence.

Samsara had never lost the team competition, Tiny Herb had never lost the group arena, as for Happy? One person had never lost an individual round!

Ye Xiu. He had retired, returned, and then switched classes, but his performances on stage were as eye-catching as ever. After getting swept 0-10 in Round 1 against Samsara, Ye Xiu started playing in the individual competition, becoming a stabilizing piece for Happy. From then on, no matter if it was a loss, this 1 point had never left Happy's pockets. Before, Ye Xiu had always stayed hidden, never appearing on camera. After returning to the scene, even though he wasn't particularly great for the media, he at least didn't completely avoid them, though it was hard to say if that was a curse or a blessing.

Another week quickly passed, and 12/20 welcomed the Glory Pro League's sixteenth round. The most hyped match was Happy versus Thunderclap, the two most surprising teams this season, were chosen without question as the highlight match.

Thunderclap was in 4th place with 104 points, while Happy was in 6th place with 98 points, a difference of only 6 points. This round was Happy's home game. If they did a good job, they could pass Thunderclap in just one round. But if they wanted to do a good job, beating Thunderclap in the team competition was necessary. Up until now, Thunderclap had only lost to Royal Style in the team competition. In all of their other matches, they always won the team competition. Even down 5-0, they had won, tying the score. And the the team they had tied was Team Blue Rain, who had the Master Tactician, Yu Wenzhou.

Just how mysterious were Thunderclap's team tactics? Many people were curious and had even studied this issue. At the moment, opinions differed, and when Xiao Shiqin was interviewed, he simply smiled and gave three words as a reply: believe in yourself.

What was that supposed to mean? Was that his philosophy? Was that the way to a psychological win?

Not many approved of his reply, so everyone continued to analyze Thunderclap's mysterious tactics. Confrontations between Master Tacticians were always the best research material, so this match would bring in more valuable data. Happy's Ye Xiu, may be the current 1v1 King with a 14 round win streak, but don't forget that this old general was also one of the four Master Tacticians.

"You guys are doing well!"

"Back at you."

After a quick greeting, the two teams went to their own sides. As the two most surprising teams this season, each knew how the other felt. Thunderclap's captain, Xiao Shiqin, could be considered as having the deepest impression of Happy before the season. He had fought against Happy in a bitter struggle in the Challenger League. In particular, the group arena 1v3 had nearly killed Happy's heart, but in the end, Happy was the one to have the last laugh. Excellent Era lost in the Challenger League finals, and Xiao Shiqin, who had risked everything to run to the Challenger League in hopes of a better future, looked like an idiot. There had been no lack of mockery thrown at him.

Xiao Shiqin should hate Happy very much, no?

This was also a popular pre-match topic. As a result, as soon as the broadcast started, the camera zoomed in on Xiao Shiqin, hoping to catch something, especially during the greetings between the two teams on stage before the match. The camera spent nearly 70% of the time focused on Xiao Shiqin's face. When Xiao Shiqin shook Ye Xiu's hands, the cameras locked tightly onto him. The crowd fixed their eyes on his expression and held their breath.

Murderous spirit!

Let's see some murderous spirit!

The drama loving people hoped to see some sparks.

But all they saw a very normal and warm smile.

He's hiding it well!

The drama loving people didn't believe that Xiao Shiqin bore no hatred towards Happy. Since they couldn't see any murderous spirit on him, that must mean Xiao Shiqin was hiding it. Afterwards, even when Xiao Shiqin was just wiping his glasses, his actions were interpreted in all sorts of ways. It was like everyone suddenly became body language experts.

The individual competition began, and Happy's first player would be...

Ye Xiu, Ye Xiu again.

Everyone knew that Ye Xiu always went out first. In that case, it was easy to come up with a strategic plan to counter him.

But did that matter?

Ye Xiu's 14 consecutive wins was the best answer.

It didn't matter. Even if you knew Ye Xiu would be the first player sent up and prepared a countermeasure, it was no use. The winner would still be Ye Xiu.

Was that because the ace players defended the group arena for those 2 points instead of 1?

These were some people's opinions, and it was a valid reason. However, arranging the lineups was up to every team. If you're going to send your ace player for the group arena, then who are you to blame for not getting that one point in an individual round? This sort of perspective had a bit of sour grapes feeling to it.

As for Thunderclap? Who would they send?

Thunderclap performed spectacularly in team competitions, but in the individual competition and group arena, their performances weren't too noteworthy. Apart from Xiao Shiqin, no one else in their team was particularly eye-catching. They probably didn't have anyone for Ye Xiu, right?

A name popped onto the screen. Thunderclap's first player in the individual competition was...　

Mi Xiuyuan.

Not a sound could be heard. Everyone looked at Xiao Shiqin, and then started whispering to each other.

Mi Xiuyuan? Who was that?

The crowd was discussing this question. The reporters were hastily looking at their data. On the broadcast, Pan Lin had been predicting who Thunderclap would send onto the stage and when the answer was revealed, he said "Ah, so it's Mi Xiuyuan." After that came silence. He was also caught off guard. Who the fuck was this?

"Mi Xiuyuan… a new rookie this season?" Li Yibo was flipping through his data as he said earnestly. He had a "in the end, nothing can trouble this senior" look on his face.

"Ah… before, it seems like…" Pan Lin was also looking through his data, "he's never appeared on stage before." He finally confirmed it.

"Yes," Li Yibo said.

"But this round, facing Happy and the 1v1 king Ye Xiu, Thunderclap sent him up!" Pan Lin's voice started rising.　　

"Yes."

"Why? Could he be a secret weapon?" Pan Lin said. The camera zoomed in onto this rookie, who was pulled aside by captain Xiao Shiqin. The two people looked in one direction. The camera followed their line of sight to Ye Xiu.

"Xiao Shiqin is personally giving him instructions. What has he come up with to beat Ye Xiu? Yes, let's look at Mi Xiuyuan. His class… Assassin. Ah, could he be looking for a one hit kill?" Pan Lin started displaying his imagination.

Xiao Shiqin finally finished talking with Mi Xiuyuan. The young player stepped onto his first match on stage.

This was truly an amazing first appearance on stage. The broadcast gave him quite a few close-ups. Everyone instantly took note of this new Thunderclap rookie.　　

He was the secret weapon prepared for Ye Xiu! Everyone thought to themselves. They sucked in a deep breath of air and looked forward to the match.

After 3 minutes 42 seconds, Mi Xiuyuan returned to his seat.

Accounting for about 2 minutes to walk to his player booth and then about 1 minute to walk back to his seat, this match took precisely 58 seconds, not even a minute.

Mi Xiuyuan lost.

There were no hidden killing moves nor a one hit kill. The two players loaded into the small 1v1 map chosen by Ye Xiu and then quickly came across each other. Ping ping pong pong, Mi Xiuyuan's Assassin died.

Secret weapon?

A super killing move?

The entire world wanted to laugh.

Chapter 1235: Calm Individual Rounds

Commentating Happy's matches is truly filled with opportunities and challenges! Pan Lin sighed endlessly. There never seemed to be a lack of topics, and it was always full of traps.

Of course, this time, it wasn't Happy's fault. Mi Xiuyuan was from Thunderclap. However, Thunderclap's opponent was Happy, so Pan Lin's first thought was to focus on Happy. Fortunately, Pan Lin's remark had only been a hopeful guess, not a serious analysis, so it didn't result in too embarrassing of a situation. Pan Lin could already feel a premonition creeping into his heart though.

The broadcast still gave Mi Xiuyuan more than enough camera time.

Losing an individual round in less than a minute was very embarrassing for a pro player. But when the cameras locked onto Mi Xiuyuan, he looked calm. After he returned to his seat, the entire Thunderclap team even stood up and clapped their hands to welcome him. Dai Yanqi even rubbed Mi Xiuyuan's head roughly as if she were a big sis, despite only being a third year rookie.

"It looks like… Thunderclap gave up on beating Ye Xiu, so they just sent up a rookie to gain some experience," Li Yibo carefully observed for a while before speaking up.

"Uh, I don't know how much experience a less than one minute loss is going to bring to a player," Pan Lin said. His words carried a slight sting to it. He clearly wasn't happy with Thunderclap's methodology. As for whether he was unhappy with Thunderclap's arrangements, or because Mi Xiuyuan didn't turn out to be a secret weapon, no one knew.

The match continued. Su Mucheng went after Ye Xiu, while Thunderclap's Fang Xue went after Mi Xiuyuan. Fang Xue was also an Assassin. In the end, he was no match for Su Mucheng, and Happy won yet another point.

2-0. The crowd riled up. Cries for another 10-0 started echoing around the stadium.

But in the third match, Thunderclap unexpectedly sent Xiao Shiqin, while Happy sent Mo Fan.

Xiao Shiqin was famed as a Master Tactician, but his 1v1 skills weren't weak. In Thunderclap, he was often the anchor for the group arena, but in today's match, he came out in the individual competition. What arrangements had Thunderclap made?

"Xiao Shiqin vs Mo Fan… these two have actually fought before in the Challenger League. At that time, it was in the group arena. Xiao Shiqin performed spectacularly that round, winning the group arena with a 1v3. Let's see how their rematch is going to turn out," Pan Lin set the backdrop for the match.

The atmosphere that Pan Lin had drawn out for this match didn't end up appearing. Xiao Shiqin won with a steady lead against Mo Fan.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn't know what to say. The match was so dull. What should have happened, happened. That was all there was to it.

The emotions of the loser weren't as calm as the match.

As Mo Fan walked down from the stage, he didn't have that usual expressionless face. His gaze had stopped on Xiao Shiqin. A clear pondering expression showed.

After losing twice to the same person, Mo Fan was searching for where the issue lay. Even if there was a difference in strength, competition wasn't just about strength, it was about utilizing that strength.

Seeing Mo Fan's attentive expression, Ye Xiu didn't say anything. Once you reached a certain level, improving depended more on yourself. After all, the only person who truly understands you is you yourself. Other people could only help give and clear the clouds.

How to beat Xiao Shiqin?

If Ye Xiu could instruct him on how to do it with just a few words, then pro players would be of little value.

With the individual competition finished, Happy led 2 to 1. A 10-0 was impossible now, and the crowd appeared somewhat downcast. Happy's fans had been spoiled too much by Happy's crazy performances recently. If it wasn't a 10-0, they couldn't feel satisfied. Despite not being a powerhouse, Happy's fans had the same expectations as powerhouses.

For the following group arena, Pan Lin and Li Yibo both believed that Happy had an advantage. After all, Thunderclap's players weren't very top notch. Happy at the very least had Fang Rui as the anchor. In addition, while Tang Rou's image may have been destroyed, her explosiveness hadn't.

"If nothing surprising comes, Happy's chances should be fairly high," Li Yibo's cautiousness had already reached this point. He was too afraid to even use the word winning, only saying their "chances should be fairly high." Fairly high chances didn't mean he thought Happy would definitely win. Li Yibo was truly quite crafty.

But in the group arena, no surprises came and Happy won.

Pan Lin announced this expected outcome and discovered that he unexpectedly felt a bit bored.

What's going on? Am I too used to being slapped by Happy? Am I masochist? Taking advantage of the long break between the team competition and group arena, Pan Lin did a deep self reflection.

In the meanwhile, the two teams were preparing for the following team competition.　　

"Something feels off," said Fang Rui.

"What is it," Ye Xiu said.

"I don't know. It's just a feeling," Fang Rui said.

"This senior also feels like something's off. It's too calm," Wei Chen said.

"It won't be for the team competition," Ye Xiu said.

"Are you saying they've been saving up their strength?" Wei Chen asked.

"Maybe not saving up strength, but in the individual rounds, their strength wasn't very impressive. However, to be so calm despite losing so many points means that they must be incomparably confident in the team competition." Ye Xiu said.

"Confidence in themselves? Could that actually be the reason for their dominance in the team competition?" Fang Rui had evidently seen Xiao Shiqin's interview response about Thunderclap's performance this season.

"Without confidence, there will be a lot of choices that you'll be too afraid to make. The more confident you are, the more options you'll have, and the more variations there will be," Ye Xiu said.

"Are you talking about Xiao Shiqin? He's always been confident, huh," Fang Rui said.

"His confidence now isn't just in himself," Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui was starting to understand. The others were as well. Everyone subconsciously turned their heads to look at Thunderclap. It turned out that Thunderclap was also looking at them. The two sides made eye contact, and Xiao Shiqin gave them a friendly wave.

"This match is really lacking the gunpowder…" This scene had also been grasped by the cameras, but the broadcast was currently playing ads, so Pan Lin could only say this to himself in private. If his mics were on, saying these words definitely wouldn't be good. He would have to comment on the friendly and peaceful relations between the two teams. 　

"This match isn't going to be easy. Everyone, focus. Let's start things slow," Ye Xiu said.　

He obviously studied all of his opponents, studying the styles of the players and the team's tactical styles. However, Thunderclap, this strong team competition team, was truly difficult to deal with.

Thunderclap was not like Samsara. Samsara's overwhelming momentum was inseparable from the strength of the individual players. The image of the Battle God One Autumn Leaf was slowly being transformed. On Samsara, One Autumn Leaf was no longer that unrivalled "one". There was another "one" beside him, Cloud Piercer.

Many people had been worried about compatibility issues between Sun Xiang and Samsara, but their worries never turned into a reality. And as a result, Samsara's incredible win record came about. Sun Xiang and Zhou Zekai were titled as the "Two No.1s" this season. Two number ones pointed that the two best players had number one characters to go along with them.

Possessing this powerful duo, Samsara was able to achieve this perfect win record. But Thunderclap? The individual rounds showed that their players weren't top of the pack. However, their team competition record had 14 wins. Why? Tactics!

Thunderclap had always relied on tactics to win. However, their tactics had never brought them to such formidable heights. According to the current public opinions, if Thunderclap could continue their team competition win record, then the Four Master Tacticians should be changed. Xiao Shiqin should be taken out and given an even greater title.

After all, Ye Xiu, Yu Wenzhou, and Zhang Xinjie, whether it was now or before, the chips held in their hands were quite a bit stronger than Xiao Shiqin's. Their teams were similar to Samsara. All of them possessed top individual players.

It was like a chef cooking food.

Ye Xiu, Yu Wenzhou, and Zhang Xinjie had fresh high-quality ingredients and had the skill to turn those ingredients into wonderful dishes.

But Xiao Shiqin was someone who could take mediocre ingredients and turn them into just as, or perhaps even more delicious dishes. If one looked at it from this perspective, it was obvious who was superior.

When these words came out, many agreed with this opinion. However, someone soon pointed out: Last season, in the Challenger League, Ye Xiu had taken rotten food and then beat Xiao Shiqin, who had outstanding Excellent Era ingredients. What did that mean?

As a result, the other side took this season and brought out Xiao Shiqin's matches against Yu Wenzhou and Zhang Xinjie. Thunderclap had won those team competitions. This was also a solid argument.

The only remaining uncertainty was Ye Xiu.　　

This time, the ingredients in Ye Xiu's hands were far better than his ingredients back in the Challenger League. The rookies had grown. Su Mucheng and Fang Rui had joined. The team now had two All Star characters, and the other characters had improved significantly as well.

On the other hand, Thunderclap's roster dimmed in comparison to Su Mucheng and Fang Rui. Their characters were more in line with the gradual step by step improvement from not-so-wealthy teams.

Ye Xiu's ingredients had vastly improved, while XIao Shiqin's ingredients had diminished in quality compared to Excellent Era. This time, what would the confrontation between the two sides be like?

The start of the match was approaching, and the commentators focused their discussion of this round's team competition on this fight between two Master Tacticians.

Whoever won would become the existence above the Four Master Tacticians.

Pan Lin didn't directly say these words, but many people thought of it. Everyone's eyes were focused on the screen as the match began.

Chapter 1236: Thunderclap’s Aggressive Offense

The map was War Grasslands, a map divided by rocks and shrubs in a staircase-like arrangement. The spawn points were located on the northeast and southwest corner, and after each side crossed their two story high platforms, the two teams would meet on a field of grass. It was a map, where the two spawn points were relatively close together, and it was often used by teams who liked rushing their opponents. The map restricted more tactical teams to a certain extent because of the close distance. If the offense was launched fast enough, the other side might not have time to set up any tactical formation.

Pan Lin quickly introduced the map before the two teams loaded into the map. However, both Thunderclap and Happy were tactic-heavy teams. By choosing this map, who exactly was the one being restricted? The map had been chosen by Happy, and Pan Lin didn't dare try to guess what Happy was planning, so he simply stopped the subject there. After explaining the features of this match, he was done. As for why Happy chose the map, Pan Lin let the viewers guess, he himself wasn't going to open his mouth. Out of consideration, he also didn't toss this hot potato to Li Yibo. Li Yibo noticed his good intentions and gave Pan Lin a smile.

A map suitable for a fast offense.

As a result, as soon as the teams loaded in, the viewers looked at the two teams spawning, wanting to know which team would take the initiative.

"We'll rush them!"

It was Thunderclap. Xiao Shiqin immediately gave the order.

Everyone was surprised.

Even though Pan Lin and Li Yibo weren't analyzing the situation out loud, anyone who understood Glory would have their own thoughts. These two were just afraid of getting their faces slapped. They certainly had their own viewpoints in their mind.

From their view, Happy had chosen this map, so the one to rush the opponent should be Happy. However, it was Thunderclap who decisively gave the order as soon as the match began.

Thunderclap's players didn't have any objections towards their captain's orders. They immediately went into position and started moving as a whole.　　

Thunderclap had spawned on the northeast corner. This map was split into three-story platforms. Two of these six three-story platforms made up the spawn points, while the other four were support zones, lined up symmetrically from east to west. The two starting points were linked to their respective east and west support zones by two-story platforms. The three-story support zones of the northeast corner and southeast corner were directly linked together by large slopes that met in a grassy area in the center. The six three-story high platforms were not directly connected to each other and could only be traveled to through two-story or ground regions. As a result, the fighting often took place in these two-story or ground story regions.

Thunderclap wanted to rush, so they didn't take a roundabout path. The team charged out from their three-story high spawn point directly down towards the grasslands.

How close were these spawn points? The answer could be seen right now. As soon as Thunderclap leaped down to the grasslands, they saw Happy also leaping down. The two sides could already see each other.

"Yo, nice rush!" Ye Xiu typed in the public chat.

"Same to you," Xiao Shiqin replied.

"No, we're moving strategically," said Ye Xiu.

"That's a bit of stretch, don't you think?" Xiao Shiqin replied.

Moving strategically required at least a little bit of covertness. In this map, if one walked along the two-story high platforms, the rushing opponents would not be able to see them so quickly. But Happy charging directly towards the grasslands? How was that moving strategically? Unless they thought Thunderclap wouldn't do the standard rush.

"Rushing isn't your style. Shouldn't you guys be waiting and watching first before coming up with counter strategies?" Ye Xiu said.

"We can't wait and watch because you guys would also wait and watch," Xiao Shiqin replied.

He hit the nail on the head...

Waiting and watching was a part of combat. Another part of it was pre-match preparations, studying the opponent and coming up with countermeasures beforehand. These two teams both had the same tactical style, so when the two confronted each other, it became awkward.

To put it simply, the two teams were used to waiting for their opponents to act before they acted. If neither side acted first, then there would be no fight.

"So?" Ye Xiu asked.

"So we can only fight," Xiao Shiqin said in the public chat. This wasn't a bluff, because in the team chat, he clearly gave the order: "Go!"

Thunderclap set out and charged at their opponents.

Everyone was shocked. Team Thunderclap had been watched closely this season, but they had never taken the initiative and attacked aggressively. After all, their players and characters weren't that great. A direct clash often relied on each individual player's own skill to be effective.

But against Happy, Thunderclap unexpectedly launched an aggressive attack!　

No one would regard Happy as a weak team anymore. The return of Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, the class-changed Fang Rui, these three All Stars had proved that their skills were still at the peak. In terms of individual player skill, even Xiao Shiqin, who was the best in Thunderclap, didn't seem a match to any of Happy's top three. However, Thunderclap had bravely rushed at Happy, an unprecedented aggressiveness. They had never done this against any other team.

Why?

Every person who followed Thunderclap this season asked this question.　　

While no one else in the Alliance dared to underestimate Happy, Thunderclap did the very opposite. Was this… a psychological tactic?

"You're coming to us? Are you underestimating Happy?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Of course not," Xiao Shiqin, who was already charging over, replied.

"Then it looks like we'll need to be careful," Ye Xiu said.

"You always need to be careful in a match," Xiao Shiqin said. In the team chat, he gave another order: Scatter!　

Thunderclap had spread into a line and surrounded Happy in a wing-like formation. On the left end was Dai Yanqi's Elementalist, Firebird Messenger. On the right end was Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic, Life Extinguisher. These two were at the very tip of the wings as if they were going to escape.

Positioned in the middle was Cheng Tai's Grappler, Shattering Wind. And Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Returning Wind, was between Shattering Wind and Firebird Messenger. Between Life Extinguisher and Shattering Wind was Fang Xuecai's Assassin, Demon Talent.

"Thunderclap is being very proactive. They've quickly pulled apart into a formation very skillfully. Did they practice this specifically for Happy? What are your thoughts on this formation, Coach Li?" Pan Lin had restrained himself for a long time, but he was still a passionate commentator in the end. Thunderclap had chosen an unprecedented aggressive offense. This surprising choice instantly riled him up. He excitedly shouted and dragged Li Yibo into the water as well.

Li Yibo was in an awkward spot! He hadn't even figured out why Thunderclap would choose to go on the offensive against Happy, when Pan Lin directly asked him to explain Thunderclap's offensive formation.

"Uh, this… it looks like they're planning on surrounding Happy and then shrinking the circle," Li Yibo snorted.

"But Happy isn't lacking in attackers!" Pan Lin immediately answered back.　　

"Thunderclap surely has a method to deal with them. Let's see what they're going to do," Li Yibo was finally able to dodge this topic.

These two could pass over it with some vague words, but Ye Xiu, who was playing on stage, couldn't be so unclear.

Xiao Shiqin's decision for an aggressive offense had surprised him. He said "being underestimated", but he knew that Xiao Shiqin wasn't that type of person. Even when facing Seaside or Bright Green, the two weakest teams practically guaranteed to be relegated from the league, Thunderclap still carefully planned out their strategy. Xiao Shiqin wasn't someone who underestimated his opponent. If he dared to attack aggressively, then it could only mean he was confident that it would work, that in a direct confrontation, Thunderclap would have a greater chance of winning than Happy.

Their chances of winning didn't come from their players or characters individually. It was publicly acknowledged that Thunderclap was weak in this area. Thunderclap's chances of winning came from their tactics. For example, their team must have spread out for a purpose.

But for what purpose?

It wasn't just Ye Xiu asking this question.　　

However, no one else's judgement was more accurate than Ye Xiu's because Ye Xiu knew better than anyone else who the weak point of their team was.

Lord Grim retreated to Little Cold Hand's side.

"Group up, towards…" Ye Xiu typed. He wanted to have everyone group up and break through an opening in Thunderclap's formation, but when he swept his eyes across their formation, he discovered that he wasn't able to find such an opening.

Thunderclap's five characters were in a very simple line, but they used each of their classes well, allowing for the best possible options from any direction. If Happy tried to break through, they would be met with a lot of trouble no matter which direction they went towards. There were no clear holes or weaknesses. Breaking through from any point would be troublesome, which also meant that breaking through from any point would be the same.

"Firebird Messenger, break through!"

Ye Xiu had only hesitated for an instant. He quickly made a firm decision. As soon as Happy heard the order, their decisiveness in carrying it out was not much worse than Thunderclap's.

"Oh? We've been underestimated!" Happy's intentions were clear. Dai Yanqi, who was controlling Firebird Messenger, used Ye Xiu's own words from before. Happy had clearly chosen this direction to break through because they thought it would be easier to do so.

"But this is all according to plan!" Dai Yanqi followed.

When she said these words, everyone's hearts thumped. No one thought Thunderclap would just rashly attack. They felt like Thunderclap must have an ulterior motive. Dai Yanqi's "all according to plan" immediately confirmed this notion.

Whether or not the viewers believed in it wouldn't affect who won this match. Dai Yanqi's words were aimed as a psychological attack towards Happy. However, even if Happy believed her, it was probably too late for them to make adjustments.

That was what most people thought, but on stage were a particularly special group of people amongst the countless Glory players...

"Dang, that girl said it's all according to plan. We should find a different breakthrough point," Wei Chen said.

"Sure." Ye Xiu said.

As a result, Happy really did make a switch. Everyone turned towards Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher instead of Dai Yanqi's Firebird Messenger.　

Fuck!

The viewers were dumbfounded. This was a high-level pro match! You guys are just going to switch up your tactics because the opponent said a few words? Where's your determination? Decisiveness? Confidence?

Chapter 1237: Thunderclap’s Focus

"Ah, the older generation really is…" Dai Yanqi was also dumbstruck. She had already put her guard up. Who would have thought that Happy would turn away so decisively just because of the words she said? This sort of reason wasn't logical! But the problem was that it truly happened, and Dai Yanqi couldn't help but feel a bit afraid. She hadn't ruined her own team's rhythm, right?

"Concentrate. Defend your position well and get back on track!" Xiao Shiqin messaged the team chat. Seeing the captain's words, Dai Yanqi seemed to have been hit by a tranquilizer and calmed down. Soon afterwards, her Elementalist Firebird Messenger hurried forward.

"Be careful of them switching targets, " Xiao Shiqin added.　　

"Switching targets?" Dai Yanqi was a bit surprised.

The crowd was in an even more of an uproar, because just when Xiao Shiqin typed out those words, Ye Xiu had typed in Happy's team chat: turn!

All of Happy suddenly turned around and switched back to Dai Yanqi's Firebird Messenger. Their shift towards Xiao Shiqin had been a bait. Unfortunately, Xiao Shiqin saw through their little trick and promptly warned Dai Yanqi no to cut in too deep. Dai Yanqi had originally readied a Teleport, and the moment she paused because of the warning, she saw Happy suddenly turn around and rush towards her.

"How crafty," Dai Yanqi wasn't a chatterbox, but she was among those who liked to talk in matches. As she grumbled, Firebird Messenger quickly retreated. Her staff flashed with lightning and a Lightning Bolt shot out. It was the very first attack in this team battle.

Lightning spells were fast, but in the end, it wasn't as immediate as firing a bullet. It only took the blink of an eye for elemental power to condense into electricity, but it still took some time, enough to react to. To pro players, a window for reacting and a close enough distance to complete the necessary action was more than enough.

Firebird Messenger's Lightning Bolt pierced through Happy's formation, but it didn't hit anyone. Following afterwards, Dai Yanqi had Firebird Messenger activate Absolute Focus and cast the Level 75 skill, Fire Bird. A Fire Bird formed at the tip of her staff and flew out with with its wings spread. The heat waves swept over the grasslands, wilting the once tall and straight stalks of green grass. Stalk after stalk bent over to half the size of their surrounding friends.

Compared to Lightning Bold, the area covered by Fire Bird was much larger, so Happy could not just open a path for the spell to pass by. Since it was no longer possible to continue maintaining their formation, Happy split up to the left and right. As the Fire Bird flew, the heat waves blurred their figures.

From the rear, sounds of machinery turning could be heard. They hadn't targeted Xiao Shiqin, instead, it was Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher who took the initiative to look for them. The knee-high grass hid lots of the ground machines. Happy could only see rustles from wherever the machines passed by, but they didn't know what exactly was hidden in the grass.

Firebird Messenger retreated as Life Extinguisher advanced.

But Firebird Messenger didn't back away too hard, and Life Extinguisher didn't advance too fiercely either. They seemed to be intentionally leaving Happy some space. These two long-ranged classes carefully controlled the distance, maintaining a certain gap between them.

The unknown machines traversing along the ground were getting nearer and nearer from multiple directions, arriving at different times.

Landmine Quake!

Fang Rui's Boundless Sea leaped into the air and slammed his two hands towards the ground. A wave of formless and colorless qi could be seen from its effects on the grass as it spread out towards the surroundings with Boundless Sea at the center.

Boom boom boom boom!

When the rustling grass and the grass wave collided, fire and light exploded into the air, creating a plume of smoke. Fang Rui had timed it well. He didn't care what the machines were and simply let out a Landquake Mine to destroy them.

But… those weren't all of them.

Who knew how many machines Xiao Shiqin had put into this wave. There were still three rustles in the grass. Perhaps they hadn't arrived yet, or perhaps Xiao Shiqin had maneuvered them away, but either way, they had avoided Boundless Sea's earthquake and started charging towards Happy again.

Qi Bullet!

Boundless Sea punched in the direction of a rustle.

However, Qi Bullet's flight speed was nothing worth noting. The mechanical tool sped up and easily evaded it.

Bang! Bang!　

Lord Grm's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into its gun form and fired twice. But under the cover of the grass, it was difficult to get a good aim. After two shots, the rustling was still there.

Ta ta ta ta ta...

Su Mucheng saw that Lord Grim's few shots didn't hit, so she had Dancing Rain use Gatling Gun. The stream of bullets chased after the rustling grass in a line, finally shooting it into a smoke and fire. Su Mucheng didn't stop. While her skill was still in effect, she immediately switched to a different direction. However, Xiao Shiqin was clearly wary of Happy catching them all in one fell swoop. He had all three of his machines move along paths far from each other. Even though Su Mucheng quickly switched directions, she didn't have much time left on her skill. After a few bullets, her Gatling Gun stopped.

However...

Ta ta ta ta ta...　　

Lord Grim's Gatling Gun fired. His attack path followed along Dancing Rain's previous path. If you didn't look at the starting points of the bullets, it was practically impossible to tell that this attack had actually been done by two people.

Boom! The machine on that path exploded. When Lord Grim turned his gun, he still had half of Gatling Gun's duration left. Bullets chased after the last remaining mechanical tool, but who would have thought that it wouldn't be enough! Everyone could clearly see that the bullets landed on the right patch of grass, but the mechanical tool seemed to be perfectly fine!

Mechanical tools weren't like summoned creatures with health. They would go boom with just a knock. A bullet hitting, let alone multiple, was enough. The only explanation was that it didn't hit, but… the bullets clearly landed on it, unless...

Ye Xiu suddenly reacted, but it was too late. A patch of grass rustled in front of them, and then something suddenly leaped up out of the grass.

This wasn't a mechanical tool that traversed on the ground. It was an aerial Air Drop. However, Xiao Shiqin had it fly extremely low so that it would be covered by the grass. But because it wasn't touching the ground, Ye Xiu's previous attacks missed because of the slight deviation in position. At this moment, Air Drop was suddenly in front of them. Its stomach opened up and was just about to drop some bombs...

Boom!

The Air Drop suddenly exploded before it could drop any bombs. Amidst the black smoke, a white flame could clearly be seen.

Sacred Fire!　　

Prediction and timing were An Wenyi's strengths. At the most crucial moment, a calm Sacred Fire block the Air Drop.

The crowd applauded.

This wave of machines had happened in just a few short seconds. All of Team Happy had worked together to intercept these machines. Their teamwork had been beautiful.

"Pay attention. The other side's Assassin has disappeared…" Fang Rui typed in the chat.

Fang Xuecai's Assassin Demon Talent had been between Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher and Cheng Tai's Shattering Wind, but he was now nowhere to be seen.

Was he crawling through the grass, or was he using the Thief skill on his weapon, Stealth? Ye Xiu and the others started searching the grass. No matter which option he had chosen, any movement in the grass would leave behind a trace. The grass was only knee-high. The Mechanic's mechanical tools could hide there quite cleanly, but it wasn't so easy to hide an adult.

Demon Talent was gone right now, but Dai Yanqi's and Xiao Shiqin's pincer was still ongoing. While Happy was busy cleaning up Life Extinguisher's machines, Firebird Messenger took the opportunity to cast two high-level spells. Without trying to make any predictions, lightning and fire AoE spells were cast directly above Happy's heads. From the looks of it, she wasn't trying to stop Happy from advancing, but trying to blast Happy's formation apart.

A pincer from the front and rear. An Assassin gone without a trace. Chen Tai's Grappler, Shattering Wind, was the closest to Happy. He was constantly moving, and even though he had yet to make an attack, his presence alone gave them quite a bit of pressure. Happy had to dodge the attacks from the front and rear, while also making sure they weren't grabbed by Shattering Wind. If a Grappler grabbed them, the formation would certainly fall apart. Shattering Wind was moving around, looking for an opening. As Happy dodged, they also tried to see if they could swallow up Shattering Wind. However, Thunderclap had Xiao Shiqin watching over. His judgement towards tactics was clear and precise. Only the crowd knew just how dense Thunderclap's chat was. The density of messages was not lower than that of their match against Blue Rain.

Was Xiao Shiqin planning on using these varied and complex tactics to outpace Happy?

However, Happy's leader was Ye Xiu, not Yu Wenzhou. Their tactical skill was the same, but in terms of hand speed, if you said Ye Xiu was superior to Yu Wenzhou, then even Yu Wenzhou's most loyal fans could only concede tearfully.

Why? Why did Thunderclap need to make things so complicated? Xiao Shiqin made numerous commands, and every player's movements and attack rhythms were constantly changing. Not only were they adjusting according to Xiao Shiqn's instructions, but they had their own plans too. Thunderclap had clearly prepared this set of tactics.

What exactly is this?

"I get it!" Li Yibo suddenly shouted. His skill level was still far higher than the average player's. He saw through Thunderclap's tactical intentions first. But right after he yelled it out, he immediately felt regret. He was exposing himself too much! Why am I so overjoyed? I should be calmly explaining the thought behind Thunderclap's tactics. That would have made me look even more knowledgeable!

Unfortunately, the deed had been done. Pan Lin helped lead him in: "Coach Li, you've seen through Thunderclap's intentions?"

"Haha, I had a feeling earlier, but now I'm certain. Thunderclap is doing exactly what I had thought," Li Yibo said mysteriously.

"Please guide us Coach Li." How could Pan Lin not know of Li Yibo's cunning plot. In his heart, he was looking down on him, but out loud, he had to praise him.

"Thunderclap's strategy is similar to their one against Blue Rain with lots of variations. But when facing Blue Rain, they were mainly focused on varying and adjusting their tactics. Right now, they're more focused on their attack positioning and variation in rhythm."

"The purpose is the same. They're targeting a certain player on the opposing team. Against Blue Rain, their target was Yu Wenzhou. If Yu Wenzhou is unable to give out enough commands on time, Blue Rain would have trouble keeping up with Thunderclap's fast-changing tactics. Against Happy, their target is An Wenyi, Happy's healer!" Li Yibo said with certainty.

Chapter 1238: Symbol For a Healer

Happy's healer, An Wenyi!

Li Yibo spoke with power and resonance, but since this was a live broadcast, he probably didn't know how many boos came his way when he said these words.

Happy's weak point was An Wenyi. We don't need you to say that. Who doesn't know it?

Yes, everyone knew, including Pan Lin. He hadn't thought that Li Yibo's secret ace would be such an obvious answer. After staring blankly for a few seconds, he finally followed up: "Yeah… An Wenyi really is Happy's weak point."　

"Yes," Li Yibo was still smiling confidently, "Everyone knows this, but who among Happy's previous opponents fully took advantage of this weakness?"

Pan Lin was stunned again. He could hear that Li Yibo's words had substance to them, and he subconsciously started thinking about Li Yibo's question. Had any of Happy's previous opponents specifically created a plan to target An Wenyi?"

"We won't talk about matches too far in the past. Let's take a look at the two rather strong teams that Happy had faced in their recent win streak, Misty Rain and Void. Our friends who have watched Happy's matches against these two team, recall Happy's performances in the team competition," Li Yibo betrayed the key points in his analysis.

"Happy's performances in those two matches?" Pan Lin echoed as he pondered in his mind. His perception was quite a bit higher than the average player's. After thinking about it for a bit, he found out that he truly wasn't able to find anything.

"In Misty Rain's match, Happy utilized the terrain to set up their formation. At that time, An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands hid behind that big rock. Misty Rain didn't have the conditions to launch any attacks directly towards him," Li Yibo answered.

Pan Lin completely remembered now: "In Void's match, Happy switched out their Cleric to get into position faster. By the time An Wenyi went onto the field, Void only had four players remaining, and Happy's victory had pretty much been decided at that point."

"For those interested, we can go even farther back. In their match against Hundred Blossoms, even in the Challenger League finals against Excellent Era, these matches against strong opponents give us an even clearer picture."

"Right," Pan Lin completely understood what Li Yibo wanted to say.

"Happy's tactics seem similar to Thunderclap's in the sense that they're always targeting a certain person. However, Happy's tactics are always built off a foundation: protecting their weak point, An Wenyi. In every match, they will always try their best to end the battle without there being too great of a burden on An Wenyi," Li Yibo said.

"Xiao Shiqin has completely seen through this point, so in this match, he's taken the initiative to strike preemptively at Happy's tactical framework. He doesn't plan on letting Happy set up a situation easy for An Wenyi," Pan Lin said.

"Yes, so that's why their offensive rhythm is constantly changing. For a healer, grasping the opponent's offensive rhythm is extremely important. A healer needs to pay attention to any possible dangers, sometimes even needing to predict a crisis ahead of time, in order to prepare a long cast time heal in advance. Does Happy's An Wenyi have the ability to deal with such a hurried situation?" Li Yibo said.

The broadcast team coordinated with him and cut to An Wenyi's point of view.

His screen was shifting around extremely chaotically.

Sure enough, the situation was just as Li Yibo said. Before a healer healed, the first thing that needed to be done was to figure out who needed to be healed, which meant that the healer couldn't solely pay attention to his opponents. The healer needed to look at the overall situation from time to time. However, Xiao Shiqin had set it up such that the battle was spread out all around. An Wenyi could not simply look in one direction to observe the battlefield. He had to look towards one side and then look towards a different side from time to time. Along with Thunderclap's constantly changing rhythm, his inability to keep up and his confusion was completely exposed by the cameras.

The broadcast and the crowd's electronic screens aptly showed the health bars of the two teams.

This sort of image was usually shown to let the viewers know which side's healer was controlling the field well. A good healer would keep his teammate's health above a certain safe line at all times. The health bars would leap up and down like musical notes.

But the health bars of Happy's characters were a complete mess. It was like he was banging around clumsily without any vision. No one could tell what An Wenyi's safe line was.

Without a safe line, it wasn't possible to heal dependably.

Happy's stadium was quiet.

An Wenyi was Happy's weak point. This had been known since the very beginning, but up until now, it had never been fully exposed because every time the team lost, it didn't look like An Wenyi was dragging down the team. But when Li Yibo gave his analysis, everyone discovered that though An Wenyi didn't drag down the team in Happy's losses, he didn't contribute too much in their wins either. An Wenyi's role in Happy seemed to just be a symbol, letting the opponents know: we have a healer. Had Happy ever used any tactics that relied on their healer? Never. Even though An Wenyi had his moments of brilliance, he had always played under relatively safe conditions - conditions that Happy had set up for him.

But in this round against Thunderclap, Xiao Shiqin didn't give them an opportunity to set up these conditions. These multi-directional and constantly changing attacks forced out Happy's weakness. In a team battle, if the healer could not keep up, the entire team would suffer. Thunderclap's attacks weren't focused on any one person. They frequently changed targets, forcing An Wenyi to constantly search for their focuses, pressuring him into making more mistakes.

Happy wasn't routed yet. Their team still had Ye Xiu and Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. The unspecialized had limited healing capabilities, but it was better than nothing. These heals might be enough for crucial saves, but relying on Lord Grim to keep up the entire team's health was impossible.

What are they going to do?

This was Happy's home stadium, so the crowd was obviously worried for Happy. Thunderclap couldn't be too relaxed either though. Maintaining this sort of battle tempo without making mistakes was not an easy task.

"Keep this up!" From time to time, Xiao Shiqin would give encouraging words to boost the team's morale.

Thunderclap's offense was maintained extremely well. No matter how amazing a team's tactics were, if the team couldn't carry it out, then it was pointless. And in terms of execution, Thunderclap's players were second to none. This team had always relied on tactics to beat stronger teams. The team's players were very accomplished at tactics, even more so under Xiao Shiqin's guidance. They understood his commands very quickly and executed them smoothly.

"Happy's in trouble," Li Yibo was already announcing it.

"Let's see if they've got a way out!" Pan Lin said.

"Thunderclap is utilizing the map extremely well. I nearly forgot who chose the map," Li Yibo chuckled.

"Uh… I'm sure Happy chose this map for a reason." Pan Lin chose his words carefully because he had a premonition that as soon as he came out and announced Happy's demise, he would definitely be slapped in the face.

Li Yibo could feel Pan Lin's cautiousness and laughed. What could Happy do in this situation? No matter which direction you rush towards, you won't be able to escape from battle. Thunderclap doesn't need to trap you here. As long as they can continuously harass you and can stop your healer from being effective, this harassment is equivalent to damage. And enough damage means that it's their win! In addition, Thunderclap's leader is Xiao Shiqin. With him watching over, what tactical intents could be hidden from him?

"Cheng, pressure with triangular movement!"

"Dai, turn 30 degrees."

"Fang, move back."

Commands continued to be given as Happy wasn't just sitting there letting An Wenyi deal with the pressure himself. However, their intentions were always seen through by Xiao Shiqin, who would promptly respond and stop Happy from escaping this situation.

"Fuck. Bullying the rookie, you call that skill!" Fang Rui complained in the public chat.

"Keep pressuring them. Fang, move a little towards my location." Xiao Shiqin was unmoved. In a match, there was no such thing as trash talk only for the purpose of complaining. The words that jumped onto the screen always contained a message, which would automatically be read by the eyes. This sort of small distraction could lead to an unconscious change in emotions and ultimately, a mistake. Xiao Shiqin wouldn't be affected by it though. As soon as Fang Rui said these words, his first thought was that the opponents would be making a move soon, so he immediately warned his team to be wary.

Sky Piercing Strike!

After Fang Rui's grumble, Boundless Sea pushed out a blast of qi. The qi swept past the grass directly towards Life Extinguisher.

Laser Beam!

Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain immediately added to Boundless Sea's attack with a Laser Beam.

But their coordination was a bit off beat, so the effects weren't the most optimal. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher easily dodged it. However, his line of sight left that area for a short moment.

Chaotic Rain!

At this moment, greenish purplish raindrops suddenly poured down. It was Chaotic Rain summoned by a Warlock.　　

"Oh, so those attacks were cover for Chaotic Rain. Then, they plan on using Chaotic Rain's AoE to attack. In that case, we need to…" Xiao Shiqin thought and prepared to give another order.

Wait...

1, 2, 3, 4...　　

Happy was missing a person!　

The missing person was Lord Grim?

"Where's Lord Grim?" Xiao Shiqin hastily asked in the chat. Did he disappear from view while I was dodging those attacks? Even if I didn't see him, my other teammates should have, right?"

"Ah?" His teammates all gasped in surprise.

No one saw?

Xiao Shiqin didn't ask further. Everyone's "Ah?" was clear enough.　　

Had there been a blind spot in everyone's field of view at that instant?

Was that a coincidence, or… had it been set up?

Xiao Shiqin reflected on this question. If it was the latter, then Happy's plan was currently being set in motion. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was hiding in the grass. What was he planning on doing?

"Cheng, approach and search. Fang, support him." Xiao Shiqin immediately ordered.